<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 11:58:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 11:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Musk retweeted X account @a, @v, and other information updates to Grok partner&apos;s tweet</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22991</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, Musk retweeted a tweet which said, &quot;The accounts on the X Platform with the handle @a have modified their profiles to the xAI-developed Grok humanoid companion Ani. The accounts with the handle @v have changed their profiles to the xAI-developed Grok humanoid companion Valentine. The accounts with the handle @Rudi have updated their profiles to the xAI-developed Grok pet companion Rudi, and so on.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 11:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22991</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum&apos;s Second Largest Holder SBET Holds Unrealized Gains of Over $200 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22990</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, as SharpLink Gaming (SBET) once more boosted its ETH holdings today, its strategic ETH reserve has grown to 480,204 coins. The weighted average price is approximately $3,045, and it currently shows an unrealized gain of $221 million.According to HTX market data, ETH has surpassed $3,500 and is currently trading at $3,507, with a 24-hour increase of 0.45%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22990</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Surges to Touch $114,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22989</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin rebounded and touched $114,000. It is currently priced at $114,000 and has a 24-hour gain of 0.34%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 11:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22989</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Insider Trader」 @qwatio Increases Short Position to $300 Million Nominal Value, Currently Profiting $7 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22987</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, as per Ember Monitor, the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio continued to add to their short position one and a half hours ago, raising the value of the short position to 300 million US dollars. @qwatio is currently shorting four tokens: BTC, ETH, XRP, and SOL, with an unrealized profit of 7 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22987</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Officially Unveils &quot;Truth&quot; Token-Related Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22988</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, according to DL News, the Trump Media and Technology Group (TMTG) officially presented its plans for the Truth brand utility token and digital wallet in the most recent filing submitted to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As early as several months ago, the company hinted at this concept in a letter to its shareholders.The filing shows that the token will be a part of a &quot;more extensive reward plan&quot; and integrated into the &quot;Truth digital wallet&quot;. Its initial uses involve paying for Truth+ subscription fees. As the project advances, the token may also be applicable to other products and services within the Truth ecosystem, suggesting that it may have a broader range of uses across the entire platform in the future.Although the filing does not directly refer to it as &quot;cryptocurrency&quot;, the wording implies that it is likely to be built on blockchain infrastructure. This second-quarter earnings report is the first time this project has appeared in public</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22988</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Sets 10 Big Goals: Bitcoin Long Position Already Up $1.31M</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22985</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, a screenshot disclosed by the whale &quot;Setting 10 Big Goals First&quot; on their personal social media platform indicates that their 5x leveraged Bitcoin long position is currently making a profit of $1.31 million. They took a long position on BTC with an average price of $112,992.84, and their total position size currently amounts to 1930.979 BTC, with a collateral of approximately $43.9 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 09:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22985</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source: InsiderInsider: JD, Ant Group May Have Difficulty Appearing on Initial Hong Kong Stablecoin License List</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22986</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, as reported by Caixin, a source close to the applicant for the Hong Kong stablecoin license disclosed that with the finalization of regulatory rules, the Hong Kong stablecoin craze will wane. Especially since the main application scenario is for non-financial institutions engaged in cross-border payments, some applicants may proactively withdraw from early participation due to the difficulty of meeting the regulatory requirement of &quot;verifying the identity of each holder.&quot; This also implies that previously popular internet platforms like JD.com and Ant Group may face challenges in appearing on the first batch of license lists.Furthermore, CITIC Group, through its Hong Kong subsidiary CITIC International, has joined forces with some institutions to apply for the first batch of stablecoin licenses. Some industry insiders have indicated that Bank of China Hong Kong, as one of Hong Kong&apos;s three note-issuing banks, would have a natural advantage if it were to issue a stablec</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 09:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22986</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rate displays a market-wide bearish trend.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22984</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, according to Coinglass data, the current funding rates of mainstream CEX and DEX suggest a generally bearish market. The specific funding rates for mainstream coins are presented in the attached image.BlockBeats Note: The funding rate is a rate set by cryptocurrency trading platforms to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price. It is usually applicable to perpetual contracts and is a mechanism for the exchange of funds between long and short traders. The trading platform does not charge this fee. It is used to adjust the cost or profit of traders holding contracts to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the funding rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the funding rate is greater than 0.01%, it indicates a generally bullish market. When the funding rate is less than 0.005%, it indicates a generally bearish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 09:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X Account@a updated the profile to Grok humanoid companion Ani, with the namesake Meme Coin surging over 60% in the last 6 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22983</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, the account with the handle @a on Platform X updated its profile and changed it to Ani, which is a humanoid companion developed by xAI, an artificial intelligence company owned by Musk.Currently, the custom name, background image, and bio of the @a account do not clearly show any official affiliation with xAI&apos;s Grok or other products. It seems that the related information is more of a personal creative choice rather than an official endorsement.According to GMGN market data (https://t.me/gmgnaibot?start=i_m4TE56o8), the Solana-based Meme coin Ani has exceeded a market capitalization of $47 million and is currently at $47.36 million with a 6-hour increase of 62.13%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 08:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22983</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satoshi Statue Project Owner Satoshigallery Offers 0.1 BTC Reward to Find Stolen Statue</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22982</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, based on a post from Satoshigallery, which is the planner of the Satoshi statue, on the X platform: We will provide 0.1 BTC to the person who assists us in recovering the Satoshi statue that was stolen in Lugano yesterday. Satoshigallery addresses the thief, saying, &quot;You can steal our symbol, but you can never steal our soul.&quot; The Satoshigallery team stated that they will collaborate to place this statue in 21 locations worldwide.In a previous communication, the Satoshi statue in Lugano, Switzerland, was stolen. This statue, co-founded by Tether, was designed by the Italian artist Valentina Picozzi and took 18 months of research and 3 months to construct.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 08:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22982</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>