<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:02:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ZORA Hits New All-Time High, Surges Over 110% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21564</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on HTX market data, ZORA surged to be above $0.0476 and reached a new all-time high with a 24-hour increase of 111%, which pushed its market capitalization to $165 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21564</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 1 hour, there has been a total of $151 million in liquidations across the entire network, with the majority coming from long positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21563</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on Coinglass data, within the past 1 hour, the total liquidation across the network reached $151 million. Among them, there was $141 million in long liquidations and $9.735 million in short liquidations.In the past 24 hours, a total of 175,828 people worldwide have been liquidated, and the total liquidation amount is $509 million. The largest single liquidation took place on Binance - ETHUSDT, amounting to $3.9652 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21563</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker of the House: &quot;Disappointed&quot; in Powell, Open to Reforming the Fed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21562</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. House Speaker Johnson said that he is receptive to reforming the Federal Reserve, yet it hinges on the specific details. He voiced &quot;disappointment&quot; towards Federal Reserve Chair Powell. It remains unclear whether the removal of the Federal Reserve Chair is legally compliant. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21562</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LazAI Ecosystem&apos;s AI Agent Launch Platform Lazpad Introduces AI Companion DAT and Opens Whitelist Event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21561</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Web3-native AI infrastructure protocol LazAI will make its debut with the AI Companion Data Anchoring Token (DAT) on its testnet for the very first time. This enables users to connect with a memory-holding and continuously evolving AI entity and obtain rewards through interactions.This event will be launched on the LazAI ecosystem&apos;s AI agent launchpad Lazpad. Users who complete a series of tasks will be eligible for the whitelist. Each whitelisted address will receive a free DAT blind box along with additional rewards and the qualification for a C.ALITH airdrop. Meanwhile, LazAI will also launch a referral invitation event. By inviting friends, users can earn activity points. The top ten referrers will receive additional rare DAT rewards based on their rankings.Lazpad is a user-friendly on-chain AI agent launchpad that supports both open and curated assetization paths. It is powered by the robust LazAI internal incentive ecosystem and is deeply integrated into the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21561</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Inference Platform Gaia Completes $20 Million Seed and Series A Funding, Led by Mantle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21560</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the decentralized AI inference platform Gaia announced the completion of a $20 million seed round and Series A financing. The financing was led by ByteTrade, SIG, Mirana, and Mantle, with the participation of Outlier Ventures, NGC, Taisu Ventures, Consensys Mesh, and others.The new funds will be utilized to expand the decentralized AI infrastructure and officially launch the world&apos;s first AI-native smartphone designed for user-centric intelligence. The Gaia AI Phone is based on Galaxy S25 Edge hardware, with all AI inference processes running locally, eliminating the need for the cloud and avoiding data uploads to prevent privacy leaks.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21559</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and surpassed $11,800. The 24-hour decline was narrowed to 0.32%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21559</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company U Power has entered into a strategic partnership with IoTeX to explore the realm of Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21558</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U Power Limited (with Nasdaq stock code: UCAR; hereinafter referred to as &quot;U Power&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) - a provider concentrating on next-generation smart grid and intelligent transportation systems driven by AI solutions - announced today the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding and a Business Cooperation Agreement with IoTeX.IoTeX is a blockchain pioneer committed to transforming machine-generated data into AI collective intelligence. According to the terms of the strategic cooperation agreement:IoTeX will purchase Real World Assets (RWA) issued by U Power and backed by corporate bonds. This will enhance U Power&apos;s capital structure and support the continuous research and development of its UOTTA? electric vehicle battery swapping technology, facilitating U Power&apos;s expansion in Web 3.0 AI-driven energy and transportation system solutions.The two parties will also actively explore innovative solutions for tokenizing these RWA and integrate advanced AI technology</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperion launches the native staking mechanism RION StakingⅠ and announces the official unveiling of RION Utility</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21557</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Aptos, which is the largest decentralized exchange platform, announced the official launch of the RION Utility Prologue for Hyperion and took the lead in opening the native staking Staking Phase I. Users are now able to lock up RION to participate in the native staking mechanism and enter the first stage of network construction and value sharing.Staking Phase I will last for a total of 1 month and will end at 9 p.m. Beijing time on August 22nd. The user&apos;s staking time will be based on the actual participation time, and the rewards will come from a portion of the platform&apos;s transaction fee income. This mechanism is designed to identify and incentivize real contributors, lay the foundation for more RION application scenarios in the future, and reflect Hyperion&apos;s high regard for genuine interaction and ecosystem virtuous cycle.Hyperion stated that this phase is the first step in unlocking RION Utility, and more utility scenarios based on real income will be continuously</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Further Increases Holdings by 117.93 BTC, Bringing Total Holdings to 628.22 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21556</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Swedish-listed company announced another increase in its holdings by 117.93 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 628.22 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: U.S. to Lift Burdensome AI Development Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21555</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the White House made an announcement that President Trump will promote the swift construction of artificial intelligence data centers. The US will repeal onerous AI development regulations. (Forex)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21555</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>