<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>吴杰庄 on &quot;Hong Kong Compliance Stablecoin Holder Identity Verification Requirement&quot;: The HKMA will implement KYC rules, but the specific approach will be submitted by the stablecoin issuer.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22398</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Wu Jiezhuang elaborated on &quot;the identity requirements of Hong Kong compliance stablecoin holders for real-name verification.&quot; He pointed out that the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) will indeed implement KYC rules. However, the specific implementation method has not been fully determined yet, and real-name verification is only one of the methods. Wu Jiezhuang emphasized that the specific plan will be submitted to the HKMA by the stablecoin issuer. After obtaining the satisfaction and approval of the HKMA, it can be implemented. In addition, compared to cash, the KYC rules related to stablecoins will be more stringent. (Techub News)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22398</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will delist the XVS/TRY and YGG/TRY spot trading pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22397</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per an official announcement, Binance will remove the XVS/TRY and YGG/TRY spot trading pairs from its platform on August 1, 2025, at 03:00 (UTC) and will cease providing related trading bot services. Users will still be able to trade the affected assets in other trading pairs.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22397</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Anchorage Digital Address Receives 8052 ETH Redeemed from Lido, Price Surge Results in $15.79 Million Gain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22396</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a wallet suspected to be under the ownership of Anchorage Digital received a Lido redemption of 8052 ETH 11 hours ago, with a value of $30.25 million. This 7575.98 ETH was originally deposited in 2028.08 ETH from Coinbase when the price was merely $1672.79. In addition to the Lido staking rewards over the two years, there was an additional gain of $15.79 million due to the price increase.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22396</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed Whisperer」: This week&apos;s Fed meeting may see two governors dissenting from the wait-and-see approach and instead advocating for a rate cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22395</link>
      <description>On July 30th, &quot;The Fed Whisperer&quot; Nick Timiraos released an article indicating that during this week&apos;s Fed meeting, there may be dissents from two governors. This is a situation that has not occurred in more than 30 years (or in other words, in 259 consecutive policy meetings).&quot;Powell and some of his colleagues have already shown a preference for a wait-and-see attitude at this week&apos;s meeting. Meanwhile, the potential dissenting ones - Fed governors Waller and Bowman - happen to be two of President Trump&apos;s appointees. Both have expressed support for a rate cut, a move that Trump has openly advocated. Regardless of Powell&apos;s decision, this week&apos;s dissent may be unavoidable - if the Fed cuts rates, it may face opposition from hawkish policymakers who are concerned about reigniting inflation.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22395</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Money Cleans House: One Month Ago, ETH and AAVE Hoarded by the Whale, With Overall Earnings of Approximately $950,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22394</link>
      <description>July 30th. Based on the monitoring of on-chain data analyst Ai Yi, the whale address 0xCE7 is said to have liquidated the 1401 ETH and 6826 AAVE accumulated in the past month five hours ago. The total value is approximately $7.17 million. If all are sold, the estimated overall profit would be around $951,000. There is a profit of $1.232 million from the ETH part and a loss of $291,000 from the AAVE part.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22394</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum&apos;s largest holder entity BMNR has a current cost basis of $3,755, only about 1.5% higher than the current market price.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22393</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on the data disclosed by Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), the largest Ethereum hodler. It is stated that the current total holdings of BTC have reached 192 coins, and the total holdings of ETH have reached approximately 625,000 coins. The company has increased its ETH holdings by 58,224 coins, with an overall average purchase cost for ETH being approximately $3,755.According to HTX Market Data, the current price of ETH is $3,810, which indicates that BMNR&apos;s average purchase cost is only about 1.46% higher than the current market price.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22393</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sichuan Court in China Tries Virtual Currency Forex Exchange Case Involving Over 200 Million RMB</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22392</link>
      <description>July 30th. From 2020 to 2021, the defendants Wan Moyuan, Chen Mouwen, and Huang Moyuan carried out illegal foreign exchange transactions outside of the regulated trading venues for the purpose of making a profit. Wan Moyuan was responsible for contacting clients in need of US dollars. Through Chen Mouwen, he contacted Huang Moyuan and transferred the corresponding amount of Chinese yuan or USDT (Tether, a cryptocurrency purchased with Chinese yuan) to the Chinese yuan receiving account or USDT receiving address provided by Huang Moyuan. Huang Moyuan used two Hong Kong company accounts under his control to transfer US dollars online to the receiving company account provided by Chen Mouwen and sent the US dollar transfer &quot;receipt&quot; (remittance certificate) to Chen Mouwen. After the transaction was negotiated or the US dollars were received, the clients transferred the Chinese yuan used to purchase US dollars to the bank account provided by Wan Moyuan or paid the Chinese yuan to Wan Moyuan</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram founder Pavel Durov on Monday underwent questioning by French investigative judges in Paris</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22390</link>
      <description>July 30th. According to Agence France-Presse, in Paris on Monday, the founder of Telegram, Pavel Durov, was questioned by French investigating magistrates regarding the alleged involvement of the platform in criminal activities. Pavel Durov, who has been detained in Paris since 2024, has repeatedly been accused of being linked to organized crime, illegal transactions, and the spread of illegal content. Durov has denied all the charges and, through his lawyer, stated that he has detailed the absurdity of the related facts to the investigators and has questioned the legality of the case, filing for a preliminary ruling with the European Court of Justice.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22390</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radix Network Founder Dan Hughes Passed Away Unexpectedly at Home this Past Sunday Evening</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22389</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Dan Hughes, the founder and lead architect of the Radix Network, passed away unexpectedly at his home last Sunday evening. Since 2013, Dan has been committed to the underlying architecture research of distributed ledger technology. In 2019, he introduced the Cerberus consensus mechanism and the Radix Engine, laying the foundation for the Radix Network. Recently, Dan returned to the front line to lead the Hyperscale testing and promote the development of Radix. His sudden departure has had a significant impact on the team and the community.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22389</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tonight Ethereum Co-founder Vitalik will appear on the tenth anniversary commemorative live stream to revisit Ethereum&apos;s history</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22391</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Ethereum Foundation announced that during a live streaming event this evening at 22:30 Beijing time to celebrate its tenth anniversary, Ethereum&apos;s founder, Vitalik Buterin, and ConsenSys founder, Joseph Lubin, will lead the audience through Ethereum&apos;s history. The Foundation&apos;s Co-Executive Directors, Hsiao-Wei Wang and Tomasz Stańczak, will present the outlook for the next decade.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22391</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>