<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:13:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid&apos;s August Revenue Surpasses $100 Million, Setting a New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27263</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to DefiLlama data, Hyperliquid&apos;s revenue in August reached $1.0641 billion, reaching a new high. Meanwhile, its annualized revenue came to $12.51 billion, and the platform&apos;s total accumulated revenue has reached $5.1208 billion.BlockBeats Note: Annualized revenue refers to a method of converting the revenue data for a current period of time into an estimated annual revenue.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27263</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethereum PoS Network&apos;s ETH Staked for Withdrawal has decreased to 879,000, while over 850,000 ETH are queued to join</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27262</link>
      <description>September 2nd. Based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current amount of ETH leaving the Ethereum PoS network queue has been continuously decreasing for 4 days. It currently stands at 879,063 ETH, which is approximately valued at 3.82 billion US dollars. The exit wait time is about 15 days and 6 hours.Meanwhile, the amount of ETH queued to join the network has increased to around 857,719 ETH, with a value of approximately 3.72 billion US dollars. The estimated activation delay is about 14 days and 21 hours.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may have decided to cash out after Ethereum experienced a significant rebound from the April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and B</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27262</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surpasses $110,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27261</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin exceeded $110,000 and had a 24-hour increase of 2.33%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27261</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Announcement: Former Chinese Ambassador of Aptos Terminated, Who Hijacked Chinese Trademark and Disrupted Community Events</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27260</link>
      <description>September 2nd. As per the crypto Key Opinion Leader (KOL) @cryptobraveHQ, following the dismissal of the former Chinese ambassador for Aptos, the concerned individual took over the Aptos trademark and brand in China, thereby disrupting Aptos-supported Chinese community activities. This person used to receive a monthly salary of 200 USDT and registered Aptos-related social media accounts for the Chinese community prior to leaving their position and spreading information about Aptos.Legal professionals point out that international trademark hijacking has occurred in various industries worldwide but is relatively rare in the Web3 field. Although the probability of successful legal recourse is high, the process is costly, lengthy, and the outcome is uncertain. For Web3 projects, such behavior not only disrupts the original brand layout but may also enable the hijacker to leverage the brand&apos;s popularity for product or token sales, presenting potential risks.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27260</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Big V」 Huang Licheng currently holds approximately $144 million worth of ETH and HYPE long positions, with an unrealized loss of about $4.17 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27259</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight accessible via HyperInsight, &quot;Brother Ma Ji&quot; Huang Licheng currently has approximately $144 million worth of long positions in ETH and HYPE. There is an unrealized loss of about $4.17 million. The details are as follows:· Holds 28,642 long positions in ETH, which is worth $124 million and has an unrealized loss of about $3.37 million. The opening price is $4,443.02 and the liquidation price is $3,274.8.· Holds 460,000 long positions in HYPE, which is worth $20.05 million and has an unrealized loss of about $0.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27259</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, there have been liquidations totaling $433 million across the entire network, leading to the liquidation of over 150,000 individuals.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27258</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, a combined total of $433 million has been liquidated across the entire network. Globally, 154,761 users have been liquidated. Among them, long positions were liquidated to the tune of $325 million, while short positions were liquidated by $108 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27258</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin BRC20 Protocol Completes BRC2.0 Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27257</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as reported by Coindesk, the Bitcoin Token Protocol BRC-20 has accomplished the &quot;BRC 2.0&quot; upgrade at block 912,690. It has integrated the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) and made a significant stride towards supporting Ethereum-style smart contracts. This upgrade was jointly undertaken by the Ordinals developer Best in Slot and the BRC-20 creator Domo.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27257</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of a Fed rate cut in September has risen to 89.7%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27256</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch Tool&quot;, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point Fed rate cut in September is 89.7% (increased from 86.4% yesterday), and the probability of keeping the rates unchanged is 10.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Hunan Police Bust $170 Million Virtual Currency Laundering Case, Arrest 15 Suspects</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27255</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to the official WeChat account of the Hunan Public Security Bureau, the Yueyang police successfully cracked a significant virtual currency money laundering case. The criminal gang used &quot;blockchain over-the-counter trading businesses&quot; as a guise and attracted &quot;mules&quot; to provide bank accounts at a price that was 0.8 yuan higher than the market price of each USDT, thereby providing a money laundering channel for overseas online gambling, telecommunication fraud, and other illegal funds.Since July 2024, the gang has established a four-level money laundering network and has handled approximately 170 million yuan of illegal funds in total. The gang has illegally made a profit of more than 1 million yuan and has operated across more than 20 provinces and cities across the country. Currently, the police have arrested 15 criminal suspects, and the case is under further investigation.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27255</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain solo miner successfully mined Block 912632, receiving a reward of 3.147 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27254</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to mempool data, at 10:48:27 the previous day, a solo Bitcoin miner successfully mined block 912632 and received a block reward of 3.147 BTC, which was approximately worth $340,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27254</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>