<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:33:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Morpho Officially Launches on the Arbitrum Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24265</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the lending protocol Morpho officially launched on the Arbitrum network.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24265</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Tariff Pass-Through Effect on CPI is Minimal, Fed Likely to Cut Rates in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24264</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Guy LeBas, the Chief Fixed Income Strategist at Janney Montgomery Scott, stated that July&apos;s CPI roughly met expectations and did not pass too much tariff impact onto consumer prices. This is certainly enough to solidify the possibility of a rate cut in September. There is still a long way to go before the next month&apos;s meeting, but at least in terms of inflation data, the current situation is not a cause for concern. As an independent and impartial economist, one can interpret this data from two perspectives. Firstly, since the tariff effect has not yet fully manifested, future inflation may rise. Secondly, corporate companies are absorbing the tariff impact, so it will not be passed through to consumer inflation. But in either case, it is enough to provide the Fed with a valid reason to cut interest rates in September, provided that next month&apos;s data does not show a significant acceleration. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Launches Kickstart Program, Integrates LaaS to Provide All-in-One Project Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24266</link>
      <description>August 12th. BNB Chain made an announcement regarding the upgrade of the Kickstart Plan. It has been fully integrated with the original LaaS Program. This provides developers and high-potential projects within the ecosystem with quicker and more precise one-stop support. It helps to accelerate the entire process from concept to realization and growth.After the upgrade, the service coverage of the Kickstart Plan has been expanded to 18 major categories and more than 50 top-tier service providers. These include CertiK (for security auditing), AWS and Google (for cloud services), NodeReal (for infrastructure), PancakeSwap (for token issuance), etc. It offers comprehensive resources from technical support, security auditing to fund management, user growth, and marketing promotion for projects at different stages.The plan is divided into two phases:- The dApp Development Phase is targeted at emerging developers and teams, providing foundational support such as development frameworks, s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24266</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale/Institution Once Again Increases Holdings by 35,237 ETH, Worth $155.06 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24262</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a &quot;mysterious&quot; whale or institution once more augmented its holdings by 35,237 ETH, which is valued at $1.5506 billion.Its overall holdings reached 328,421 ETH, with a value of $1.445 billion. These holdings are distributed across 10 distinct wallets, and the held ETH originated from FalconX, Galaxy Digital, and BitGo.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24262</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonbirds Floor Price Surges Past 3.2 ETH, Marking a 7-Day Increase of 42.22%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24263</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Blur Data, the floor price of Moonbirds has exceeded 3.2 ETH. It has witnessed a 24-hour price increase of 28.53% and a 24-hour trading volume of 692.09 ETH. The 7-day price increase is 42.22%, with a 7-day trading volume of 1375.3 ETH. Currently, the market capitalization of Moonbirds has entered the top ten of the Ethereum ecosystem NFT rankings.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24263</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader TheWhiteWhaleHL ranks first on the Hyperliquid 30-day Leaderboard, with a profit of $45.8 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24260</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, the top trader @TheWhiteWhaleHL ranked first on the 30-day leaderboard of Hyperliquid with a profit of $45.8 million. During the market crash a few weeks ago, he maintained a long position.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24260</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctum Community has submitted Proposal CLOUD-005, seeking investor support for immediate CLOUD vested release</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24261</link>
      <description>August 12th. In the Solana ecosystem&apos;s LST protocol, the Sanctum community has put forward Proposal CLOUD-005. The intention is to give the Sanctum team the authorization to provide an immediate unlock of their vested CLOUD to investors and allocate 30% of their CLOUD to the team reserve. Currently, 9% of the token supply for Sanctum investors will unlock on a monthly basis over the next 24 months.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24261</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Administration Official Expanding Fed Chair Candidate Pool, Seeking President and Market Trust</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24259</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as per Politico, officials within the Trump administration are in the process of expanding the roster of candidates for the position of replacing Federal Reserve Chairman Powell next year. They are seeking an individual who can command the trust of both the President and the financial markets.According to an unnamed government official, the current list of candidates under consideration encompasses: the current Fed Vice Chairmen Richard Jefferson and Michelle Bowman, the President of the Dallas Federal Reserve Bank Lori Logan, the former President of the St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank Jim Brad, and the macroeconomic advisor Mark Summerlin. The official also signaled that candidates from the private sector might also be taken into account.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24259</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UST and Luna Crash Saga Nears its End as Terra Founder Do Kwon Pleads Guilty</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24258</link>
      <description>August 12th: During a hearing in a U.S. court, Terra&apos;s founder, Do Kwon, entered a guilty plea to two counts of conspiracy to commit fraud and wire fraud. These charges are related to the previous $40 billion TerraUSD (UST) and Luna collapse.Do Kwon, who was born in Seoul, South Korea in 1991, co-founded Terraform Labs in Singapore in 2018 with others. They launched the algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD and the governance token Luna, which were once regarded as an innovative benchmark in DeFi. In May 2022, due to algorithmic imbalance, TerraUSD detached from the U.S. dollar, resulting in a sharp decline in the prices of Luna and UST. The market value nearly reached zero, triggering market panic and a chain reaction. This further plunged the crypto market into the abyss of a bear market. Global investors suffered approximately $40 billion in losses, and as a result, Do Kwon was charged with financial fraud.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24258</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top trader @TheWhiteWhaleHL has claimed the #1 spot on Hyperliquid&apos;s 30-day leaderboard with $45.8M in profits.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24257</link>
      <description>Top trader @TheWhiteWhaleHL has claimed the #1 spot on Hyperliquid&apos;s 30-day leaderboard with $45.8M in profits. A true bull, he held his positions strong through the market crash a couple of weeks ago. He&apos;s still long on $ETH, $SOL, and $HYPE.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24257</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>