<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:28:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) will release a summary of the Stablecoin Issuer Rules next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21439</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per Mars Financial, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority is scheduled to release a summary of the Stablecoin Issuer Guidelines in the coming week.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21439</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein Case Defense Lawyer Roy Black Passes Away</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21438</link>
      <description>July 23rd. According to the Associated Press, Roy Black, the renowned celebrity lawyer who once brokered the &quot;sweetheart deal&quot; for Epstein, has passed away at the age of 80. The client list of this legal giant resembles a who&apos;s who of America&apos;s elite, encompassing conservative pundit Rush Limbaugh, members of the Kennedy family, actress Kelsey Grammer, media outlet BuzzFeed, and even the luxury car brand Rolls-Royce.BlockBeats previously reported that in early June, Musk tweeted stating that the reason why Trump did not release the Epstein files was that Trump himself was included in the files. This is the actual reason for the non-publication of these files. Subsequently, in an attempt to alleviate tensions with Trump, Musk deleted the relevant tweet.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21438</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new address received an additional 33,600 ETH from FalconX, bringing the total balance to 105,900 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21437</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as monitored by Onchain lens, a newly established wallet address has once more received 33,644 ETH from FalconX within the past 25 minutes. The value of this amount is $1.2573 billion.At present, the wallet holds 105,977 ETH, with a value of $3.96 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21437</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale &quot;Sets 10 Major Goals First&quot; to Short BTC, Reaching a Position Size of $217 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21436</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the contract trading whale user &quot;First Set 10 Big Goals&quot; posted on social media &quot;Real-name Shorting&quot;. According to the screenshot provided by the user, they are currently using 36.2 million US dollars as collateral, holding a short position of 1817 BTC, with a position size of 217 million US dollars. The entry price is 119,425 US dollars and the liquidation price is 133,678 US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21436</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Company Skycorp Solar to Accept Cryptocurrency Payments and Invest in Ethereum</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21435</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to official information, the Nasdaq-listed company Skycorp Solar Group Limited (stock code: PN) declared that starting from August 1st, it will commence accepting Bitcoin, Ethereum, as well as major stablecoins like USDC and USDT as international transaction payment means. The solar photovoltaic product supplier also intends to allocate a portion of its cash reserves and earnings from renewable energy projects to a strategic acquisition of Ethereum as part of its long-term digital asset management strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21435</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU Token Deployment Address transferred an additional 2.266 billion tokens to a CEX in the past 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21434</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as monitored by on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, in the past 24 hours, 226.6 million PENGU tokens (approximately $9.05 million) have been continuously transferred from the PENGU token deployment address to multiple CEXs.Since July 12th, a total of 1.81 billion PENGU tokens (approximately $54.61 million) have been transferred from the PENGU token deployment address to CEXs.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Associated Address bought 6144 ETH in the last 20 minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21433</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the address linked to the Trump family-backed project WLFI, which is 0x77a...F94F6, has utilized a total of 2300 USDC to acquire 6144.97 ETH within the past 20 minutes. Up to now, the cumulative amount of ETH purchased through three WLFI transactions in the past six days has risen to 10,013.54 ETH (approximately $35.98 million), with an average price of $3593.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21433</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the world&apos;s largest market makers, Citadel Securities, urges the SEC to regulate tokenized stocks rigorously</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21432</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, one of the world&apos;s largest market makers, Citadel Securities, recently made a plea to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to impose equivalent regulations on tokenized stocks and traditional stocks.In a letter sent to the SEC&apos;s Crypto Asset Working Group this week, the company stated that regulators should refrain from granting exemptions from securities rules and instead focus on market liquidity and investor protection. &quot;In short, while we wholeheartedly support technological innovation aimed at addressing market inefficiencies, attempting to issue &apos;securities-like&apos; products through regulatory arbitrage is far from being innovative.&quot;TD Cowen analyst Jaret Seiberg also pointed out in a research report on Monday that there remains uncertainty in tokenized trading mechanisms, with some of the challenges revolving around optimal price discovery. &quot;The traditional stock trading system requires achieving the national best bid or offer, which is what gives rise</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI&apos;s associated address has once again increased its ETH holdings by 1740 coins. In the past 6 days, WLFI has acquired a total of 5608 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21431</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the WLFI-related address added another 1740 ETH to its position just 2 minutes ago, with a value of $6.5 million.Over the past six days, three WLFI addresses have collectively purchased a total of 5608.48 ETH (approximately $19.46 million) at an average price of $3469.66. This amount has already achieved a profit of $1.457 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21431</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address created recently increased its ETH holdings by 32,600 coins through an OTC trade 20 minutes ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21430</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the newly established wallet address 0x3dF3 has just completed another over-the-counter (OTC) purchase of 32,640 ETH (valued at $122.18 million), and it has accumulated a total of 43,787 ETH (worth $163 million) over the past 4 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>