<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:26:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet has received 3500 BTC from Gemini in the past 3 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22256</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet has received 3,500 BTC from Gemini within the past 3 days. The total value of these BTC amounts to 4.1567 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Co-Founder: SharpLink Aims to Accumulate ETH Faster than Other Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22255</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Cointelegraph, Joe Lubin, the co-founder of Ethereum and CEO of Consensys, is one of the Ethereum Treasury Strategists at SharpLink Gaming. He anticipates that the company can amass Ethereum (ETH) for its shareholders as promptly as feasible, raising the &quot;battle cry&quot; during the corporate rush to become the foremost ETH accumulator.Joe Lubin declared: &quot;We hold the view that, on a per-share (fully-diluted) basis, our rate of ETH accumulation will outstrip that of any other Ethereum project and definitely be quicker than Bitcoin-related projects. SharpLink is accumulating funds &apos;daily&apos; through a market-price-based issuance mechanism to augment its ETH reserves, while staking existing holdings to earn rewards and achieve compound growth.&quot;SharpLink is vying with BitMine for the status of &quot;Ethereum Treasury Premier Company.&quot; According to the data from StrategicETHReserve, BitMine currently leads, holding 566,800 ETH with a market value of approximately $2.13 billion,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22255</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFX Surpasses $0.24, Up Over 29% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22254</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to HTX market data, CFX exceeded $0.24 and is currently priced at $0.2427, with a 24-hour increase of more than 29%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22254</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoPunks Floor Price Surpasses $200,000 Mark for the First Time in Over a Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22253</link>
      <description>July 29th. As per Decrypt, since August of the previous year, the floor price of CryptoPunks has been on a continuous upward trajectory, increasing from 20.45 ETH to 53.98 ETH, which represents a 163% growth. Given the current Ethereum price of approximately $3,745, the floor price of CryptoPunks has exceeded $200,000 and reached its highest point since March 8, 2024. This upward trend commenced with a large-scale &quot;buying spree&quot; last week when an address made a single transaction to purchase 45 CryptoPunks.According to CoinGecko data, the total market value of the NFT market has witnessed a significant surge, rising from $3.6 billion in early July to $6.8 billion. Historical data indicates that when Ethereum shows strong performance, it often leads to an increase in the prices of leading NFT projects on its blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22253</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Family&apos;s cryptocurrency project WLFI bought 256.75 ETH 20 hours ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22252</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, 20 hours ago, the crypto project WLFI of the Trump family spent 1 million USDC to purchase 256.75 ETH at an average price of $3,895 per ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22252</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letsbonk&apos;s Solana Launchpad market share has risen to 83.5% in the last 24 hours, while pump.fun has dropped to 7.94%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22251</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours in the Solana yield farming platform market share ranking, Letsbonk took the lead with 83.5%, pump.fun came in second with 7.94%, and Jup Studio ranked third with 2.69%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22251</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institution: The Federal Reserve is expected to remain on hold this week, with two major doves likely to dissent.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22250</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Pascal&apos;s Chief U.S. Economist Urup Ruxi stated that it is anticipated that the Federal Reserve will maintain the interest rate at 4.25%-4.5% unchanged this week. However, Waller and Bowman may express opposition. This might heighten speculation that once more officials appointed by Trump start to serve on the Fed&apos;s Board of Governors starting from the first quarter of 2026, the pace of rate cuts will quicken.The dovish Waller and Bowman may contend that monetary policy is restrictive because tariff-related inflation is being offset by other factors and advocate for a rate cut by citing a neutral rate close to 3%. It is expected that Powell will attempt to guide the FOMC to wait as long as possible for the next rate cut, with higher probabilities of a rate cut in October compared to September. (Kyodo)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22250</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PetroChina Capital: Currently not involved in stablecoin-related business, conducting research on relevant regulatory policies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22249</link>
      <description>On July 29th, during an institutional research, CNPC Capital indicated that the company is currently not engaged in stablecoin-related business. The company has observed that some investors have a significant level of interest in stablecoin business. In order to address the concerns of investors, the company is conducting research on policies related to this field.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22249</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will upgrade the Wallet Network Servers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22248</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per official information, Binance is scheduled to upgrade its wallet network servers on July 31, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). In order to facilitate this upgrade, Binance will halt all network deposit and withdrawal services at 16:00 (UTC+8) on July 31, 2025. The upgrade is anticipated to last for 15 minutes.During the wallet upgrade period, users will still be able to trade tokens normally. Once the wallet upgrade is completed and the network becomes stable, the deposit and withdrawal services for the affected tokens will be reopened without any additional notifications.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine: Multiple Institutions Estimate ETH&apos;s Implied Value to Reach $60,000 Using the &quot;Store of Value&quot; Model</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22247</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Ethereum treasury and the crypto mining company Bitmine announced that they have invited multiple research institutions to value Ethereum (ETH) according to Wall Street&apos;s &quot;alternative value&quot; model. This valuation is for reference only. The findings indicate that the implied value of ETH is $60,000, while the current market price is approximately $3,800.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22247</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>