<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Withdrawal Trend Reversal, 24-hour Net Outflow of 17,940.48 BTC from CEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26892</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to Coinglass data, during the past 24 hours, the total net outflow of BTC from CEXs was 17,940.48 BTC. The top three CEXs with the largest outflow amounts are as follows:· Kraken, with an outflow of 16,859.07 BTC;· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 1,914.07 BTC;· Binance, with an outflow of 551.76 BTC.In addition, Bitfinex had an inflow of 884.28 BTC, ranking first in the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26892</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US PCE Continues to Exceed Target, Fed Faces Challenges Ahead of September Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26891</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Market analyst Matt Grossman stated that the inflation gauge that the Federal Reserve favors did not approach the 2% target level in July, emphasizing the policy challenge that the Fed is facing as it prepares for a possible rate cut in September. Data from the US Commerce Department&apos;s Bureau of Economic Analysis showed that the US PCE Price Index increased by 2.6% year-on-year in July, remaining the same as the previous month.The core PCE Price Index rose by 2.9% year-on-year in July, which is higher than June&apos;s 2.8%. This reading was widely anticipated as economists could very accurately predict PCE inflation using other official data released earlier this month. While some price increases driven by tariffs continue to exceed the target level, Fed Chairman Powell previously hinted that considering the cooling labor market, the Fed is considering implementing the first rate cut of the year in September. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26891</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins is entering the mobile gaming space with the launch of a new battle royale party game called Pudgy Party.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26890</link>
      <description>August 29th — It was announced on Friday by the well-known NFT brand Pudgy Penguins about the global launch of the Web3 mobile game Pudgy Party in collaboration with the developer of FIFA Rivals, Mythical Games. Pudgy Party is a light-hearted party battle royale game set in a fast-paced mini-game world where all the in-game characters are made up of the iconic Pudgy Penguins imagery. Each character has unique features, abilities, and personalities. Every match is designed to be fresh and unpredictable, with rotating challenges and unexpected twists to ensure that no two parties are the same.Players can customize their penguin characters by using outfits, emotes, and collectibles. Some of these are non-tradable, while others are limited edition and can be traded on Mythical&apos;s marketplace. Players can also mint, upgrade, and fuse rare items on Mythical&apos;s EVM-compatible Polkadot parallel chain, Mythos Chain, and turn them into NFTs.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26890</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Falls Below $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26889</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum fell below $4400, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 4.34%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26889</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Updates Old Blockchain Transition Plan: Will Not Freeze Smart Contracts on the Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26888</link>
      <description>August 29th. Stablecoin issuer Tether declared today an update regarding its transition plan for five legacy blockchains, namely Omni Layer, Bitcoin Cash SLP, Kusama, EOS, and Algorand. More than a year ago, Tether announced its intention to halt the redemption and freezing of USDT tokens on these legacy blockchains starting from September 1, 2025, with a gradual phasing out of support.In response to feedback from the discontinued blockchain communities, Tether has adjusted this approach and will not freeze smart contracts on these networks. Although users can still transfer tokens between wallets, Tether will discontinue the direct issuance and redemption of tokens on these blockchains. This indicates that these tokens will no longer receive official support like other Tether tokens. Tether remains dedicated to a smooth transition and will continue to cooperate with the community to ensure transparency and clarity throughout the entire process.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. July Consumer Spending and Inflation Rise Together, but Weak Jobs Data May Pave the Way for Fed Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26887</link>
      <description>August 29th: In July, U.S. consumer spending demonstrated a solid growth. Meanwhile, the core PCE witnessed a slight upward trend as the prices of some goods rose due to import tariffs. Nevertheless, against the backdrop of the softening labor market conditions, these data might not prevent the Fed from cutting interest rates next month. The low unemployment rate is sustaining steady wage growth, which provides support for consumption.However, President Trump&apos;s imposition of tariffs on imported goods is elevating business costs, intensifying corporate caution and causing employers to be reluctant to increase hiring. Government reports this month indicated that during the past three months up to July, employment has been increasing at an average rate of 35,000 people per month, in contrast to 123,000 people during the same period in 2024. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26887</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the release of the US PCE data, traders still expect the Fed to cut interest rates in September.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26886</link>
      <description>August 29th: After the release of the U.S. PCE economic data, short-term interest rate futures reduced their earlier losses; traders still anticipate that the Fed will implement a rate cut in September.The current probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September is currently 85.3%, and the probability of maintaining the current rate is 14.7%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26886</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Personal Spending in July Recorded a Monthly Rate of 0.5%, Reaching a New High Since March 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26885</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the U.S. Personal Spending M/M for July was reported at 0.5%, which met the anticipated value of 0.50%. The previous figure was revised from 0.30% to 0.4%, reaching a new high since March 2025. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26885</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 Index Futures, Nasdaq 100 Index Futures both saw a decline following the release of PCE data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26884</link>
      <description>On August 29th, both S&amp;P 500 Index Futures and Nasdaq 100 Index Futures experienced a decline following the release of PCE data. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26884</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Surges Above $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26883</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum witnessed a rebound and managed to break through $4400. The 24-hour decrease was narrowed to 3.88%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26883</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>