<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:46:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock&apos;s ETHA has increased its holdings by 1.25 million ETH this month, surpassing a total of 3 million ETH held.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22518</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per the monitoring of lookonchain, starting from July 1st, BlackRock&apos;s ETH Trust has added an additional 1.25 million ETH. This is approximately worth $4.73 billion. Currently, its total holdings have surpassed 3 million ETH, with a total value of around $11.36 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22518</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram username &apos;@crypto&apos; receives a $25 million offer, with the price skyrocketing 70x in two years</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22517</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Pavel Durov, the CEO of Telegram, stated in a post on Wednesday that an early user of Telegram and Toncoin (TON) had recently received a $25 million offer to purchase their &quot;crypto&quot; username on Telegram.The username was originally bought for $350,000 in 2023. The username holder also recently said, &quot;If these cannot be taken away by others, then I want to own all rare usernames.&quot; - This is the quote that Durov referenced in the post.All usernames on Telegram are tokenized on the TON blockchain, meaning each username is unique and cannot be replicated. According to Statista data, the most expensive username in 2024 was @news, selling for as much as $5.8 million, while @auto also fetched a high price of $5.2 million.In the post, Durov wrote: &quot;Miracles happen when people can directly own their digital assets - just like this tokenized Telegram username, which has increased in value by 70 times.&quot; &quot;Telegram users are true sovereigns: no middlemen, no forced confiscation,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22517</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian financial company VERT Capital will tokenize real-world assets worth $1 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22516</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Brazilian credit structuring and securitization firm VERT Capital intends to tokenize up to $1 billion worth of debt and receivables on the XDC Network. As part of this transaction, the two companies will transfer a variety of financial instruments such as corporate debt, agricultural agribusiness receivables, and structured credit products onto the blockchain within the next 30 months.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22516</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched the U-based A2Z perpetual contract, with leverage ranging from 1 to 50x.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22515</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to an official announcement, Bitget has declared the commencement of the U-based A2Z perpetual contract. The leverage range is set from 1 to 50x. Additionally, the contract trading BOT will be made available simultaneously.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuvve, a publicly traded company, approves first-time purchase of up to $3 million in HYPE</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22514</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Nuvve Holding Corp., a publicly traded electric vehicle technology firm, announced today that its board of directors has given the green light for the initial purchase of a maximum of $3 million worth of HYPE.The company also disclosed a $4.8 million common stock offering at a price of $0.95 per share to back its HYPE financial strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22514</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institution: Powell&apos;s Continued Ambiguity Today Is Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22513</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Peter Boockvar, the Chief Investment Officer of One Point BFG Wealth Partners, stated that Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is facing a tough task. There are some cracks emerging in the labor market. Inflation is still significantly above his targeted sustainable level of 2%. However, the financial environment is extremely loose. With a significant amount of time still remaining until the September meeting, Powell&apos;s maintaining a vague stance is beneficial to him. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22513</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Belgravia Hartford secures new $5 million funding for Bitcoin purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22512</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the publicly traded Canadian company Belgravia Hartford announced that it had completed a $5 million convertible bond financing with Round 13 Digital Asset Fund.Belgravia Hartford Capital indicated that it would utilize the full $5 million to enhance its holdings of Bitcoin (currently 40.77 BTC), and further details would be announced after the purchase was completed.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polygon Network Allegedly Experiencing Outage</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22511</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to data from blockchain explorers, it appears that the Polygon network has experienced downtime. The latest block on it was recorded 2 hours ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid is planning to automatically refund users affected by API issues</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22510</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to market information, Hyperliquid intends to automatically refund users who were affected by API issues.BlockBeats reported earlier today that Hyperliquid announced on Discord that from 22:10 to 22:47 (UTC+8) last night, the API server encountered problems, resulting in delays when orders were sent to the node. This was due to a surge in traffic. There was no hacking or exploitation involved. The issue has been resolved, and further improvements are planned for the future. In addition, various levels of the technical stack will also implement additional protection measures to detect API server issues and prevent users from encountering unexpected problems.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to strong data-driven momentum, the US Dollar is poised to achieve its longest winning streak since February.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22509</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the latest data indicates that the U.S. economy is robust, and the dollar is moving towards its longest consecutive upward trend since February. The Bloomberg Dollar Spot Index increased by 0.3%, reaching its highest level since June 23rd, with the index rising for five consecutive trading days.The U.S. economic growth and inflation data released on Wednesday were both higher than expected, which supported the Federal Reserve&apos;s hawkish stance. In the second quarter, U.S. economic activity rebounded as consumer spending picked up slightly, and the Fed&apos;s preferred inflation indicator, core PCE, rose by 2.5% year-on-year.Meanwhile, ADP private sector employment data shows that the labor market remains strong. Valentin Marinov, the head of G10 currency strategy at Credit Agricole CIB, said, &quot;The market may view this data as suggesting that the Fed&apos;s future rate cuts will be slower and more postponed. If Federal Reserve Chair Powell continues to maintain his current relative</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>