<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater: What is Behind the Federal Reserve&apos;s Unwillingness to Cut Interest Rates, Expected to Announce Fed Chair Nomination by Year-End</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22655</link>
      <description>July 31st: U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen stated, &quot;I&apos;m uncertain about the reason for not reducing interest rates. I have compiled a detailed list for the Fed Chair candidate. There will be two vacant positions on the Federal Reserve Board. It is anticipated to announce the nomination for the Fed Chair by the end of the year.&quot; (Xinhua Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22655</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: BTC Price Above Short-Term Holder Cost Range, Strong Support Expected on Pullback</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22654</link>
      <description>On July 31, Glassnode stated in a post that &quot;The present BTC price remains above the holding cost range of all short-term holder subgroups (ranging from 24 hours to 3 months: $110,000 to $117,000). This price aligns with a low transaction volume range, suggesting that in the event of a pullback, there will be strong support.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22654</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institution: US Stock Market&apos;s &quot;Super Month&quot; Coming to an End, August May See Profit-Taking</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22653</link>
      <description>July 31st. The market research firm SentimenTrader declared that the U.S. stock market is on the verge of concluding its most heated July ever. During this month, the S&amp;P 500 index has reached a historic high 10 times (making it the third best July performance since 1928), and the Nasdaq Composite index has hit a historic high 14 times. This &quot;super month&quot; is uncommon during the summer, and historical data indicates that after experiencing such a surge in July, August tends to become difficult.Historically, when the S&amp;P 500 index hits at least 7 multi-year highs in July, the likelihood of it rising in August is merely 36%, with a probability of rising in the following two months being less than half. The Nasdaq Composite index has demonstrated greater resilience and usually experiences a strong rebound 4 months later, but August still seems like a gamble. (Jin10)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22653</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Season Index Rises to 41</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22652</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to Coinmarketcap data, the Altcoin Season Index has gone up to 41. It had dropped to 35 on July 30th. This index shows that among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, approximately 41 projects have outperformed Bitcoin in terms of price increase over the past 90 days.Note: The CMC Cryptocurrency Altseason Index is a real-time indicator that is designed to determine whether the cryptocurrency market is currently in a season where altcoins dominate. This index is based on the performance of the top 100 altcoins compared to Bitcoin over the past 90 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22652</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireverse is launching an OG NFT Limited-Time Claim Event, and the TGE countdown is also starting simultaneously.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22651</link>
      <description>July 31st - The decentralized AI music platform Fireverse, after teasing about the upcoming TGE (Token Generation Event), officially launched its original NFT (Non-Fungible Token) today. This OG NFT is a commemorative badge dedicated to early builders and long-term supporters, with a total supply of 10,000 and is non-transferable. The OG NFT not only symbolizes the important identity of the participants but will also unlock exclusive benefits in the future ecosystem of the platform.This round of OG NFT will be distributed to active users of the Fireverse platform, VBOX holders, FireTrack NFT creators, Nobody NFT holders, Discord contributors. It will also be distributed through whitelist distribution by partners and KOLs (Key Opinion Leaders). Each eligible wallet address can receive up to 1 piece, and the claiming window is from July 30th to August 5th. Unclaimed allocations after the deadline will be available for public claim on a first-come, first-served basis.As Fireverse prep</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22651</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The total strategic Ethereum reserves held by 64 entities has surpassed $10 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22650</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to data from strategicethreserve, the total strategic Ethereum (ETH) reserve held by 64 entities has exceeded $10 billion and reached $10.57 billion. Among them:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) is in the first place, currently holding 625,000 ETH, with a value of approximately $24.1 billion;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) is in the second place, currently holding 438,200 ETH, with a value of approximately $16.9 billion;The Ethereum Foundation is in the third place, holding 234,600 ETH, with a value of approximately $9.042 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22650</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Bitget Derivatives Market Share Rises to 7.2%, Ranking Third Among Global CEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22649</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bitcoin.com issued a Cryptocurrency Derivatives Market Analysis Report titled &quot;Crypto Derivatives 101&quot;. This report systematically examines key products like futures, perpetual contracts, options, etc., and offers a comprehensive comparison of the advantages of centralized exchanges (CEX) and decentralized exchanges (DEX) in terms of liquidity, slippage, fees, risk management, and asset custody. The report indicates that Binance, Bitget, and OKX are rated as the platforms with the most institutional trading advantages, while GMX and Hyperliquid provide higher transparency and self-custody capabilities for DeFi native users.The report&apos;s data reveals that Bitget has surged and is expected to become the world&apos;s third-largest derivatives exchange by 2025. Its market share has increased from 4.6% at the beginning of the year to 7.2%. In April alone, Bitget&apos;s futures trading volume reached $920 billion, demonstrating leading liquidity and market depth in multiple core trading</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22649</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Powell Refuses to Cut Interest Rates Again, Unsuitable for Fed Chair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22648</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Trump stated, &quot;Powell did not cut interest rates again. His move is belated. In fact, he is too angry, too foolish, and too politicized to hold the position of Fed chairman.&quot; (Kyodo News)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) website has launched a Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Register, but there are currently no issuers listed.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22647</link>
      <description>July 31st. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) has refreshed its website, indicating that with the enforcement of the Stablecoin Issuer Oversight Framework under the Stablecoin Law on August 1, 2025, the issuance of fiat-backed stablecoins has transformed into a licensed and regulated undertaking. The regulatory particulars of the oversight framework encompass: the Stablecoin Issuer Licensing Regime, supervision of Licensed Stablecoin Issuers, and the Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Register.The Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Register holds the names and fundamental information of Licensed Stablecoin Issuers. The public is capable of accessing the most recent list of licensed entities via the register. Presently, there are no Licensed Stablecoin Issuers, and the list will be updated in due course.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22647</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui Ecosystem MPC Network Token IKA Market Cap Surpasses $400 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate 35.15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22646</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on GMGN data, the token Ika (IKA) of the Secure Multiparty Computation (MPC) network in the Sui ecosystem has exceeded a market capitalization of $400 million. It has a 24-hour price increase of 35.15%, with a current price of $0.0402 and a 24-hour trading volume of $6.7 million.BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of related tokens are highly volatile and that investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22646</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>