<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Jito Labs and other organizations have jointly written to the SEC urging the inclusion of liquidity staking tokens in the Solana ETF.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22695</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Jito Labs, Bitwise, Multicoin Capital, VanEck, and the Solana Policy Institute submitted an open letter to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This letter proposed the utilization of Liquidity Staking Tokens (LST) as a collateral mechanism in Exchange-Traded Products (ETPs). The proposal specifically pertains to the 8 Solana ETF applications submitted earlier in June and the additional applications submitted on June 25th.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22695</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Whale has accumulated 1% of the total Bitcoin supply over the past 4 months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22694</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on data from the crypto market analysis platform Santiment, whale addresses holding between 10 and 10,000 bitcoins have accumulated 0.9% of the total supply over the past four months. Given that the current circulating supply of Bitcoin is 19,899,417 coins, this ratio actually reaches 1%. This is because there is still a portion of Bitcoin that has not been mined yet (with a total supply of 21 million coins).During the just-past 48 hours, on-chain analyst Ali Martinez stated that Bitcoin whales have accumulated an additional 30,000 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22694</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine Holdings Disclosure: Holds 625,000 ETH and 92 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22693</link>
      <description>On July 31, Bitmine sent out a tweet stating that it possesses 625,000 ETH and 92 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22693</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase CEO: White House Digital Asset Report Emphasizes Market Legislation to Help U.S. Become Global Crypto Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22692</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, tweeted and said, &quot;The US White House has issued its first-ever report on digital assets, which clearly indicates that market structure legislation is crucial in fulfilling the President&apos;s commitment to make the US a global cryptocurrency hub. Let&apos;s work together to make it a reality.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22692</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meteora Season One Points Query is Now Open</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22691</link>
      <description>July 31st: The liquidity protocol Meteora within the Solana ecosystem has initiated the query for the points of the first season. The snapshot for the first season was taken on June 30th. The Meteora second season event is currently in progress. During this event, users provide liquidity to earn fees and obtain points in the second season LP incentive program.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22691</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant Analyst: Bitcoin&apos;s New Investor Dominance Power is Growing</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22690</link>
      <description>On July 31st, CryptoQuant analyst Axel said, &quot;The dominant force of new investors is continuously expanding. However, there remains room before reaching extreme levels. This indicates that the market still has upward potential, and the bullish momentum is anticipated to persist until the typical euphoric range (over 60-70%) is achieved.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22690</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liu Feng: Quantitative Change is the Best Vessel for Innovation, Content Creation will Achieve Breakthroughs through Continuous &quot;Emergence&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22689</link>
      <description>On July 31st, BODL Ventures Partner Liu Feng, as a guest on BlockBeats&apos; &quot;Content Coin: Hype, Hope, or the Second Spring of Creator Economy?&quot; themed Space, expressed that the vision of content coins should not be confined to the present. In the future, there may be an explosive period during which billions of tokens are issued daily. This can be described with a popular term as &quot;emergence&quot;, similar to how AI suddenly made breakthroughs during continuous &quot;emergence&quot;. Perhaps by then, all new content creation, new forms, new modes of dissemination, and the so-called use cases will truly emerge. At present, we should bravely envision this scenario, which may shatter all our imaginations. Looking back at the nearly 30-year evolution of the internet, it was the same. It&apos;s not that the current content is too poor; it&apos;s that we haven&apos;t created enough. A miracle can happen when we go all out. Without quantitative change, where does qualitative change come from? Quantity change is the best carri</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22689</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin and Ethereum Futures Trading Volume Reach $223.6 Billion, Hit 5-Month High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22688</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to CryptoQuant data, the trading volume of alternative coins and Ethereum (ETH) futures amounted to $223.6 billion, reaching a new high in 5 months.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine, Sharplink Gaming, and The Ether Machine collectively hold more ETH than the Ethereum Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22687</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on the data from strategicethreserve, three companies, namely Bitmine, Sharplink Gaming, and The Ether Machine, possess a greater amount of ETH than the Ethereum Foundation. Among them:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) holds the top position and currently has 625,000 ETH;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) comes in second and currently holds 438,200 ETH;The Ether Machine ranks third, with 334,800 ETH;The Ethereum Foundation is in the fourth place, holding 234,600 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22687</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonit, launched in collaboration with 9GAG, Memeland, and others, introduces a Meme Coin Market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22686</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Moonit launched the Meme Currency Market, an AI protocol capable of automatically tokenizing internet culture and viral memes. This project was jointly established by 9GAG, Memeland, Helio Pay, MoonPay, Dexscreener, and collaborated with technology providers like Jupiter Exchange and Meteora. The platform is now officially in operation.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22686</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>