<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:51:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will open airdrop distribution today at 15:00 UTC, with a minimum threshold of 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22762</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Binance Alpha will commence the Alpha airdrop at 15:00 (UTC+8). Users who possess at least 200 Binance Alpha points will be eligible to claim the token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. The specific airdropped token has not been made public as of now.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: New Coin WLFI Launches on Solana, OG Sees Short-Term Market Cap Surge, Base Chain Veteran Token BNKR Shows Active Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22761</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to GMGN data, within the past 6 hours on the Solana chain, the top five tokens in the &quot;Next Blue Chip&quot; sector were WLFI, PUMP, OG, MarsMi, and URANUS. WLFI and OG are new meme tokens that have been listed for less than 10 hours and have fewer than a thousand holders, presenting a significant risk.On the other hand, on the Base chain, in the past 24 hours, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume released on Clanker were BNKR, CLANKER, DRB, Fartcoin, and LUM. These five tokens have been listed for a longer time and have more than a thousand holders.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins usually lack practical use cases, experience high price volatility, and investments should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22761</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stock Concept Stock Stablecoin Plunges in the Afternoon, Guotai Junan International Falls Over 7%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22760</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to market data from RockFlow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), the afternoon decline of Hong Kong stock stablecoin concept stocks widened. YBB Digital and OSL Group fell by nearly 10%, Kinetic Investments dropped by more than 8%, Guotai Junan International dropped by more than 7%, and ZhongAn Online dropped by more than 6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury Burns 52 Million USDC on the Ethereum Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22758</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as monitored by Whale Alert, the USDC Treasury has just incinerated 52 million USDC on the Ethereum blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Adds TREE, A2Z, KERNEL, and SPK as Borrowable Assets on the Lending Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22759</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Binance has incorporated TREE, A2Z, KERNEL, and SPK into its lending platform as new borrowable assets and collateral assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC Chair: Project Crypto Will Drive On-chain Activity in the U.S. Financial Market, Regulatory Shift is a Time-sensitive Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22757</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the Chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Paul Atkins, stated that we are at the inception of a new era in the history of the market. The SEC&apos;s Project Crypto initiative will allow the U.S. financial market to undergo tokenization. This project will serve as the guiding beacon for the SEC and help President Trump establish the U.S. as the &quot;Capital of the Crypto World&quot; and maintain its dominant position in the crypto asset market.The primary task of the SEC is to promptly establish a regulatory framework for the distribution of crypto assets in the U.S. rather than being restricted by excessive bureaucracy and blanket rules. This not only indicates a shift in regulation but also presents an opportunity of the era.This morning, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced the launch of Project Crypto, aiming to modernize securities regulations and enable the U.S. financial market to undergo tokenization.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22757</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jie Zhuang Ng: The Stablecoin Regulation Will Surely Drive Hong Kong to Become a Global Web3 Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22756</link>
      <description>August 1st. Hong Kong Legislative Councilor Wu Jiezhuang posted on social media, stating that the official enforcement of the Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation took place today. He is glad to witness that many institutions from around the world are visiting Hong Kong to gain an understanding or express their intention to apply for a stablecoin license. This will undoubtedly contribute to the development of Hong Kong as a global Web3 hub. Meanwhile, it is necessary to remind industry practitioners and relevant institutions: after the law comes into effect, any business related to stablecoins must strictly comply with regulations. Recently, many industry insiders have inquired whether offline &quot;cryptocurrency exchange shops&quot; can continue to exchange and sell so-called &quot;stablecoins.&quot; It is recommended that everyone pay close attention to:Thoroughly studying the specific provisions of Article 6 and Article 9 of the Stablecoin Regulation;Urging users in Hong Kong who are interested in part</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22756</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority: Stablecoin License &quot;Invitation-Only&quot; Unofficial Term, Institutions Can Proactively Engage in Licensing Matters</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22755</link>
      <description>August 1st. An official from the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) pointed out that the term &quot;license by invitation&quot; for stablecoins is not an official designation but rather a market perception. This term does not completely represent the licensing process of the HKMA. Institutions that have the intention and interest to apply can actively communicate with the HKMA regarding licensing matters.A week ago, Eddie Yue, the chief of the HKMA, disclosed that although it was clearly stated that only a few stablecoin licenses would be issued in the initial stage, dozens of institutions have already taken the initiative to approach the HKMA team. The HKMA announcement on July 29th also indicated that institutions interested in applying for the license should contact the HKMA by August 31, 2025, so that the HKMA can communicate regulatory expectations and provide corresponding feedback. The licensing process will continue. If individual institutions feel fully prepared and wish to be consid</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22755</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Binance Retail Bitcoin Sell-off Surges, Whale Contrarian Accumulates $900 Million Worth of Ethereum</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22754</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Cryptoquant analyst Amr Taha issued a market analysis stating that the 7-day moving average of Bitcoin inflows to Binance by Short-Term Holders (STHs) has witnessed a significant spike. It rose from approximately 10,000 BTC to more than 36,000 BTC by the end of July. This sharp increase indicates abnormal activities among retail investors, which may be driven by profit-taking. A surge in exchange inflows usually implies that short-term investors are preparing to sell, especially when the price reaches a new high. This is in line with Bitcoin&apos;s recent record-breaking surge, further supporting the assumption that retail investors are reducing their BTC exposure.In sharp contrast to retail selling behavior, on July 31st, a whale wallet transferred over $9 billion worth of ETH from a centralized exchange (CEX) to an off-exchange wallet. Large-scale exchange outflows are usually related to accumulation strategies. When whales move assets to cold storage wallets, it indicate</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22754</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale 24-Hour Intensive Withdrawal: Total USDC outflow exceeding 22 million, exacerbating downward market pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22753</link>
      <description>Update, August 1st: Based on HyperInsight&apos;s monitoring, a whale has withdrawn nearly 16.1 million USDC within the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x540545 withdrew approximately 7 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x9Cb4F2 withdrew approximately 1.85 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0xc68E69 withdrew approximately 1.2 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x2ac1fA3 withdrew approximately 2 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x29862 withdrew approximately 4.05 million USDC in the past 2 hours. Meanwhile, the whale at address 0x3077fA made a deposit of approximately 1.85 million USDC in the past 1 hour.Earlier today, before 10 a.m., several whales had already withdrawn more than 6.4 million USDC, bringing the total withdrawal amount to over 22 million USDC so far. Additionally, due to the bearish market conditions, some whale ETH and BTC short positions are still under pressure.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22753</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>