<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:37:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: BTC Back above $120,000, ETH Set to Break $4,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21901</link>
      <description>July 26th: Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio put forward an analysis of the Bitcoin market, stating that &quot;BTC needs to demonstrate strength within a specific time period to maintain the current upward trend. Currently, BTC is fluctuating between $112,000 and $120,000, while the momentum of other assets in the market continues to decline. As bullish participants, they hope to see BTC regain $120,000, which may enable ETH to break through $4,000 (while maintaining a 0.03 exchange rate). In such a situation, the crypto party will continue, and bullish trading will proceed smoothly. If this cannot be achieved, both bulls and bears will encounter a range-bound market. If BTC falls below $112,000, the long-term bullish structure will no longer be favored.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21901</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: ETH seems sufficiently resilient, has opened long positions on ETH and SUI</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21899</link>
      <description>On July 26th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio shared on his personal channel, saying, &quot;As of today, considering the overall defense of altcoins against BTC, I have initiated some long positions. This is a short-term trade on a low time frame (LTF) rather than a hold on a high time frame (HTF). Nevertheless, ETH appears to be resilient enough to maintain the $3500 level. Presently, I am holding long positions in ETH and SUI. If ETH drops below the low point of $3500, the trade will be nullified.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21899</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Founder CZ Denies Involvement in Fundraising to Establish BNB Treasury Reserve Company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21900</link>
      <description>On July 26th, Binance founder CZ refuted any involvement in fundraising to establish a particular BNB Treasury Reserve company.Today, some community members claimed, &quot;CZ participated in a listed company and holds a 28% stake, raising funds to create a MicroStrategy for BNB. The seed round was closed last weekend, but the specific company was not disclosed.&quot; CZ responded to this claim by saying, &quot;Fake.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21900</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragonfly Partner Responds to Potential US Department of Justice Charges: Fully Intends to Defend Itself</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21898</link>
      <description>On July 26th, Haseeb, a partner of Dragonfly, responded to the news that &quot;The U.S. Department of Justice is considering charging DragonFly employees in the Tornado Cash case&quot; by stating, &quot;Dragonfly invested in PepperSec, Inc., the developer of Tornado Cash, in August 2020. This was because they recognized the importance of open-source privacy protection technology. Prior to the investment, Dragonfly obtained external legal advice confirming that the development of Tornado Cash was in compliance with the law and in line with the guidelines issued by FinCEN, an agency of the U.S. Treasury Department, in 2019. The U.S. government has publicly stated in court that they are considering charges against Dragonfly. Based on legal advice, we have decided not to make public comments at this time, but we have chosen not to remain silent.&quot;&quot;We firmly believe that Americans have the right to privacy. The lack of privacy remains one of the biggest unresolved problems in the cryptocurrency field. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21898</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Bounces Back above $116,000, 24-hour Loss Narrows to 2.05%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21897</link>
      <description>On July 26th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and exceeded $116,000. The 24-hour decline was narrowed to 2.05%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21897</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniswap Foundation: Anti-MEV DEX Angstrom is Now Live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21896</link>
      <description>On July 26th, the Uniswap Foundation made an announcement. The new decentralized exchange (DEX), Angstrom, developed by Sorella Labs, which is a MEV protection tool developer, is now operational. It provides native MEV protection for token swaps and liquidity providers (LPs). This is supported by the Uniswap v4 Hook Design Lab.Aiming to tackle the Ethereum MEV problem, the crypto startup Sorella Labs completed a $7.5 million seed round in August of the previous year. Paradigm led this round, and Uniswap Ventures, Bankless Ventures, Robot Ventures, and Nascent also participated. Sorella Labs is developing tools to address Ethereum&apos;s Maximum Extractable Value (MEV) issue, including Angstrom.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase CEO Clarifies Addition of RSC to Listing Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21895</link>
      <description>On July 26th, Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, clarified the announcement &quot;Coinbase to Add ResearchCoin (RSC) to Listing Roadmap&quot;:&quot;We, as the co-founder of ResearchHub, would like to share some details about the precautions we took a few years ago to eliminate conflicts of interest. All assets listed on Coinbase go through the review of our Digital Asset Support Group (DASG). DASG conducts a review of all assets listed on Coinbase from legal, compliance, and cybersecurity perspectives. I am not a member of DASG, so I do not have voting power to decide which assets receive listing approval. My relationship with ResearchHub has been disclosed to the Coinbase Board, which is a standard practice. I wrote a blog post on this topic in March 2022 and publicly committed not to sell RSC for at least four years, and this commitment remains unchanged.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21895</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResearchCoin (RSC) Experiences Short-Term Surge, Breaking $0.69</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21894</link>
      <description>On July 26th, based on HTX market information, due to the &quot;Addition to Coinbase Listing Roadmap&quot; news, ResearchCoin (RSC) witnessed a short-term sharp increase and broke through $0.69, with a market capitalization exceeding $20 million.BlockBeats Note: ResearchCoin is a crypto research platform co-founded by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong and others and belongs to the DeSci (Decentralized Science) field. The project aims to transform the traditional scientific journal publishing model. Users obtain ResearchCoin (RSC) by publishing content on ResearchHub, and the amount of RSC received is directly proportional to the value that other community members attach to the content.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21894</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Adds ResearchCoin (RSC) to Its Listing Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21893</link>
      <description>On July 26th, as per official channels, Coinbase has made an announcement regarding the inclusion of ResearchCoin (RSC) in its listing roadmap.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21893</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Appearance of Ancient BTC Whale After 14.5 Years of Dormancy, Holding Assets Worth Approximately $457 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21892</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the sell-off pressure from an ancient whale that holds 80,000 BTC is coming to an end. Meanwhile, another dormant whale that has been holding coins for 14.5 years may be getting ready to sell. The address &quot;bc1qsea3m&quot; made its first external transfer since January 2011 yesterday. And the receiving address moved 50 BTC to the address &quot;bc1q5&quot; 2 hours ago. The ownership of this receiving address is unknown, but it has interacted with addresses related to Coinbase, B2C2, and Galaxy Digital. The ancient whale holds 3,963 BTC, which is approximately $457 million, and its cost basis per coin is astonishingly low at $0.32.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21892</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>