<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Investment Advisor」 Emerges as the Largest Purchasing Group for Crypto Spot ETF, Signaling a Shift in Funds Flow from Speculation to Long-term, Portfolio-driven Allocation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26618</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to the data disclosed by Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart, the investment advisor &quot;which is known for dominating the Ethereum ETF&quot; made an investment of over $1.3 billion in the second quarter. This is equivalent to 539,000 Ether, representing a 68% increase compared to the previous quarter. A similar situation was observed with the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF. &quot;Now, advisors are the largest holders,&quot; holding 161,000 Bitcoin with a value of over $17 billion.In response to this, Vincent Liu, the Chief Investment Officer of Kronos Research, stated that this data indicates a shift in fund flows from being speculative to being long-term and portfolio-driven allocations. &quot;As the largest holders, their strategic positioning has provided deeper liquidity and a more stable foundation for the integration of cryptocurrency into the global markets.&quot; Furthermore, as more advisors adopt Bitcoin and Ether ETFs, cryptocurrency will be recommended and recognized as a long-term diver</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26618</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun: Bought around $10.65 million worth of PUMP tokens in the past week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26617</link>
      <description>Update: On August 28th, pump.fun declared in a post that they had acquired approximately $10.65 million worth of PUMP tokens in the past week. This amount is equivalent to 99.32% of their total earnings during the period from August 20th to August 26th.As of the present moment, pump.fun has made a total purchase of more than $58.13 million worth of PUMP tokens, which accounts for 4.261% of the circulating supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26617</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>glassnode: Bitcoin&apos;s recent support is located in the $107k range, and if broken, it will test the $93k to $95k range.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26616</link>
      <description>August 28th: Glassnode presented a report indicating that the crucial support range for Bitcoin is between $107,000 and $108,900. In case this range is broken through, there is additional downside potential within the range of $93,000 to $95,000, where a cluster of on-chain support levels is located. Due to the selling pressure from short-term holders, $113,600 may serve as a resistance level for any rebound.Presently, the spot market demand for Bitcoin is neutral, while the perpetual futures market sentiment is bearish yet fragile. The funding rate remains at approximately 0.01%, suggesting that market sentiment remains uncertain. When compared to previous cycles, the current correction is not substantial, but confidence is declining, and the market is likely to reach a balance between a rebound and further downside.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Senator Proposes On-chain National Budget to Enhance Fiscal Transparency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26615</link>
      <description>August 28th, Philippine Senator Bam Aquino proposed at the Manila Tech Summit that national budget transactions should be documented on the blockchain in order for citizens to monitor every fund flow. He stated, &quot;No one would be inclined to place transactions on a chain that can be traced by everyone, but we are willing to give it a try.&quot;There has not been a formal bill submitted yet. Once implemented, the plan will rely on the blockchain platform already launched by the Philippine Department of Budget and Management (DBM), which has become the first in Asia to place certain financial documents on the chain.The platform is supported by the local blockchain infrastructure company BayaniChain. Its CEO Paul Soliman pointed out that although blockchain is not a &quot;panacea&quot; against corruption, it can enhance accountability through an unalterable record. The existing DBM system utilizes the Polygon PoS network as a transparency and consensus layer, where budget-related documents such as Sp</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26615</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Expects USD Stablecoin Supply to Reach $10 Trillion by 2028, Triggering DeFi Bull Run</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26614</link>
      <description>August 28th. Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of BitMEX, recently released an article stating that by 2028, the total supply of USD-pegged stablecoins in circulation is projected to reach at least $10 trillion. This figure is significant considering the enormous and exponentially increasing deficit that the United States has to bear. The more Bezos finances the government with Treasury bills, the quicker the debt accumulates as he needs to roll over the debt annually.Consequently, this represents a once-in-a-century transformation of the global monetary architecture. &quot;Perhaps, we will never encounter such an event again in our investment careers. You will never witness such a bull market in the foundational pillars of DeFi as these foundational pillars are reaping great benefits from the surge of USD-pegged stablecoins.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26614</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana&apos;s &quot;150ms Block Finality Confirmation Achieved Major Consensus Upgrade&quot; proposal has entered the voting stage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26613</link>
      <description>August 28th. Based on the relevant governance page, the Solana &quot;Achieve 150ms Block Finality Confirmation Major Consensus Upgrade&quot; proposal (SIMD-326) has entered the voting stage.The voting rule stipulates that the approval vote ratio needs to reach 2/3 of the total votes (approval + rejection) in order to pass. Currently, the voting participation rate is approximately 9.87%, with approximately 9.758% being approval votes.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26613</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the United States Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $307 million, while the Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $81.4 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26612</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as monitored by Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF was $307 million yesterday, indicating that it has witnessed net inflows for five consecutive days. Specifically, the BlackRock ETHA received a net inflow of $2.626 billion.Regarding the US Bitcoin spot ETF, it had a net inflow of $81.4 million yesterday, with IBIT seeing a net inflow of $50.9 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26612</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistics: Over the past 30 hours, a total of 78,891 ETH has been received by 4 new addresses, possibly for Bitmine</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26611</link>
      <description>August 28th. In the past 30 hours, 4 new wallets (which may be related to Bitmine) have transferred 78,891 ETH to FalconX.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26611</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale qianbaidu.eth has deposited $5.72 million into Hyperliquid and has purchased $3.94 million worth of HYPE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26610</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the whale &quot;qianbaidu.eth&quot; transferred $5.72 million into Hyperliquid and purchased 81,572.11 HYPE with $3.94 million. It still holds $1.787 million USDC and has placed a limit price buy order for HYPE at $48.2.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26610</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOON Foundation Announces First Airdrop Guidelines for the simpfor.fun Mirror Trading Platform on Hyperliquid</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26609</link>
      <description>August 28th: The SOON Foundation declared the initial batch of airdrop regulations for the Hyperliquid mirror trading platform simpfor.fun, anticipating the distribution of 1,500,000 SOON tokens.The airdrop will be centered around users&apos; mirror trading volume on simpfor.fun. There is a base pool of 1,000,000 SOON and an additional pool of 500,000 SOON. The additional pool will offer a 30% to 70% bonus depending on the quantity of Coming SOON NFTs held. Currently, Simpfor.fun has a user base exceeding 250 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26609</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>