<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:46:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Market Cap Surpasses Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21567</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on 8marketcap data, the market capitalization of BNB has reached $109.5 billion, and the 24-hour growth rate is 2.86%. It has now surpassed the coffee giant Starbucks (with a market capitalization of approximately $109.21 billion) and ranks 198th in the global asset market capitalization ranking.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21567</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspecta has revealed the ASP tokenomics, with 7.6% airdropped to users during the TGE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21566</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the blockchain infrastructure platform Aspecta announced the tokenomics of its native token ASP, which has a total supply of 1 billion tokens. 45% of the supply is allocated to the community and ecosystem. During the TGE (Token Generation Event), 7.6% of the tokens will be airdropped to users and community supporters. 6.7% is allocated to the market and the broader blockchain community. 0.7% is allocated to Aspecta BuildKey Launch. 30% is for community and ecosystem growth. 20% is for investors. 15% is for early contributors. 3% is for liquidity, and 17% is for the foundation. Aspecta will open the airdrop check on July 24th at 15:00, and the distribution will start at 18:00 during the TGE.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21566</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX DAO Listing Governance Vote Phase 1 Project List Revealed, Simultaneous Voting Launched, Participate to Share from a 10 Billion HTX Prize Pool</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21565</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to an official announcement from HTX DAO, the HTX DAO Listing Governance Voting Event has officially unveiled the first batch of 8 candidate projects, indicating the full launch of a community-driven listing new era. This voting round has attracted more than 50 high-quality projects competing for listing qualifications. The first batch list is just the beginning, and more projects will be announced in the future.This round&apos;s list is based on comprehensive considerations from various aspects, such as community recommendations, market discussions, user attention, project popularity, and trading performance. The first batch of shortlisted projects for voting includes Mira, MONAD, Succinct, MANYU, COCORO, ETHS, KENDU, and Froggie.This voting event features a total of 10 billion HTX in a super prize pool. All users participating in staking and voting can share generous rewards, and there are mysterious &quot;Easter egg&quot; rewards waiting to be unlocked. The voting perio</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21565</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZORA Hits New All-Time High, Surges Over 110% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21564</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on HTX market data, ZORA surged to be above $0.0476 and reached a new all-time high with a 24-hour increase of 111%, which pushed its market capitalization to $165 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21564</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 1 hour, there has been a total of $151 million in liquidations across the entire network, with the majority coming from long positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21563</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on Coinglass data, within the past 1 hour, the total liquidation across the network reached $151 million. Among them, there was $141 million in long liquidations and $9.735 million in short liquidations.In the past 24 hours, a total of 175,828 people worldwide have been liquidated, and the total liquidation amount is $509 million. The largest single liquidation took place on Binance - ETHUSDT, amounting to $3.9652 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21563</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Inference Platform Gaia Completes $20 Million Seed and Series A Funding, Led by Mantle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21560</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the decentralized AI inference platform Gaia announced the completion of a $20 million seed round and Series A financing. The financing was led by ByteTrade, SIG, Mirana, and Mantle, with the participation of Outlier Ventures, NGC, Taisu Ventures, Consensys Mesh, and others.The new funds will be utilized to expand the decentralized AI infrastructure and officially launch the world&apos;s first AI-native smartphone designed for user-centric intelligence. The Gaia AI Phone is based on Galaxy S25 Edge hardware, with all AI inference processes running locally, eliminating the need for the cloud and avoiding data uploads to prevent privacy leaks.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker of the House: &quot;Disappointed&quot; in Powell, Open to Reforming the Fed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21562</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. House Speaker Johnson said that he is receptive to reforming the Federal Reserve, yet it hinges on the specific details. He voiced &quot;disappointment&quot; towards Federal Reserve Chair Powell. It remains unclear whether the removal of the Federal Reserve Chair is legally compliant. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21562</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LazAI Ecosystem&apos;s AI Agent Launch Platform Lazpad Introduces AI Companion DAT and Opens Whitelist Event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21561</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Web3-native AI infrastructure protocol LazAI will make its debut with the AI Companion Data Anchoring Token (DAT) on its testnet for the very first time. This enables users to connect with a memory-holding and continuously evolving AI entity and obtain rewards through interactions.This event will be launched on the LazAI ecosystem&apos;s AI agent launchpad Lazpad. Users who complete a series of tasks will be eligible for the whitelist. Each whitelisted address will receive a free DAT blind box along with additional rewards and the qualification for a C.ALITH airdrop. Meanwhile, LazAI will also launch a referral invitation event. By inviting friends, users can earn activity points. The top ten referrers will receive additional rare DAT rewards based on their rankings.Lazpad is a user-friendly on-chain AI agent launchpad that supports both open and curated assetization paths. It is powered by the robust LazAI internal incentive ecosystem and is deeply integrated into the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21561</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21559</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and surpassed $11,800. The 24-hour decline was narrowed to 0.32%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21559</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company U Power has entered into a strategic partnership with IoTeX to explore the realm of Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21558</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U Power Limited (with Nasdaq stock code: UCAR; hereinafter referred to as &quot;U Power&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) - a provider concentrating on next-generation smart grid and intelligent transportation systems driven by AI solutions - announced today the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding and a Business Cooperation Agreement with IoTeX.IoTeX is a blockchain pioneer committed to transforming machine-generated data into AI collective intelligence. According to the terms of the strategic cooperation agreement:IoTeX will purchase Real World Assets (RWA) issued by U Power and backed by corporate bonds. This will enhance U Power&apos;s capital structure and support the continuous research and development of its UOTTA? electric vehicle battery swapping technology, facilitating U Power&apos;s expansion in Web 3.0 AI-driven energy and transportation system solutions.The two parties will also actively explore innovative solutions for tokenizing these RWA and integrate advanced AI technology</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>