<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:25:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale is attempting to manipulate the XPL price on Hyperliquid to liquidate short positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26775</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale is making an attempt to manipulate XPL in order to liquidate a short position.During the past three hours, the whale (possibly the same as the previous one) has created 4 wallets and deposited 10 million USDC into Hyperliquid to take a long position in XPL.Earlier reports showed that on August 27th, XPL witnessed a short-term 200% surge on Hyperliquid. At that time, a whale went long and swept the order book within just 1 minute, earning $16 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26775</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalshi has added support for SOL and Solana-native USDC deposits.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26774</link>
      <description>August 29th. According to official channels, the prediction market Kalshi announced that it has added support for SOL and Solana-based USDC native deposits.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26774</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Nominates Fed Board Nominee Judy Shelton Hearing Set for September 4th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26773</link>
      <description>August 29th. The Senate Banking Committee of the Federal Reserve announced that the confirmation hearing for Trump&apos;s nominee for Federal Reserve Governor, Judy Shelton, is slated to take place on September 4th at 10 p.m. Beijing time. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26773</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three wallet addresses deposited a total of 7.49 million USDC to Hyperliquid and went long on XPL with 2x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26771</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, three wallets that are likely to be owned by the same entity deposited 7.49 million USDC into Hyperliquid. These wallets took a long position on XPL with 1x leverage and have an outstanding order to increase their XPL position within the next 21 to 23 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Coin Launch Imminent, Ecosystem Coin B (BUILDon) Surges Above $0.7 to Hit All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26772</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on GMGN data, the market capitalization of the BSC-based Meme coin B (BUILDon) has exceeded 700 million USD and reached a historical high. It is currently priced at 0.71 USD, with a 24-hour increase of 23%. The B token is the first USD1 concept coin. Possibly due to the upcoming launch of the WLFI token, B (BUILDon) has shown significant volatility in the past two days.Previously reported by BlockBeats, on July 12th, BUILDon was officially renamed as BUILDON GALAXY, announcing the upcoming launch of the first USD1 ecosystem Launchpad, which will focus on high-quality projects. It will provide rigorous selection and review processes, multi-chain deployment, flexible launches, and continuous market support to inject new impetus into the USD1 ecosystem.BlockBeats reminds users that the market is volatile and token prices are subject to significant fluctuations, so investment should be made with</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26772</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frax Founder Joins Stable as Chief Technology Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26770</link>
      <description>August 29th. Sam Kazemian, the founder of Frax Finance, announced that he has joined the new blockchain project Stable which is centered around Tether&apos;s USDT as the Chief Technology Officer. Meanwhile, he will continue to serve as the CEO of Frax.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26770</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk&apos;s X Company Faces Antitrust Lawsuit from Eliza Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26769</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per Reuters, the software development firm Eliza Labs has filed a lawsuit against Elon Musk&apos;s X Corp. It is claimed that X Corp obtained key technical information from the company before suspending Eliza&apos;s account and launching a mimicking AI product.Eliza, along with its founder and plaintiff Shaw Walters, stated that X induced them to disclose technical details about the AI agent operating on the social platform and compelled developers to pay a high enterprise license fee to keep operating.The lawsuit alleges that X abused its dominance in the social media realm to suppress competitors, violating antitrust laws. Eliza emphasized that its expulsion from the platform was not an editorial decision but a &quot;carefully planned and deceitful&quot; act that harmed the company&apos;s customer relationships and restricted its growth. The case is currently pending in a San Francisco federal court, and representatives of X and Eliza have not yet responded to requests for comment.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26769</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 17,836 ETH from OKX, approximately $79.77 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26768</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on ChainInfo, a significant amount of cryptocurrency was withdrawn. Specifically, a whale transferred 17,836 ETH (approximately equivalent to $79.77 million) from OKX within the past 4 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX&apos;s former law firm Fenwick &amp; West files motion to dismiss aiding FTX in fraud allegation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26767</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per Cointelegraph, Fenwick &amp; West LLP, the former law firm of FTX, has submitted a motion to dismiss a lawsuit that accuses the firm of playing a crucial role in the multi-billion-dollar downfall of a cryptocurrency exchange.The law firm pointed out that after two years of litigation, the plaintiff still has not been able to prove that Fenwick &amp; West was aware of its client&apos;s fraudulent activities. The lawsuit was filed in 2023 and listed a number of defendants. The investors claimed that they were aware of FTX&apos;s fraudulent behavior.Fenwick &amp; West firmly maintains that it should be excluded from this dispute. The law firm did not respond immediately to a request for comment.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26767</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address received 1.48 billion USD worth of ETH from the Kraken hot wallet, and the owner is currently unknown</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26766</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a fresh wallet address received 329,444 ETH from Kraken&apos;s hot wallet, with an approximate value of 1.48 billion US dollars.As for the owner of this wallet, it has not been confirmed yet and it is possible that it is held by Kraken itself.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>