<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 06:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 06:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador has accumulated an additional 8 BTC in the past 7 days, increasing its total holdings to 6271.18 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24914</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on data from the website of the Salvadoran Ministry of Finance, in the past 7 days, El Salvador has accumulated an extra 8 Bitcoins. As a result, its total Bitcoin holdings have reached 6271.18 BTC, which is worth more than $736 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 06:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24914</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue Increases to around 888,000 ETH, Join Queue Decreases to around 286,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24913</link>
      <description>August 17th. Based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 888,416 ETH. When calculated at the current price, approximately 39.7 billion US dollars&apos; worth of ETH is exiting the PoS network. The withdrawal delay is currently reported to be 15 days and 10 hours.At the same time, the staking demand for new validator activations has decreased. Today, the admission queue has dropped to 286,175 ETH, which is worth around 12.81 billion US dollars. The current queuing time for admission is 4 days and 23 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 06:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24913</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helius is launching a new feature where transactions can earn SOL rewards.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24912</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per official channels, Helius has made an official announcement regarding the launch of a new feature. Under this feature, users will be able to obtain SOL rewards while conducting transactions. The purpose of this mechanism is to assist users in reaping the profits that were previously obtained by arbitrageurs, thereby making transactions more efficient and rewarding.Specifically, when users complete a transaction (such as buying/selling/exchanging), if the transaction triggers an arbitrage opportunity (for instance, a price update on different trading platforms), the user will receive a 50% reward. The entire transaction process will not have an impact on the execution of the transaction itself, and there is no malicious MEV risk. This model is referred to as &quot;productive MEV&quot; because it can facilitate the timely update of prices and enhance market efficiency.This feature is completely optional for participation and will only be activated when users choose to op</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 06:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of a 25 basis points interest rate cut by the Federal Reserve in September has slightly decreased to 92.1%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24911</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, by the time of this writing, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September has somewhat decreased to 92.1%, while the probability of maintaining the interest rate unchanged stands at 7.9%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 06:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24911</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTCS CEO: Frequent Public Disclosure of Crypto Holdings Not Necessarily in Shareholders&apos; Best Interests</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24910</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Charles Allen, the CEO of the Ethereum strategic reserve company BTCS, mentioned that although the cryptocurrency field attaches great importance to real-time transparency, U.S. listed companies adhere to a quarterly disclosure rhythm. For major events, they are required to disclose within 4 days, which is the current stipulation.U.S. listed companies are naturally able to choose to disclose information more frequently as long as they refrain from involving GAAP (Generally Accepted Accounting Principles) metrics that demand auditor review.However, more frequent disclosure is not always beneficial to shareholders. The board has a fiduciary duty to safeguard the interests of shareholders. After all, revealing all one&apos;s cards on the table is not the winning approach in the game.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 05:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24910</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKB Surges Beyond $125, Up Over 20% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24909</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on market data, OKB has exceeded $125 and is now trading at $125.07, with a 24-hour increase of 20.06%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 05:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24909</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X Layer&apos;s on-chain transaction volume in the last 24 hours reached $42.87 million, representing a 253% increase compared to the previous period.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24908</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on geckoterminal data, the on-chain transaction volume of X Layer in the past 24 hours reached $42.87 million, which saw a 253% increase compared to the previous period and there were a total of 26.83 thousand transactions.The meme coin XDOG has a market capitalization of $11.85 million and its 24-hour price increased by 102.6%.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coin prices are highly volatile. Please be cautious about asset protection and avoid the fear of missing out (FOMO).</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24908</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeFi Smart Agent Platform Almanak Completes $8.45M Funding Round, with Participation from Delphi Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24907</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per official channels, the DeFi smart agent platform Almanak announced the conclusion of an $8.45 million financing round. Participating in this round were Delphi Labs, HashKey Capital, BanklessVC, the NEAR Foundation, RockawayX, Matrix Partners, AppWorks, Sparkle VC, Shima Capital, and others.According to the introduction, Almanak intends to create and deploy automated financial strategies by means of financial agents. In contrast to traditional DeFi automation that adheres to static rules, Almanak is establishing a framework to analyze market patterns and manage risks through AI-assisted decision-making.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24907</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Rebounds, Reaches $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24906</link>
      <description>On August 17th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and reached $118,000. It is currently trading at $118,000 with a 24-hour change of 0.22%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24906</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraday Future launches the first C10 Treasury Program on the US Stock Market and introduces the C10 Index</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24905</link>
      <description>August 17th. According to official channels, Faraday Future has put forward and launched the &quot;EAI+Crypto&quot; Dual Flywheel &amp; Dual Bridging Eco Strategy. The company intends to bring the EAI EV asset onto the blockchain, establishing an ecosystem encompassing EAI Mobility + Web3 + Blockchain Technology + Crypto Asset Applications.In addition, Faraday Future has officially initiated the C10 Index, which is the first market crypto asset basket index launched by a US-listed company (excluding stablecoins).Faraday Future has also concurrently released the C10 Treasury, a treasury product based on the &quot;C10 Index.&quot; In the first phase, it aims to purchase a total of $5 to $10 billion worth of crypto assets after obtaining the necessary funds. The initial allocation amount is $30 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24905</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>