<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:35:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale increased their ETH holdings with an average price of $3,916, acquiring 2,415 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22113</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the monitoring of EmberCN, a whale address utilized 9.45 million USDC to make a purchase of 2415 ETH on-chain within the past 2 hours. The price at which this transaction took place was $3916 per ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22113</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Over the past decade, Bitcoin has only seen price increases in August for three years, potentially entering a consolidation phase due to seasonal disturbances.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22112</link>
      <description>July 28th: According to Matrixport&apos;s analysis, &quot;A month ago, based on contrarian seasonal analysis, we proposed that Bitcoin was expected to rise to $116,000, and now this prediction has been verified by the market. The current market sentiment is gradually becoming optimistic. This week will witness a series of key events: the intensive disclosure of U.S. stock earnings reports, the delayed release of the White House&apos;s digital asset report, and the Federal Reserve interest rate decision, which may become a new round of catalysts driving market volatility.&quot;However, historical data indicates that August and September have historically been relatively weak months for Bitcoin performance. Over the past decade, the average return rate in August has been nearly zero, with only three years showing gains. Therefore, many traders often choose to lock in profits at this stage. Although we still maintain a bullish outlook for the year, considering seasonal fluctuations, the market may face a t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Dips Below $119,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22111</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $119,000, and its 24-hour growth rate narrowed to 0.63%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22111</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate launches various investment options, with BTC&apos;s annualized return currently at 13.14%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22110</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Gate recently launched the 290th round of the Launchpool event, enabling users to stake BTC and NERO in order to earn 40,000,000 NERO tokens as rewards. This round of the event will officially commence at 20:00 (UTC+8) on July 28th and will continue until 20:00 (UTC+8) on August 11th.According to the official page, the estimated annualized yield for BTC in this round of the event is as high as 13.14%, and VIP users are also eligible to enjoy a bonus of up to 500% on the staking amount. Users can stake early, and the rewards will be automatically distributed on an hourly basis after the mining begins.At the same time, Gate has launched various BTC financial products. The current on-chain BTC staking annualized yield is 3%, and the BTC Flexible Savings Yield is 5.64%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22110</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale increased their holdings by acquiring 5,097.17 ETH at an average price of $3,924.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22109</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as monitored by OnchainLens, a whale address spent 20 million USDT to acquire 5,097.17 ETH at a price of around $3,924 per ETH.Address: 0x6e1784b360f1becb692fcf8393a699811af90733.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22109</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smarter Web Company has secured a ￡19.7 million funding to advance its Bitcoin reserve strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22105</link>
      <description>July 28th. The Smarter Web Company, a publicly listed company in the UK, issued an RNS announcement: Update on Subscription for New Shares — ￡19.7 million Fundraising Secured. Out of the total 14 million ordinary shares to be issued in this round, 6,057,914 shares have been successfully placed.The funds raised from this part of the new share issuance amount to ￡19,680,874 (excluding relevant expenses), which is approximately ￡3.25 per share. The company is anticipated to receive the settlement of around 97% of the funds early this week.BlockBeats previously reported that on July 25th, The Smarter Web Company announced the acquisition of an additional 225 bitcoins, with an average acquisition price of approximately $118,076. Its total holdings have now reached 1825 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22105</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list BANANAS31/TRY, CVX/USDC, and other spot trading pairs, and will also make available related trading bot services.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22108</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Binance will list the trading pairs of BANANAS31/TRY, CVX/USDC, FUN/USDC, and LISTA/USDC on the spot market. These listings will take place on July 29th, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8), offering users more options for spot trading.In addition, Binance will launch trading bot services for the following pairs at 16:00 (UTC+8) on July 29th, 2025: Spot Algorithm Orders for BANANAS31/TRY, CVX/USDC, FUN/USDC, and LISTA/USDC spot grids; and Spot DCA (Dollar-Cost Averaging) for BCH/USDC and SPK/USDC.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22108</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX DeepThink: Trade Truce Boosts Crypto Market Confidence, Fed Decision Remains Short-Term Key Variable</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22107</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the HTX researcher Chloe pointed out in a post that there have been indications of a relaxation in the global trade situation recently. The US and Europe reached an accord on their tariff dispute. High-level officials from China and the US are continuously advancing negotiations. And regional talks such as the Japan-US and US-Canada-Mexico talks are also picking up speed, providing support for the stability of the global supply chain and a resurgence in market risk appetite. This trend may boost medium- to long-term investor confidence and lay the foundation for a phase of recovery for risk assets such as BTC.In the short term, the market&apos;s attention has shifted to the July 25th (Thursday) Federal Reserve interest rate decision. Although the market generally anticipates that the interest rate will remain unchanged, Powell&apos;s remarks during the press conference will be crucial. Currently, the US core inflation is gradually easing, the pressure of fiscal deficits persists,</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22107</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShellAgent 2.0 Launched 5 Days Ago, Trial Applications Exceed 500,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22106</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the AI-powered platform MyShell announced the launch of its latest framework product, ShellAgent 2.0. This is the first AI application generation framework that can be interacted with solely through natural language. Within just 5 days of its launch, the number of trial applications exceeded 500,000. Real-world testing results have outperformed similar products like Lovable and Bolt.new. The relevant content has received over 60 million views across the entire web, and tens of thousands of people participated in the live product launch event. This update has brought MyShell nearly a 10-fold increase in new users, with each new user on average creating 5 AI applications.Before this, MyShell officially released ShellAgent 2.0, liberating creators from the tedious process of code development and deployment. Whether a beginner or a professional developer, anyone only needs to express their ideas or requirements to instantly generate an AI application and share their applica</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22106</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The H100 Group has raised approximately $114 million in total for its Bitcoin reserve strategy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22104</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to an official announcement from the Swedish listed company H100 Group, H100 Group AB has successfully completed a private placement, raising approximately 109.19 million Swedish Krona (SEK). The issue price is 7.82 Swedish Krona per share, based on the closing price of last Friday.Since implementing a Bitcoin asset reserve strategy, H100 Group has raised a total of 1.095 billion Swedish Krona (approximately $114 million) in funding.It was previously reported by BlockBeats that on July 23rd, the Swedish listed company announced an additional purchase of 117.93 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 628.22 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>