<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:34:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Fireverse is launching an OG NFT Limited-Time Claim Event, and the TGE countdown is also starting simultaneously.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22651</link>
      <description>July 31st - The decentralized AI music platform Fireverse, after teasing about the upcoming TGE (Token Generation Event), officially launched its original NFT (Non-Fungible Token) today. This OG NFT is a commemorative badge dedicated to early builders and long-term supporters, with a total supply of 10,000 and is non-transferable. The OG NFT not only symbolizes the important identity of the participants but will also unlock exclusive benefits in the future ecosystem of the platform.This round of OG NFT will be distributed to active users of the Fireverse platform, VBOX holders, FireTrack NFT creators, Nobody NFT holders, Discord contributors. It will also be distributed through whitelist distribution by partners and KOLs (Key Opinion Leaders). Each eligible wallet address can receive up to 1 piece, and the claiming window is from July 30th to August 5th. Unclaimed allocations after the deadline will be available for public claim on a first-come, first-served basis.As Fireverse prep</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22651</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The total strategic Ethereum reserves held by 64 entities has surpassed $10 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22650</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to data from strategicethreserve, the total strategic Ethereum (ETH) reserve held by 64 entities has exceeded $10 billion and reached $10.57 billion. Among them:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) is in the first place, currently holding 625,000 ETH, with a value of approximately $24.1 billion;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) is in the second place, currently holding 438,200 ETH, with a value of approximately $16.9 billion;The Ethereum Foundation is in the third place, holding 234,600 ETH, with a value of approximately $9.042 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22650</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Bitget Derivatives Market Share Rises to 7.2%, Ranking Third Among Global CEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22649</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bitcoin.com issued a Cryptocurrency Derivatives Market Analysis Report titled &quot;Crypto Derivatives 101&quot;. This report systematically examines key products like futures, perpetual contracts, options, etc., and offers a comprehensive comparison of the advantages of centralized exchanges (CEX) and decentralized exchanges (DEX) in terms of liquidity, slippage, fees, risk management, and asset custody. The report indicates that Binance, Bitget, and OKX are rated as the platforms with the most institutional trading advantages, while GMX and Hyperliquid provide higher transparency and self-custody capabilities for DeFi native users.The report&apos;s data reveals that Bitget has surged and is expected to become the world&apos;s third-largest derivatives exchange by 2025. Its market share has increased from 4.6% at the beginning of the year to 7.2%. In April alone, Bitget&apos;s futures trading volume reached $920 billion, demonstrating leading liquidity and market depth in multiple core trading</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22649</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Powell Refuses to Cut Interest Rates Again, Unsuitable for Fed Chair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22648</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Trump stated, &quot;Powell did not cut interest rates again. His move is belated. In fact, he is too angry, too foolish, and too politicized to hold the position of Fed chairman.&quot; (Kyodo News)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) website has launched a Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Register, but there are currently no issuers listed.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22647</link>
      <description>July 31st. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) has refreshed its website, indicating that with the enforcement of the Stablecoin Issuer Oversight Framework under the Stablecoin Law on August 1, 2025, the issuance of fiat-backed stablecoins has transformed into a licensed and regulated undertaking. The regulatory particulars of the oversight framework encompass: the Stablecoin Issuer Licensing Regime, supervision of Licensed Stablecoin Issuers, and the Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Register.The Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Register holds the names and fundamental information of Licensed Stablecoin Issuers. The public is capable of accessing the most recent list of licensed entities via the register. Presently, there are no Licensed Stablecoin Issuers, and the list will be updated in due course.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22647</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui Ecosystem MPC Network Token IKA Market Cap Surpasses $400 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate 35.15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22646</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on GMGN data, the token Ika (IKA) of the Secure Multiparty Computation (MPC) network in the Sui ecosystem has exceeded a market capitalization of $400 million. It has a 24-hour price increase of 35.15%, with a current price of $0.0402 and a 24-hour trading volume of $6.7 million.BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of related tokens are highly volatile and that investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22646</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House Reiterates Support for Trump&apos;s Nomination of Brian Quintenz as CFTC Chairman</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22645</link>
      <description>July 31st: According to Bloomberg, the White House has once again expressed its support for Trump&apos;s nominee, Brian Quintenz, to serve as the chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). Previously, the confirmation of Brian Quintenz as CFTC chairman was postponed. On Monday, the Senate Agriculture Committee abruptly called off the vote on Quintenz&apos;s nomination. However, the White House made it clear on Wednesday that Quintenz still remains the top candidate for the position and they anticipate his prompt confirmation.Quintenz, a former CFTC commissioner, is currently serving as the policy head of the renowned venture capital firm a16z&apos;s crypto department. Last week, his name was also unexpectedly removed from the voting list during another meeting of the same committee. Although the official reasons for his removal were not disclosed, it is widely speculated in the public that there may be problems with his nomination.Yesterday, crypto journalist Eleanor Terret</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22645</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Tech Stocks See Significant Pre-market Gains, NVIDIA Hits New All-time High Market Cap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22644</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to the market data from RockFlow, after the solid financial reports of Microsoft and Meta, the major U.S. tech stocks witnessed significant pre-market gains. The pre-market gain of Nvidia reached 2.48% and is currently up by 1.68%, setting a new all-time high in market value. For other tech stocks: Microsoft (MSFT) increased by 8.3%; Meta Platforms (META) rose by 12%; Apple (AAPL) went up by 0.24%; Amazon (AMZN) advanced by 3.39%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22644</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank&apos;s DWS Teams Up with Galaxy to Launch Germany&apos;s First Regulated Euro-Backed Stablecoin - EURAU</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22643</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to Bloomberg, Deutsche Bank&apos;s DWS, in partnership with Galaxy, has launched Germany&apos;s first regulated Euro stablecoin, EURAU. Deutsche Bank&apos;s asset management subsidiary DWS, Flow Traders, and Galaxy&apos;s joint venture AllUnity obtained an Electronic Money Institution (EMI) license from the German Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin) at the beginning of the month and announced the issuance of Germany&apos;s first regulated Euro stablecoin, EURAU. EURAU will fully adhere to the European Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) framework, be 100% backed, and provide institutional-grade transparency through reserve proof and regulatory reports. This stablecoin can be used for 24/7 instantaneous cross-border settlements, enabling seamless integration for regulated financial institutions, fintech companies, and corporate clients in Europe and other regions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22643</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Layer Token Ecosystem Experiences Price Surge, CLANKER Up by 31.96% in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22642</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on GMGN market data, the Base ecosystem tokens generally witnessed a rise. These include:CLANKER saw a 31.96% increase within the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $58 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $5.3 million.BNKR saw a 40.99% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $84 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $15.65 million.DRB saw a 35.91% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $22.48 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $2.24 million.noice saw a 5.13% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $29.5 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $2.06 million.KTA saw a 4.9% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $1.2 billion, and the 24-hour trading volume is $17.5 million.MAMO saw a 12.13% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $120 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $1.27 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22642</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>