<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:46:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The trading volume of $PENGU on #Upbit is skyrocketing, exceeding $DOGE&apos;s trading volume on #Upbit.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22021</link>
      <description>The trading volume of $PENGU on #Upbit is skyrocketing, exceeding $DOGE&apos;s trading volume on #Upbit.Yet $PENGU&apos;s market cap is still less than 1/13 of $DOGE’s. Koreans keep accumulating $PENGU.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22021</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: The unilateral promotion of a stablecoin by individual countries will exacerbate systemic risk due to hazards such as U.S. Treasury bond and U.S. Dollar volatility spillover.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22020</link>
      <description>On July 27th, President Chen Yulu of Nankai University stated in the opening speech of the &quot;2025 International Financial Forum&quot; that artificial intelligence and the digital economy are reshaping the global economic development process, and digital currency has become a core variable in the reconstruction of the international monetary system.He emphasized that the one-sided promotion of stablecoins by individual countries will exacerbate systemic risks due to five major hidden dangers: &quot;departing from a multipolar framework, amplifying traditional financial risks, the spillover of fluctuations in U.S. Treasury bonds and the U.S. dollar, the increased risk of traditional currency misalignment through new transmission channels, and a regulatory vacuum.&quot; Chen Yulu called for adhering to the three major principles of &quot;intrinsic value, systemic stability, and inclusive outreach,&quot; promoting the coordinated development of central bank digital currencies and compliant stablecoins, jointly bui</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22020</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistic: This week, the Bitcoin Treasury Strategy Entity collectively added 29,500 BTC to its holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22019</link>
      <description>Update, July 27th. Based on @btcNLNico&apos;s data, Bitcoin Treasury Reserve Strategy Entities have collectively purchased 29,500 BTC this week. The entities have released a total of 62 announcements, which include:8 new entities have announced that they have acquired 20,368 BTC for their treasury reserve strategies.24 companies have added 9,183 BTC to their reserves.10 companies have disclosed their future Bitcoin treasury strategies and plan to allocate $132 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22019</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitdeer: Recent Market Saw Impersonation of Company Employees for Scams, Reminding the Community to Stay Vigilant</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22018</link>
      <description>On July 27th, the Nasdaq-listed company Bitdeer announced on the X platform that they had recently discovered that someone was impersonating Bitdeer employees through various channels (including email and Telegram and other social media platforms) to carry out scams. They advised everyone to be vigilant, carefully verify the source of information, beware of all kinds of fraud, and avoid unnecessary losses to protect their rights and interests.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22018</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought $1.58M worth of GP at an average price of $6.57.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22017</link>
      <description>On July 27th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale utilized USDC and SOL to purchase $1.58 million worth of GP at an average price of $6.57.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22017</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checks founder&apos;s brand Visualize Value launches token on Zora platform, market cap surpasses $10 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22016</link>
      <description>On July 27th, according to GMGN market data, Visualize Value launched a token of the same name on the Zora platform 2 hours ago. Its market value exceeded 10 million US dollars and is currently at 10.14 million US dollars, with a trading volume of 5.7 million US dollars.It is reported that Visualize Value is affiliated with Jack Butcher, the founder of the NFT project Checks. The latter posted on Platform X and said, &quot;I didn&apos;t plan to activate the Zora coin. However, apparently, it will be activated automatically when you log in to the iOS app, which is a bit unbelievable.&quot;BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of related projects are highly volatile, and users should invest with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: In the past 7 days, Ethereum&apos;s on-chain NFT trading volume has reached nearly $160 million, with CryptoPunks, Fat Penguins, and Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) ranking in the top three.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22015</link>
      <description>On July 27th, according to CryptoSlam data, the NFT sales volume on the Ethereum blockchain has reached nearly $160 million in the past 7 days, currently totaling $157,608,881. This includes:- CryptoPunks sales reached $35,143,654 with 172 transactions.- Pudgy Penguins sales reached $8,363,264 with 148 transactions.- BAYC sales reached $5,862,545 with 128 transactions.- MAYC sales reached $4,874,728 with 128 transactions.- Moonbirds sales reached $4,727,400 with 683 transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22015</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallup Survey: 14% of U.S. Adults Own Cryptocurrency, 60% of Surveyed Individuals Unlikely to Purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22014</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on a new survey carried out by Gallup from June 2nd to 15th, approximately 14% of American adults state that they own cryptocurrency. However, the majority claim that they have no interest in purchasing it. Despite a slight rise in digital asset ownership since 2021, the majority of Americans still view digital assets as a speculative investment.The survey indicates that the phenomenon of men under 50 owning cryptocurrency is more prevalent. 25% of men declare that they own Bitcoin or other digital currencies.Furthermore, college graduates (19%), high-income adults (19%), and political conservatives (18%) have a higher rate of cryptocurrency ownership. In contrast, only 7% of adults aged 65 and above state that they own some form of cryptocurrency.17% of Americans mention that they are interested in cryptocurrency but do not plan to invest in the near future. Only 4% say that they may purchase cryptocurrency soon. 60% of people state that they have no intentio</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22014</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director of the U.S. Office of Management and Budget: Trump Clearly States No Intention to Fire Powell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22013</link>
      <description>On July 27th, the Director of the US Office of Management and Budget, Vought, stated that Trump has clearly demonstrated no intention of dismissing Powell. (FX678 News)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22013</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Secretary of Commerce: August 1 Tariff Increase Deadline Will Not Be Further Extended</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22012</link>
      <description>On July 27th, U.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick announced that the deadline for the tariff increase set for August 1st will not be extended any further. Europe expresses a need and a willingness to reach a trade agreement with the United States. The key question now is whether the agreement proposed by the EU is sufficient to persuade Trump to abandon the 30% tariff threat.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22012</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>