<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 03:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 03:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ark Invest increased its holdings of Block stock yesterday, bringing the total value to $19.2 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24142</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as reported by The Block, Cathie Wood-led Ark Invest has made changes to its holdings in crypto-related stocks. It has once again purchased a total of $19.2 million worth of Block company stock through its three exchange-traded funds (ETFs). According to Rockflow data, this transaction took place when Block&apos;s stock price dropped by 0.49% on Monday and closed at $73.03, which was the lowest closing price since July 18th.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24142</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI CEO Taunts Elon Musk: Hopes to Launch Counter Investigation into Musk&apos;s Influence on X</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24141</link>
      <description>August 12th: In response to Musk&apos;s threat of taking legal action against Apple, Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI, retweeted Musk&apos;s post on X and said: &quot;I have heard someone alleging that Musk is manipulating X to seek personal and corporate gains and harming his competitors and those he dislikes. This allegation is astonishing. I hope someone will conduct a counter-investigation into this. Many of us are eager to know what actually happened. Nevertheless, OpenAI will concentrate on creating excellent products.&quot;Altman also retweeted a 2023 media article which stated that Musk had pressured the Twitter team to significantly enhance the weighting of his tweets. (Financial Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24141</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Reclaims $4300 as It Prepares for a New All-Time High Push, Needs About 13% More Gains</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24140</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum has reverted to $4300. It is currently trading at $4308, showing a 0.03% increase in the past 24 hours. It still needs to rise by approximately 13% to break its all-time high of $4868.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24140</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum breaks above $4400, the mainstream CEX total short liquidation volume will reach $1.495 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24139</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Coinglass data, if Ethereum manages to break through $4400, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will amount to $1.495 billion.Conversely, if Ethereum drops below $4200, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $335 million.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not provide the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to neighboring liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the target price will be influenced when it reaches a particular level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that when the price reaches that level, there will be a more intense reaction due to a surge in liquidity.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24139</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the net inflow of the US Ethereum Spot ETF surpassed $1 billion, setting a new historical record</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24138</link>
      <description>On August 12th, yesterday the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF reached 10.1962 billion US dollars. This is the highest inflow amount since its establishment, and it is the first time that the inflow has exceeded 1 billion US dollars. The specific inflow of each ETF is as follows:· ETHA (BlackRock): 640.68 million US dollars;· FETH (Fidelity): 276.9 million US dollars;· ETHW (Bitwise): 4.3 million US dollars;· CETH (21Shares): 3.86 million US dollars;· QETH (Invesco): 0 US dollars;· EZET (Franklin): 4.88 million US dollars;· ETHV (Van Eck): 9.42 million US dollars;· ETHE (Grayscale): 13.01 million US dollars;· ETH (Grayscale mini): 66.57 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24138</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATNF Surges Nearly 55% in After-Hours Trading, Leading Ethereum Reserve Stock Concept</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24137</link>
      <description>August 12th: During after-hours trading, the US stock ATNF witnessed a significant surge of nearly 55%, with its market value reaching $201.7 million, thereby leading the Ethereum Reserve concept stocks.· After hours, SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) increased by 3.43%.· After hours, Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) rose by 1.73%.· After hours, GameSquare (GAME.US) went up by 0.51%.· After hours, Bit Digital (BTBT.US) advanced by 2.39%.Before this, according to the latest filings from the US SEC, Peter Thiel and his investment team acquired a 7.5% stake in the Ethereum Treasury Reserve company ETHZilla (formerly 180 Life Sciences Corp., with the ticker ATNF).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24137</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eugene: As the market approaches its peak, the trading frenzy will become even more intense, but the opportunity for wealth accumulation is also slipping away</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24136</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio shared on his personal channel, saying, &quot;After Trump took office, the crypto market witnessed a continuous and strong uptrend for a full two months. Subsequently, the TRUMP token was launched, and it became the biggest driver of the mass wealth growth at that time.&quot;This also coincides with a fact: as the market is gradually approaching its peak, the trend becomes more and more frenzied, and the opportunities for quick gains increase exponentially. I believe we are now getting close to that stage. Please pay attention to the next target of the uptrend. At the same time, remember that time is passing by.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Thiel Double Downs on Ethereum, Acquires 7.5% Stake in ETHZilla</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24135</link>
      <description>On August 12th, billionaire Peter Thiel once more expounded on his stance regarding Ethereum. According to the latest filing with the SEC, Peter Thiel and his investment team acquired a 7.5% stake in the Ethereum treasury reserve company ETHZilla (formerly 180 Life Sciences Corp.).180 Life Sciences (stock code: ATNF) witnessed its stock price increase by over 11% at the close on Monday, with a surge of approximately 57% in after-hours trading. The company announced its Ethereum treasury plan at the end of July. This Monday, the biotech company stated that it had sold $156 million of 2028 senior secured convertible notes to an institutional investor and had previously completed a $425 million private placement. The raised funds will mainly be used to purchase Ethereum, income-generating assets, and the company&apos;s online gaming (iGaming) business, while monetizing its existing biotech intellectual property.BlockBeats had previously reported that on July 16th, in an SEC filing submitte</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24135</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Meeting Putin, I knew the outcome within two minutes because I&apos;m a dealmaker</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24134</link>
      <description>On August 12th, President Trump of the United States stated at a White House press conference on the 11th that his upcoming meeting with Russian President Putin on the 15th in Alaska will be an &quot;exploratory meeting.&quot; He added that the outcome could be &quot;either good or bad,&quot; but he believed that both sides would engage in &quot;constructive dialogue.&quot;Trump claimed that he would be able to determine the outcome of the meeting within two minutes as he is a &quot;dealmaker.&quot; He further stated that after the Alaska meeting between the US and Russian leaders, he hoped to &quot;eventually&quot; arrange a meeting between Ukrainian President Zelensky and Putin. If necessary, a trilateral meeting among the US, Russia, and Ukraine could be held. Additionally, Trump said that after Russia and Ukraine reach an agreement, the US-Russia trade volume might increase. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24134</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEX Ethereum Balance Hits Lowest Level Since July 2016, Down 6.7% in Q3 2021 So Far</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24133</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Michael Nadeau, the founder of The DeFi Report, shared in a post that the supply shock of ETH is unfolding in real time. So far in the third quarter, the amount of ETH on CEXs has decreased by 6.7%. It has now dropped to the lowest level since July 2016.With ETH treasury-like companies starting to implement on-chain strategies to increase yield and per-ETH holdings, this number is anticipated to keep declining.More capital flowing on-chain may trigger a stronger &quot;reflexivity&quot; effect, in which market activity and fundamentals will further improve along with the price trend.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24133</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>