<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Solana On-Chain 24-hour Market Update: New Coin POKEDEX Trading Volume Surges; PLAY, MarsMi Lead the Way in the &apos;Next Blue Chips&apos; Sector</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22443</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to GMGN data, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume within the past 24 hours are POKEDEX, PUMP, Fartoin, Ani, and USELESS. Among them, the POKEDEX token has been listed for less than 24 hours, with a relatively low market value and a high level of risk. Therefore, investors should pay close attention to the security of their funds.According to GMGN&apos;s &quot;Next Blue Chip&quot; section recommendation, the top five tokens in terms of market capitalization within the past 24 hours are PLAY, PUMP, MarsMi, COAI, and PHY. Tokens in the blue chip sector are often listed for less than 24 hours, with concentrated chips and a relatively low market value, presenting high risks. Hence, investors should pay attention to the security of their funds.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins often lack practical use cases and have large price fluctuations. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22443</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Modular Infrastructure Project Super ModuleX Protocol (MX) Announces Key Technical Breakthrough</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22442</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Bitcoin modular infrastructure project Super ModuleX Protocol (MX) announced a significant technical breakthrough in achieving full protocol asset modular abstraction and cross-chain composability on the Bitcoin mainnet. ModuleX offers a general module framework for the Bitcoin network, facilitating the unified packaging and interaction of existing and future protocol assets, such as Taproot and Ordinals, and it can be extended in the future to Ark, BitVM, and other Layer 2 or scaling solutions.Its core architecture is based on the abstraction of the UTXO layer verification mechanism and combined with the design of Modular Script Components. This decouples the composition and validation of protocol assets from low-level script implementation and transitions to standardized module invocations, composable interfaces, and verifiable states. In this way, developers can build cross-protocol applications and asset compositions based on ModuleX without directly manipulatin</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22442</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: ETH May Break $5000 in the Next Month</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22441</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per Decrypt&apos;s report, although Bitcoin is experiencing a pullback, the price of Ethereum remains strong. Analysts point out that the favorable market conditions this week may accelerate its upward trend and push it to $5000. Several bullish fundamentals are at work, including the potential approval of a US Ether ETF with open staking, significant inflows into existing ETFs, and an increasing number of digital asset treasuries buying Ethereum.Although the overall market sentiment is optimistic, Republic Technologies CEO Daniel Liu stated that it is still uncertain which pullback will truly break the $4000 mark. He noted that the &quot;leveraged buying demand near $3500&quot; and the &quot;significant selling pressure near $4000&quot; may lead Ethereum to remain range-bound in the short term.However, Daniel Liu mentioned that despite the short-term uncertainty, the market is poised for a &quot;short squeeze.&quot; A series of &quot;favorable macroeconomic news&quot; could disrupt the balance, triggering in</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22441</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Earn, One-Click Buy, Swap, Leverage, Futures Trading of Arena-Z (A2Z)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22440</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to official channels, Binance&apos;s Savings, One-Click Buy, Instant Exchange, Leverage, and Futures are going to launch Arena-Z (A2Z).Specifically, Binance will commence the A2Z 1-75x USDT-margined perpetual contract on July 30, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Once again reducing a significant portion of long positions, the current alt season&apos;s wealth effect may be the weakest in history</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22439</link>
      <description>On July 30th, trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio posted on his personal channel, saying, &quot;I have once more cut down the majority of my long positions and am still maintaining a defensive stance. Historically, August usually presents challenges, and I don&apos;t think this year will be smooth sailing.&quot;Interestingly, in terms of the wealth effect resulting from the increase in the price of Ethereum, this round of the altcoin season may be the weakest. This once again indicates that institutional funds are the main force driving the buying pressure, and the funds have not flowed back into altcoins (which also reconfirms my previous stance of only holding ETH).&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22439</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users holding at least 200 Alpha tokens are eligible to claim an airdrop of 1000 RHEA tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22438</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per official information, Binance is the first exchange to list Rhea Finance (RHEA), and trading will commence on July 30, 2025, at 21:30 (UTC+8). After the start of trading, users who hold at least 200 Alpha points can claim a 1000 RHEA token airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. Claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22438</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Season Index Drops to 38</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22437</link>
      <description>July 30th: As per Coinmarketcap data, the Altcoin Season Index dropped to 38 on July 30th after reaching 55 on July 21st. This index shows that among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, approximately 38 projects have outperformed Bitcoin in terms of price appreciation over the past 90 days.Note: The CMC Altcoin Season Index is a real-time index formulated to assess whether the cryptocurrency market is currently in an altcoin-dominant season. This index is based on the performance of the top 100 altcoins in relation to Bitcoin over the past 90 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22437</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve will announce its interest rate decision tonight, with only a 2.1% probability of a rate cut in July.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22436</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Federal Reserve will announce its interest rate decision this evening (2 a.m. Beijing Time on July 31st), and Federal Reserve Chair Powell will hold a press conference 30 minutes later.According to the &quot;FedWatch&quot; data from CME, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut in July is 2.1%, while the probability of maintaining the rate unchanged is 97.9%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22436</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: The current sentiment is diverging from the fundamentals, which may signal a cooling-off period in the market in the short term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22435</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Matrixport released today&apos;s market analysis which stated, &quot;The current Greed and Fear Index is approaching a high level, and the slow moving average is also showing signs of a top signal. Looking back at history, whenever this indicator is in an upward phase, the Bitcoin price usually demonstrates strength; however, once it begins to decline, it often indicates a cooling-off of market sentiment, and investors need to be more cautious.&quot;&quot;In early July, we made a bullish judgment that went against the mainstream view. But as the market developed, we have also shifted to a more cautious stance, expecting Bitcoin to enter a consolidation phase in August. The latest trend of the Greed and Fear Index also validates this assessment: despite the continuous positive news, market momentum has weakened.&quot;&quot;The current divergence between sentiment and fundamentals may suggest that the market could enter a cooling-off phase in the short term. It is recommended that investors closely</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22435</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avantis, a derivatives trading platform in the Base Protocol ecosystem, has established a foundation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22434</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Base Protocol derivative trading platform Avantis announced the establishment of a foundation. Its main mission is to guarantee protocol development and security, community governance and transparency, as well as ecosystem growth and innovation.Before this announcement, Avantis completed an $8 million Series A funding round. Peter Thiel&apos;s Founders Fund and Pantera Capital took the lead in this round, with participants including Symbolic Capital, SALT Fund, and Flowdesk.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>