<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:57:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Four.Meme has announced the first CTO investment portfolio, with emmm, Donkey, TUT, and U making the cut.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27511</link>
      <description>September 3rd. As per official channels, Four.Meme has officially declared its first-phase CTO project portfolio today. The ultimately selected projects comprise $emmm, $Donkey, $TUT, and $U. Here, emmm took the first place overall, Donkey ranked second, and TUT tied with U for the third position.Four.Meme stated that they have set up a professional dashboard and monitoring procedure to conduct a comprehensive assessment of projects from seven aspects such as liquidity, community activity, and innovation capability. This ensures that their investment portfolio is both solid and growth-oriented.Regarding the investment strategy, Four.Meme will gradually build positions in five rounds. This initial round of purchases mainly focuses on projects related to the BNB Chain ecosystem, aiming to further promote value discovery and market activity in the meme coin sector within the ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Announcement: Linea Airdrop Lookup Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27510</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on community feedback, Linea has now initiated the airdrop lookup.BlockBeats Note: Currently, there has been no official announcement. However, community reports indicate that the domain of the relevant link is correct. For security purposes, users are advised to wait until the official announcement before conducting the check.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSL HK has officially launched BNB, becoming the first Hong Kong-based trading platform to support BNB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27509</link>
      <description>September 3rd, as per official information, OSL HK has made an announcement. It has now initiated BNB trading services for professional investors, thereby becoming the first exchange platform in Hong Kong to offer BNB trading. It has officially launched three trading pairs: BNB/USD, BNB/USDT, and BNB/USDC.BNB, which ranks among the top digital assets in terms of market capitalization, is the native token of the BNB Chain. This chain is renowned for its rich applications and its capabilities of low-cost and high-speed transactions. The opening of BNB trading this time is intended to meet the increasing demand of institutional investors for high-quality digital assets. It also reflects the company&apos;s long-term strategic plan in diversified asset allocation. By integrating more mainstream digital assets, OSL HK is presenting investors and potential partners with a more diverse range of assets.Eddie Yue, the Chief Business Development Officer of the OSL Group, stated: &quot;We are delighted</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump withdrew 50.68 million WLFI tokens from CEX 4 hours ago, worth $11.58 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27508</link>
      <description>September 3rd. Based on The Data Nerd&apos;s monitoring, 4 hours ago, Jump took out 50.68 million WLFI from Bybit and Binance (about $11.58 million). Additionally, 16 hours ago, Whale 0x8C4 withdrew $40.87 million from Bybit (about $10 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Average Balance per Whale Address has been continuously decreasing since November 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27507</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Glassnode announced on social media that starting from November 2024, the average Bitcoin holdings of whales (entities holding 100 to 1,000 Bitcoins) have been continuously declining. Currently, each whale holds around 488 Bitcoins, which is a level that was last seen in December 2018.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank President: EU Should Address Stablecoin Regulation Gaps</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27506</link>
      <description>On Wednesday, September 3rd, European Central Bank President Lagarde stated that EU lawmakers should demand that foreign stablecoin issuers implement &quot;safeguards&quot; and a &quot;robust equivalent regulatory regime&quot; in order to prevent the risk of reserve run within the EU.During a regulatory meeting, she said: &quot;European legislation should ensure that such schemes cannot operate within the EU unless they have strong support from equivalent regimes in other jurisdictions and safeguard measures related to asset transfers between EU and non-EU entities.&quot;She also added: &quot;This further emphasizes why international cooperation is essential. Without a fair global regulatory environment, risks will always find the weakest link.&quot; (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address has transferred 7500 ETH to Binance, expecting a profit of $6.7 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27505</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to on-chain data analyst Embermonitor, a whale address transferred 7,500 ETH (approximately $32.33 million) to Binance 20 minutes ago.It is reported that this address had previously withdrawn 15,202 ETH (approximately $58.82 million) from Binance to the on-chain between July 21 and August 12, with an average withdrawal price of $3,869.After withdrawing and accumulating at an average price of $3,869, the assets are now being transferred to a trading platform at a price of $4,310, with an expected profit of $6.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27505</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paradigm Reth Client Vulnerability Causes Temporary Disruption of Multiple Ethereum Nodes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27504</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as per The Block, Georgios Konstantopoulos, the Chief Technology Officer of the cryptocurrency venture capital firm Paradigm, declared that there is a program flaw within Reth, the Ethereum execution client developed by the company. This flaw leads to nodes relying on this client to come to a standstill.According to Paradigm&apos;s announcement on GitHub, the vulnerability was activated at block height 2327426 and affected Ethereum mainnet versions 1.6.0 and 1.4.8. Although Konstantopoulos has provided a series of instructions to assist operators in recovering Reth nodes, Paradigm is still conducting an investigation into the root cause of the vulnerability.Reth is an Ethereum execution layer client developed by Paradigm using the Rust programming language. It is designed with a focus on high performance and modularity. An execution client is a software application that processes transactions and applies state updates used to calculate the state root. The state root is</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with at least 220 Alpha Points can claim 1000 MCH airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27503</link>
      <description>September 3rd. According to official channels, trading of Moonchain (MCH) on Binance Alpha will open on September 3, 2025, at 7:00 PM (Beijing time). Once trading begins, users with at least 220 Alpha points can get a 1,000 MCH token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the reward pool is not completely distributed, the point threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points every hour. It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points. Users must confirm their claim on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours; otherwise, they will be regarded as having waived their right to the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Official Announcement: Sonic (S) Tokenomics Update Notification</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27502</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Binance made an official announcement. As per the approved proposal by Sonic, the total supply of Sonic (S) will be increased from approximately 3.41 billion to around 3.89 billion, with a circulating supply increase of 472 million (a 14.2% increase).It is only when the ETF final protocol is reached that an additional $50 million worth of Sonic (S) will be added to the total supply.The Binance trading page will synchronize the display of a risk warning pop-up and banner.BlockBeats had previously reported that the Sonic Labs community voted in favor of the &quot;U.S. Market Expansion and TradFi Adoption Plan&quot; proposal, which aims to establish Sonic USA LLC to start U.S. operations. Approval was granted for the issuance of tokens for a $50 million ETF quota, a $100 million Nasdaq PIPE development, and 1.5 billion S tokens for Sonic USA.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>