<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:45:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cao Cao&apos;s stock surged over 20% intra-day following the announcement yesterday that it will explore RWA, stablecoin payments, and compliant digital currency issuance.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23519</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on market data, Cao Cao Mobility witnessed a more than 20% intraday surge and is currently trading at HK$59.25.Yesterday&apos;s news stated that Cao Cao Mobility partnered with Victory Securities to explore RWA, stablecoin payments, and compliant digital currency issuance.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23519</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashFlare Founder Faces 10-Year Prison Sentence in $577 Million Fraud Case, U.S. Authorities Call for Stern Action</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23518</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Sergei Potapenko and Ivan Tur?gin, the founders of the defunct cryptocurrency mining service company HashFlare, admitted to telecommunications fraud. They asked a U.S. court not to impose additional prison time. However, prosecutors recommended a 10-year sentence for each of them. In a sentencing memorandum submitted to the Seattle federal court, the prosecution stated that the two men had orchestrated a Ponzi scheme totaling $577 million, resulting in approximately $300 million in victim losses, making it the largest fraud case ever tried by the court. The defendants cited their time served in detention in Estonia and their cooperation in the case as reasons for a reduced sentence. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23518</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is set to release GPT-5 tomorrow morning at Beijing time.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23517</link>
      <description>August 7th. Today, the official OpenAI account made a post on the social platform X, indicating that a live streaming event will take place at 10 a.m. Pacific Time on Thursday (1 a.m. Friday Beijing Time).According to the analysis by Caixin, the official tweet replaced the letter &quot;S&quot; in the word &quot;LIVESTREAM&quot; with the number &quot;5&quot;, which might suggest that this live stream will present the GPT-5 model.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23517</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong-listed company YeeCorp Financial strategically invested $5 million in Lightnet, further expanding its footprint in the Real World Asset (RWA) ecosystem.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23516</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the Hong Kong-listed company YeeTech announced a strategic investment of $5 million in Lightnet, a fintech company under the Jardine Matheson Group. This investment is aimed at supporting Lightnet&apos;s Web 3 technology and cross-border payment business development. Additionally, YeeTech stated that it will further enhance its Real World Asset (RWA) strategic layout in order to build its own RWA ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23516</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past month, the total Ethereum staked has decreased by 97,572 ETH, representing a slight decrease of 0.1% in the circulation ratio.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23515</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, the data indicates that the amount of Ethereum staked in the past month has decreased by 97,572 ETH. It was 35,530,752 ETH on July 9th and has now reached 35,433,180 ETH. Although there was a significant drop on July 25th, it quickly regained its original level.The corresponding percentage of Ethereum staked in relation to the total circulation has decreased from 29.39% to 29.29%, generally remaining stable.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 05:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, China New City has reached a partnership with HashKey Exchange, and the two parties will collaborate on compliant digital asset management and other fields.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23514</link>
      <description>On August 7, a Hong Kong-listed company, China New City Group Limited, entered into a Memorandum of Understanding with the Hong Kong-licensed virtual asset trading platform HashKey Exchange. The two parties will cooperate in regulatory-compliant digital asset management, technical exploration, and market expansion. China New City Group Limited is a Hong Kong-listed company primarily engaged in commercial real estate development and operation management.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23514</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin Frequently Testing 50-Day Moving Average, Showing Signs of Exhaustion in Its Uptrend</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23513</link>
      <description>July 7th, Regarding the recent market adjustment, certain analysts have cautioned that the summer lull will persist. Alex Kuptsikevich, the Chief Market Analyst at FxPro, stated in a report on Thursday: &quot;The support attained in the previous peak area suggests that the market is pausing momentarily to secure profits. Nevertheless, the market downturn is causing the most active traders to waver as they have now shifted to very minor undertakings.&quot;On the other hand, Bitcoin is once more drawing near to its 50-day moving average. Such repeated testing of the mid-term trend signal line indicates that as the largest cryptocurrency, Bitcoin has entered a state of accumulation fatigue.&quot; (CoinDesk)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23513</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list INFINIT (IN) spot trading and futures trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23512</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per the official announcement, Gate is set to list INFINIT (IN) spot trading at 18:00 (UTC+8) on August 7th. Furthermore, at 18:10, INFINIT (IN) perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT) will commence, with support for 1-20x leverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Interview process for the next Fed Chair has begun, with all 3 candidates from Wall Street</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23511</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Trump declared that the interview procedure for the next Federal Reserve Chair has commenced. The current list of candidates has been narrowed down to three, and it is noted that they all originate from Wall Street. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishing Shield: The top result on Google search for &quot;Aave&quot; is a phishing website</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23510</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as monitored by PeckShield, a phishing advertisement imitating the decentralized lending protocol Aave showed up as the top result in Google search results. It is advised that users refrain from interacting with it. It is recommended that when visiting Web3 sites, users always verify the authenticity of the website to avoid phishing attacks.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>