<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:02:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Willy Woo: Bitcoin Enters Consolidation Phase, Correction and Consolidation May Precede Next Breakout</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22667</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the cryptocurrency analyst Willy Woo tweeted, stating, &quot;July witnesses Bitcoin&apos;s shift from an uptrend to a consolidation stage. The intensified speculation and profit-taking behavior are suppressing the market&apos;s momentum, suggesting that Bitcoin may require a correction or a period of consolidation before attempting the next breakout.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22667</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of initial jobless claims in the United States was roughly flat last week, raising concerns among economists about potential underlying weakness.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22666</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the U.S. Department of Labor announced on Thursday that the number of initial unemployment claims in the United States last week remained stable, which is a source of reassurance. For the week ending July 26th, the number of initial claims for unemployment benefits was 218,000, compared to 217,000 in the previous week. The number of ongoing claims for unemployment benefits was 1.95 million, remaining unchanged from the previous week. Last night, the Fed maintained its interest rate for the fifth consecutive meeting. At a press conference, Fed Chairman Powell stated that the stable labor market suggests no haste to switch to a more accommodative monetary policy stance through rate cuts. However, some economists are concerned that the weakness in the labor market is concealed behind a strong appearance. Despite the still relatively low unemployment rate, many workers report long job search times and difficulties in finding opportunities. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22666</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The key inflation indicator in the United States is rising, while consumer spending is nearly stagnant.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22665</link>
      <description>July 31st: The Federal Reserve&apos;s favored core inflation indicator picked up pace in June and reached one of the swiftest rates this year. Meanwhile, consumer spending witnessed only a minimal growth, highlighting the factors that have led policymakers to differ in their interest rate stances. The data made public on Thursday indicated that the &quot;Core Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) Price Index,&quot; which excludes food and energy prices, rose by 0.3% from May. It also showed a 2.8% year-on-year increase, suggesting that there has been limited advancement in curbing inflation over the past year.The data revealed that inflation-adjusted consumer spending experienced a slight rise in June after a decline in May. These data imply that the economic tug-of-war has caused Fed officials to diverge in their monetary policy directions. On one side, the progress of inflation has essentially come to a standstill, and central bank officials are worried that President Trump&apos;s tariffs may exert</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22665</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Core PCE Inflation Heats Up in June, Adding Another Variable to Fed&apos;s September Rate Cut Prospects</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22664</link>
      <description>July 31st: The U.S. inflation data for June came in slightly above expectations, introducing an additional variable to the Fed&apos;s interest rate cut timeline. The Fed-preferred core PCE price index witnessed a month-on-month increase of 0.3% and a year-on-year increase of 2.8%, which was slightly higher than the market&apos;s forecast of 0.29% and 2.7% respectively. The overall PCE index, which encompasses food and energy, rose by 0.3% month-on-month and 2.6% year-on-year, also exceeding the market expectations of 0.23% and 2.5%.This higher-than-expected inflation report has rendered the Fed&apos;s interest rate cut path more intricate. Policymakers had previously emphasized the necessity of observing more evidence of inflation consistently reverting to the 2% target, and the latest data may postpone this process. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. June Core PCE Price Index YoY 2.8%, Expected 2.7%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22663</link>
      <description>July 31st: The YoY rate of the US June Core PCE Price Index was 2.8%, reaching a new high since February and exceeding the expected 2.7%. The previous value was revised from 2.7% to 2.8%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22663</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During the week ending on July 26, initial jobless claims in the United States were 218,000, compared to an expectation of 224,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22662</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the initial jobless claims in the United States for the week ending July 26 were 218,000. The expected value was 224,000, while the prior value was 217,000. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22662</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Hines: US Government Holds Bitcoin Amount Currently &quot;Cannot be Discussed&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22661</link>
      <description>On July 31st, in the latest podcast episode, Bo Hines, the executive director of the White House Cryptocurrency Committee, refused to disclose the amount of Bitcoin held by the U.S. government. Previous reports indicated that the actual amount of Bitcoin held by the U.S. government might be much lower than the 200,000 estimated by former Trump cryptocurrency advisor David Sacks. In fact, the actual amount is only 29,000. Regarding the specific number, Hines said that it &quot;is currently not possible to be discussed&quot; but confirmed that the government plans to increase its Bitcoin holdings through a &quot;budget-neutral&quot; approach. Due to differences in asset classification, only forfeited Bitcoins that have completed judicial procedures can be counted as government assets, while Bitcoins under seizure still face legal uncertainties.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22661</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empery Digital has increased its holdings by 303 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 3803 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22660</link>
      <description>On July 31, Empery Digital, a US-listed company (formerly known as Volcon), increased its holdings of BTC by 303 coins, raising its total holdings to 3,803 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22660</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor: The Q2 Earnings Call will be the most important event in the history of the company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22659</link>
      <description>On July 31, Michael Saylor, the founder of Strategy, tweeted, &quot;The Strategy&apos;s second-quarter earnings conference call will be the most significant event in the company&apos;s history.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22659</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa Adds Support for Stablecoins PYUSD, USDG, and EURC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22658</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per Cointelegraph, Visa has provided support for the stablecoins PYUSD, USDG, and EURC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22658</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>