<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:51:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin fell below $116,000 this morning before rebounding, now trading at $117,365.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22548</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin dipped below $116,000 this morning and has now rebounded to $117,365, with a 24-hour decrease of 0.31%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22548</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of a Fed rate cut in September is 45.7%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22547</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of the Fed keeping interest rates unchanged in September is 54.3%, while the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 45.7%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22547</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Fed&apos;s Future Rate Cuts Pose a Significant Communication Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22546</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Tom Graff, the Chief Investment Officer of Facet Company, stated that the Federal Reserve is clearly in a rather delicate situation. Logically speaking, they had anticipated that the new tariffs would bring a certain level of inflation. Ideally, the Fed would prefer to wait until inflation reaches its peak before considering a rate cut. Nevertheless, the pressure is constantly building. Even if the White House is not applying external pressure, the recent weakness in the labor market is sufficient to cause concern for the Fed.In fact, this is likely the reason why Bullard and Bowman voted against maintaining the existing interest rate and advocated for a rate cut at this meeting. I believe that this decision has laid the groundwork for the Fed to initiate rate cuts at the September meeting and may implement 1 to 2 more rate cuts this year. The challenge lies in the fact that despite the potential for rising prices, the Fed still needs to cut rates. This will pose extrem</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22546</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Powell&apos;s Statement Leans Toward Hawkish Stance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22545</link>
      <description>On July 31st, analyst Chris Anstey declared that Powell mentioned, &quot;There remains a great deal and a great deal of uncertainty to navigate through. Indeed, we are constantly obtaining more data. However, it seems to be a distance away at present, the conclusion of that process. I believe there will be a lot of developments out there.&quot; This assertion leans towards a hawkish stance.The Federal Reserve Chair Powell also pointed out that it is not feasible to make a decision six weeks from now based on the June forecasts (dot plot). In his personal view, we are in a moderately restrictive range, but there is a range of opinions on this matter. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22545</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economist: Federal Reserve&apos;s Statement Adjustment Surprisingly Reduces Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22544</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Kathy Bostjancic, the Chief Economist at American Life Insurance Company, declared that surprisingly, the Fed removed the previous language regarding the reduction of uncertainty in the economic outlook from the policy statement and instead focused on the fact that uncertainty remains &quot;still elevated.&quot;In our perspective, although uncertainty still exists, it has actually decreased significantly as the trade and tariff situation has become more clarified. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: Economy in a Solid Position, Inflation Rate Slightly Above Target</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22543</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Federal Reserve Chair Powell declared that the economy is in a favorable state, with inflation being slightly higher than the target. The present policy stance has placed us in a beneficial position to respond promptly. The Fed remains committed to its dual mandate. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22543</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: Tariffs Have Boosted Some Prices</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22542</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Federal Reserve Chair Powell stated that the year-on-year June core personal consumption expenditures (PCE) inflation rate might be 2.7%. Although inflation has moderated compared to 2022, it still remains at a relatively high level. The majority of long-term inflation expectations indicators are in line with the Fed&apos;s target.Tariffs have led to an increase in the prices of some goods. Whether inflation is transient or more persistent remains to be seen. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22542</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: The fundamental message is that the tariffs will have a transitory impact on inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22541</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell stated that the reasonable assumption is that the impact of tariffs on inflation is of a temporary nature. The forthcoming data will assist the Fed in determining the future policy direction. Given the inflation risks, the current policy stance is appropriate. The current policy can be characterized as moderately restrictive. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: No Decision Yet on September Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22540</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell indicated that there exist downside risks to the labor market. It is expected that more information will become available in the coming months. No decisions have been reached regarding the September meeting. (Xinhua News)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Cryptocurrency Report Officially Released</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22539</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the White House Cryptocurrency Report was officially made public. From the construction of railways connecting the East and West coasts to the connection of the world through the internet, since its establishment, each generation of American entrepreneurs has led the construction of the next-generation technology. &quot;Crypto 3.0&quot; should be no exception.As the author of this report, the Working Group is of the opinion that digital assets and blockchain technology can not only completely innovate America&apos;s financial system but also innovate ownership structures and governance systems across the entire economic system. American entrepreneurs who pioneer emerging industries using these technologies should receive clear policy guidance and full recognition of their achievements. The core policy recommendations are as follows:· American citizens and businesses should have the right to legally hold digital assets and use blockchain technology without the fear of being held acco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>