<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:13:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Mitosis Genesis Airdrop registration will open on August 20, with claiming expected to be available until September 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25306</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Mitosis officially announced that the registration for the Genesis Airdrop will commence on August 20th and the registration window will remain open until August 26th. The airdrop lookup website is now active, and claiming is expected to open prior to September 10th with a one-week claiming period. During the airdrop claiming process, users have the option to claim directly or stake for 180 days to receive additional airdrop allocations.Previously, on August 17th, the Mitosis Foundation unveiled the MITO tokenomics. The total supply of tokens is 1 billion, allocated as follows: 45.5% to the ecosystem, 15% to the team, 8.76% to investors, 10% to the foundation, 10% to the Genesis Airdrop, 2% to builder rewards, 3.5% to exchange platform marketing, 4% to initial liquidity, and 1.24% to research and development.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25306</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Season Index Drops to 45</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25305</link>
      <description>August 20th. According to the data from Coinmarketcap, the Altcoin Season Index plummeted to 45. It had briefly dropped to 29 on August 11th. This index shows that among the top 100 cryptocurrency projects in terms of market capitalization, approximately 45 projects have outperformed Bitcoin in the past 90 days.Note: The CMC Altcoin Season Index is a real-time indicator utilized to evaluate whether the cryptocurrency market is currently in an altcoin-dominated season. This index is based on the performance of the top 100 altcoins compared to Bitcoin over the past 90 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25305</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Exchange Trading Volume Rebounds, ETH, XRP, BTC Hold Top Three Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25304</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit has rebounded to $2.922 billion, showing a 11.9% increase. Among them, the ETH/KRW trading pair accounted for 17.22% of the volume and ranked first in the Korean won market. The remaining top five were: XRP, BTC, API3, ADA.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Foundation partners with Hex Trust to provide BTC Equity Staking Service to Institutional Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25303</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the Core Foundation made an announcement about a deep collaboration with the digital asset custodian Hex Trust. This collaboration involves integrating Core&apos;s Double Proof-of-Stake into Hex Trust&apos;s institutional-grade custody system. Hex Trust&apos;s fully licensed custody solution simplifies institutional access to Core&apos;s BTCFi product flow, enabling clients to scale their participation more efficiently. This collaboration will offer a secure and compliant Bitcoin yield channel for institutional investors in the Asia-Pacific and Middle East regions. Institutional clients will be able to earn real on-chain block rewards by staking Bitcoin and CORE tokens without the need to transfer or sell Bitcoin, thereby accelerating the development of the BTCFi ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25303</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst Tom Lee: Ethereum Consolidation to Continue Until Midweek, Then Will Reach New Highs, Bitcoin to Break $130,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25302</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the newly appointed Chairman of BitMine, Tom Lee, whose Fundstrat Capital fund analyst released an opinion yesterday. It was stated that the recent consolidation of Ethereum is expected to continue for another 1-2 days. However, the range of $4075-$4150 will present a good risk/reward opportunity and extend into mid-week. After that, Ethereum is supposed to rise to nearly $5100 and set a slight new high.This pullback trend is similar to what is suggested by Elliott Wave Theory (which assumes that the financial market does not move randomly but follows specific and predictable wave patterns. These patterns reflect cyclical changes in investor sentiment and can be used to identify major trends and reversal points in the market), so there is no need to worry. At the same time, Bitcoin should not fall below $111,900 and will then rise to the range of $130,000-$140,000.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 19th, the newly appointed Chairman of BitMine, Tom Lee, r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25302</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monad is issuing Monad Cards to Crypto Twitter users, with approximately 5,000 accounts qualifying to claim them.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25301</link>
      <description>August 20th. According to official channels, Monad is set to release Monad Cards targeted at crypto Twitter users. In the initial phase, around 5,000 active crypto Twitter accounts are qualified to receive the cards. In the subsequent phase, each account can nominate 3 friends. There are a total of 10,000 nomination slots available on a first-come, first-served basis.Some members within the crypto community hypothesize that holders of these Monad Cards may be eligible to receive a token airdrop reward once the Monad mainnet becomes operational.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25301</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Big Brother Whale」, AguilaTrades, and other contract whales have lost over 55 million USD in the past week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25300</link>
      <description>August 20th. Based on on-chain data, with the recent continuous downturn in the cryptocurrency market, several well-known whale positions in contract trading have endured significant losses. The specific data is as follows:· &quot;Brother Ma&quot; Huang Licheng suffered a loss of more than $12.7 million in the past week.· James Wynn suffered a loss of $13,000 in the past week.· There was a loss of more than $6.87 million in the past week.· The two addresses of the &quot;125K USD Liquidation Long ETH to 6.99M USD&quot; whale suffered losses of $11.5 million and $24.5 million respectively in the past week.· The &quot;Insider Whale&quot; @qwatio did not trade in the past week, and the assets in the address are now zero, with a loss of $2.8 million in the past month.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25300</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha and Futures will list Sapien (SAPIEN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25299</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Binance Alpha and Binance Futures made an announcement regarding the listing of Sapien (SAPIEN).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25299</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launchpad Platform Heaven&apos;s Market Share Surges, Token Circulating Supply Second Only to pump.fun</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25298</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on DUNE data, Solana&apos;s ecosystem AMM and Launchpad platform Heaven experienced a notable increase in market share. The token issuance in the past 5 days ranked second only to pump.fun, significantly outperforming platforms such as Bags, Moonshot, LetsBonk, and others.Heaven&apos;s native token LIGHT saw a surge of over 290% in the past 5 days, exceeding a market capitalization of 2 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25298</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institution sold 4,000 ETH at an average price of $4,164, and has already sold over 12,500 ETH to date.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25297</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst AI Auntie ai_9684xtpa, an institution has once again sold 4,000 ETH within the past 12 hours. The value of these sold ETH is $16.65 million, with an average price of $4,164.From 08.18 to the present date, this address has sold a total of 12,575 ETH. The total value of these sales amounts to up to $53.68 million. Currently, it still holds 6,210 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25297</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>