<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:33:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency and FinTech Executives Urge Trump to Ban Banks from Charging Customer Data Fees</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24714</link>
      <description>On August 15th, more than 80 executives from the cryptocurrency and fintech sectors jointly sent a letter to U.S. President Donald Trump. In the letter, they accused banks of imposing fees for accessing customer data and characterized this practice as suppressing consumer choice. The letter alleged that large banks were trying to &quot;preserve their market dominance by imposing excessive new &apos;account access&apos; fees, which would prevent consumers from linking their accounts to better financial products that they preferred.&quot; The Biden administration had previously attempted to promote open access to bank customer data but had faced opposition from the banking industry, which had hindered its implementation. Later, U.S. President Trump stated that fee regulations would remain in effect until new guidelines were issued.CEX Gemini, the trading platform Robinhood, as well as cryptocurrency advocacy groups such as the CryptoCurrency Innovation Commission and the Blockchain Association supported t</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnicornX&apos;s latest UniCall Signal project has reached a new all-time high market capitalization for CYC, with a 24-hour price increase of 84.57%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24713</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on market data, the latest UniCall signal project CYC of UnicornX achieved a new intraday high in FDV of $149 million, and the highest increase reached 294.47%.At the time of this writing, the price of CYC is currently at $0.1067, with a 24-hour increase of 84.57%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24713</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX is exclusively launching the &quot;Trade Account Auto Earning&quot; feature, balancing yield and trading flexibility</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24712</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to official data, OKX launched the exclusive &quot;Auto Earn&quot; feature for VIP users on August 15th, 2025. This feature enables users to automatically lend out the assets in their trading accounts (with full collateral) without influencing the assets&apos; use for staking and trading margins, allowing them to obtain rewards. It is known that initially, this feature only supports USDT and is applicable to spot, futures, cross-margin, portfolio margin, and other account models. More assets will be gradually supported in the future. Users only need to enable it once and do not need to subscribe manually. Changes in full collateralized equity will be immediately reflected in the earned assets, and normal orders and trades will not be affected.Furthermore, as stated in the announcement, after users activate this feature, their assets will participate in the interest rate auction together based on the set lending annual percentage yield (APY) and simple earning assets. If th</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong&apos;s Securities and Futures Commission Clarifies Robust Custodial Standards to Safeguard Customer Virtual Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24711</link>
      <description>August 15th. Today, the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission issued a circular to all licensed virtual asset trading platforms, making clear its requirements for the secure custody of client virtual assets. This lays a solid foundation for the industry to systematically adopt more advanced custody technology in accordance with the ASPIRe roadmap.In the latest circular, the Commission cited several examples of good practices and minimum standards that virtual asset trading platform operators should meet. These aspects cover the responsibilities of senior management, the infrastructure and operation of client cold wallets, the use of third-party wallets, and real-time threat monitoring, etc. In the future, these standards will also become the core regulatory requirements for virtual asset custodians and help drive the industry to establish an effective virtual asset custody framework. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24711</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Spot Trading Volume Skyrockets by 61.4% in One Month, Reaching $698.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24710</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as per a Coingecko report, in July, with Bitcoin reaching an all-time high, Binance&apos;s spot trading volume increased by 61.4% compared to the previous month and reached $698.3 billion. It far exceeded MEXC (with an 8.6% market share and $150.4 billion) and Gate (with a 7.8% share and $137.2 billion), holding nearly 40% of the global spot trading volume market share.Also in July, Binance&apos;s trading volume exceeded the total of several top ten global exchanges. This advantage is not restricted to a single month. During the second quarter of 2025, Binance accounted for 38.0% of the total trading volume among the top ten CEXs, with a volume of $1.47 trillion (while the total volume of these ten exchanges was $3.8 trillion).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24710</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: stETH Faces Depegging Risk, Potentially Triggering Liquidation Across Lending Protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24709</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Ben Lilly, a digital analyst at Jlabs, pointed out that currently stETH is being redeemed from Lido. Meanwhile, another lending protocol, Figment, is seizing the market share of Lido, suggesting that Figment may be the staking partner of the ETF. 32% of stETH (wstETH) is being used as collateral for the lending protocol, and the decoupling may indicate a liquidation event for the lending protocol.It is worth noting that currently, 278,000 wstETH is in a &quot;high-risk&quot; state (where high-risk is defined as a health factor between 1-1.1 times).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24709</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 788,000 ETH is currently queued to exit the Ethereum PoS network, setting a new record.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24708</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 788,624 ETH, which is approximately worth $36.51 billion, setting a record for the largest exit queue in terms of coin value.At the same time, about 332,846 ETH are queued to join the network.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market: on one hand, some stakers may be cashing out after Ethereum rebounded by more than 160% from the April low, resulting in a significant increase in the exit queue; on the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also boosting the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion are increasing their ETH holdings and engaging in staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24708</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Over the past 30 days, the amount of ETH purchased by Ethereum strategic entities and ETFs is 47 times the network&apos;s net issuance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24707</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on @sassal0x&apos;s data, within the past 30 days:ETH Net Issuance: 74,000 ETH;ETH Purchased by Investment Firms: 1.8 million ETH;ETH Amount Purchased by ETFs: 1.7 million ETH;This indicates that during the past 30 days, the amount of ETH purchased by these entities is 47 times the network&apos;s net issuance.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 03:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24707</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHZilla Surpasses BTCS to Enter Ethereum Treasury Company Holdings Top 10, ETH Balance Increases to Around 82,200 Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24706</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the latest figures from Strategicethreserve, the amount of Ethereum held by the Nasdaq-listed company ETHZilla (formerly 180 Life Sciences) has gone up to around 82,200 ETH. This is equivalent to approximately $380.5 million at the current price. Currently, its Ethereum holding has exceeded that of BTCS and ranked 10th among the holdings of Ethereum Treasury Companies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 03:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24706</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. White House: Trump to Hold Bilateral Meeting with Putin at 11 a.m. Alaska Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24705</link>
      <description>August 15, at the White House in the USA: 11:00 AM Alaska Time (3:00 AM Beijing Time the next day), Trump is scheduled to hold a bilateral meeting with Russian President Putin in Anchorage, Alaska. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 03:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24705</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>