<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:50:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Monad is issuing Monad Cards to Crypto Twitter users, with approximately 5,000 accounts qualifying to claim them.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25301</link>
      <description>August 20th. According to official channels, Monad is set to release Monad Cards targeted at crypto Twitter users. In the initial phase, around 5,000 active crypto Twitter accounts are qualified to receive the cards. In the subsequent phase, each account can nominate 3 friends. There are a total of 10,000 nomination slots available on a first-come, first-served basis.Some members within the crypto community hypothesize that holders of these Monad Cards may be eligible to receive a token airdrop reward once the Monad mainnet becomes operational.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25301</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Big Brother Whale」, AguilaTrades, and other contract whales have lost over 55 million USD in the past week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25300</link>
      <description>August 20th. Based on on-chain data, with the recent continuous downturn in the cryptocurrency market, several well-known whale positions in contract trading have endured significant losses. The specific data is as follows:· &quot;Brother Ma&quot; Huang Licheng suffered a loss of more than $12.7 million in the past week.· James Wynn suffered a loss of $13,000 in the past week.· There was a loss of more than $6.87 million in the past week.· The two addresses of the &quot;125K USD Liquidation Long ETH to 6.99M USD&quot; whale suffered losses of $11.5 million and $24.5 million respectively in the past week.· The &quot;Insider Whale&quot; @qwatio did not trade in the past week, and the assets in the address are now zero, with a loss of $2.8 million in the past month.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25300</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha and Futures will list Sapien (SAPIEN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25299</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Binance Alpha and Binance Futures made an announcement regarding the listing of Sapien (SAPIEN).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25299</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launchpad Platform Heaven&apos;s Market Share Surges, Token Circulating Supply Second Only to pump.fun</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25298</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on DUNE data, Solana&apos;s ecosystem AMM and Launchpad platform Heaven experienced a notable increase in market share. The token issuance in the past 5 days ranked second only to pump.fun, significantly outperforming platforms such as Bags, Moonshot, LetsBonk, and others.Heaven&apos;s native token LIGHT saw a surge of over 290% in the past 5 days, exceeding a market capitalization of 2 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25298</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institution sold 4,000 ETH at an average price of $4,164, and has already sold over 12,500 ETH to date.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25297</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst AI Auntie ai_9684xtpa, an institution has once again sold 4,000 ETH within the past 12 hours. The value of these sold ETH is $16.65 million, with an average price of $4,164.From 08.18 to the present date, this address has sold a total of 12,575 ETH. The total value of these sales amounts to up to $53.68 million. Currently, it still holds 6,210 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25297</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celsius will conduct its third distribution to lenders, with a total amount of $220.6 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25296</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per Cointelegraph, Celsius is set to commence its third distribution to eligible creditors, amounting to $2.206 billion. This will bring the cumulative recovery rate to approximately 64.9% of the claim value.BlockBeats had previously reported that on May 9th, Celsius founder Alex Mashinsky was sentenced to 12 years in prison for crypto fraud. The two charges against him resulted in sentences of 120 months and 144 months (to be served concurrently for 144 months). Alex Mashinsky agreed to forfeit $48 million and several properties. Prior to Celsius&apos; collapse in 2022, Alex Mashinsky repeatedly deceived investors regarding the security of customer deposits. The prosecution pointed out that he falsely claimed that the platform had regulatory approval, insisted that they never issued unsecured loans (while in fact they did), and manipulated the price of the CEL token for personal gain - the illicit gains related to CEL alone exceeded $48 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puffer&apos;s official website and social media channels have been attacked. Please do not engage with this protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25295</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as monitored by PeckShield, the official website and social media channels of the rebase protocol Puffer Finance have been hacked. It is advised that you do not interact with any Puffer applications and refrain from visiting official social media channels.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25295</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: U.S. and China had a &quot;very productive discussion&quot; on economic and trade issues</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25294</link>
      <description>August 20th. As per Reuters, on August 19th local time, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen stated in an interview that the U.S. and China had engaged in a &quot;very good dialogue&quot; regarding economic and trade matters. Yellen said, &quot;We had a highly productive dialogue with the Chinese side, and I anticipate that we will hold another meeting prior to November. I believe that the ongoing work is progressing in an extremely smooth manner.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25294</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Radiant Capital Flashbot」 conducted a sandwich attack in the past 1 hour, sniping 2109.5 ETH at an average price of $4096</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25293</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to Ashes Monitor, the Radiant Capital hacker has once again purchased 2,109.5 ETH with 8.64 million DAI at a price of $4,096 within the past hour. A week ago, they sold 9,631 ETH at an average price of $4,562 and exchanged it for 43.937 million DAI.Now, the Radiant Capital hacker holds 14,436 ETH + 35.29 million DAI, which is worth $94.63 million. Compared to the $53 million of funds they stole last year, the value has increased by $41.63 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25293</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell to Deliver Speech on Friday Evening, Some Traders Lower Rate Cut Expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25292</link>
      <description>August 20th: Chairman Powell of the Federal Reserve is slated to give a crucial speech at this year&apos;s gathering in Wyoming on Friday evening according to Beijing time. Meanwhile, the recent release of inflation data that is higher than expected has led some traders to reduce their expectations of interest rate cuts while still maintaining the judgment of a rate cut next month.Ian Lyngen, the head of U.S. Rate Strategy at BMO Capital Markets, stated in a research report that &quot;as the market gets ready for Powell&apos;s speech at Jackson Hole, the greatest risk facing the Treasury market is that the Fed Chair may pour cold water on the market&apos;s widespread expectation of a rate cut in September.&quot;Currently, there are approximately 325,000 options positions (costing about $10 million) that are likely to make a profit of up to $100 million if they accurately predict a 50-basis-point rate cut by the Fed at the September policy meeting. In addition, the current market pricing indicates that ther</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25292</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>