<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:26:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Netherlands Treasury BV has announced the completion of a €126 million private placement to acquire over 1000 BTC, with lead investment from Winklevoss Capital and others.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27518</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as reported by Coindesk, the Dutch company Treasury BV announced that it had raised 126 million euros (equivalent to 147 million US dollars) through private financing. This round of financing was led by Winklevoss Capital (the founder brothers of Gemini) and Nakamoto Holdings. The company utilized this funding to acquire more than 1000 bitcoins with the intention of becoming Europe&apos;s largest publicly traded Bitcoin asset management company.In order to attain its listing goal, the company, led by CEO Khing Oei, has signed a binding agreement with the Dutch small and medium-sized enterprise investment company MKB Nedsense NV (MKBN) to be listed on the Amsterdam Pan-European Exchange through a reverse takeover.This Dutch company also announced the acquisition of the European flagship Bitcoin event Bitcoin Amsterdam in order to expand Bitcoin&apos;s mainstream application.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27518</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address has once again withdrawn 12,869 ETH from OKX, bringing its total holdings to 17,969 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27516</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale address once more withdrew 12,869 ETH from OKX, with a value of 55.59 million US dollars.Currently, this whale address holds 17,969 ETH, which is worth 77.62 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27516</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 2 years of inactivity, the Rollbit Treasury associated address sold 50,000 SOL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27517</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as monitored by LookOnChain, the address associated with the Rollbit Treasury sold 50,000 SOL. It had been dormant for 2 years and the average selling price was $203.4 (approximately $10.17 million).The wallet had received these 50,000 SOL from the Rollbit Treasury 2 years ago (approximately $1.23 million at that time), when the price of SOL was only $24.6.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27517</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea: TGE on September 10th, all airdrops fully unlocked, initial allocation scheme mimicking ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27515</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Linea official announced on social media that the airdrop whitelist is now open and that the TGE will take place on September 10th.LINEA mimics Ethereum&apos;s initial allocation scheme: 85% of tokens are allocated to the ecosystem. 10% of the tokens are allocated to early users and builders and are fully unlocked. 75% of the tokens are allocated to the largest ecosystem fund in cryptocurrency history. Within this fund, another 4% of the shares will be allocated to the liquidity provider community airdrop.Neither the project team nor venture capital firms have been allocated any shares. They are dedicated solely to the sustainable long-term ecosystem development.The claiming window will open on September 10th and will run until December 9th (a total of 90 days). All airdropped tokens will be fully unlocked with no vesting period. Any unclaimed tokens will be returned to the ecosystem fund after December 9th.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet will host a FOMO Morph Day event on September 4th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27514</link>
      <description>September 3rd. As per official information, today Morph officially selected BGB as the gas token and governance token. Bitget Wallet will hold a special FOMO Morph Day event this Thursday. The event participation rules are as follows:- Staking 2 BGB (on the Morph Chain) makes one eligible for the lucky draw.- When trading any token on the Morph Chain, for every 50 USDT spent, one will receive an additional ticket (up to a maximum of 5 tickets).The grand prize for this event is 300 BGB, and there will be a single winner. Lucky winners will each receive 2 BGB, and there will be a total of 5,000 winners.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27514</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YZY Token&apos;s 24-Hour Trading Volume Only $640,000 Two Weeks After Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27513</link>
      <description>September 3rd. Based on GMGN market data, the official Meme coin YZY Token launched by the renowned rapper and Internet celebrity Kanye West had a 24-hour trading volume of merely $639,700 after 13 days of its release. The current market capitalization is reported to be $469 million. Since attaining its peak on the first day of release, the token has undergone a long-term decline, and its value has now decreased by 85%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27513</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX has launched WLFI contract grid trading and contract copy trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27512</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as per an official announcement, Huobi HTX has now initiated WLFI USDT-based contract grid trading and WLFI contract copy trading.Previously, Huobi HTX had launched WLFI/USDT spot trading, WLFI/USDT (10X) isolated margin trading, and WLFI/USDT perpetual contract trading.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four.Meme has announced the first CTO investment portfolio, with emmm, Donkey, TUT, and U making the cut.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27511</link>
      <description>September 3rd. As per official channels, Four.Meme has officially declared its first-phase CTO project portfolio today. The ultimately selected projects comprise $emmm, $Donkey, $TUT, and $U. Here, emmm took the first place overall, Donkey ranked second, and TUT tied with U for the third position.Four.Meme stated that they have set up a professional dashboard and monitoring procedure to conduct a comprehensive assessment of projects from seven aspects such as liquidity, community activity, and innovation capability. This ensures that their investment portfolio is both solid and growth-oriented.Regarding the investment strategy, Four.Meme will gradually build positions in five rounds. This initial round of purchases mainly focuses on projects related to the BNB Chain ecosystem, aiming to further promote value discovery and market activity in the meme coin sector within the ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Announcement: Linea Airdrop Lookup Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27510</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on community feedback, Linea has now initiated the airdrop lookup.BlockBeats Note: Currently, there has been no official announcement. However, community reports indicate that the domain of the relevant link is correct. For security purposes, users are advised to wait until the official announcement before conducting the check.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSL HK has officially launched BNB, becoming the first Hong Kong-based trading platform to support BNB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27509</link>
      <description>September 3rd, as per official information, OSL HK has made an announcement. It has now initiated BNB trading services for professional investors, thereby becoming the first exchange platform in Hong Kong to offer BNB trading. It has officially launched three trading pairs: BNB/USD, BNB/USDT, and BNB/USDC.BNB, which ranks among the top digital assets in terms of market capitalization, is the native token of the BNB Chain. This chain is renowned for its rich applications and its capabilities of low-cost and high-speed transactions. The opening of BNB trading this time is intended to meet the increasing demand of institutional investors for high-quality digital assets. It also reflects the company&apos;s long-term strategic plan in diversified asset allocation. By integrating more mainstream digital assets, OSL HK is presenting investors and potential partners with a more diverse range of assets.Eddie Yue, the Chief Business Development Officer of the OSL Group, stated: &quot;We are delighted</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>