<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:29:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the United States Ethereum spot ETF saw a net inflow of $639.6 million, while the Bitcoin spot ETF saw a net inflow of $230.8 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24737</link>
      <description>August 15th. As reported by Farside Investors, yesterday, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF reached $639.6 million, indicating the 8th consecutive day of net inflows. Specifically, the BlackRock ETHA witnessed a net inflow of $519.7 million.Yesterday, the net inflow of the US Bitcoin spot ETF was $230.8 million, maintaining its streak of 7 consecutive days of net inflows. Among them, BlackRock&apos;s IBIT had a net inflow of $523.7 million, while ARK&apos;s ARKB experienced a net outflow of $149.9 million, and Fidelity&apos;s FBTC had a net outflow of $113.5 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24737</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha PublicAI (PUBLIC) airdrop schedule has been changed to today at 15:30.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24735</link>
      <description>August 15th. According to an official announcement, PublicAI (PUBLIC) has postponed the trading on Binance Alpha until today and it will start at 15:30 (UTC+8).The Binance Alpha airdrop will be distributed in two stages:Stage One (the first 18 hours): Users who hold at least 240 Alpha points can make a claim.Stage Two (the next 6 hours): Users holding at least 200 Alpha points can participate in the second-stage airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is still in progress, the point threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points per hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24735</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A savvy whale with a 100% win rate in four previous trades has sold off their position and accumulated approximately 2174 ETH today.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24736</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai9684xtpa), the smart money that achieved a 100% success rate in four ETH swing trades purchased 2,174.02 WETH early this morning at a cost of $4,599.77. This amount of ETH was sold with a limit order at $4,655, realizing a profit of $108,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The total supply of OKB has now officially decreased to 21 million tokens after the burn.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24733</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on Etherscan data, the OKEx OKB Buy-Back and Burn Wallet officially transferred 279 million OKB tokens to the Null Address: 0x00…0000 at 14:00 in UTC+8 today, achieving a genuine burn. The total supply of OKB has now officially decreased to 21 million tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24733</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha PublicAI (PUBLIC) Token Airdrop Currently Facing Delay</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24734</link>
      <description>On August 15, according to an official announcement, the airdrop of the Binance Alpha PublicAI (PUBLIC) token is currently experiencing a delay.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24734</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant: Bitcoin Long-Term Holders Profit Taken Reached a Bottom Lower Than Before, Accumulation Trend Dominates Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24732</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the CryptoQuant analyst Axel Adler Jr. posted a message indicating that the cumulative distribution of long-term holders who have held Bitcoin for six months to two years shows that the supply they hold has increased from 3.551 million BTC in April (when the Bitcoin price was $83,000) to the current 5.191 million BTC, with a growth of 1.64 million BTC. During the test at the all-time high (ATH) of $118,000, there was a moderate profit-taking, and the 7-day average outflow of long-term holders rose to 20,000 BTC, which is significantly lower than the past typical outflow peaks (40,000 to 70,000 BTC). Overall, this suggests that in the current market, the Bitcoin accumulation trend is more dominant compared to profit distribution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24732</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czech Police Detain Key Figure in $45 Million Bitcoin Donation Scandal and Seize Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24731</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to the report by Decrypt, the Czech police have apprehended convicted drug dealer Tomas Jirikovsky and seized his Bitcoin worth 45 million USD and other relevant assets that were donated to the Czech Ministry of Justice. The donation occurred earlier this year, and the then Minister of Justice, Pavel Blazek, accepted the donation without verifying its origin. Pavel Blazek resigned in May later due to growing criticism. Prosecutors stated that the main focus of the investigation has now shifted to suspected money laundering and illegal drug trading.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24731</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: The Fed has lagged behind market expectations in its interest rate cuts for 32 consecutive months. It is expected to cut rates by a total of approximately 62 basis points over the next ...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24730</link>
      <description>August 15th. Matrixport disclosed its latest research report indicating that the U.S. market is entering a brand-new liquidity release cycle. Structural funding support may potentially lead to continuous upside for Bitcoin and risk assets. The market is expected to maintain this trend until 2026. The current fund structure, credit environment, and policy shift towards dovishness closely resemble the early stages of past bull markets. Abundant liquidity, an improved credit environment, and dovish policy shifts - all these multiple bullish factors are resonating to drive up asset prices.In the U.S., the money market fund has witnessed rapid expansion since the fourth quarter of 2018. It has grown from $3 trillion to $7.4 trillion, reaching a historical high. Currently, the annual interest income reaches $320 billion, constituting significant incremental funds flowing into high-yield assets. At the same time, corporate buybacks have also significantly accelerated. Since 2025, the announ</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24730</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhu Su: Curious about SBF&apos;s view on Hyperliquid and the current Solana ecosystem, hoping to engage in a discussion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24729</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Zhu Su, the founder of Three Arrows Capital, stated in a post that 3AC has emerged victorious in the lawsuit against FTX and has been awarded a compensation of $15.3 billion. He indicated that if SBF has any new project concepts, he would be inclined to listen, and he is also intrigued by SBF&apos;s perspectives on Hyperliquid and the present Solana ecosystem. Is there a means to get in touch with him via email?On March 14th, 2025, the Delaware Bankruptcy Court gave its approval to Three Arrows Capital (3AC)&apos;s application, raising its claim against FTX from $120 million to $15.3 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24729</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yi Lihua: The future decade of the crypto industry is still the greatest opportunity for the average person. Long-term bullishness is the key to growth and success.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24728</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the founder of Liquid Capital (formerly LD Capital), Li Huayi, posted on the X Platform, stating: &quot;In the past decade, the crypto industry has been the greatest opportunity for ordinary people, and it will continue to be so in the next decade. Do not let short-term thinking mislead the long-term trend. I come from a rural area, and both of my parents are illiterate. After earning my first bucket of gold through entrepreneurship, I invested in tech companies while going all-in on the crypto industry. Looking back at 2015, none of these decisions seemed reliable at that time, but now it has been proved that they were all correct (although a substantial tuition fee was paid during the investment/trading/management process). Only by having a long-term bullish view can one achieve exponential growth and harvest.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>