<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:59:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「$2249 Short Position on ETH」 Faces Massive Unrealized Loss of Nearly $18 Million, Previously Liquidated with 25x Leverage, Been Stuck for Four Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27608</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight, the whale that shorted ETH at $2249 last night has decreased its holdings by 333.19 ETH. Currently, it is facing a loss of approximately $17.938 million, with a liquidation price of $5784.94. This whale established a 25x short position in April when the ETH price was around $2249.7. Subsequently, it continuously raised the average entry price to around $2760 by continuously adding positions. It has been gradually reducing the position since the end of August.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 new addresses withdrew 34,000 ETH from Binance last night after ETH surged.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27607</link>
      <description>On September 4th, based on the monitoring of on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, last night after ETH surged from $4,350 to $4,480, 34,000 ETH (approximately $150 million) was then withdrawn from Binance to two new wallet addresses at 1 am according to American language usage.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27607</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonshot is excited to announce the addition of CARDS!Stay tuned for this next big thing in the NFT world.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27606</link>
      <description>On September 4th, based on monitoring, Moonshot incorporated Collector Crypt (CARDS) onto its platform. At the time of listing, it had an initial fully diluted valuation (FDV) of $4.16 billion and a 24-hour trading volume of $1 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27606</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDS surges over 200% in the last 24 hours, now trading at $0.2068.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27605</link>
      <description>On September 4th, based on GMGN market data, the token CARDS of the Solana ecosystem NFT trading platform Collector Crypt has surged above $0.2 and is currently trading at $0.2068, indicating a 24-hour price increase of 202.6%. The current market capitalization is reported to be $81.33 million, and the fully diluted valuation (FDV) is $413 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27605</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH Transaction Platform Balance Hits Nearly 3-Year Low, Withdrawal Acceleration Seen in the Past 3 Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27604</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to CryptoQuant&apos;s data, since peaking at around 28.8 million in September 2022, the ETH exchange platform reserve has decreased by nearly 10.7 million. The current reserve stands at approximately 17.4 million ETH, with about 2.5 million ETH being withdrawn from the exchange platform just in the past three months.The data indicates that the spot ETH ETF launched in July 2024 has attracted more than $13 billion in net inflows up to now. From June to August, these funds witnessed net inflows of over $10 billion, with a record $5.4 billion in inflows alone in July.Corporate bonds are also fueling demand. In the past few months, several publicly traded companies have announced the issuance of ETH bonds, and corporate treasury purchases are affecting the exchange&apos;s ETH supply. It is known that 17 publicly listed companies hold ETH on their balance sheets, with a total holding of over 3.6 million ETH.An analyst at Bitfinex stated that one of the key attraction</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27604</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address newly created 8 hours ago withdrew 692 BTC from Galaxy Digital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27603</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a new address withdrew 692 BTC from Galaxy Digital 8 hours ago. The amount withdrawn is worth $77.32 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27603</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ondo Tokenized Stocks Officially Launched, Initial Offering Supports Over 100 Equities and ETFs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27602</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to official channels, Ondo Global Markets has officially commenced. It offers non-US investors with round-the-clock instantaneous access to tokenized US stocks, ETFs, and other securities. These come with access to traditional market liquidity and institutional-grade protection. Non-US investors can trade more than 100 tokenized US stocks and ETFs (subject to jurisdictional limitations) and plan to expand to over 1000 by the end of the year, marking the largest-ever tokenized equity asset issuance. Ondo&apos;s tokenized stocks are now operational on Ethereum and are soon to expand to the BNB Chain, Solana, Ondo Chain, and other networks.It is reported that Ondo&apos;s tokenized stocks are backed by the on-hand securities held by a US-registered broker-dealer and readily available cash in full. Non-US users can instantly mint, redeem, and transfer these assets 24/7/365 (transfers are available throughout the day, while minting and redeeming are liquidity-matched duri</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27602</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonshot is launching the xStocks tokenized stocks, currently not available to users from the United States</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27601</link>
      <description>Update, September 4th. According to official channels, Moonshot has declared the commencement of the launch of xStocks tokenized stocks. Users are now capable of participating in the traditional market and trading assets (such as NVDAx, COINx, and TSLAx) via xStocks. The service is accessible in certain countries/regions and is currently not available to users in the United States.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27601</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Family Backs Mining Firm American Bitcoin, Stock Price Surges 17% on First Day of Trading, Eric Trump&apos;s Holdings Valued at Over $500 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27600</link>
      <description>On September 4th, during the listing debut of mining company American Bitcoin (with the code ABTC) supported by the Trump family, the stock price increased by nearly 17% to $8.04 per share, and reached a high of $14 during the trading session. The trading volume of the stock on the first day exceeded 29 million shares.Eric Trump stated, &quot;We possess a core, high-quality mining operation. Currently, the mining costs are only 50% of the Bitcoin market price. The company holds hundreds of millions of dollars&apos; worth of hardware assets and data centers... While others can only purchase at face value, we can acquire Bitcoin at a significant discount.&quot;According to Bloomberg&apos;s estimation, the successful listing of American Bitcoin indicates that the stake held by Eric Trump, the second son of Trump, is valued at more than $500 million.Founded in March of this year, American Bitcoin is a cryptocurrency mining and holding company co-founded by Eric Trump and supported by Donald Trump Jr. (t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created address withdrew 17,000 ETH from Binance, worth $75.81 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27599</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, the new address &apos;0x900&apos; withdrew 17,000 ETH from Binance, with a value of $75.81 million. Additionally, a whale address beginning with &apos;0x8e0&apos; withdrew 2,312 ETH from Kraken, having a value of $10.31 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 23:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27599</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>