<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:59:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes Joins Solana Ecosystem&apos;s Upexi Advisory Council</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24233</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the Solana DeFi platform Upexi announced that Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of BitMEX, has joined as the first member of its Advisory Board. The Upexi Advisory Board will lead strategic planning, increase market exposure, and attract more capital to Upexi&apos;s SOL treasury.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24233</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vietnamese National Assembly has approved the establishment of an International Financial Center to pilot cryptocurrency asset trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24232</link>
      <description>August 12th: Pham Tien Dung, who is the Deputy Governor of the State Bank of Vietnam, declared that the Vietnamese National Assembly has given its approval to a resolution for establishing an International Financial Center. This allows for the establishment of a digital asset exchange platform. Additionally, the Ministry of Finance has presented a draft resolution for a pilot program, designating blockchain as a core operational infrastructure. The &quot;Industrial and Digital Transformation Law&quot; has clearly defined digital assets, virtual assets, and tokenized assets, thus laying a specific legal foundation. The Vietnamese government has shown its determination to meet regulatory requirements while creating a flexible sandbox environment that adheres to global standards for businesses and investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale withdrew 500 BTC from Binance 5 hours ago, with a total of 3000 BTC withdrawn within 3 months.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24229</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale address beginning with bc1q5r withdrew 500 BTC from Binance 5 hours ago, which is approximately worth $59.53 million. This whale has withdrawn a total of 3000 BTC from Binance within the past 3 months, amounting to around $355 million, with an average price of $109,895.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24229</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Stock Futures Rise in Unison, Ethereum Surges Towards $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24231</link>
      <description>On August 12th, following the release of the US CPI, the futures of the three major US stock indexes all witnessed an increase. The Nasdaq 100 Index went up by 0.44%, and the S&amp;P 500 Index rose by 0.38%. According to HTX market data, Bitcoin surged to above $119,000, while Ethereum rose to nearly $4,400 and is currently trading at $4,397.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24231</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Breaks $4400, Hits New High Since January 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24230</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum exceeded $4400, showing a 24-hour increase of 5.27% and reaching a new high since January 2022.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24230</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the CPI is published, traders increase their bets that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates in September and December.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24228</link>
      <description>August 12th: Following the release of the U.S. CPI, traders enhanced their wagers on a September rate cut by the Federal Reserve. They continued to bet on rate cuts in both September and December.Spot gold witnessed a short-term surge of more than $10, while the U.S. Dollar Index (DXY) witnessed a short-term decline of more than 30 points and was trading at 98.25.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24228</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Core CPI Rises to Five-Month High, Exceeds Expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24227</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the year-on-year rate of the US July non-seasonally adjusted core CPI further rose to 3.1%, reaching a five-month high and being above the market expectation of 3.0% and the previous value of 2.90%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24227</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In July, the U.S. seasonally adjusted core CPI saw a year-on-year increase of 3.1%, slightly below expectations.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24226</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the US July Non-Seasonally Adjusted Core CPI YoY was 3.1%. The expected value was 3.00%, and the previous value was 2.90%. It remained flat from the previous month and was slightly below expectations. (FX Street)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24226</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guangzhou, China: Strengthen Investment Attraction Efforts for Key Digital Service Providers in Blockchain, Artificial Intelligence, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24225</link>
      <description>August 12. Lately, the People&apos;s Government of Guangzhou, China has issued the &quot;Implementation Plan for Implementing the Opinions on Implementing Financial Support for Guangzhou Nansha to Deepen the Guangdong-Hong Kong-Macao Comprehensive Cooperation Oriented to the World.&quot; It brought up the support for the development of the digital industry. Enhance the investment attraction efforts for key digital service institutions like blockchain and artificial intelligence, and cultivate local high-quality digital service institutions. Encourage digital industry companies to strengthen cooperation with Nansha financial institutions and expand the financial scenario integration applications. Support the establishment in Nansha of data and computing power centers, R&amp;D certification centers, evaluation centers, and regulatory platforms that integrate key digital technologies such as blockchain and artificial intelligence with financial scenarios. Promote data exchanges to improve the comprehensive</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24225</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before the release of the US CPI, the probability of a Fed rate cut in September was 82.5%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24224</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot;: The likelihood of the Fed maintaining the interest rate steady in September is 17.5%, and the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 82.5%.There is a 6.5% probability of the Fed keeping the interest rate steady in October. The cumulative probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 41.5%, and the cumulative probability of a 50-basis-point rate cut is 52.0%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>