<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:32:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha New Airdrop SLAY Claim Threshold: Phase 1 requires 227 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24023</link>
      <description>August 11th. Binance Alpha will be the first to launch SatLayer (SLAY). And Alpha trading will commence on August 11th, 2025, at 10:00 (UTC). Qualified users can claim a 525 SLAY airdrop on the Alpha event page by using Binance Alpha points within 24 hours after the trading starts.The Binance Alpha airdrop will be distributed in two stages:Stage 1 (First 18 hours): Users who hold at least 227 Binance Alpha points can claim the airdrop.Stage 2 (Last 6 hours): Users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha points can participate in the airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the rewards are not completely distributed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points per hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24023</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes recently increased his holdings by nearly $10 million in ETH and its ecosystem&apos;s shitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24022</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst AI Auntie @ai_9684xtpa, &quot;Arthur Hayes has transformed into the leader of token chasing in the ETH ecosystem. From yesterday until now, he has accumulated a total of $9.514 million worth of a basket of tokens, including ETH, ETHFI, LDO, and PENDLE. ETH accounts for 78% of the portfolio volume.In addition, two hours ago, he received 10 ENA from Wintermute for testing, and he is expected to initiate a continuous accumulation mode in the near future.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24022</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Concept Stock Soars Pre-market, Bitmine Up Over 9%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24021</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to Rockflow market data, there were significant gains in the pre-market trading of US cryptocurrency-related stocks. These included:· Sharplink Gaming increasing by 8.99%;· Bitmine rising by 9.70%;· Strategy rising by 4.07%;· Circle rising by 2.49%;· Coinbase rising by 4.43%;· HOOD rising by 2.09%;· BTCS rising by 6.60%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24021</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem OG AI Coin Soars, AVA Surges Over 35% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24020</link>
      <description>On August 11th, there was a general upward trend in established AI coins within the Solana ecosystem. These included:· AVA increased by more than 35% in the past 24 hours, with a market capitalization of $43.6 million;· ARC rose by more than 33% in the past 24 hours, with a market capitalization of $28.08 million;· SWARMS surged by more than 25% in the past 24 hours, with a market capitalization of $25.8 million;· GRIFFAIN went up by more than 23% in the past 24 hours, with a market capitalization of $49.72 million;· TAI rose by more than 16% in the past 24 hours, with a market capitalization of $45.76 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24020</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyStonks launched its contract trading public beta on August 11, supporting RWA Stock Token perpetual contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24019</link>
      <description>Update, August 11th: MyStonks officially commenced contract trading public testing at 16:00 UTC on August 11, 2025. The first batch will offer support for RWA Sector US Stock Token Perpetual Contracts, with adjustable leverage up to 20x and a matching engine offering millisecond-level feedback. The platform&apos;s weekly contract fee of $9283.75 will be refunded in BMNR.M tokens, and the refund mechanism will expire after the public testing phase.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24019</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit&apos;s 24-hour trading volume drops by 25%: XRP, ETH, BTC currently in the top three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24018</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, Upbit&apos;s trading volume declined to $3.12 billion, representing a 25% decrease. Among them, the XRP/KRW trading pair took the lead with a 13.42% trading volume share, followed by ETH, BTC, PROVE, and ENA in the top five.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24018</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Moody&apos;s Warns Recession Concerns Mount, BTC Surges to High-Density Supply Zone, Strategy Emphasizes Risk Management and Equal-weight Phased Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24017</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Moody&apos;s issued a warning stating that more than half of the industry has exhibited signs of layoffs. The risk of an economic turning point is on the rise. The non-agricultural employment number increased by only 73,000 last month, which is far below the forecast of approximately 100,000. Meanwhile, May&apos;s statistics were revised down from 144,000 to 19,000. If the employment data is revised down again, market risk aversion sentiment could quickly intensify. Such macro uncertainties will amplify short-term price fluctuations and fund rotations in crypto assets.Recently, the price of BTC has rapidly risen from around 112k to nearly 123k, with selling pressure in the range of 122k - 123k. If a breakthrough is accompanied by an increase in volume, the next supply levels will be at 124k and 127k.The suggestion of the Bitunix analyst is as follows: Currently, BTC is mainly in a stage of waiting for confirmation. If BTC can break through with volume and stabilize above 120k</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24017</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citigroup: Bond Market Sentiment Shift, Possible Stock Market Pullback in the Next Three Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24016</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Stuart Kaiser, the chief of Citigroup&apos;s US Options Strat, stated that in the past few weeks, the derivatives trading desk of the bank has witnessed a substantial increase in the demand from asset management clients to short products linked to the iShares index or junk bond benchmarks. This might indicate that macro investors have an outlook on the future direction or imply that they are hedging against the rise in risk assets. The fact that people are hedging credit risk suggests that they anticipate a considerable pullback in the stock market within the next three months. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Ethereum&apos;s Next Target Price Could Be $4362, Boosted by Recent Institutional Buying Pressure and Regulatory Tailwinds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24015</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Matrixport issued its daily chart analysis indicating that the Ethereum price surged beyond the $4,000 level and reached a new high since the end of 2021. This round of upward momentum was primarily driven by institutional buying pressure and a short squeeze. The on-chain activity also achieved a new all-time high, with a daily transaction volume exceeding 1.8 million and more than 30% of the supply already being staked.The SEC ruled that liquidity staking tokens are not securities, which brought significant regulatory optimism to the industry and enhanced market confidence in Ethereum and staking platforms. Encouraged by this, some public companies have expedited their strategic deployments, and their treasuries now hold more than $3.5 billion worth of ETH, which is nearly a tenfold increase compared to last year.The next target for the market may be $4,362, and the all-time high of $4,892 is still regarded as the ultimate milestone.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24015</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin breaks its all-time high, the mainstream CEX cumulative short liquidation intensity will reach 793 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24014</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to Coinglass data, in the event that Bitcoin surpasses its all-time high, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will amount to 793 million.On the other hand, if Bitcoin drops below $120,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach 1.084 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not provide the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of liquidated contracts. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, which is referred to as intensity.Consequently, the liquidation chart indicates the extent to which reaching a particular price level will have an impact. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; suggests that the price will encounter a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade when it reaches that level.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24014</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>