<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:38:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>X Layer&apos;s on-chain transaction volume has increased by 250% in the past 24 hours, reaching $68.2 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25594</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on geckoterminal data, within the past 24 hours, the on-chain transaction volume of X Layer reached $68.2 million, experiencing a 250% increase and having a transaction count of 34.75 thousand.The market capitalization of the Meme coin OKAY has reached $11.8 million, with a 24-hour price increase of 101%.BlockBeats reminds users that the price of the Meme coin is highly volatile. Please be cautious about asset protection and avoid the fear of missing out (FOMO).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25594</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimism is now collaborating with Flashbots to bring fast and verifiable transaction sorting to Superchain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25595</link>
      <description>August 21st. Optimism declared that it is collaborating with Flashbots to introduce fast and verifiable transaction sorting to the Superchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25595</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Asset Exchange Company LO:TECH Completes $5 Million Seed Round Funding, Led by 13books Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25593</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as reported by The Block, LO:TECH, a London-based digital asset exchange company, has successfully completed a $5 million seed round of financing. The lead investor is 13books Capital, with participation from Lightspeed Faction, Veris Ventures, CRIT Ventures USA, as well as angel investors Mark Ransford and Rodney Ngone. The company has indicated that this funding will be utilized to expand its on-chain capital market high-frequency trading business.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25593</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Trump Policy Could Weaken Dollar&apos;s Cyclical Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25592</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Jill Hirzel from Insight Investment declared in a report that the US dollar might weaken. This is because Trump&apos;s policies have diminished the allure of US exceptionalism and could result in a reduction of capital inflows into the US. Hirzel said, &quot;Policy uncertainty and a more assertive &apos;America First&apos; agenda may eat away at the cyclical support for the US dollar, causing it to enter a prolonged period of weakness.&quot; Nevertheless, she also noted that investors should be cautious when overly betting on the dollar&apos;s decline through short positions. This is because growth outside the US is expected to be at best lackluster, and speculators may already have significant short positions on the dollar. Additionally, before there are signs of economic weakness that are sufficient to worry policymakers, real interest rates adjusted for inflation may still remain high. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Co-Founder: Kanye Could Have Had Global Fans Singing Together for Free Coins, Building a TikTok Competitor Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25591</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Anatoly Yakovenko, a co-founder of Solana, posted and said, &quot;Kanye could have enabled global fans to record videos of &apos;Runaway&apos; and have them spliced into a huge synchronous video with more than 100 million people singing together. This video could then be distributed as media. At the same time, he could have distributed all his tokens for free and used them as the currency of a global TikTok competition platform.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25591</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase to Add USD1 to Asset Listing Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25590</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Coinbase declared the inclusion of World Liberty Financial USD (USD1) in its asset listing plan.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25590</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKB 24-hour Price Surge Widens to 71%, Currently Trading at $226.73</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25589</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on market data, the 24-hour gain of OKB has expanded to 71%. It is currently trading at $226.73 and has hit a new all-time high.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25589</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reborn Coffee Launches Cryptocurrency Payment Pilot</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25588</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the Nasdaq-listed U.S. coffee chain Reborn Coffee announced its intention to conduct pilot cryptocurrency payments at some of its Southern California stores in 2025 and integrate this feature into its existing Point of Sale (POS) platform. Previously, Reborn Coffee had announced the start of a strategic assessment to consider incorporating regulated digital assets into its financial management framework. The company plans to explore blockchain assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum in order to optimize fund management efficiency and achieve the diversification of non-operational capital reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25588</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. initial jobless claims saw the largest three-month increase in three months, while continued claims rose to a high for 2021.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25587</link>
      <description>August 21st. In the US last week, initial jobless claims witnessed the largest rise in nearly three months, suggesting a rising trend in layoffs and further intensifying signs of labor market weakness. The Labor Department stated on Thursday that for the week ending August 16th, seasonally adjusted initial jobless claims increased by 11,000 to 235,000, marking the largest jump since late May. As businesses were dealing with Trump&apos;s protectionist trade policies, the labor market was characterized by &quot;low layoffs and weak hiring.&quot;Earlier this month, the government reported that over the past three months, employment had been increasing by an average of 35,000 jobs per month. The second-quarter domestic demand growth rate had slowed down to the lowest level since the fourth quarter of 2022. The report showed that for the week ending August 9th, continuing jobless claims rose by 30,000 to 1.972 million, reaching the highest level since November 2021. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25587</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether and Circle Executives to Meet with CEO of Major South Korean Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25586</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as per Decrypt, representatives from Tether and Circle are slated to hold meetings with the CEOs of several leading financial groups in South Korea this week. These include CEO Jin Ok-dong of NewHan Financial Group and CEO Ham Young-joo of Hana Financial Group. The meetings will center around the potential distribution and utilization of the US dollar stablecoin within Korea, as well as the issuance of a stablecoin backed by the Korean won. This meeting takes place as South Korea is gearing up to launch a stablecoin regulatory framework in October of this year, with the ruling party and the opposition party holding divergent views on stablecoin regulation.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25586</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>