<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:42:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: Will &quot;Definitely&quot; Know Trump&apos;s Fed Chair Pick in the Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26508</link>
      <description>On August 27, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen stated: We will present 3 to 4 candidates for the position of Federal Reserve Chair to U.S. President Trump. President Trump holds great respect for the Federal Reserve and is currently considering candidates for the Fed Chair, and he will have conversations with them. According to President Trump, the selection of the Fed Chair will &quot;definitely&quot; be made known in the autumn. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pantera-Led New SOL Treasury Company &quot;Solana Co&quot; to Launch Jointly with Li Lin&apos;s Avenir Group and Summer Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26507</link>
      <description>August 27th. As per The Information, a novel SOL treasury firm named &quot;Solana Co&quot; and led by Pantera Capital is set to launch in collaboration with Summer Capital and Avenir Group, which are two strategic Asian partners. Summer Capital, founded in 2017, is one of the earliest licensed financial institutions in Asia engaged in digital asset investments. Avenir Group, founded by Li Lin, is an emerging investment group concentrating on financial innovation and investments in cutting-edge technology and has operations in the United States, the United Kingdom, Japan, Singapore, and Hong Kong.BlockBeats reported yesterday that the cryptocurrency fund Pantera is aiming to raise up to $1.25 billion to convert a public company into a Solana investment company. Galaxy Digital, Multicoin Capital, and Jump Crypto are engaged in discussions with potential investors to raise approximately $1 billion for a substantial SOL acquisition, making it the largest treasury dedicated to this digital</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock and Crypto Stock Pre-market Shows General Decline, BMNR Down 4.3%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26506</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on market data, during the pre-market trading in the US stock market, the AI industry benchmark NVIDIA rose by 0.67%, and it will release its financial report after the market closes today. Cryptocurrency stocks all showed a downward trend, including:Coinbase (COIN) down by 0.09%;Circle (CRCL) down by 0.26%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) down by 0.32%;Bullish (BLSH) down by 0.71%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) down by 1.2%;Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR) down by 4.3%;ETHZilla (ETHZ) down by 0.62%; BTCS (BTCS) down by 0.23%;BNB Network Company (BNC) up by 1.64%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean financial group Mirae Asset has increased its Strategy position, with the current holdings valued at $153 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26505</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to BitcoinTreasuries, the South Korean financial group Mirae Asset, which has a total Assets Under Management (AUM) of $61.4 billion, has raised its holdings in Strategy (MSTR) by 25%. Currently, it holds MSTR shares worth $153 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26505</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over a hundred crypto companies have signed a joint letter requesting the inclusion of DeFi protection provisions in the cryptocurrency market structure bill.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26504</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per cryptocurrency journalist Eleanor Terrett, more than 110 cryptocurrency companies, investors, and advocacy groups have signed a joint letter to caution the leaders of the U.S. Senate Banking and Agriculture Committee. They stated that they will be unable to support the market structure legislation unless it explicitly safeguards open-source software developers and non-custodial service providers. With the backing of heavyweight firms such as Coinbase, a16z crypto, Ripple, top projects, investment firms, and state blockchain committees, the DeFi Education Fund warned that labeling developers who release code or enable non-custodial blockchain access as financial intermediaries could impede U.S. blockchain innovation.The alliance pointed out that according to a recent White House report on digital assets, the proportion of U.S. open-source software developers has witnessed a significant decline, dropping from 25% in 2021 to 18% in 2025. While the alliance commend</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit launches BSU inverse perpetual contract, with up to 20x leverage</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26503</link>
      <description>August 27th. Bybit has initiated the BSU U inverse perpetual contract featuring a leverage of up to 20 times.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: Does Not Believe Nvidia Needs Financial Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26502</link>
      <description>On August 27th, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen said: (When asked if the U.S. government would invest in NVIDIA) I don&apos;t believe NVIDIA requires financial support. It appears that the possibility of the U.S. government investing in NVIDIA is &quot;not being discussed.&quot; (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Powell to Sue Trump for Firing Him as Early as Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26501</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per CNBC, sources disclosed that a Federal Reserve Board member, Lisa Cook, is scheduled to file a lawsuit as early as today (in connection with Trump&apos;s dismissal).BlockBeats reported yesterday that U.S. President Trump signed a document removing the Federal Reserve Board member Cook from office with immediate effect. In the document, Trump stated: &quot;By the authority vested in me by Article II of the U.S. Constitution and the amended 1913 Federal Reserve Act, I hereby dismiss Cook from the Board of the Federal Reserve System. Given Cook&apos;s lack of honesty in financial matters and potential engagement in criminal activities, I cannot have confidence in your integrity. At the very least, these actions demonstrate serious negligence in your financial transactions, raising doubts about your ability and credibility as a financial regulator.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by Binance Spot Trading Listing, DOLO Surges Over 40% Short-term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26500</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on market data, due to its listing on Binance Spot, DOLO witnessed a significant surge of over 40% in a short span. Currently, it is trading at $0.307, which represents a 14% increase from Binance&apos;s announcement.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26500</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list Dolomite (DOLO) Spot Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26499</link>
      <description>August 27th. According to official information, Binance is set to launch DOLO on August 28, 2025, at 0:00 (Beijing Time) and initiate trading pairs with USDT, USDC, BNB, FDUSD, and TRY. DOLO will be marked with a seed tag. Users will be able to commence depositing DOLO on August 27, 2025, at 12:30 (UTC).It is crucial to keep in mind that currently, users can trade DOLO on the Binance Alpha Market. Nevertheless, once spot trading is activated, DOLO will no longer be displayed on the Alpha Market, and its trading volume will not be factored into Alpha Points.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26499</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>