<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:42:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Official Announcement: Sonic (S) Tokenomics Update Notification</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27502</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Binance made an official announcement. As per the approved proposal by Sonic, the total supply of Sonic (S) will be increased from approximately 3.41 billion to around 3.89 billion, with a circulating supply increase of 472 million (a 14.2% increase).It is only when the ETF final protocol is reached that an additional $50 million worth of Sonic (S) will be added to the total supply.The Binance trading page will synchronize the display of a risk warning pop-up and banner.BlockBeats had previously reported that the Sonic Labs community voted in favor of the &quot;U.S. Market Expansion and TradFi Adoption Plan&quot; proposal, which aims to establish Sonic USA LLC to start U.S. operations. Approval was granted for the issuance of tokens for a $50 million ETF quota, a $100 million Nasdaq PIPE development, and 1.5 billion S tokens for Sonic USA.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Strongly Bullish on Bitcoin&apos;s Long-Term Outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27501</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Matrixport announced on its official channel that gold has surpassed the $3400 mark, which is a key resistance level that has been suppressing the price for the past four months. Although the current currency issuance is relatively moderate, this rally still occurred. Forward-looking investors have simultaneously positioned themselves in gold and Bitcoin. While Bitcoin is still in a consolidation stage, its long-term outlook remains firmly bullish. (This analysis was written by independent analyst Markus Thielen.)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Announces PTB Alpha Airdrop Claim Rules</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27500</link>
      <description>September 3rd, according to official channels, Binance Alpha is set to launch the Portal To Bitcoin (PTB).Alpha Trading Commences: September 3, 2025, at 8:00 PM (UTC+8).Contract Trading Opens: September 3, 2025, at 8:30 PM (UTC+8).Qualified users can utilize Alpha Points to claim 1,320 PTB airdropped tokens on the Alpha event page within 24 hours following the start of trading. This Alpha airdrop will be distributed in two stages:Stage 1 (First 18 hours): Users possessing at least 245 Alpha Points are eligible to claim.Stage 2 (Last 6 hours): Users holding at least 220 Alpha Points can participate in the second-phase airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points per hour.It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as relinquishing the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27500</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency CEX and DEX Trading Volumes Hit New Highs Since January</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27499</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on The Block data, the total spot trading volume of cryptocurrency exchanges in August reached $1.86 trillion, which was a 5% increase from July&apos;s $1.77 trillion, making it the most active trading month since January.Binance continues to hold the largest market share. Its spot trading volume rose from $706.1 billion in July to $737.1 billion, reaching a peak that had not been seen since January ($801.1 billion).Furthermore, the trading volume of decentralized exchanges surged to $368.8 billion in August, also hitting a new high since January. Uniswap took the lead with $143 billion, followed closely by PancakeSwap with $58.7 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27499</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEMI surges over 30% in the last 24 hours, now trading at $0.0414.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27498</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to GMGN market data, HEMI saw a significant surge in the early morning. It briefly broke through $0.049 and then pulled back. Currently, it is trading at $0.0414, with a 24-hour increase of 32.8%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27498</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will delist trading pairs including BYBY/FDUSD, THE/FDUSD.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27497</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Binance announced that according to a recent audit, the platform will remove BABY/EUR, BABY/FDUSD, BMT/BNB, and THE/FDUSD from its listing on September 5, 2025, at 11:00 AM Beijing time.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27497</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rate display still indicates a bearish sentiment towards BTC and ETH in the market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27496</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on Coinglass data, the current funding rates of mainstream CEX and DEX show that the market still leans towards being bearish on BTC and ETH. The specific funding rates are presented in the attached image.BlockBeats Note: The funding rate is a fee set by cryptocurrency trading platforms to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price. It is usually applicable to perpetual contracts and is a fund exchange mechanism between long and short traders. The trading platform does not charge this fee. It is used to adjust the cost or gain of traders holding contracts to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the funding rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the funding rate is greater than 0.01%, it indicates a general market bullish sentiment. When the funding rate is less than 0.005%, it indicates a general market bearish sentiment.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「25x Short ETH Whale」 Opens 40x Bitcoin Short, Total Position Value Approaching $30 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27494</link>
      <description>September 3rd. This morning, a whale transferred 3.25 million USDC to Hyperliquid and took a short position in ETH with a leverage of 25x. Subsequently, the same address opened a short position in Bitcoin with a leverage of 40x. The total position values were $12.93 million and $16.6 million respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27494</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese 30-Year Government Bond Yield Rises by 8.5 Basis Points to 3.285%, Reaching a Historic High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27495</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the yield of the 30-year Japanese government bond increased by 8.5 basis points to 3.285%, reaching a record high. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27495</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 Infrastructure Sign Announces Landing in Hong Kong, Will Cooperate with Several Listed Companies in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27493</link>
      <description>September 3rd. The CEO of Web3 infrastructure Sign, Xin Yan, announced today that Sign has established a presence in Hong Kong. It was noted that Sign will collaborate with several listed companies in Hong Kong at this stage to promote the large-scale adoption of various Web3 applications. Meanwhile, Sarah and Jerry will be in charge of building the Hong Kong team.In terms of talent, both technical and business positions are expected to start recruitment soon. On the community operation front, Sign plans to carry out activities in Hong Kong, including &quot;Orange Karaoke&quot; and offline meetups. The official stated that its community application, Orange Dynasty, is accelerating its global expansion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27493</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>