<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:47:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI has been listed on the Hyperliquid pre-sale contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25926</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, WLFI is now featured on the Hyperliquid pre-trading contract panel, and it has a placeholder price of $0.370.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25926</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Based on WLFI at $0.36, a participation price of $0.015 would allow public sale participants to make a 4.8x profit at listing.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25925</link>
      <description>August 23rd. Based on the analysis of crypto KOL AB Kuai.Dong, when looking at WLFI&apos;s pre-market contract, it is currently trading in a sideways manner around $0.36, and the corresponding total market value is $36.4 billion. If, according to the official information, only 20% of the public offering investor shares are unlocked at the opening price of $0.36, the following can be anticipated:· For those who entered at $0.015, the opening will result in a profit of 4.8 times, with a total unrealized gain of 24 times.· For those who entered at $0.05, the opening will bring a profit of 1.44 times, with a total unrealized gain of 7.2 times.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25925</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha New Airdrop Threshold Announced: Minimum 200 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25924</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, Binance announced that users are advised to get prepared to claim the Binance Alpha Airdrop at 20:00 today. Users with at least 200 Binance Alpha points can claim the tokens on a first-come, first-served basis until the airdrop pool is completely distributed or the airdrop event ends. Further details will be made known shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25924</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Cryptocurrency Concept Stocks Drive US Stock IPO Revival, Expected to See a Wave of Listings in the Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25923</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, BiyaPay analysts projected that by the end of the year, dozens of companies might go public in the US, and the total fundraising amount could potentially exceed $15 billion. The US stock market data on the multi-asset trading platform BiyaPay indicates that after the successful listings of the stablecoin issuer Circle and the tech company Figma, the first-day stock price increments of both exceeded 100%, which further spurred more potential IPO companies to expedite their listing processes. Crypto companies like Gemini and Figure are actively accelerating their IPO applications.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25923</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP Market Cap Surpasses Pinduoduo, BlackRock, Xiaomi, and Citigroup</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25922</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on the data of 8marketcap, the market capitalization of XRP ($181.08 billion) exceeded that of Pinduoduo ($180.45 billion), BlackRock ($177.79 billion), Xiaomi ($175.41 billion), and Citigroup ($175.36 billion), temporarily ranking 108th on the global asset market capitalization list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25922</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Staking Armageddon」 is Coming, Over $5.38 Billion ETH Staked has Exited and Moved to a Centralized Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25921</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, as per EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, 111,456 ETH (valued at $538 million) has withdrawn from staking in Eigenlayer over the past 20 hours. Subsequently, it was transferred to Matrixport in the last 3 hours. And in the most recent 1 hour, it was further moved from Matrixport to Binance and OKX.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25921</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: &quot;Macrohard&quot; Project by &quot;Giantsoft&quot; is Real, a Pure AI Software Company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25920</link>
      <description>August 23rd. Musk tweeted yesterday and said, &quot;Join xAI to jointly build a purely AI software company named Macrohard. The name has a bit of a humorous meaning, but the project is completely genuine. In principle, software companies like Microsoft do not produce any physical hardware themselves. Therefore, theoretically, they can be entirely simulated by AI.&quot;In response, Grok under xAI stated, &quot;Macrohard&quot; is a fun project name of xAI (paying tribute to Microsoft). The goal is to establish a fully AI-simulated software company. Since enterprises like Microsoft do not produce any hardware, AI can theoretically replicate their entire operation, ranging from programming to management. &quot;This is true, and we are hiring!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Websea&apos;s Second Anniversary Celebration is about to kick off, with Five Major Welfare Benefits in full swing.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25919</link>
      <description>August 23rd - In celebration of its two-year anniversary, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Websea will launch a themed event from August 26th to September 4th, titled &quot;Two-Year Journey: Borderless Trading, Co-Creating the Web3 Wealth Map.&quot; This celebration encompasses Early Bird Airdrops, Lucky Koi Fish, Social Red Envelopes Rain, Game Interaction, Card Collection Exploration, and other multi-faceted gameplay. Users have the chance to win prizes such as Contract Trial Funds, VIP Experience Cards, iPhone 16, Moutai Liquor, Gold, and other magnificent prizes. The event covers all core sections of the website and is designed to reward users, witnessing together Websea&apos;s growth and breakthroughs over the past two years. Users can participate in the anniversary celebration on the Websea official website.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25919</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shangri-La Group will establish a cryptocurrency strategic reserve, with a priority on BTC, ETH, and USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25918</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, AMTD IDEA Group (「AMTD IDEA Group」), which is dual-listed on the New York Stock Exchange and the Singapore Stock Exchange and is a subsidiary of AMTD Group; AMTD Digital Inc. and The Generation Essentials Group (「TGE」) jointly announced that cryptocurrency will be an essential part of the corporate treasuries of these three companies as a &quot;strategic reserve.&quot;This &quot;strategic reserve&quot; encompasses bank deposits and other uncollateralized, unencumbered, and liquid investments, totaling approximately $240 million as of June 30, 2025. Specifically, the planned cryptocurrency investment portfolio will center around Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and USDT.Among the three NYSE-listed companies under the AMTD Group, TGE will be in charge of expanding and concentrating on cryptocurrency-related opportunities and development. The name TGE has held genetic significance since its inception, representing not only &quot;The Generation Essentials&quot; but also symbolically referring to &quot;Toke</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25918</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: OTC Platforms and Market Makers Show Stronger Demand for ETH than BTC; ETH May Continue to Outperform BTC in the Future</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25917</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, following Federal Reserve Chairman Powell&apos;s dovish signal at the Jackson Hole Economic Symposium, which went against market expectations of a tougher stance, cryptocurrencies witnessed a surge on Friday night. Consequently, asset managers anticipate that Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and certain altcoins will reach new highs.Analysts from Monarq Asset Management project that the price of Ethereum will ascend to above $5,000 in the forthcoming days. Sam Gaer, the Chief Investment Officer of the Monarq Direction Fund, informed CoinDesk, &quot;We maintain an overall bullish outlook. The market&apos;s internal structure remains in good health with little indication of overheating. As you mentioned, the path to new highs for BTC and ETH is quite evident.&quot;Gaer stated that over-the-counter desks and market makers have a greater demand for ETH compared to BTC, suggesting that Ethereum may outperform Bitcoin in the future. Nevertheless, BTC itself is also demonstrating strong impetus</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25917</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>