<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:57:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 39,875 SOL into Bybit, with an unrealized gain of $2.93 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24551</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale transferred 39,875 SOL into Bybit (amounting to approximately $8.9 million), and it had an unrealized gain of $2.93 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Overlay Protocol (OVL) Airdrop Distribution to Resume at 16:45</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24550</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to official information, Binance announced that the distribution of the Overlay Protocol (OVL) token airdrop will resume at 16:45 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected HashKey Capital Address Sells 7300 ETH, Approximately $34.116M</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24548</link>
      <description>August 14th. As per Chainalysis, an address suspected to be HashKey Capital is going to transfer 7300 ETH to Binance for sale, with an average price of $4673. 3 hours prior to this, this address withdrew 34.116 million USDT from Binance.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24548</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay is excited to announce the launch of a promotion where completing a stock transaction will earn you a $50 USDT cash reward.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24549</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per official channels, BiyaPay declared that users are able to deposit funds into BiyaPay by using the same recharge address as that on the original platform. And by completing any stock transaction, they can receive a $50 USDT cash reward.BiyaPay attaches great importance to asset security with multiple risk control measures and fund isolation. It provides a simple process, transparent cash withdrawal, and seamless user migration for secure transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24549</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0xSun: Missed Out on Over Tenfold Potential Gains in WLFI First and Second Round Due to KYC and High Price</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24547</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Smart Money and the crypto KOL 0xsun.sol (@0xSunNFT) posted on social media, indicating that because they did not complete KYC in a timely manner and hesitated about the price, they missed the WLFI first round at $0.015 and the second round at $0.05 for subscription. A short while ago, they suddenly remembered the 1000 KYC accounts they had previously held, thus missing an opportunity for more than tenfold returns.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24547</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle has minted an additional 5.5 billion USDC on the Solana blockchain in the past month.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24546</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Circle minted 5.5 billion USDC on the Solana chain during the past month.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24546</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport is pleased to announce a strategic partnership with The University of Hong Kong&apos;s Institute for Advanced Study in Finance.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24545</link>
      <description>August 14th witnessed Matrixport&apos;s announcement that it has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding with the Institute for Advanced Study at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, formalizing a strategic partnership. The two parties are set to conduct cutting-edge financial research on real-world issues related to digital assets and RWA tokenization, with the aim of promoting the sustainable development of the fintech ecosystem both in Hong Kong and on an international scale.This collaboration between Matrixport and the Institute for Advanced Study at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology represents a significant attempt at cross-disciplinary industry-academia research, which has the potential to set a new industry benchmark for RWA tokenization and infuse new vitality into the continuous innovative development of Hong Kong&apos;s financial center.It is reported that the two parties will utilize XAUm (a physical gold token launched by Matrixport) as the rese</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24545</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway&apos;s Sovereign Wealth Fund Bitcoin Exposure Doubles, Sovereign Funds Ride the Cryptocurrency Wave Becoming a Trend</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24544</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to the data from the cryptocurrency research firm K33 Research, Norway&apos;s sovereign wealth fund, being the world&apos;s largest country-driven fund, witnessed a 192% increase in its indirect Bitcoin exposure last year.The fund holds 7,161 bitcoins indirectly through its portfolio, which encompasses holdings in companies like Strategy, Metaplanet, and the cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase.Norway&apos;s augmented Bitcoin holdings mirror a broader trend: as the world&apos;s first cryptocurrency gradually integrates into the traditional financial system, sovereign wealth funds are obtaining indirect exposure by means of Bitcoin investment tools and corporate agents. In July, Kazakhstan&apos;s sovereign wealth fund announced its plan to convert a portion of its assets into cryptocurrency. (SMM)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Overlay Protocol (OVL) Airdrop Delayed Open for Claim</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24543</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per official channels, Binance has announced that the airdrop of the Overlay Protocol (OVL) token is currently experiencing a delay. It is recommended to stay tuned for further official announcements regarding the specific distribution schedule.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24543</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CME Ethereum Futures Trading Volume Hits Record $118 Billion in July</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24542</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to market sources, the trading volume of CME&apos;s Ethereum futures reached a record high of $118 billion in July, which reignited market enthusiasm.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24542</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>