<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:10:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bluemoon Interactive disclosed that it purchased a total of approximately $7.85 million worth of BTC, ETH, and SOL in the first half of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26849</link>
      <description>August 29th. According to an announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, Bluehole Interactive stated that by June 30, 2025, the main addition to intangible assets during the past six months was the acquisition of cryptocurrency.During the six months ending on June 30th, the Group purchased cryptocurrency, including 62.98 Bitcoins, 330.49 Ethereums, and 6991.7 Solanas, with a total cash outlay of $7.85 million (approximately RMB 56.36 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26849</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PetroChina: closely monitoring the Hong Kong stablecoin, will initiate cross-border settlement feasibility study</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26848</link>
      <description>On August 29th, PetroChina (00857.HK) disclosed at its semi-annual earnings conference that it is closely observing the licensing policy of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority for stablecoins and is planning to launch a feasibility study on using stablecoins for cross-border settlement and payments.As one of China&apos;s largest state-owned energy enterprises, PetroChina has become one of the first traditional energy giants to publicly respond to Hong Kong&apos;s &quot;Stablecoin Regulation.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump: China is &quot;an absolutely terrifying force&quot; in the cryptocurrency space</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26847</link>
      <description>August 29th, Eric Trump, the son of the former U.S. President, during the BITCOIN ASIA 2025 conference, declared: In the cryptocurrency field, although China has effectively prohibited digital token transactions since 2021, it is &quot;an extremely powerful country.&quot;On Friday, at the Bitcoin Asia conference in Hong Kong, when Eric Trump was having a Q&amp;A session with crypto investor David Bailey, he said: &quot;There is no doubt that China is an absolute power in this domain.&quot; He was responding to Bailey&apos;s comparison of China and the United States as the &quot;two superpowers of Bitcoin.&quot; (Bloomberg)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26847</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum Could Drop to Around $4270 to Find Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26846</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to crypto analyst Lennaert Snyder, the next key support level for Ethereum that requires attention is $4270. If Ethereum is able to hold above this level and &quot;confirm&quot; support, then it would be reasonable to consider taking a long position.[If $4,270 is breached, one can consider opening a short position. Deeper liquidity can be found around $3,950, and if a reversal signal occurs, that area is a key support level to watch for a potential long opportunity.]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26846</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Sell the HYPE and Long ETH Whale] Nearly half an hour stop loss resulted in a $1.26 billion liquidation of long positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26845</link>
      <description>August 29th: As per Infura, with the price of ETH getting close to the liquidation price of the [Sell the Hype, Long the ETH Whale] position. In an effort to avoid liquidation, the whale has already sold 28,959 ETH ($126 million) in the market within the past half an hour.After reducing the position, the whale still maintains a long position of 57,800 ETH ($251 million), and the liquidation price has decreased to $4,233.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will suspend Conflux Network (CFX) token deposits and withdrawals on September 1st to support its network upgrade and hard fork.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26844</link>
      <description>Update, August 29: As per an official communication, Binance is anticipated to halt token deposits and withdrawals for the Conflux Network (CFX) on September 1 at 08:03 (UTC+8) in order to support its network upgrade and hard fork. This measure is being taken to offer users a more enhanced experience.The project team is set to carry out the network upgrade and hard fork at block height 129,680,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26844</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoldTech Holdings has completed a HKD 2.65 billion new share placement financing, which will be used to explore Risk-Weighted Assets (RWA) applications and develop new blockchain businesses.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26843</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the Hong Kong-listed company Crystal International Group Limited (02228.HK) successfully completed a new share placement with a pricing of HKD 2.65 billion. The placement price was set at HKD 9.28 per share, which represents a premium of approximately 75.8% compared to the IPO price. According to the announcement, in addition to being used for company operations, product development, and mergers and acquisitions, the funds will also be utilized to explore innovative financial instruments such as Real World Assets (RWA) and Real Data Assets (RDA), and to conduct research and development on new blockchain businesses. (Securities Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL &quot;Price Manipulator&quot; Claims $38 Million Profit Was an &quot;Accident Due to Sleep Deprivation&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26842</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to the tweet screenshot of on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), XPL &quot;price manipulator&quot; @Techno_Revenant once posted that the sudden surge in the XPL price was actually due to an accident caused by lack of sleep. @Techno_Revenant claimed to be a novice in contract trading. This was only his 5th contract operation, but he accidentally made a profit of around 38 million USD. The detailed process is as follows:1. After Hyperliquid launched XPL, he spent more than two days accumulating long positions worth around 30 million USD and gradually scaled in through a strategy of buying $44,000 per order.2. Early on August 27th, he planned to finish his position after adding the final 5 million USD. However, because he was too sleepy, he accidentally increased the order speed by 10 times, changing the order size from $44,000 per order to $444,000 per order.3. Due to the poor depth of HL, the large orders instantly caused a sharp rise in XPL, resulting in more tha</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26842</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Openledger&apos;s inaugural Booster event has started, with a participation threshold of 61 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26841</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to official information, Binance Wallet announced that the first Booster event of Openledger has commenced. This event will distribute a total of 2 million OPEN tokens as airdrop rewards. The participation requirement is that users must possess 61 or more Alpha points.Binance Wallet indicated that the reward tokens for this event have a lock-up period, and the unlock date will be determined by the project team and may not be disclosed in advance. Please understand the relevant restrictions before participating in the event.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26841</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillhouse Capital&apos;s Chairman, Zhang Lei, and YZi Labs&apos; CEO engaged in a Fireside Chat at the BNB Chain Fifth Anniversary Celebration Event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26840</link>
      <description>On August 29th, during the BNB Chain fifth-anniversary celebration event held in Hong Kong, Ella Zhang, the CEO of YZi Labs, and Xu Yanqing, the chairwoman of the board of directors of Huaxing Capital and the wife of Huaxing Capital&apos;s founder Bao Fan, engaged in a fireside chat with the theme &quot;BNB Meets Wall Street, Initiating a New Era of Institutional Adoption.&quot;They delved into topics such as &quot;The Outlook for Institutional Acceleration of Cryptographic Technology,&quot; &quot;BNB Chain&apos;s positioning as the preferred infrastructure for RWA issuance,&quot; and &quot;TradFi × Web3 Integration.&quot;Public information shows that Xu Yanqing currently serves as the chairwoman of the board of directors and executive director of Huaxing Capital Holdings Limited, responsible for group strategic planning, wealth management business, and emerging market expansion. Xu Yanqing is married to Bao Fan. After Bao Fan resigned from all positions at Huaxing Capital in February 2024, Xu Yanqing was transferred from a non-ex</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>