<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:53:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor: We may see multiple interest rate cuts, depending on the data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27552</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Federal Reserve Governor Waller expressed that he thinks a rate cut should be implemented at the upcoming meeting. The yield on the U.S. 10-year Treasury bond has remained at a relatively stable level.We may witness multiple rate cuts, and whether they take place at each meeting or every other meeting will be contingent on how the data progresses. There is no need to adhere to a prearranged sequence of rate cuts.There is a hope to prevent a decline in the labor market. &quot;We are aware that there will be a slight increase in inflation at a certain point, but it will not be persistent and will be closer to the 2% target within six months.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Powell has made this week&apos;s non-farm payroll data especially important; if the labor market data falls short of expectations, it will significantly increase rate cut expectations.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27551</link>
      <description>September 3rd: Antje Praefcke, a foreign exchange analyst at Deutsche Bank, pointed out that during his speech at the Jackson Hole symposium, Powell emphasized the downside risks faced by the economy and employment. This is in order to balance the market&apos;s and the expectations of colleagues on the Federal Open Market Committee regarding interest rate cuts with the inflation risks that tariffs may bring. The focus on current labor market data has exceeded the usual level by a wide margin, and the weight of the impact of this data will also increase significantly.This naturally implies that if the labor market data fails to meet expectations, it may further significantly enhance the market&apos;s expectations of a Fed rate cut and may even rekindle expectations of one or more 50-basis-point rate cuts.If this situation occurs, it is expected that the US dollar will once again encounter a severe setback. If tomorrow&apos;s ADP data is lower than expected (the market consensus is 80,000 people),</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump family&apos;s closely affiliated Bitcoin mining company, American Bitcoin, is set to debut on the Nasdaq with the stock symbol ABTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27550</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as reported by WSJ, American Bitcoin, a Bitcoin mining and reserve company supported by two of President Trump&apos;s sons, is scheduled to be listed on the Nasdaq Stock Exchange this Wednesday after completing a merger with Gryphon Digital Mining.After the merger, Trump&apos;s elder son, Donald Trump Jr., his second son, Eric Trump, and the mining company Hut 8 will jointly own 98% of the shares of the new entity. The new entity will retain the name American Bitcoin and trade under the stock symbol ABTC.American Bitcoin has also recently been seeking acquisition targets in Asia to build a Bitcoin asset reserve. The company has started discussions with investors regarding potential acquisitions and is currently planning to acquire a publicly listed company in Japan. At the same time, it is also considering expanding into the Hong Kong market. Sources familiar with the matter stated that the company intends to replicate the MicroStrategy model by establishing a cryptocurrenc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: If Data Does Not Cooperate, Dollar Upside Momentum May Stall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27549</link>
      <description>September 3rd. The strength of the US dollar yesterday was mainly driven by a global long-term bond sell-off, with no other clear catalysts. Francesco Pesole, a foreign exchange analyst at ING, believes that this driver is not likely to sustain the strength of the dollar ahead of the release of key data and the upcoming rate cut by the Fed.After Trump appointed a new head of the Bureau of Labor Statistics, the focus on non-farm official data may also increase. Pesole stated that the strength of the dollar yesterday lacked strong fundamental support. He expects to see a &quot;momentum retracement&quot; before Friday&apos;s non-farm data, and there are downside risks for the dollar index. If the data does not cooperate, it may be difficult to maintain the upward momentum of the dollar. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27549</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Bank is reintroducing its cryptocurrency custody services for institutional clients, including Bitcoin ETF.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27548</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, U.S. Bank declared that it is going to resume offering cryptocurrency custody services to institutional clients. It plans to expand its product lineup to encompass Bitcoin ETFs. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27548</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Asset Platform Utila Completes $22 Million Financing Round, Led by Red Dot Capital Partners</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27547</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the digital asset operating platform Utila announced the completion of a $22 million financing round. The company stated that its valuation has nearly tripled in the past six months. This funding round was led by Red Dot Capital Partners, with the participation of investors such as Nyca, Wing VC, DCG, and Cerca Partners. The Series A funding, which was from March this year, has been expanded to $40 million.Utila, based in New York and Tel Aviv, provides a digital asset operating platform designed for enterprises using stablecoins. The system can handle functions like payments, fund management, and transactions. It also provides compliance and business continuity support to enterprises. Its clients include payment service providers, neobanks, and asset management companies, reflecting the increasingly prominent role of USD-backed stablecoins in the global financial system.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27547</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Etherealize has completed a $40 million financing round, led by Electric Capital and Paradigm, with participation from Vitalik.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27546</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Ethereum startup Etherealize declared the accomplishment of a $40 million financing round. This financing round was spearheaded by Electric Capital and Paradigm. Ethereum&apos;s co-founder Vitalik Buterin and the non-profit Ethereum Foundation, which is dedicated to Ethereum protocol development, also offered support to Etherealize through an early grant. The financing round adopted the forms of equity and token warrants.In the early days of 2025, Raman, along with Danny Ryan who is a long-time Ethereum developer and researcher, Grant Hummer who is an Ethereum supporter from the traditional finance sector, and Zach Obront who is an Ethereum security engineer, established Etherealize - a name that combines Ethereum and realize.Etherealize aims to persuade Wall Street to explore the crypto field more deeply. The new funds will be used to assist financial institutions in building products and infrastructure on Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27546</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlloyX Group Reaches Merger Agreement with Nasdaq-Listed Huaying Holdings at a $350 Million Valuation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27545</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, AlloyX, a stablecoin infrastructure group concentrating on cross-border payments and institutional asset tokenization, announced today that it has officially reached a merger agreement with Huaying Holding, a Nasdaq-listed company (NASDAQ: SWIN). This merger will make full use of the strengths of both parties in traditional finance and the Web3 ecosystem. They will work together to establish a new financial ecosystem centered around innovative financial payments, promoting the deep integration of traditional finance and digital assets.Before this merger, AlloyX has received recognition from several internationally renowned investment institutions. Leading institutions such as Fenbushi Capital, Longling Capital, Kiln, Arbitrum Foundation, and Offchain Labs have all participated in AlloyX&apos;s latest round of financing, which shows the high recognition of AlloyX&apos;s development prospects in the industry.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27545</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong May Issue First Stablecoin License Early Next Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27544</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Hong Kong Legislative Councilor Wu Jiezhuang recently stated in an interview that the regulation of Hong Kong stablecoins is extremely strict, and a very limited number of licenses have been issued. It is possible that a license may be granted early next year. After obtaining the license, compliance with the legal requirements of the applying country also needs to be met. In addition, the Hong Kong Legislative Council will also expedite the legislative process for offline over-the-counter transactions next year.Wu Jiezhuang mentioned that data assets are already a major trend, and many countries and companies include digital assets such as Bitcoin in their reserves. If you act too slowly, the cost of catching up in the competition will only increase. Finally, Councilor Wu stated that Hong Kong has no foreign exchange controls, very low taxes, and is backed by a gateway to a country with 1.4 billion people. It will further connect to the &quot;Belt and Road Initiative.&quot; B</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL Whale Nets $38 Million Profit, Holds Over $3.6 Million Unrealized Loss on XPL Long Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27543</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on the monitoring of @EmberCN, Techno Revenant, who manipulated the XPL settlement to make a profit of 38 million USD, continued to take a long position on XPL with 1x leverage through more than 15 addresses. At one point, it occupied 70% of the long positions of XPL on Hyperliquid.With the recent pullback in the XPL price, his XPL long position, currently worth 26 million USD (37.17 million XPL), has changed from an unrealized gain of 10 million USD a few days ago to an unrealized loss of 3.67 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27543</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>