<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:46:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Within one week of the implementation of the Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation, the size of the local OTC trading market has decreased by approximately 32.94%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24188</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as per Bitrace&apos;s monitoring, within a week after the implementation of the Hong Kong stablecoin regulations, the local OTC market size has witnessed a reduction of approximately 32.94%. The daily average USDT transfer volume of the business addresses of storefront service providers has dropped by 43.20% (from 9.47 million to 5.38 million), while that of the business addresses of non-storefront service providers has decreased by 30.65% (from 42.57 million to 29.52 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24188</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena is the sixth DeFi protocol to surpass $10 billion TVL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24187</link>
      <description>On August 12th, 21.co&apos;s Strategy Analyst, Tom Wan, posted on social media stating, &quot;Ethena has emerged as the sixth DeFi protocol to surpass a TVL of $10 billion, and it is the second non-staking DeFi protocol to achieve this milestone following Aave.&quot;According to Dune data, Ethena&apos;s current TVL has attained $11.893 billion, with an sUSDe APY of 4.72%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24187</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presto Research Director: Ethereum is Ready to Win Wall Street&apos;s Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24186</link>
      <description>On August 12th, with the second-largest cryptocurrency ETH surging to its highest level in nearly four years, the U.S. Ethereum spot ETF witnessed its largest single-day inflow of funds. The data indicates that on Monday, the Ethereum spot ETF attracted a total inflow of slightly more than $1 billion. So far this year, the total inflow of these 9 funds has exceeded $8.2 billion.It turns out that the focus of &quot;treasury companies&quot; on ETH is an important driving force behind the token&apos;s rise. These listed companies are continuously expanding their digital asset reserves. According to the data compiled by Strategic EthReserve.xyz, the so-called &quot;digital asset treasury companies&quot; have absorbed more than $15 billion worth of ETH so far. Peter, the research director at the quant trading firm Presto, said: &quot;Recent stablecoin legislation and the cryptocurrency roadmap outlined by the Chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission both suggest that the Ethereum blockchain behind Ether</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24186</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fosun International&apos;s Response to Stablecoin License Application: No Comment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24185</link>
      <description>On August 12th, market news indicated that Fosun has confirmed its application for a stablecoin license in Hong Kong and has already set up a complete stablecoin license application team. In response to the above news, Fosun stated that they have &quot;no comment&quot; at this moment.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24185</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market ETH Strategy Stocks Surge in Pre-market Trading, Bitmine Up Over 7%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24184</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to the market data of Rockflow, there was a general rise in the pre-market trading of US ETH strategy stocks. These include:· Bitmine increased by 7.29%;· Sharplink Gaming rose by 3.87%;· BTCS went up by 3.4%;· Circle went up by 1.04%;· Coinbase rose by 0.74%;· Strategy rose by 0.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Launches World3 (WAI)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24183</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Binance Alpha launched World3 (WAI).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24183</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: CPI Bi-directional Risk on the Table, BTC in Range within High-Density Supply Zone — Risk Management and Phased Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24182</link>
      <description>August 12th: The market generally anticipated that the July CPI would rise by +0.2% month-on-month and by 2.8% year-on-year. The core CPI was expected to increase by +0.3% month-on-month and by 3.0% year-on-year. Regardless of whether the data is &quot;hot&quot; or &quot;cold&quot;, it could trigger a market reaction in different directions but with equally strong volatility, posing a two-way risk to stocks, forex, bonds, and other risk assets in the short term.Bitunix Analyst Suggestion:For BTC, the range of 120k–123k is a zone with significantly high density of supply and concentrated selling pressure above. The levels of 116k and 112k below act as secondary supports. Without a volume breakout above the supply zone, it is likely to encounter rejection and fall back. In the case of colder-than-expected data (favorable to rate cuts), it is necessary to observe the trend of the US dollar and US Treasuries. If BTC witnesses a daily volume surge and breaks through the supply zone, it is expected to open u</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24182</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale AguilaTrades ETH Long/Short, current position value $33.58M in ETH Long position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24181</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, contract transaction whale AguilaTrades. After suffering consecutive losses of 3 short ETH positions through stop-loss, with a total loss of $3.65 million, it has now switched from short to long. Starting 20 minutes ago, it took a long position on ETH with 15 times leverage. Currently, it holds 7700 ETH with a value of $33.58 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24181</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin&apos;s upward momentum has started to slow down, cautioning the emergence of a potential double top pattern</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24180</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Coindesk analyst Omkar Godbole stated that the upward momentum of Bitcoin has decelerated, raising the likelihood of a bearish technical pattern called a double top. When looking at the daily chart, the bulls on Monday were unable to maintain a breakthrough above the key Fibonacci level of $122,056. This pattern closely resembles the situation on July 14th. Two instances of failing to hold above a key price point with short pullbacks in between are typical features of a &quot;double top&quot; formation. The neck line of this formation is the lowest point reached during the brief pullback at $111,982, which is a crucial support level to monitor.If the price decisively drops below this neck line level, it will confirm the breakdown of the double top formation, potentially triggering selling pressure down to $100,000. The resistance levels are $120,000, $122,056, and $123,181. The support levels are $114,295, $111,982, and $100,000.As the market enters the period of today&apos;s CPI</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24180</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the listing of the Upbit Korean won trading pair, CYBER experiences a temporary surge of over 178%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24179</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to HTX market data, affected by the listing on Upbit&apos;s Korean Won and USDT trading pairs, CYBER saw a brief surge of over 178% and is now priced at $5.12.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24179</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>