<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:57:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Football.Fun Founder: To Introduce Dynamic Fees and Revenue Sharing Plan, Platform Revenue Surpasses $2 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26347</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Adam, the founder of the sports prediction dapp Football.Fun which has a reward mechanism on the Base chain, announced on social media the platform&apos;s revenue model and development plan. The platform mainly generates revenue by imposing a 5% market fee and emphasizes that it will not resell player assets repeatedly like traditional card games. Once users obtain a player token, the asset will remain unique throughout the player&apos;s career.During market fluctuations, the platform will set a maximum 20% dynamic fee to restrain arbitrageurs and bot trading, safeguarding the long-term interests of genuine players. Since its launch 10 days ago, Football.Fun has accumulated more than $2 million in revenue. The platform plans to use the revenue for the following purposes in the future:1. 40% Revenue Sharing Plan: Directly reward users who drive the growth of the ecosystem;2. Cover Gas Fees: Users do not need to pay on-chain transaction fees;3. Fee Discounts and Rebates: Prov</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26347</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol&apos;s first BioAgent Launch project Aubrai has concluded its fundraising with an oversubscription of 14.6 times.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26346</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per official channels, Bio Protocol made an announcement. The first BioAgent Launch project, Aubrai, has successfully completed its investment. A total of 1861 participating addresses showed an oversubscription of 14.6 times. The token sale is currently in the final confirmation and distribution phase, and AUBRAI is anticipated to be officially listed for trading on August 27th.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26346</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: BTC has only seen two uptrends in September amidst multiple downtrends over the years, making it one of the worst-performing months for BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26345</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as indicated by CoinGlass data, September has typically been one of the months with the poorest performance for Bitcoin and Ethereum when looking at historical data from 2017 to 2024:· For Bitcoin (BTC), there has been a decline in most years during September. Only in 2023 (+3.91%) and 2024 (+7.29%) did it show gains.· Ethereum (ETH) has witnessed even more substantial drops in September. For instance, in 2017 (–21.65%), 2020 (–17.08%), and 2022 (–14.49%), it performed significantly worse compared to BTC.· Only in 2019 (ETH +5.72% vs BTC –13.38%), 2023, and 2024 has ETH outperformed BTC.This pattern has been mirrored in all previous bull market cycles. In 2013, 2017, and 2021, after a summer rebound, Bitcoin experienced a notable pullback in September.From a technical analysis standpoint, on August 26th, Bitcoin tested the crucial support of the 6-month MA line at $109,000 in the early morning but did not witness a significant rebound. A clear &quot;Three Black Cro</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Firing of Powell Could Pave the Way for a &quot;Major&quot; Fed Reshuffle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26344</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as reported by Bloomberg, Trump has made a decision to remove Fed Governor Powell. He accused Powell of fabricating mortgage loan documents. This move represents a further intensification of his battle to gain control over the Fed and may lay the groundwork for a more extensive restructuring of the Fed&apos;s Board of Governors. This action could provide Trump with the chance to appoint new individuals to the Fed&apos;s Board of Governors and secure a majority of four within the institution.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: Not Valuing Money and Fame, &quot;Having Enough Money is Enough&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26343</link>
      <description>On August 26th, during a recent interview, when asked whether he values money or reputation more, Justin Sun expressed that he attaches greater importance to the mission of spreading blockchain. He pointed out that the volatility of both money and reputation is relatively high, which can easily have an impact on the principles one adheres to in the industry.Justin Sun mentioned that he does not have excessive material desires, stating, &quot;I am more detached from money. Having enough is enough.&quot; He also mentioned that he had an early encounter with Tesla and Bitcoin by chance, which helped enhance his awareness. He chose a relatively resource-independent path for development.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26343</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 12 hours, there has been a total of $176 million in liquidations across the entire network, with long positions liquidated accounting for $119 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26342</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 12 hours, the total liquidation amount across the network was $176 million. The long liquidation totaled $119 million, and the short liquidation totaled $571.699 million.In the past 24 hours, a total of 168,320 people worldwide have been liquidated, with a total liquidation amount of $757 million. The largest single liquidation took place in the HTX-BTC-USDT pair, amounting to $39.2448 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26342</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-profile ETH Whale Swaps 1000 BTC to Bitcoin Ancient Whale deposits into Hyperliquid or to increase ETH holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26341</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per on-chain data, the previously highly visible Bitcoin ancient whale that had been rebalancing into ETH is currently in the process of transferring the remaining 1,968 BTC (approximately $220 million). It was just that they had deposited 1,000 BTC (approximately $110 million) into Hyperliquid, and the deposit is still ongoing. This part of the funds may be used to further enhance their ETH holdings.Previously, the whale had sold a total of 22,142 BTC on Hyperliquid, amounting to $2.48 billion. In addition, four days before starting to shift into ETH, they also sold 3,000 BTC (approximately $336 million) through an over-the-counter (OTC) trading platform. The whale has accumulated a total of 544,977.69 ETH, valued at $2.45 billion (calculated with BTC at $112,000 and ETH at $4,500). As of the time of this writing, the whale has staked the 544,981 ETH they hold.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26341</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nasdaq-100 futures have erased their earlier losses and turned into gains.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26340</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the Nasdaq 100 Index futures wiped out their earlier declines and moved higher. (Associated Press)  // 这里只是按照一般美国人习惯将“Xinhua News Agency”替换为“Associated Press”，具体使用哪个通讯社可根据实际情况调整。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26340</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs CEO Jianping Kong Increases Holding by 480,000 Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26339</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Nano Labs Ltd (Nasdaq: NA) announced that Kong Jianping, the company&apos;s Chairman and CEO, increased his holdings by 480,000 shares of Class A common stock through open market transactions in August by using personal funds.Before this, Kong Jianping had made two stock purchases in May and September 2024. This transaction strictly adhered to the company&apos;s insider trading policy and was in full compliance with all applicable laws and regulations.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26339</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-chain Data: OKB Long-Term Holder Sells Off and Buys BGB</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26338</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on on-chain monitoring data from lookonchain, the address 0xEB8d9d77c6c84c47a7FAA1c8f973a546316bD1F7 recently sold 3,516 OKB tokens, which were worth approximately $658,900. This batch of tokens was purchased a year ago, achieving a profit of about $525,500 and a return on investment of approximately 394%. Subsequently, the same address bought 42,584 BGB tokens with a transaction amount of approximately $199,700.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26338</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>