<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:44:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Wormhole Foundation Engages in Competition with LayerZero to Acquire Stargate Cross-Chain Bridge, Planning to Submit a Tender Offer Exceeding $110 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25418</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the Wormhole Foundation made a statement, indicating that the LayerZero Foundation had previously proposed to acquire the Stargate cross-chain bridge and its STG token for $110 million. The Wormhole Foundation thought that the offer was too low and failed to recognize the strong growth of Stargate. The Wormhole Foundation is preparing to submit a higher bid and has asked for a pause of the ongoing snapshot vote for 5 working days.Previously, on August 11th, the LayerZero Foundation proposed to acquire the Stargate cross-chain bridge and its STG token for $110 million. According to the terms of the proposal, the STG token will be phased out, and STG holders can swap their tokens for LayerZero&apos;s native token ZRO at an exchange rate of 1 STG to 0.08634 ZRO, which is equivalent to a value of $0.1675 per STG and $1.94 per ZRO.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25418</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKB Surges Past $160 to Hit All-Time High, 24-hour Gain Expands to 30%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25417</link>
      <description>August 21st. Based on HTX market data, OKB has exceeded $160, witnessing a 30% increase within the past 24 hours and breaking through last week&apos;s all-time high of $142.85.On August 13th, OKX announced that it would conduct a one-time burn of 65,256,712.097 OKB from historical buybacks and reserves. This would be achieved through a smart contract, which automatically burns all transferred OKB to a black hole address. The total supply of OKB remains fixed at 21 million tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25417</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rekt Drinks collaborates with Base to launch a limited edition &quot;Based Lime&quot; flavored sparkling water, which sold out within 1 minute.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25416</link>
      <description>August 21st. Rekt Drinks&apos; limited edition &quot;Based Lime&quot; flavored sparkling water, which was launched in collaboration with Base, started its pre-sale at 12:00 a.m. tonight and was sold out in just 1 minute. A total of 833 cases were sold worldwide, with each case containing 24 cans. Cryptocurrency payment was accepted, and each case was priced at $69.69 plus shipping.Rekt Drinks is an innovative brand project that integrates Web3 technology with physical consumer goods. It originated from the Rektguy NFT project on the Ethereum blockchain. In 2023, the Rekt team introduced Rekt Drinks, a non-alcoholic and caffeine-free flavored sparkling water. Their flagship product, &quot;Liquidated Lime,&quot; has sold more than 600,000 cans worldwide and is available in 32 countries. In June 2025, Rekt Drinks entered some 7-Eleven stores in Southern California, marking its first move from online to offline retail.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Co-founder Donates $21 Million Worth of Bitcoin to Support U.S. Crypto Legislation Drive</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25415</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the Winklevoss brothers, who are the co-founders of the U.S. cryptocurrency exchange Gemini, announced that they have donated Bitcoin worth $21 million, approximately 188.4547 BTC, to the Digital Freedom Fund Political Action Committee (PAC). The Winklevoss brothers stated that since Trump took office, not only has he fulfilled the promises made during the election but has also exceeded expectations. They hope that this unprecedented progress and momentum can continue to support President Trump and his administration in leading the United States into a golden age.The Digital Freedom Fund will focus on the following:Winning the midterm elections by identifying and supporting candidates in the primaries and midterm elections who advocate for President Trump&apos;s cryptocurrency agenda;Advocating for well-thought-out market structure legislation that enhances the freedom for the cryptocurrency industry to thrive and avoids excessive regulation and cumbersome licensing re</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25415</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC has opened an account on the social media platform Truth Social</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25414</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the Chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Paul Atkins, stated that the SEC has established an account on Truth Social, a social media platform founded by former President Donald Trump.Trump announced the establishment of the social platform Truth Social in October 2021. It was developed by the Trump Media &amp; Technology Group in an attempt to challenge mainstream social media platforms like Facebook and Twitter, which had banned Trump.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25414</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Leveraged Long on ETH Liquidation」 Whale&apos;s Position Closed in Just 26 Minutes, Earning $100,000 Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25413</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, the &quot;Long ETH with $125k Liquidation&quot; whale opened a 25x leveraged long position for 3694 ETH this evening. The value of this position is $15.75 million, with an entry price of $4272 and a liquidation price of $4183.This position was held for only 26 minutes this time. It earned a profit of $100k and was immediately closed. The whale withdrew all funds from Hyperliquid and deposited them into Aave or temporarily suspended operations.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25413</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks.Live: Market Divided on Whether to Enter Bear Market, Overall Sentiment Still Leans Bearish on Short-Term Trend</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25412</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Greeks.Live released the daily market brief, suggesting that the overall market sentiment still tends towards short-term bearish trends. The majority of traders are concentrating on the support range between $110,000 and $108,000, and they believe that this low level may be reached. There is a divergence in the market regarding whether we are entering a bear market. Some community members think that if the price continues to decline next Monday, it will confirm the arrival of a bear market.Mid-September to October is regarded as a potential rebound period. It is expected that a rate cut policy could lead to a market turnaround. From a technical perspective, the BTC weekly MACD is facing the risk of a bearish crossover, similar to the market situation in December last year. The expected adjustment period is around one month.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25412</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intraday Rebound of the Three Major U.S. Stock Indexes, Dow Turns Positive</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25411</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on market data, the three major U.S. stock indexes rebounded during the trading day. The Dow turned positive, and the decline of the Nasdaq narrowed to approximately 1.2%. Previously, it had fallen by nearly 2%. The S&amp;P 500 index is currently down by around 0.5%, having previously dropped by more than 1%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25411</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Recent Pullback Aligns with Bull Market Characteristics, Bitcoin Liquidity Concentrated Around $120,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25410</link>
      <description>August 20th. Analysts have stated that the price trend of Bitcoin is increasingly resembling the outcome of intentional manipulation. BTC touched its lowest level since August 3rd due to continuous selling pressure from the United States. As the US stock market opened today, Bitcoin fell below $113,000 and failed to maintain the support level. The buying liquidity on trading platforms is being depleted, and $112,300 has now become a level worthy of attention.Well-known trader Daan Crypto Trades summarized the current Bitcoin liquidity situation, indicating that BTC has cleared a substantial amount of liquidity from both the long and short sides within the past 6 weeks. Currently, the closest large liquidity is concentrated around $120,000, but the local low point at $112,000 remains effective and often turns into a local reversal area.Renowned trader and analyst Rekt Capital issued a bullish signal by comparing the current price trend to previous bull market pullbacks. &quot;The most bu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25410</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Surges Above $4300, With a 24-hour Gain of 2.17%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25409</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum experienced a rebound and broke through $4300, registering a 24-hour gain of 2.17%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25409</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>