<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Tide Investment announces a $10 million Web3.0 and Virtual Asset Investment Plan, with ETH as the key investment focus</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22154</link>
      <description>July 28th. Jin Yung Investment declared that the company has authorized a total budget of $10 million for the development of the group&apos;s third-generation Internet (Web3.0) business and the investment in virtual assets, especially Ethereum. (ChainNews)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22154</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company 3E Network Technology Group is planning to purchase BTC to establish a crypto reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22155</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the report in businessinsider, enterprise information technology solutions provider 3E Network Technology Group Limited (NASDAQ: MASK) announced today that it has successfully completed the first batch of deliveries for three previously disclosed private placements scheduled for June 9, 2025. The company intends to use a portion of the proceeds to purchase Bitcoin. This strategic action is aimed at building the company&apos;s cryptocurrency reserves to support its development plans in the Web3.0 era.This issuance consists of three tranches of private placements to institutional investors, with a total principal amount of up to $7.4 million in senior secured convertible notes along with accompanying warrants. The principal amount of the first batch of notes is $2.2 million, and the related warrants are issued in two tranches, with the delivery completed on July 8, 2025.It is reported that 3E Network Technology Group Limited is an enterprise information technol</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22155</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Watch: Market Rebound, Some Whales Reduce their Contract Positions but Remain in Unrealized Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22156</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the monitoring of HyperInsight, with the pause of the retracement market, the coin price rebounded. There were changes in the Hyperliquid contract holdings of several whales, mainly reducing short positions. These include:A whale with an address beginning with 0x880ac increased its ETH short position by 88 coins. Currently, it has a floating loss of approximately $21.82 million, and the current liquidation price is $4,928.885.A whale with an address starting with 0x5d2f44 reduced its BTC short position amount by $811,773.16. Currently, it has a floating loss of approximately $12.26 million, and the current liquidation price is $125,235.714.The whale with the address starting with 0x7fdafd opened a new AVAX short position of 187,238.61 coins. Currently, it has a P&amp;L of -$944,159.91, and the liquidation price is about $145.A whale with an address starting with 0x4a207d reduced its BTC long positi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22156</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Biopharmaceutical Company Liminatus Pharma Plans to Raise $500 Million to Invest in BNB</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22153</link>
      <description>July 28th. As per a report from businessinsider, the clinical-stage biopharmaceutical company Liminatus Pharma, Inc. (NASDAQ: LIMN) announced today that it has planned to strategically expand into the cryptocurrency and blockchain domain.The company intends to set up a subsidiary named &quot;American BNB Strategy&quot; to take the lead in its digital asset investment and management scheme. By means of this platform, Liminatus plans to gradually raise and allocate up to $500 million in funds, with the aim of making strategic long-term investments in BNB.Liminatus stressed that although the company remains fully dedicated to its core business - advancing cancer treatments and pancreatic cancer diagnostic technologies, expanding into the digital asset space is regarded as a necessary measure to support long-term growth and enhance shareholder value.Liminatus is a clinical-stage biopharmaceutical company that focuses on developing immunotherapies for cancer patients. The company is progressing</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22153</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DePIN Project Starpower will take an airdrop snapshot on August 4th at 8:00 AM.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22152</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the Decentralized Power Infrastructure Network (DePIN) project Starpower announced on social media that its airdrop snapshot will be carried out on August 4th at 08:00 (Beijing time).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese nail art chain Convano has announced another round of funding of 1.5 billion yen to increase its BTC holdings.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22151</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per market information, the Japanese nail salon chain operator Convano Co., Ltd. acquired approximately 80 bitcoins during the previous week. Additionally, it recently announced another round of financing amounting to 1.5 billion yen (approximately $10.1 million), and the funds will be utilized to enhance its holdings of bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22151</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch GAIA (GAIA) on July 30th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22150</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per official channels, Binance Alpha is set to list GAIA (GAIA) on July 30th. Qualified users can utilize Alpha Points on the Alpha event page to claim the airdrop, which can be claimed once trading commences. Further details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22150</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Whale Addresses withdrew a total of approximately 123,000 SOL from CEXs within a day</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22149</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, 4 whale addresses collectively withdrew approximately 123,269 SOL from CEX within a day. These include:路 The address 7VbjYZ withdrew 58,700 SOL from Binance 16 hours ago (with a value of $11 million).路 The address BnwZvG withdrew 38,000 SOL from Binance in the past 5 hours (with a value of $7.3 million).路 The address 2AbHLS withdrew 14,569 SOL from Binance 2 hours ago (with a value of $2.8 million).路 The address KMhcqN withdrew 12,000 SOL from Kraken 14 hours ago (with a value of $2.25 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22149</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTCS announced that it has increased its holding of 14,240 ETH, surpassing a total of 70,000 ETH held.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22148</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per official information, BTCS Inc. made an announcement regarding an increase in its holdings by 14,240 ETH, raising its total holdings to 70,028 ETH. Given an Ethereum price of $3,850, the current holdings are valued at around $270 million.Furthermore, the official statement pointed out that BTCS has successfully completed a $10 million convertible note offering. The conversion price for this financing is $13 per share, which represents a 198% premium over BTCS&apos;s closing price on July 18, 2025.Influenced by this news, the pre-market trading of BTCS in the US stock market witnessed an extended increase of 10.24%, with a pre-market price of $5.6.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22148</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the Purchase of 14,000 ETH, BTCS Pre-market Gain Expanded to 10.24%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22147</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on Rockflow data, likely influenced by the news of acquiring an extra 14,000 ETH, the pre-market gain of BTCS expanded to 10.24%, with a pre-market price of $5.60.Previously, BTCS Inc. announced the acquisition of 14,240 ETH, raising its total holdings to 70,028 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22147</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>