<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CoinUp.io&apos;s platform token CP surpasses $1, marking a more than 34x increase from the opening price</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22225</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on market data, the native token CP of the crypto exchange platform CoinUp.io has exceeded $1. It is currently priced at $1.02, showing a more than 34-fold increase from the opening price. Since its launch on the 12th, the price has surged by up to 240%, and the total market capitalization has exceeded $1 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22225</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launchpool will launch Gaia (GAIA), with 3.85 million GAIA unlocked from locked BGB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22224</link>
      <description>July 29th. The Bitget Launchpool is about to launch the Gaia (GAIA) project. There is a total reward pool of 3,858,300 GAIA. The lock-up channel will be open from July 30th at 17:00 to August 1st at 17:00 (UTC+8). The details are as follows:BGB Lock-up PoolAirdrop Total Supply: 3,858,300 GAIAVIP User Lock-up Limit: 50,000 BGBRegular User Lock-up Limit: 5,000 BGBIn addition, the GAIA spot trading channel will open on July 30th at 17:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ark Invest increased its holdings in BMNR by over $20 million yesterday, and sold its shares in COIN and HOOD.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22223</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to Ark Invest Daily, yesterday Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest added to its holdings of BMNR (Bitmine Immersion) stock by $20.8 million. Meanwhile, it sold $12.62 million worth of HOOD (Robinhood Markets) stock and $6.9 million worth of COIN (Coinbase Global) stock.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22223</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain user suffered a loss of 4.35 BTC due to using an e-commerce platform to purchase a counterfeit hardware wallet.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22222</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Tu Xin, the founder of SlowMist, disclosed a new case in a post. He stated, &quot;Another individual purchased a so-called imToken secure cold hardware wallet on JD.com. The wallet was pre-initialized by a scammer, which means the scammer had control over the mnemonic phrase. The user directly used this mnemonic phrase as their own wallet, resulting in 4.35 BTC being stolen, equivalent to losing millions of RMB.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22222</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Galaxy Digital once again mass sells Bitcoin, transferring out 3,782 BTC in the past 12 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22221</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to the monitoring of Lookonchain, the Galaxy Digital address has once again dispatched 3,782 BTC (approximately $447 million) within the past 12 hours. The majority of it has flowed into a trading platform.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22221</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed&apos;s Soundbites」: The Fed is not ready to cut rates this week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22220</link>
      <description>On July 29th, in an article titled &quot;Fed Whisperer&quot;, Nick Timiraos stated that Federal Reserve officials anticipate that they will eventually have to continue reducing interest rates. However, they were not prepared to do so on Wednesday. The division among them lies in what evidence they need to observe first and whether waiting for clarity is a misstep.Officials are currently divided into three camps regarding the question of whether to resume rate cuts. The focus will be on whether Powell will offer any hints of a September rate cut during the press conference and whether his colleagues will begin laying the groundwork for a rate cut at the next meeting in the coming days and weeks. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22220</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new &quot;BNB Version of Masternode&quot; VAPE closed this morning at $57.585, with a trading volume surpassing $900 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22219</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to RockFlow market data, the newly launched &quot;BNB Version Micro Strategy&quot; American stock CEA Industries (VAPE) closed this morning at $57.585, showing a gain of 548.85% and a trading volume of $9.1 billion. After the market closed, VAPE fell by 5.62%, and the stock price dropped to $54.350.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22219</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC: Market No Longer Focused on EU-US Trade Agreement, Urgently Needs Another New Catalyst</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22218</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per CNBC, the European and American stock markets responded rather lacklusterly to the transatlantic trade agreement that was reached over the weekend. The S&amp;P 500 index inched up slightly, but the increase was almost negligible; meanwhile, the STOXX Europe 600 index declined. Both indices witnessed temporary surges during their respective trading sessions but gave back most of those gains towards the close.On the European continent, there may be a dawning realization that this agreement might not actually be advantageous for them. German Chancellor Friedrich Merz and French Minister for European Affairs Benjamin Addad expressed hopes for more open trade. Simultaneously, U.S. President Trump announced on Monday that he is &quot;very likely&quot; to impose a uniform tariff ranging from 15% to 20% on countries that have not signed a trade agreement with the United States. This indicates that most tariffs in the future are likely to stabilize at this level, which helps to allevia</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22218</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary CS:GO player s1mple joins BC.GAME ESPORTS</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22217</link>
      <description>July 29th. The cryptocurrency entertainment platform BC.GAME declared that the legendary CS2 player s1mple has officially become a part of its esports team, BC.GAME ESPORTS. This marks the first instance where a top esports player has been deeply integrated with a Web3 platform and is regarded as a significant step in the crypto esports realm.BC.GAME is a Web3 entertainment platform that combines encrypted payments with on-chain gaming experiences. It has issued its native token BC and launched multiple chain games that ensure verifiable fairness. On July 18th, the BC token just reached an all-time high, and the popularity of the ecosystem continues to grow.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22217</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address received an additional 12,749 ETH from FalconX, pushing the total holdings beyond 80,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22216</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as monitored by OnchainLens, following three days of silence, this newly established wallet received 12,749 ETH from FalconX, amounting to approximately $49.25 million.Currently, the wallet holds a total of 80,174 ETH, with a total value of approximately $302.72 million. The wallet address is 0x286f3e05f18a515f8F461f2DBEb0f4abe482aEa4.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>