<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:54:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Soluna has secured a $20 million investment from Spring Lane Capital to launch the Kati 1 project construction.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21368</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, as reported by businesswire, the data center developer Soluna Holdings, Inc. (Nasdaq: SLNH) declared today that it has successfully completed its latest round of financing. The funding was provided by Spring Lane Capital (SLC) to facilitate the expansion of its Kati project in Texas to 35 megawatts, thereby officially commencing the Kati 1 project.With this financial support, Soluna intends to initiate the construction of the Kati 1 project in the third quarter of 2025 and aims to achieve the initial power-on and gradually commence production by the first quarter of 2026. The new facility is engineered to accommodate approximately 12,000 next-generation Bitcoin mining machines.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell did not comment on the economic or monetary policy outlook in his speech.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21366</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell indicated that the Fed is a dynamic institution that is inclined to listen to new ideas and feedback regarding how to enhance the large bank capital framework.Powell did not offer any remarks on the economic or monetary policy outlook during his speech. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21366</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARK Invest Acquires $182 Million in BMNR Common Stock, Boosting Ethereum Treasury Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21367</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, as per PR Newswire, BitMine declared today that ARK Invest has purchased 4,773,444 shares of BitMine common stock BMNR, and the total value amounts to 182 million US dollars. BitMine intends to utilize all net proceeds (approximately 177 million US dollars) to acquire Ethereum (ETH).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21367</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic has announced that the first phase of the S Token airdrop claiming is now open</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21365</link>
      <description>July 22nd. According to official channels, Sonic has made an announcement that the first phase of the S Token airdrop claiming has now commenced. The Paintswap team has put out the &quot;Airdrop Order Book&quot; airdrop order, enabling users to claim, trade, and unlock a total of 1.9 billion S Tokens in airdrop rewards.Users are able to claim 25% of the airdrop directly into their wallets, while the remaining 75% will be minted into fNFT and unlocked linearly over a period of 270 days. The airdrop must be claimed within 180 days; otherwise, it will expire and be destroyed.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21365</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Customs Busts $1.15 Billion Money Laundering Case Involving Virtual Asset Trading and Cash Smuggling</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21364</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, according to the report in &quot;Sing Tao Daily&quot;, Hong Kong Customs today uncovered a suspected money laundering case involving the smuggling of cash and virtual assets. The amount involved is approximately 1.15 billion Hong Kong dollars, and one local male and one non-local male were arrested.Earlier, based on intelligence, Customs targeted a 37-year-old local male and a 50-year-old non-local male and initiated a financial investigation. It was found that the two individuals were suspected of illegally smuggling cash out of the country and rapidly conducting large transactions between stablecoins and fiat currencies. The funding sources were unclear and did not match their backgrounds, indicating potential money laundering activities.After an in-depth investigation, Customs conducted a surprise search this morning on 4 residential units and 2 companies and arrested the two individuals under the &quot;Organized and Serious Crimes Ordinance&quot; on charges of &quot;dealing with property</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21364</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink Gaming invested $258 million last week to acquire an additional 79,949 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21363</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, SharpLink Gaming enhanced its holdings last week by 258 million dollars to obtain 79,949 ETH at an average price of 3,238 dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21363</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: No Sign Powell Should Resign at This Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21362</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, US Treasury Secretary Yellen stated that there is no evidence suggesting that Powell should resign at present. If he wishes to resign prematurely, he is at liberty to do so. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21362</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary: Calls for an Internal Review of the Federal Reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21361</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen stated that she had called for an internal review of the Fed. Such a review may potentially become one of Powell&apos;s institutional heritages. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21361</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs conducts an OTC buyback of 45,684 BNB, approximately 34.9 million US dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21360</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, according to GlobeNewswire, the U.S.-listed company Nano Labs Ltd (Nasdaq: NA) announced today that its holdings of BNB have witnessed a significant increase to 120,000 coins. The current total value of these holdings is approximately 90 million U.S. dollars.Recently, Nano Labs added 45,684.9862 BNB through over-the-counter (OTC) transactions. The average purchase price per coin was around 764 U.S. dollars. As of now, the company holds a total of about 120,000 BNB. The average acquisition cost per coin is 707 U.S. dollars, and the current market value is approximately 90 million U.S. dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese textile materials company Kitabo has announced plans to purchase approximately $5.4 million worth of Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21359</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, based on the monitoring of @btcNLNico, the Japanese textile materials company Kitabo Co. announced that as part of its new financial strategy, it intends to purchase approximately 800 million yen (approximately $5.4 million) worth of Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21359</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>