<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:55:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Recently, three hacker groups have profited additionally due to the ETH price surge. The Radiant Capital hackers have stolen assets that have appreciated by an additional $48.3 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24766</link>
      <description>August 15th. Based on EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, three groups of hackers have recently made additional profits by selling ETH. The details are as follows:Radiant Capital hacker stole approximately $53 million in assets last October. They then exchanged it for 21,957 ETH at a price of $2,414. Starting 3 days ago, they have been selling ETH. As of now, they have sold 9,631 ETH and obtained 43.937 million DAI, with an average selling price of $4,562. The hacker now holds 12,326 ETH and 43.937 million DAI, and the total value is $101 million, which is an additional appreciation of $48.3 million compared to the stolen asset value.Infini hacker stole about 49.5 million USDC in February. They then exchanged it for 17,696 ETH at a price of $2,798. They have sold 3,540 ETH and received 13.318 million DAI, with an average price of $3,762. The Infini hacker has benefited from the rise in ETH and gained an additional $25.15 million.An unknown hacker received 17,412 ETH at the end of March from pl</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet will launch the Real Rice AI (RICE) TGE on August 18th.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24765</link>
      <description>August 15th. Binance Wallet will list Real Rice AI (RICE) TGE on August 18th, 2025, between 16:00 and 18:00. Qualified users will be required to use Alpha Points to participate in the subscription. Additionally, 40 million RICE tokens will be set aside for future activities, and the specific details will be announced separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24765</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital has withdrawn 37,808 ETH from CEX in the past 24 hours, equivalent to around $172 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24764</link>
      <description>Update: On August 15th, as per TheDataNerd, within the past 24 hours, Galaxy Digital withdrew a combined total of 37,808 ETH from exchanges. This amount is approximately equivalent to $172 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24764</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Treasury and ETF Total Holdings Surpass 10 Million Coins, Accounting for 8.3% of ETH&apos;s Current Total Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24763</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to strategicethreserve data, the combined total holdings of Ethereum by treasury companies and ETFs have exceeded 10 million, accounting for approximately 8.3% of the current total supply. The top holders among treasury companies and institutions are as follows:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) takes the lead and currently holds 1.2 million ETH, with a value of around $5.33 billion;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) comes in second and currently holds 598,800 ETH, valued at around $2.77 billion;The Ether Machine (DYNX) ranks third and currently holds 345,000 ETH, with a value of around $1.6 billion;The Ethereum Foundation ranks fourth and holds 231,600 ETH, valued at around $1.07 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24763</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&apos;s Central Bank: Implementing and Detailing a Moderately Loose Monetary Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24762</link>
      <description>August 15: The People&apos;s Bank of China issued the China Monetary Policy Implementation Report for the second quarter of 2025. In the subsequent stage, a moderately loose monetary policy will be implemented and refined. Based on the domestic and international economic and financial situation and the operation of the financial market, we will control the strength and pace of policy implementation, maintain liquidity, ensure that the scale of social financing and the amount of money supply increase in line with economic growth and the expected target of the overall price level, and continuously create a suitable financial environment. Regarding promoting a reasonable rise in prices, it is regarded as an important factor in guiding monetary policy and driving prices to remain at a reasonable level. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Candle Capital experienced a daily drawdown of approximately $24.495 million, regaining $20.675 million in profits.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24760</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the data from the Binance platform indicates that the crypto venture capital firm Big Candle Capital witnessed a single-day asset drawdown of approximately $24.495 million yesterday. Prior to this, on the Binance platform, Big Candle Capital had a 30-day profit of $114 million.Based on her analysis, this might be due to holding positions during yesterday&apos;s significant market decline or partially reducing positions. The profit and loss curve for the past 7 days shows that on August 13th, the profit reached a peak of $20.675 million, but yesterday the profit quickly turned into a negative value (-$3.82 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Treasury Mints 1 Billion USDT on Ethereum Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24761</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as monitored by Whale Alert, the Tether Treasury minted 1 billion USDT on the Ethereum blockchain approximately 4 minutes ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24761</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BtcTurk&apos;s Suspicious Withdrawals Reach Around $54 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24759</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as monitored by CertiK Alert, the suspicious withdrawals from the Turkish cryptocurrency exchange BtcTurk have surged to approximately $54 million.Yesterday, BtcTurk issued a statement indicating that abnormal hot wallet operations were detected. As a preventive measure, the platform has temporarily halted cryptocurrency deposits and withdrawals until the investigation is completed. The official announcement mentioned that the majority of assets are stored in secure cold wallets, the company&apos;s finances are in good condition, and user assets are not impacted. The functions of Turkish Lira deposits, withdrawals, and trading are operating normally. The platform has notified the regulatory authorities and implemented all security measures.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALT5 Sigma Appoints Former GSR Executive as Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24758</link>
      <description>On August 15th, ALT5 Sigma (ALTS), a US-listed company that obtained a $1.5 billion financing to initiate the WLFI Treasury, declared the appointment of Jonathan Hugh as the Chief Financial Officer. Jonathan holds more than 25 years of senior financial and business leadership experience in digital assets, technology, energy, and commodity trading. He has previously held the position of CFO at global market maker GSR International and institutional custody company Zodia Custody.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Strategy Set to Be Included in S&amp;P 500 in September, Bitcoin&apos;s Leap to Blue-Chip Asset Status Is Underway</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24757</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the asset management company Strive released a market commentary on Strategy. It was stated that Strategy, as the world&apos;s largest Bitcoin treasury company, is one step away from being included in the S&amp;P 500 Index. If this milestone is achieved, it will fundamentally establish Bitcoin&apos;s position in the US financial landscape. The market value of Strategy exceeds $100 billion, already surpassing the market capitalization threshold of the S&amp;P 500. However, the inclusion criteria for the S&amp;P 500 are not only based on market capitalization but also require the company to be registered in the US, listed on a major exchange, and to have been profitable in the past quarter and year. The latter profitability requirement has always been a barrier for Strategy.Recently, Strategy released its second-quarter financial report, and its profitability over the past 12 months has overcome the final hurdle, making it possible to be included in the S&amp;P 500 as early as September. However</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24757</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>