<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:36:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Wallet launches YZY and introduces a $50,000 New User Airdrop Event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25729</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per the official announcement, WEEX has launched YZY spot trading and U-based contracts. It has also introduced the YZY New User Airdrop Event with a total prize pool of $50,000. Event Period: from 15:00 on August 22nd to 0:00 on August 30th (UTC+8).During the event period, new users with a net deposit of ≥ $100 and who make their first YZY spot trade will receive a $15 USDT reward. New users with a total trading volume on any contract pair of ≥ $500 will receive $15 USDT + $10 USDT contract bonus. New users with a daily trading volume on any contract pair of ≥ $10,000 will be regarded as having successfully checked in. Those who accumulate trading check-ins for 3 days or more will be eligible to participate in a $20,000 USDT prize pool based on their trading volume share. New and existing users who invite friends to register on WEEX will receive a $10 USDT reward for each qualifying invitation completed, with a maximum of $1,000 USDT per person.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25729</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Futures Soar in a &quot;V&quot; Shape, All Three Major Futures Turn Green</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25730</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on market data, the US stock market witnessed a rise in pre-market trading. Futures took on a &quot;V&quot; shape, and all three major futures turned positive. Dow Jones Industrial Average Futures increased by 0.20%, S&amp;P 500 Futures rose by 0.13%, and Nasdaq 100 Futures went up by 0.07%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25730</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southwest Securities: Currently, we have not yet engaged in any stablecoin-related business.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25728</link>
      <description>August 22nd. Southwest Securities stated on its interactive platform today that the company has a subsidiary established in Hong Kong and is conducting business in accordance with overseas regulations. At present, the company has not yet been engaged in stablecoin-related business. Meanwhile, the company, under the premise of compliance, actively explores and researches various business opportunities based on its own situation.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpack Exchange is now integrated with Aptos</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25727</link>
      <description>August 22nd. Backpack Exchange has now incorporated Aptos.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25727</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Opens 40x Long Position with a $22.65 Million BTC Position, at an Average Entry Price of $113,622.9</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25726</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a new contract whale with the address 0xeA2 has deposited 10 million USDC into HyperLiquid. This whale has augmented its Bitcoin long position with 40 times leverage and has placed an unexecuted order for its Ethereum long position.Its BTC long position is valued at $22.65 million, and the entry price is $113,622.9.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25726</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Plasma Fixed Savings Product Total Subscription Limit Increased to $1 Billion, with $250 Million Allocation Opening in One Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25725</link>
      <description>August 22nd, Binance declared that it would raise the total subscription limit of the Plasma Fixed Product to $1 billion, and a quota of 250 million USDT would be available for subscription within one hour. Subscribing with USDT would yield daily USDT rewards + XPL rewards (after TGE).The second batch of quota (250 million USDT) is scheduled to officially open for subscription at 17:00 (GMT+8) on August 22, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25725</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell&apos;s Speech Tonight Highlights Preview: Can the Overture of Policy Shift be Played, Market Awaits Clear Rate Cut Signal</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25724</link>
      <description>August 22: Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is slated to deliver a speech at the annual central bank symposium of the Kansas City Fed in Jackson Hole tonight at 10 p.m. Beijing time. The market anticipates the following key aspects from his speech:Rate Cut Path: Will Powell confirm whether the anticipated rate cut next month is the core focus of this speech? Currently, the majority of institutions expect Powell to adopt a neutral stance, without providing clear cues and continuously emphasizing a data-driven decision-making approach. Nevertheless, the market remains worried about his resistance against the rate cut expected in September;Policy Framework Review: The Fed&apos;s policy framework review has become one of Powell&apos;s key focal points for this speech. Several major investment banks anticipate that Powell may downplay the Flexible Average Inflation Targeting (FAIT) introduced in 2020 and return to a more traditional policy statement that emphasizes a more balanced approach to empl</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25724</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A user fell victim to a fraudulent Uniswap phishing transaction, resulting in the loss of approximately $1 million in tokens and NFTs.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25723</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as monitored by ScamSniffer, a user lost around 1 million dollars&apos; worth of tokens and NFTs after signing a phishing batch trade request that was disguised as a Uniswap swap transaction.The attacker employed a fake Uniswap trading interface to deceive the user into signing a transaction. Malicious code or authorization was embedded within this transaction. Unaware of the situation, the user signed the transaction, which led to the theft of their assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25723</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwanese Prosecutors in China Bust &quot;CoinWish&quot; Tech Company for Fraud, Uncovering Money Laundering Totaling NT$2.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25722</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to the United News Network, the prosecutor&apos;s office in Taiwan, China, took action against the virtual currency physical store trading platform &quot;Coinwish&quot; Technology Company for being involved in a fraud case. The money laundering amount reached 2.3 billion New Taiwan Dollars, and there were over a thousand victims. Since April, the prosecutor&apos;s office has carried out search operations and successively detained 15 people, including the person in charge Shi Qiren. They seized 60.49 million New Taiwan Dollars in cash, 640,000 USDT, and other virtual assets. Today, the Shilin District Prosecutor&apos;s Office filed charges against these 15 individuals for fraud, money laundering, and organization crimes and applied for the confiscation of criminal proceeds totaling 1.275 billion New Taiwan Dollars.The prosecutor&apos;s office pointed out that Shi Qiren and others illegally provided virtual asset services to the public through the unapproved and incomplete anti-money launderi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25722</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Powell&apos;s speech tonight may not necessarily signal a policy shift, but it could open the door to a 25 basis point rate cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25721</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Christoph Rieger, who is the Head of Rate and Credit Research at a German bank, stated in a report that the Fed Chair has in the past used the Jackson Hole Symposium to convey important policy guidance changes. However, it is not likely to occur this year. Rieger said, &quot;Although we anticipate that, when compared to previous guidance, that is, the Fed is waiting for more data, Powell&apos;s statement this time will not experience a significant change. Leaving the door open for a 25 basis point rate cut in September would be a reasonable action.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25721</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>