<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. M2 money supply has reached $22.12 trillion, hitting a new all-time high.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27061</link>
      <description>On August 31st, as reported by Cointelegraph, the M2 money supply in the US has reached $22.12 trillion, reaching a new record high.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27061</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks.Live: Market Sentiment Shows Clear Divergence, with a Focus on Ethereum&apos;s Recent Relative Strength and Fund Flows</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27060</link>
      <description>On August 31st, GreekLive issued its daily market summary, stating, &quot;There is a clear division within the community regarding the current bull market. Some members are questioning the absence of the quick-rich effect that is typical of a traditional bull market in this halving cycle. Meanwhile, others point out that Bitcoin has witnessed a significant rise from $20,000 to $120,000 and Ethereum from $1,400 to $4,900. The community is widely focusing on Ethereum&apos;s recent relative strength and the changing fund flows on exchanges. There has been an increase in Bitcoin inflows and a decrease in Ethereum outflows.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27060</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Research transferred 1,000,000 PENDLE to Binance 10 minutes ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27059</link>
      <description>On August 31st, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, Trend Research, a secondary investment institution under LD Capital, transferred 1 million PENDLE tokens (valued at $4.78 million) that were purchased a week ago to Binance 10 minutes ago. It is possible that they are planning to sell off the Ethereum ecosystem tokens they had accumulated earlier.Previously, reports showed that Trend Research transferred 203,105 ENS tokens (worth $4.72 million) to Binance 5 minutes ago. These tokens were withdrawn from Binance on July 23rd at a price of $28.82. If sold, it would lead to a loss of $1.133 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27059</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs Community Vote Passes &quot;US Market Expansion and TradFi Adoption Plan&quot; Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27058</link>
      <description>On August 31st, the Sonic Labs community cast their votes in support of the &quot;U.S. Market Expansion and TradFi Adoption Plan&quot; proposal. The intention of this proposal is to establish Sonic USA LLC in order to initiate U.S. operations. It plans to hire a Sonic USA CEO and a full U.S. team, set up an office in New York, and put in place a performance-based employee incentive plan. Meanwhile, the company intends to enhance long-term deflation through a Gas fee mechanism.It will also make adjustments to network parameters: approve the issuance of tokens for a $50 million ETF quota; $100 million Nasdaq PIPE development; 1.5 billion S tokens for Sonic USA, or reject all of the above parameter adjustments.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27058</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: The Fed is embarking on a gentle rate cut cycle after a prolonged pause</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27057</link>
      <description>August 31st. In the forthcoming weeks, the U.S. stock market will encounter a crucial period that will decide whether the latest round of rebound can persist. Employment data, key inflation indicators, and the Federal Reserve&apos;s interest rate decision will all be disclosed within the next 14 trading days, thereby setting the market tone for investors. Currently, the stock market appears to be at a crossroads: the S&amp;P 500 index just achieved its weakest monthly gain since March, and September has historically been its worst-performing month. Meanwhile, market volatility has nearly vanished. The VIX fear index only touched the key level of 20 once since the end of June.&quot;It is appropriate for investors to remain cautious in September,&quot; said Tom Lee, the Head of Research at Fundstrat Global Advisors. &quot;After a prolonged pause, the Federal Reserve is re-entering a mild rate-cutting cycle, making it difficult for traders to determine their positions.&quot; This long-time bullish analyst on U.S. s</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27057</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain new wallet deposited $1 million into HyperLiquid and shorted ETH with 25x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27054</link>
      <description>On August 31st, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet withdrew 2 million USDC from Binance and transferred 1 million US dollars into HyperLiquid for shorting ETH with a leverage of 25x.The whale still has 1 million USDC in the blockchain and may utilize it for margin or expand their short position.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27054</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Research transferred 203,105 ENS to Binance 5 minutes ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27056</link>
      <description>On August 31st, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), an affiliate of Ledger Capital named Trend Research transferred 203,105 ENS tokens (valued at $4.72 million) to Binance 5 minutes ago.This batch of tokens was withdrawn from Binance on July 23rd at a price of $28.82. If sold, it would lead to a loss of $1.133 million (with a recharge price of $23.24). A year ago, Trend&apos;s ENS trading strategy also appeared to have ended in a loss.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum Short-term Bearish, Potential for a Breakthrough of $4,600 Resistance Level and a Run at $5,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27055</link>
      <description>On August 31st, the crypto analyst @ali_charts mentioned that if Ethereum&apos;s 4-hour closing price exceeds $4,500, it will signify a breakout of the recent high downward trend line, suggesting that bullish momentum may be on the rise. The next significant resistance level is at $4,600. If Ethereum can successfully break through this level, it may open the way for a retest of $5,000.Nevertheless, currently Ethereum is still trading within the middle of the channel, following the downward trend line. The SuperTrend indicator still shows a sell signal. Unless Ethereum can regain $4,500 and transform it into a support level, it remains bearish in the short term.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27055</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale participated in the first round of the public sale, spending 15 million USDC to subscribe to 1 billion WLFI tokens. Tomorrow, they will unlock and claim 200 million WLFI tokens, wor...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27053</link>
      <description>On August 31st, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jing, starting tomorrow, the yield of public sale whales in WLFI that is set to be claimed and unlocked ranges from 7 times to 23 times.· Currently, 16.4 billion WLFI from the public sale has been activated. This indicates that 20% of it, which is 3.3 billion WLFI, will be unlocked and enter circulation tomorrow. With the current price of $0.35, the circulating market value is $1.15 billion. The actual circulation should be higher because the project team still needs to take out some tokens to provide liquidity and add as LP tokens.· The largest activated account belongs to @moonmanifest47. In the first round of public sale, they subscribed to 1 billion WLFI with 15 million USDC at a price of $0.015. Tomorrow, they will unlock and receive 200 million WLFI, which is worth $70 million at a price of $0.35.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27053</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-profile BTC Whale Rebalances into ETH Again30 minutes ago, a ancient BTC whale once again transferred 1000 BTC to Hyperliquid to rebalance into ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27052</link>
      <description>On August 31st, according to Arkham&apos;s monitoring, a high-profile BTC ancient whale that recently shifted from ETH has once again transferred 1000 BTC (with a value of $1.0844 billion) to Hyperliquid for another round of ETH swapping.In the past 10 hours, this whale has already deposited a total of 4000 BTC, which is worth $4.3376 billion, and has converted it into ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27052</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>