<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:17:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Gata (GATA) on September 4th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27470</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as per an official announcement, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list Gata (GATA) on September 4th. The details regarding the airdrop threshold have not been made public yet.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27470</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater Fund Founder: Dollar&apos;s Poor Debt Situation Indirectly Drives Cryptocurrency and Gold Price Surge</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27469</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Ray Dalio, the founder of Bridgewater Associates, stated today that he does not think that the easing of cryptocurrency regulation will pose a threat to the status of the US dollar as a reserve currency. Nevertheless, the deteriorating debt situation of the US dollar and other reserve currency-issuing governments affects their attractiveness as reserve currencies and stores of value. This has always been one of the factors driving the rise in the prices of gold and cryptocurrencies.Moreover, Ray Dalio does not believe that the exposure of stablecoins to government bonds presents a systemic risk. The real risk lies in the declining purchasing power of government bonds. If stablecoins are well-regulated, this should not pose any systemic risk.&quot;Cryptocurrency is currently an alternative currency with a limited supply. Therefore, under the same conditions, if the supply of the US dollar increases and/or the demand for it decreases, this may make cryptocurrency an attr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27469</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will delist BAKE, HIFI, SLF on September 17.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27471</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to an official announcement. Based on a recent review, Binance will delist and cease all spot trading pairs for the following tokens on September 17th at 03:00 (UTC). These tokens are BakeryToken (BAKE), Hifi Finance (HIFI), and Self Chain (SLF).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27471</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the latest round of funding news, Kite AI&apos;s official NFT saw a 209% surge in the past 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27468</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to Blur data, the official NFT series of KITE AI, &quot;FLY THE KITE&quot;, witnessed a 209% increase in floor price within the past 24 hours. The 24-hour trading volume reached 34.15 ETH. Currently, the floor price of this NFT series is 0.29 ETH.It is reported that the &quot;Fly the KITE&quot; NFT series was launched in July through Free Mint with a supply of 2,000 pieces. According to the official description, this series &quot;will serve as a badge of honor, freely dedicated to the initial 2,000 builders and supporters&quot;.BlockBeats previously reported that Kite AI raised $33 million in funding, with PayPal Ventures and General Catalyst taking the lead.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has successively wagered $13.29 million on BLOCK and WLFI.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27467</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), address 0x8C4...96CAd successively invested $13.29 million in BLOCK and WLFI. The following are the operations:1. Invested 426 ETH and 170.3 ETH respectively to participate in the WLFI first and second public sale rounds, and received 10.22 million unlocked tokens without selling them.2. Starting from August 26th, spent 298 ETH to buy 8.5 million BLOCK tokens, which is worth $1.21 million. Currently, it ranks among the top 6 holders.3. In the past 15 hours, withdrew 40.87 million WLFI tokens from Bybit, which is worth $10.07 million. The average withdrawal price is $0.2464. Currently, a total of 51.09 million WLFI tokens are held.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27467</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fenghuang Finance&apos;s stock price did not experience a pump despite the &quot;Purchase of 10,000 Ethereum&quot; news, decreasing by 4.09% during intraday trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27466</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on market information, Noah Holdings (HK:00376) opened high and declined low today. It dropped 4.09% intraday, and the stock price is currently at 3.52 Hong Kong dollars.Regarding yesterday&apos;s news, Noah Holdings announced the purchase of 10,000 ETH to establish an Ethereum asset reserve. According to public data, Alibaba&apos;s founder Jack Ma indirectly holds about 11.15% of Noah Holdings through Yunfeng Fund. He holds 29.85% in Noah Holdings Limited and 40% in Shanghai Yunfeng Innovation (without voting rights).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27466</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An whale withdrew 5100 ETH from OKX 2 hours ago, accumulating a total of 42,681 ETH in the past 5 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27465</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as monitored by LookOnChain, an unidentified entity withdrew 5,100 ETH (equivalent to 22.02 million USD) from OKX via the wallet 0x3e64 two hours ago.During the past 5 days, this entity has withdrawn a cumulative total of 42,681 ETH (amounting to 185 million USD) from OKX through 3 wallets.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27465</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea has partnered with Brevis to launch the Linea Ignition long-term incentive program.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27464</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Linea declared a strategic partnership with Brevis and officially launched the long-term incentive program &quot;Ignition&quot; within its ecosystem. It is reported that Linea will distribute a total of 1 billion LINEA tokens across the Etherex, Aave, and Euler protocols by using Brevis&apos;s zero-knowledge proof virtual machine Pico and coprocessor products. The aim is to create the world&apos;s first fully trustless on-chain liquidity incentive mechanism.The innovation of this solution is that the complex reward calculations are generated by Brevis off-chain and transformed into a ZK proof, enabling low-cost verification on-chain to complete the distribution. This ensures that the incentive calculations for protocols such as Etherex, Aave, and Euler are mathematically verifiable and completely transparent, setting a new benchmark for the DeFi ecosystem&apos;s incentive mechanisms.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea has approved to allocate 4% of LINEA to participating Linea Surge liquidity providers.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27463</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Linea Association announced in a tweet, &quot;The Linea Association has granted approval for the allocation of 4% of LINEA to the liquidity providers who have participated in the Linea Surge event. As the initial step of the distribution, SBT was issued to the eligible wallets last Friday. More detailed information regarding the conversion of these SBT into LINEA tokens will be announced through the official qualification check page.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27463</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Suspected of Dumping 2585 ETH, Profits Reach $5.33 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27462</link>
      <description>September 3rd. As per on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), a significant whale transferred the 2,585 ETH that had been accumulated over the past four months to Binance around 10 hours ago (approximately equivalent to $11.32 million USD), suggesting a possible liquidation. In the event of a sale, the return on investment over the four-month period would be approximately 89%. With an entry price of $2,316 and an exit price of $4,378, the whale&apos;s total gains from engaging in the practice of buying low and selling high over four months amount to $5.33 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 02:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27462</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>