<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:50:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sky spent $1.39 million last week to buy back 16.55 million SKY tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23123</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to official channels, Sky (formerly known as MakerDAO) spent $1.39 million during the previous week to repurchase 16.55 million SKY. Currently, the cumulative amount of SKY repurchased amounts to 1.11 billion, accounting for approximately 3.28% of the total supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERB&apos;s trading volume reached 6.8 million shares after the &quot;Raising $558 Million to Establish TON Treasury&quot; announcement, approximately 9 times the circulating supply.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23122</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to Farside Investors. Within 5 minutes after the announcement that &quot;Verb Technology has completed a $558 million private placement to initiate its TON reserve strategy&quot;, the trading volume of VERB reached 6.8 million shares, which is approximately 9 times the circulating supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Surges Above $3,600</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23121</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum has seen a rebound and broken through $3,600. It is currently priced at $3,601.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Stocks Open with Mixed Performance, SBET and VAPE Surge Over 8%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23120</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on the data from rockflow, the three major U.S. stock indexes opened higher. The Dow increased by 0.31%, the S&amp;P 500 rose by 0.62%, and the Nasdaq went up by 0.99%. Cryptocurrency-related stocks demonstrated mixed performance, including:Coinbase (COIN) with a decrease of 0.017%;Circle (CRCL) down by 1.93%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) up by 0.65%;MARA Holdings (MARA) rising by 0.16%;Riot Blockchain (RIOT) increasing by 1.66%;BTCS (BTCS) down by 2.09%;Bit Digital (BTBT) up by 2.76%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) up by 8.93%;CEA Industries (VAPE) up by 8.03%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The cryptocurrency exchange platform Bullish is planning to raise $629 million in its IPO.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23118</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to AXIOS, Block.one, the parent company of EOS (now Vaulta), has submitted a filing to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for its cryptocurrency exchange platform Bullish. The plan is to raise up to $629 million through an Initial Public Offering (IPO). The company operates a digital asset trading platform and owns the well-known cryptocurrency media CoinDesk.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23118</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS: US Stocks Face Pullback Pressure in August, Potential Strategic Buying Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23119</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to UBS Group&apos;s latest analysis, due to weakening economic data, the US stock market may be under pullback pressure in August. Last week&apos;s employment data coming in below expectations has sparked concerns about economic slowdown. The bank&apos;s strategists pointed out that the market downturn may persist until the Fed gives a signal for a rate cut - UBS expects this policy change to occur in the coming months. Despite short-term pressure, the institution regards the current correction as a strategic buying opportunity. (Bloomberg)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian entities and retail investors collectively hold approximately 1 million BTC, second only to the United States</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23117</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to financefeeds, industry data indicates that India has risen to become the second-largest country in terms of Bitcoin holdings, second only to the United States. Analysts estimate that India currently holds approximately 1 million BTC, accounting for 5.1% of the total Bitcoin circulation.Currently, the United States still holds the top position with a holding of about 7.8 million BTC (40% of the total supply), including assets held by institutional investors, publicly traded companies (such as MicroStrategy), and Bitcoin seized by law enforcement agencies. The total value of Bitcoin held by India is estimated to be between 115 billion and 120 billion US dollars. This achievement has been achieved in a challenging policy environment - India imposes a 30% capital gains tax on crypto profits and a 1% Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) on each transaction. These measures were intended to curb high-frequency large transactions, but local investors&apos; enthusiasm for Bitco</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23117</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Trump&apos;s Firing of US Labor Department Head is Negative for the Dollar</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23116</link>
      <description>On August 4th, the US dollar kept declining from Friday. This was due to the market&apos;s growing expectations of a September rate cut by the Federal Reserve and the intensified concerns about the reliability of US data.Goldman Sachs&apos; analysis indicated that President Trump&apos;s replacement of the Commissioner of the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) might undermine the market&apos;s confidence in the credibility of US policies. This has led investors to reevaluate their risk mitigation strategies. The bank anticipates that the US dollar will continue to weaken, with particularly strong pressure on the USD/JPY exchange rate. (Bloomberg)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23116</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The robot and AI startup company OpenMind has completed a $20 million funding round, with Pantera Capital leading the round and Coinbase Ventures participating.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23115</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as reported by The Block, the robotics and AI startup OpenMind has successfully completed a financing round of $20 million. This round was led by Pantera Capital, and Coinbase Ventures, Digital Currency Group, Ribbit, and other institutions also participated. The company is dedicated to achieving the interconnection of &quot;Mind Machines&quot; through open source and decentralized technology.It is reported that the startup is developing a &quot;hardware-agnostic&quot; operating system named FABRIC, which is designed to support the &quot;integration of intelligent machines into daily life.&quot; This protocol offers a means for AI-powered robots to communicate and coordinate.In a statement, the company stated: &quot;This financing enables OpenMind to get closer to making robot intelligence open, interoperable, and accessible, similar to the internet. As more robots go online, FABRIC provides a trust layer that allows them to collaborate—regardless of who manufactured them or where they operate. Robots</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23115</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Whale Addresses Have Increased Their Holdings by 39,921 ETH in the Last 6 Hours, Equivalent to around $142 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23114</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain. A newly established wallet, &quot;0x86F9&quot;, has received 24,294 ETH (approximately $86.48 million) from FalconX within the past 6 hours.Furthermore, the whale &quot;0x40E9&quot; has received 15,627 ETH (approximately $55.6 million) from the Galaxy Digital OTC wallet in the past 2 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23114</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>