<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol: AUBRAI TGE Scheduled for August 27</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26289</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Bio Protocol declared that the first BioAgent Launch project, Aubrai (AUBRAI), will not commence the TGE immediately after the subscription ends. Instead, it will start trading 24 hours later, which is on Wednesday, August 27th. According to the official website, Aubrai has received 11.6 times oversubscription.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26289</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Solana Launchpad Market Share in Last 24 Hours: pump.fun, Letsbonk, Meteora DBC in Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26288</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours, in the Solana launchpad market share ranking, pump.fun took the first place with 73.3%, Letsbonk came in second with 6.95%, and Meteora DBC ranked third with 5.48%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Committee of the Chinese People&apos;s Political Consultative Conference (CPPCC) Yao Zhisheng: Hong Kong should strive to become a global stablecoin issuance center</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26287</link>
      <description>August 26th. According to the Hong Kong Ta Kung Pao, Yao Zhisheng, a member of the National Committee of the Chinese People&apos;s Political Consultative Conference (CPPCC), published an article titled &quot;Focusing on Three Themes to Promote High-Quality Development in Hong Kong.&quot; In this article, it was pointed out that stablecoins pegged to fiat currency possess the characteristics such as openness, transparency, decentralization, and globalization that are endowed by blockchain technology and distributed ledgers. At the same time, they also have the feature of maintaining the value of fiat currency. Hong Kong, as an international financial center and the world&apos;s largest offshore RMB business center, should make good use of the &quot;one country, two systems&quot; advantage, seize the strategic high ground in stablecoin development, strive to become a global hub for stablecoin issuance, and enhance its role as a &quot;digital financial hub.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26287</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet has announced the integration of UnicornX.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26286</link>
      <description>August 26th, based on official information, OKX Wallet has declared the accomplishment of the integration with UnicornX. Users are now able to conduct trading on UnicornX via OKX Wallet and conveniently and securely explore its ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26286</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Participants of the Bitlayer Booster special stage and Phase 1 event winners can claim and trade BTR tokens within 8 hours after the token circulation begins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26285</link>
      <description>August 26th. According to official channels, Binance Alpha is set to launch and commence trading of Bitlayer (BTR) on August 27th, 2025, at 6:00 PM (GMT+8). Binance Futures trading will open at 6:30 PM (GMT+8) on the same day.Users who participated in the Bitlayer Pre-TGE will be able to trade the BTR token on Binance Alpha and the Futures exchange once trading commences.The winners of Phase 1 and the Special Phase of the Bitlayer Booster activity can claim and trade BTR tokens within 8 hours after the token&apos;s circulation begins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26285</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CEO: Every Dip Is a Buying Opportunity, Predicts BTC Will Reach $200,000 by End of Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26284</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Hunter Horsley, the CEO of Bitwise, stated, &quot;Bear in mind that the majority of people do not hold any cryptocurrency. In order to achieve mainstream adoption, there must be a significant influx of new investors entering the market for the first time.Each pullback presents an opportunity for investors to gain exposure at a lower price. Bitwise Research forecasts that Bitcoin (BTC) will reach $200,000 by the end of the year.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26284</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YZi Labs Incubation Program EASY Residency Announces First Season Selected Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26283</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the incubation program EASY Residency of YZi Labs announced the list of selected projects for the first season. A total of 16 projects were selected, such as the decentralized AI ecosystem AMMO, the AI-native oracle APRO, the Bitcoin-native lending protocol Bitway, the food delivery agent Byte A.I., the compliance process platform ComplyGen, the universal video agent Freebeat.AI, the on-chain data terminal Hubble AI, and the decentralized data network Robata.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26283</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Surges Beyond $110,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26282</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and exceeded $110,000, with a 24-hour decline of 2.44%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26282</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Board Governor Powell&apos;s Lawyer: Will Block Trump&apos;s &quot;Illegal&quot; Actions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26281</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the lawyer of the US Federal Reserve Board governor, Abbe Lowell, stated that Trump&apos;s actions &quot;are flawed. His requests lack any due process, basis, or legal merit. We will take all necessary measures to prevent his attempt to take illegal action.&quot; (Forex Factory)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26281</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Launches USDC Savings Account for Automatic Earning</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26280</link>
      <description>August 26th. According to the official announcement, OKX has officially launched the &quot;USDC Transaction Account Automatic Earn&quot; product. This product is available to VIP 1 and above users and allows them to automatically lend the USDC in the transaction account (with full-collateral rights) to earn interest without affecting the assets used as collateral or trading margin. The main account limit is 1,000,000 USDC.After activating the OKX transaction account automatic earn feature, users do not need to manually subscribe. The change in full-collateral rights will be immediately reflected in the earn asset, and the assets will always remain in the transaction account without affecting any trading operations. In addition, both the full-collateral margin and open order positions can be included in the earn asset, thereby increasing fund utilization. Previously, OKX has launched the USDT transaction account automatic earn feature and will later expand it to ETH and SOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>