<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BlockFi $13.2M Class Action Settlement Set to Be Approved, Final Objector Withdraws Opposition</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25755</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to Decrypt, the $13.2 million class-action settlement of BlockFi is about to be approved. The final objector, Yacov Baron, has withdrawn his opposition. This settlement will cover approximately 89,000 U.S. users who held BlockFi interest accounts between 2019 and 2022.BlockFi collapsed in 2022 due to its $680 million exposure to FTX, and this settlement offers a compensation channel for the affected investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25755</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: Tonight&apos;s Powell Speech Expected to Cause a 2% Price Swing for Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25754</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Pulkit Goyal, the trading lead at cryptocurrency market maker Orbit Markets, said that &quot;It is expected that the BTC options pricing will fluctuate around 2.0% based on Powell&apos;s speech at Jackson Hole. Nevertheless, if Powell&apos;s remarks deviate from the widely anticipated hints of rate cuts, there is a greater likelihood of downside volatility occurring.&quot; (CoinDesk)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25754</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Fed Harker Does Not Support Rate Cut in September, Bitcoin Breaks Below Uptrend Line, Short-Term Target at $99,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25753</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Cleveland Fed President Harker stated in an interview that he would not be in favor of a rate cut. He indicated: &quot;The current inflation level remains relatively high and has been on an upward trend over the past year. Based on the information I currently have, there is no justification for lowering interest rates in the short term.&quot; Although acknowledging certain concerns in the labor market, the unemployment rate still remains close to the ideal level of full employment. Therefore, maintaining a stance of &quot;moderate tightening&quot; still remains crucial in ensuring that inflation can continue to decline back to the target range.Influenced by this hawkish statement, Bitcoin once again tested the $112,000 level. Bitcoin (BTC) previously broke below the uptrend line since its low point of $75,000 in April of this year, forming a daily chart-level &quot;double top&quot; or 2B top pattern. Analysts at BiyaPay pointed out that if BTC effectively falls below the previous low of $111,920,</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25753</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Protocol&apos;s AI Agent project, VaderAI, has announced the discontinuation of the development of its DeFAI product related to Genesis.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25752</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Base ecosystem&apos;s AI Agent project VaderAI announced the discontinuation of the development of its DeFAI product related to Genesis. It will unlock all VADER tokens staked on VaderAI. Staking will only be possible on Virtuals with a 14-day cooldown period. Vader Yapping has been terminated, and the distribution of the next 14 days&apos; Virgen Points and token airdrop will be based on the snapshot of yesterday&apos;s stakers and yappers.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Japanese publicly traded company Convano has increased its BTC holdings by 200 coins, now owning a total of 364.93 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25751</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to the monitoring of @btcNLNico, the publicly listed Japanese company and nail salon operator Convano Co., Ltd. announced today that they have once again increased their holdings of BTC by 200 coins, and currently hold a total of 364.93 BTC.Convano plans to hold 21,000 BTC by the end of March 2027.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25751</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US stock-listed company Top Win has rebranded to AsiaStrategy and is now accepting Bitcoin payments.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25750</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to official channels, the U.S. listed company Top Win International (with Nasdaq stock code: SORA) announced that it has officially changed its name to AsiaStrategy while keeping its stock code unchanged. The company now accepts Bitcoin payments for purchasing luxury watches in order to strengthen its commitment to integrating digital assets into consumer transactions.AsiaStrategy is a leading Hong Kong-based company that focuses on the trade, distribution, and retail business of internationally renowned luxury watches. Through its subsidiary, Top Win International Trading Limited, it serves a global B2B network. Since May 2025, AsiaStrategy has entered the Web3 ecosystem.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 16th, Top Win completed a $10 million financing round, mainly for purchasing Bitcoin and potentially investing in publicly traded companies with a Bitcoin treasury strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25750</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A trader is long on XPL with 3x leverage, with an unrealized profit of approximately $175,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25749</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a trader has established a 3x leverage long position on XPL. Currently, the floating profit is approximately $175,000. Another trader has taken a 3x leverage short position on XPL and is facing a floating loss of around $122,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25749</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Meme Coin neet Surpasses $26 Million Market Cap, Surging Over 41% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25747</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to GMGN market data, the Meme coin neet within the Solana ecosystem has a market capitalization exceeding $26 million. It has a 24-hour increase of more than 41% and a 24-hour trading volume of $3.8 million.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins have no actual use cases and experience large price fluctuations. Therefore, investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25747</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL Pre-market Trading Price Surges Past $0.5, Fully Diluted Valuation Reaches $5 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25748</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the pre-market trading price of the XPL (Plasma) perpetual contract on Binance exceeded $0.5 and is currently trading at $0.505. XPL has a total supply of 10 billion tokens, and its current fully diluted valuation is $5 billion.Hyperliquid witnessed that the pre-market perpetual contract price of XPL broke through $0.5 and is currently priced at $0.508.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25748</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet will launch Hemi&apos;s exclusive Pre-TGE, with an Alpha Point threshold of 240 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25746</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Binance Wallet will hold an exclusive Hemi Pre-TGE event. Users whose Binance Alpha points are greater than or equal to 240 can participate in this Pre-TGE event through the Alpha event page, and participating in this event will consume 10 points.Event time: August 22nd, 2025, 20:00 - 22:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25746</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>