<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Bitcoin Price Stays Bullish as Long as It&apos;s Above $105,696</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23371</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Matrixport released today&apos;s market analysis which stated, &quot;At the present stage, it might still be too early and even somewhat pessimistic to determine whether Bitcoin will decline back to its 21-week moving average of $105,696. Nevertheless, we still regard this level as a reference for the key trend: if the price is above this level, the overall trend remains bullish; once it breaks below, we need to be vigilant against a bear market signal.&quot;In the past three weeks, we have maintained a more cautious attitude in our weekly reports. During this period, Bitcoin has undergone a pullback, although market sentiment remains relatively optimistic.In the short term, some funds may flow back from high-volatility alternative coins to Bitcoin, which provides some support to the price. However, we still advise investors to remain cautious and control their risk exposure. This judgment has been made multiple times in the past few weeks and is still applicable today.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23371</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: Grok2 will be open sourced next week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23370</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Musk tweeted, &quot;It is time for us to make Grok 2 open source, and this will be accomplished next week.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23370</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Quad-Shorting ETH Whale with 75% Win Rate」: 70,000 ETH Short Position Goes from Profit to Loss, Currently at Around $840,000 Unrealized Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23369</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight accessible through the link https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, the &quot;Four-Battle ETH 75% Win Rate Whale&quot; is currently holding a short position of 70,000 ETH (with a nominal value of approximately $254 million), having an opening price of $3,618.3 and a liquidation price of $3,698.29.This whale&apos;s short position in ETH has witnessed a change from a floating profit of $12.25 million to a floating loss of $840,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23369</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Increases Holdings Again by 60.6 BTC, Bringing Total Holdings to 763.2 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23368</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Swedish listed company H100 Group announced that they had once again increased their holdings by 60.6 BTC, and their total holdings had reached 763.2 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Season Index Drops to 38</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23367</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per Coinmarketcap data, the Altcoin Season Index has decreased to 38 (from 42 yesterday). This index implies that among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, approximately 38 projects have achieved higher price appreciation than Bitcoin over the past 90 days.Note: The CMC Altcoin Season Index is a real-time indicator formulated to assess whether the cryptocurrency market is currently in an altcoin-dominated season. The index is based on the performance of the top 100 altcoins in relation to Bitcoin over the past 90 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23367</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launchpool Project TOWNS is now open for staking, with BGB locked and 16.34 million TOWNS unlocked.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23366</link>
      <description>Update: On August 6th, the current Launchpool project of Bitget, Towns Protocol (TOWNS), is now open for participation. By staking BGB, users can unlock 16,340,000 TOWNS. The staking period ends at 14:00 (UTC+8) on August 10th.This round of Launchpool has opened a total of 2 staking pools, including:BGB Staking Pool· Airdrop Allocation: 15,215,000 TOWNS· VIP User Staking Limit: 50,000 BGB· Regular User Staking Limit: 5,000 BGBTOWNS Staking Pool· Airdrop Allocation: 1,125,000 TOWNS· Individual Staking Limit: 11,254,000 TOWNS</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23366</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit Co-CEO Helen Hai and Spot Lead Emily Bao Join Mantle as Key Advisors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23365</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to an official announcement, Mantle Network announced that Helen Liu, the co-CEO of Bybit, and Emily Bao, the current Spot Business Lead of Bybit, have joined as key advisors to the Mantle ecosystem. This move is regarded as an important step in driving the expansion of the ecosystem and strategic realignment.Helen Liu previously worked at Nokia and Microsoft and led Bybit&apos;s global business expansion, bringing rich experience in operations and technical deployment. Emily Bao is the founder of ByReal and has been committed to bridging real-world assets with on-chain execution for a long time. She has a deep background in market design and ecosystem architecture.Mantle stated that the addition of these two executives will help strengthen the collaboration with Bybit, drive the strategic transition of CEX to Web3, and further enhance Mantle&apos;s execution capabilities in DeFi, ecosystem partnerships, and infrastructure development.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23365</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK-listed company Vaultz Capital increases its Bitcoin holdings to 47.85 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23364</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the publicly listed company Vaultz Capital in the UK purchased 47.85 bitcoins, increasing its total bitcoin holdings to 117.85 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23364</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter Web Company issues a $21 million Bitcoin-denominated convertible bond, with institutional investor TOBAM subscribing in full.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23363</link>
      <description>August 6th. As per official channels, the Smarter Web Company has issued a convertible bond worth $21 million, which is priced in Bitcoin. This bond has been fully subscribed by the institutional investor TOBAM.It is reported that this zero-coupon bond enables conversion to stock at a 5% premium. It also incorporates Bitcoin-based downside protection and restricts the proportion of purchased Bitcoin to be within 30%. This represents the first such financing transaction in the UK market.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23363</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital Founder James: Expecting a rate cut rally to start after mid-August, all recent pullbacks have been buying opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23362</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the founder of LD Capital, Yi Lihua, stated that due to factors such as the U.S. stock market and tariffs, ETH had experienced a period of turmoil. It is expected that after mid-August, it will begin to see a market driven by the anticipation of a September rate cut. The bullish trend is undeniable, and all recent pullbacks have been buying opportunities.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23362</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>