<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:51:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>In the last 1 hour, the entire network has seen liquidations totaling $144 million, with the majority coming from long positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21654</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 1 hour, the entire network has witnessed liquidations totaling $144 million. The long liquidations amount to $137 million, and the short liquidations amount to $6.9576 million.In the last 24 hours, a total of 314,844 people worldwide have been liquidated, with a total liquidation amount of $969 million. The largest single liquidation took place on Binance - BTCUSDC, amounting to $2.9614 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21654</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Vault is about to shut down, planning to sell the business and seeking acquisition offers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21653</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the NFT platform Pixel Vault is currently in the process of planning to sell the company and is seeking potential acquirers. The team is currently engaged in discussions with multiple institutions that are interested in acquiring Pixel Vault and its assets in order to continue serving the community. Additionally, they are also having direct communication with Seedphrase regarding the transition of the Wolf Game.Pixel Vault is also the publisher of PUNKS Comic and the MetaHero Universe. They stated, &quot;After more than four years of development, we have initiated the process of winding down Pixel Vault. We have dedicated a lot of efforts to build a profitable and sustainable crypto entertainment company. Although our endeavors did not unfold as planned, we still wish to express our gratitude to the team, investors, and the community for their support.&quot;BlockBeats previously reported that on February 3, 2022, the NFT platform Pixel Vault announced the completion of a $100 m</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21653</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Assists U.S. Authorities in Freezing Terror-Related Funds and Reissuing Approximately $1.6 Million USDT</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21652</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Tether announced that it had assisted the U.S. authorities in freezing and reissuing approximately 1.6 million USDT. These USDT were associated with the Gaza-based BuyCash company and were suspected of being involved in terrorist financing.This action forms part of a U.S. Department of Justice civil forfeiture case involving approximately $2 million in digital assets. Tether stated that it had frozen more than $2.9 billion in USDT, had collaborated with 275 law enforcement agencies covering 59 jurisdictions, and had pledged to continue supporting global law enforcement in combating illicit activities.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21652</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Ventures will support the AI platform Bankr through the Base Ecosystem Fund</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21651</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Coinbase Ventures declared in a blog that it is going to back the AI agent platform Bankr by means of the Base Ecosystem Fund. Bankr is one of the agent platforms integrated into Coinbase&apos;s freshly launched Base app. Transaction agents can respond more quickly than humans, operate around the clock, and are able to make more data-based decisions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21651</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21650</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and exceeded $11,800. The 24-hour decline was narrowed to 0.39%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21650</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday, they have now been deposited into Bybit.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21649</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the 2 billion PUMP tokens yesterday were suspected to have been transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to an address related to the project. This address has been labeled by Solscan as the &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2&quot;, that is, a private investor.After receiving the refunded funds from Binance yesterday, these 2 billion tokens have been deposited into Bybit, resulting in a $6 million decrease in value compared to when they were deposited into Binance.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21649</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Nativo Resources announces initiation of Bitcoin Treasury Reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21648</link>
      <description>July 24th, The company Nativo Resources listed in London (LON:NTVO) announced today that it has implemented a digital asset treasury policy. This enables the gold-focused mining company to allocate a part of its free cash flow and future financing proceeds to hold Bitcoin. The company is getting ready to resume its gold mining operations in the Tesoro (LON:0JYA) gold mine concession area in Peru. It stated that this policy will allow it to hold Bitcoin as a long-term financial reserve asset while fulfilling operational working capital requirements.According to a press release, Nativo has collaborated with Copper.co to offer institutional-grade custody services for its digital assets and anticipates receiving additional security services from Nemean Services. The company&apos;s board thinks that holding both gold and Bitcoin can offer shareholders a diversified hedge against inflation. It is noted that Bitcoin&apos;s fixed supply and decentralized nature complement the traditional store of valu</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Market Experiences Sharp Decline, MOVE Plunges Over 27% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21647</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on HTX market data, the altcoin market experienced a general decline. Among them:In the past 24 hours, MOVE dropped by more than 27%;In the past 24 hours, WIF dropped by more than 18%;In the past 24 hours, VIRTUAL dropped by more than 18%;In the past 24 hours, NEIRO dropped by more than 18%;In the past 24 hours, APT dropped by more than 17%;In the past 24 hours, OP dropped by more than 15%;In the past 24 hours, PENGU dropped by more than 14%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21647</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 domain registrar Freename has completed a $6.5 million Series A funding round, led by Entrée Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21646</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the Web3 domain registrar Freename announced the successful completion of a $6.5 million Series A funding round. This round of funding was led by Entrée Capital. Polymorphic Capital also participated, along with its seed round investors Sparkle Ventures, Blockchain Founders Fund, and Golden Record Ventures. Additionally, new angel investors joined the round, including Mike Lobanov, the co-founder of Target Global, the Rashwan Family Office, and Aaron Schnarch, the former CEO of Coinbase Custody.The company focuses on establishing a connection between the traditional DNS and the blockchain domain system. Freename&apos;s core technology encompasses a cross-chain domain conflict management system, which supports the resolution of multiple-chain domains such as Polygon and Solana while remaining compatible with traditional browsers. Its innovative solution enables users to create custom top-level domains and generate profits through the sale of subdomains. The funds will be util</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21646</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX will attend GM Vietnam 2025 Blockchain Week as a Gold Sponsor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21645</link>
      <description>July 24th. As per the news on official social media, Huobi HTX will participate in the blockchain summit GM Vietnam 2025 as a Gold Sponsor, presenting its global layout and ecosystem strength in the Web3 field. Additionally, Huobi HTX will also jointly host the Web3 Future Night themed party with the well-known Web3 media ChainCatcher on the evening of July 31st in Hanoi. At that time, it will gather Vietnam&apos;s most active KOLs and communities to create a high-quality social environment for Web3 practitioners.It is reported that GM Vietnam - Vietnam Blockchain Week will be held at the Hanoi National Convention Center from August 1st to 2nd, attracting more than 20,000 participants and having a media exposure of 45 million, making it the largest blockchain and Web3 industry event in Vietnam.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21645</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>