<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:33:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Anthropic has completed a $1.3 billion new funding round, propelling it to the world&apos;s highest valued AI startup.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27417</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the artificial intelligence company Anthropic announced that it has recently completed a financing round of $13 billion, with its valuation soaring to $183 billion. This financing, which far exceeded expectations, has made it one of the world&apos;s most highly valued startups. The round was led by Iconiq Capital, with Fidelity Management and Research Company, Lightspeed Venture Partners, Singapore&apos;s GIC, Insight Partners, and the Qatar Investment Authority (QIA) participating.According to previous reports, Anthropic&apos;s initial target was to raise $5 billion, which was later increased to $10 billion, and finally reached $13 billion. In a statement on Tuesday, Anthropic said that this investment &quot;validates Anthropic&apos;s unprecedented growth rate and solidifies our position as the preferred intelligent platform for enterprises, developers, and high-end users.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27417</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Price Hits Another All-Time High, Safe-Haven Demand and Rate Cut Expectations Fuel Rally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27416</link>
      <description>September 3rd. The price of gold reached a record high because of the escalating demand for safe havens, strengthened expectations of a U.S. interest rate cut, and continuous central bank gold purchases. Krishan Gopaul, the Market Intelligence Manager at the World Gold Council, pointed out that the ongoing market uncertainties, concerns about the independence of the Federal Reserve, reignited expectations of a September rate cut, the resurfacing of U.S. stagflation risks, and the general weakness of the U.S. dollar have jointly enhanced the attractiveness of gold. Geopolitical tensions and tariff concerns have further consolidated this trend. Gold ETFs, gold bars, and gold coins continue to receive strong investor demand, while central banks around the world are continuously promoting reserve diversification, ensuring that the core factors driving this rally will not fade away in the short term. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI is signing a multi-signature burn agreement for 47 million tokens, with 2/3 signatures currently executed.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27415</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the cryptocurrency project of the Trump family, World Liberty Financial, is in the process of signing a pending agreement to burn 47 million WLFI tokens through a multi-signature procedure. Currently, 2/3 of the signatures have been obtained.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27415</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RWA&apos;s First Unicorn Figure Aims to Raise $526 Million Through Initial IPO, Valued at Over $4 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27414</link>
      <description>September 3rd: Figure, the first stock of RWA, intends to raise $526 million through an Initial Public Offering (IPO), with a valuation exceeding $4 billion, joining the trend of blockchain companies like Circle, Bullish, and Gemini going public. Regulatory filings submitted by Figure on Tuesday revealed plans to issue 21.5 million shares of stock at a price ranging from $18 to $20 per share, and an expected issuance of 4.9 million shares to existing shareholders. At the highest end of this price range, this IPO will result in a valuation of approximately $4.3 billion. Figure submitted its initial listing application to regulators in secret last month, disclosing its listing plans. The latest filings suggest that Figure plans to set the IPO pricing date on September 10th.Figure Technology Solutions (FTS) was founded by Mike Cagney, who is the co-founder and former CEO of SoFi. Unlike the traditional financial institution approach, Figure has been blockchain-native since its establish</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27414</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Denies H100/H200 Chip Shortage Rumors: Ample Inventory to Instantly Meet Order Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27413</link>
      <description>September 3rd, Nvidia (NVDA.O) declared that the recent media reports regarding the &quot;limited supply&quot; and &quot;sold out&quot; rumors about Nvidia&apos;s H100/H200 chips are all inaccurate. As detailed in the financial report, while cloud service partners are indeed capable of leasing all of their H100/H200 chips online, this does not imply that Nvidia is unable to accept new orders. With an ample stock of H100/H200, they can promptly fulfill all order requirements. Rumors suggesting that the H20 chip is cutting into the supply of H100/H200 or Blackwell products are also entirely unfounded—sales of the H20 chip will never have an impact on Nvidia&apos;s supply capabilities for other products. (Jinse)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27413</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Staking Queue Hits Highest Level Since September 2023, Admission Queue Currently at 832,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27412</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the staking demand for new validators activated on the Ethereum PoS network has witnessed a significant increase and reached the highest level since September 2023. The current admission queue is 832,000 ETH, which is valued at approximately $35.77 billion. The queue time is 14 days and 11 hours.The current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily at 861,000 ETH and remains at a high level. Calculated at the current price, the ETH exiting the PoS network is approximately $37 billion, and the withdrawal delay is 14 days and 23 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27412</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pump.fun has released the Dynamic Fee V1 update, where the creator fee will be tiered by market cap.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27411</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Pump.fun, the token launchpad within the Solana ecosystem, announced the Dynamic Fee V1 update. The creator fee for tokens will now be tiered according to market capitalization. This implies that the higher the token&apos;s market capitalization, the lower the percentage of the creator fee. This fee structure is applicable to all PumpSwap tokens, whether they are old or new. The Pump.fun protocol fees and the fees that are automatically compounded to liquidity providers (including burned LPs) remain unchanged from before.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27411</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink CEO: Ethereum is the Wall Street of Capital, combining Productivity, Profitability, and Programmability</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27410</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Joseph Chalom, the Co-CEO of SharpLink which is the second-largest treasury company in Ethereum, published an article to explain why ETH is favored by Wall Street capital. He stated that Ethereum is the place where capital wants to go. With 10 years of continuous operation, it ensures the storage of trillions of dollars in value. At the same time, the new foundation leadership is making significant progress at the L1 level. Therefore, SharpLink is very optimistic about the entire Ethereum ecosystem, including L1 and L2, believing that it will attract capital attention. Since Ethereum on-chain transactions are secure and ongoing, SharpLink believes that ETH is a high-quality treasury asset - the world&apos;s first truly trusted commodity with productivity, profitability, programmability and is rapidly becoming a core institutional digital asset.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27410</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venus Initiates Emergency Vote: Security Recovery Protocol and User Funds Recoupment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27409</link>
      <description>September 3rd: In response to a security incident where users fell victim to a phishing attack, the Venus Protocol has released an emergency vote. This has prompted the protocol to quickly pause in order to protect asset safety. The team has proposed a partial protocol recovery to adjust positions and prevent liquidation. Additionally, a forced liquidation of the attacker&apos;s wallet is also part of the plan. The protocol will be fully restored once the security review is completed.The vote encompasses:- Partial recovery of the Venus Protocol within 5 hours (allowing for debt repayment/supply of funds);- Recovery of stolen funds within 7 hours;- Security review of Venus within 24 hours to prevent any other users from experiencing similar attacks.Full recovery of Venus - Updates and timelines will be announced separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27409</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase International Site to List ZEN, UMA, and GMX Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27408</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Coinbase International is set to list ZEN, UMA, and GMX perpetual contracts. The markets for ZEN-PERP, UMA-PERP, and GMX-PERP will commence on September 4, 2025, at 9:30 AM (UTC) or thereafter.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>