<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:44:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest holds over $267 million worth of BMNR stock.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28030</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to the Ark Invest Tracker, Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest currently holds more than $267 million worth of Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) stock across its three funds. These funds include:· ARKK holds $178.6 million worth of BMNR stock;· ARKW holds $31 million worth of BMNR stock;· ARKF holds $57.7 million worth of BMNR stock.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28030</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Solana Launchpad Market Share in the Last 24 Hours: pump.fun, Letsbonk, Meteora DBC Rank Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28029</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, in the past 24 hours within the Solana launchpad market share ranking, pump.fun took the first place with 70.2%, Letsbonk came in second with 17.9%, and Meteora DBC ranked third with 5.2%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28029</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin&apos;s market cap is now close to twice the combined market cap of Mastercard and Visa.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28028</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to the data from 8Marketcap, the market capitalization of Bitcoin has nearly reached twice that of the combined market capitalizations of Mastercard and Visa. Currently, the market capitalization of Bitcoin is approximately $2.212 trillion. The market capitalization of Visa is around $666.16 billion, and that of Mastercard is approximately $528.14 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28028</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The National Natural Science Foundation of China has released a research project on Stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28027</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the National Natural Science Foundation of China issued the 3rd quarter 2025 Emergency Management Project titled &quot;Research on Global Stablecoin Risk Governance and Cross-Border Collaborative Regulatory System.&quot; It was stated that stablecoins, as a form of digital asset designed to be pegged to the value of a fiat currency or a specific asset, have become a core bridge connecting traditional finance and the crypto ecosystem due to their potential for efficient cross-border liquidity. The scale and influence of stablecoins pose a profound challenge to the current international monetary system and global financial regulatory framework.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28027</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Partner: Bitcoin Will Only Truly Top Out When Money Printing Stops</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28026</link>
      <description>September 7th: The former crypto lead at Ark Invest and current partner at Placeholder VC, Chris Burniske, stated that Bitcoin will only reach its true peak when the money printer stops. The fluctuations within a market cycle are short-term phenomena; the long-term trend is the inevitable rule.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28026</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wences&apos;s Response to Whether He Will Run for President in 2028: &quot;I don&apos;t want to think about that. I&apos;m more focused on the present.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28025</link>
      <description>September 7th. On September 6th in the local time zone, Fox News presented an interview featuring the U.S. Vice President Pence. When queried about his intention to run for president in 2028, Pence replied, &quot;I am not concentrating on such matters; I am more concentrated on the present.&quot; (Global Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28025</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITO Surges Over 24% in 24 Hours, Currently Trading at $0.236</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28024</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on HTX market data, MITO witnessed a surge of more than 24% in the past 24 hours and is currently trading at $0.236.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The amount of ETH queued for exiting the Ethereum PoS network has been decreasing for 9 consecutive days, with approximately $3 billion worth of ETH currently queued for withdrawal.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28023</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current amount of ETH leaving the queue of Ethereum&apos;s PoS network has been continuously decreasing for 9 days. It currently stands at 698,120 ETH, which is approximately worth $3 billion. The estimated exit waiting time is about 12 days and 3 hours.At the same time, there are approximately 860,782 ETH in the queue waiting to join the network, with a value of around $3.7 billion. The expected activation delay is about 14 days and 23 hours.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may have decided to cash out after Ethereum experienced a significant rebound from the April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also increasing the entry queue. For example, publicly traded companies like SharpLink Gamin</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28023</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve&apos;s probability of a 25 basis point interest rate cut in September is 89%, and the probability of a 50 basis point cut is 11%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28022</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on CME&apos;s FedWatch tool, there is an 89% probability of a 25-basis-point Fed rate cut in September and a 11% probability of a 50-basis-point cut.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28022</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Slams Trump Family for Amassing $5 Billion through Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28021</link>
      <description>September 7th: The U.S. Democratic Senator Elizabeth Warren made a video public, criticizing President Trump. She accused him of failing to keep his promise to reduce inflation. Meanwhile, reports indicated that his family&apos;s cryptocurrency business was alleged to have accumulated billions of dollars. Warren said in the video: &quot;What astonishes everyone is that Trump is actually a major con artist. The prices of food, gasoline, school supplies, and strollers are all on the rise. Trump has let down ordinary working families. He did not lower grocery prices. Instead, he played a &apos;red light, green light&apos; game with tariffs, actually increasing people&apos;s shopping expenses.&quot;Warren specifically pointed out that the Trump family&apos;s holdings in the WLFI token had increased significantly in value, bringing them an estimated $5 billion in paper wealth growth. She added: &quot;Trump has made a lot of profits during his presidency, while you have to bear higher costs. This is a betrayal that we will never</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28021</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>