<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:51:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Quarterly Proof of Reserves #33: Total Value of BTC, ETH, USDT, and USDC Reaches $28.8 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22477</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per official channels, OKX released the 33rd Proof of Reserves (PoR). There is a 100% reserve rate for 22 listed assets. Specifically, the reserve rates for BTC, ETH, USDT, and USDC are 106%, 101%, 103%, and 100% respectively, with a total value of $28,815,134,660.It is reported that OKX is the first platform in the industry to achieve continuous PoR releases for more than two years. During this period, OKX has been releasing PoR on a monthly basis. The number of listed assets has increased from 3 to 22. OKX has successively upgraded the PoR system using technologies such as Merkle Tree, Merkle Mountain Range, and zk-STARK in order to enhance the transparency of user assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22477</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mantle: Total ETH and Derivative ETH Holdings Reach 101,867 Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22476</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Ethereum Layer 2 network Mantle disclosed its Ethereum reserve data on the X platform. As of now, the holdings consist of 101,867 ETH and mETH, with an approximate value of $388 million. This encompasses ETH (4,454), mETH (77,218), and ETH in MI4 (20,195).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22476</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet has launched the Altventure 2025 Shitcoin Season event, with a total prize pool exceeding 700,000 USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22475</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to official channels, Bitget Wallet has officially initiated the Altventure 2025 Shitcoin Season-themed event. This event will be carried out in multiple phases, and the total prize pool amounts to 777,000 USDT.The first stage became active on July 24th, encompassing a Swap trading challenge and contract rewards. The overall prize pool for the event is 777,000 USDT. Users are able to earn points through daily predictions of Altcoin price increases, trading volume rankings, PNL% rankings, and other means. These points can be exchanged for USDT in a proportional manner and distributed through on-chain airdrops.It is reported that Altventure 2025 is an annual shitcoin-themed exploration event launched by Bitget Wallet. Its purpose is to enhance user focus and participation in market hotspots and potential assets by means of interactive tasks. Currently, Bitget Wallet supports more than 130 public chains and 29 blockchain cross-chain protocols, providing a wider</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22475</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has opened the Unified Account function to all institutional users, and retail users can apply for access.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22474</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Bitget has officially made the unified account function available to all institutional users. At the same time, it has opened the application channel for eligible individual investors. This functionality enables users to manage spot, contract, and leverage trading within a single margin pool, achieving unified profit and loss calculation and margin sharing, which effectively enhances fund efficiency and risk management capabilities.The institutional business is one of Bitget&apos;s core strategies for 2025. Since the start of the year, the platform has launched the Bitget PRO Plan and upgraded institutional lending services and liquidity incentive mechanisms to further improve the professional trader ecosystem. As of the first half of 2025, more than 90% of top institutional traders have accessed Bitget, and institutional users have contributed more than 50% of the total trading volume on the platform. Recently, Bitget has further intensified its cooperation with liquidity p</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22474</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: If the Fed&apos;s tone softens, US Treasury bond yields may fall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22473</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Bockel from DHF Capital stated in a report that if the Federal Reserve moderates its tone, U.S. Treasury yields could decrease. The Chief Business Officer said: &quot;The bond market may also respond to any surprises or rapid changes in interest rate expectations.&quot;He mentioned that the market generally anticipates that the Federal Reserve will maintain the interest rate unchanged, but speculation about a rate cut in September is on the rise. Bockel stated that the market is also keeping an eye on the wording of the Fed&apos;s statement and whether Fed governors Waller and Bowman may dissent, as they have previously hinted at a preference for loose monetary policy. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22473</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has increased its holdings by acquiring 2000 ETH at an average price of $3839, totaling approximately $7.68 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22472</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per the monitoring of Spot On Chain, yesterday the whale &quot;0x720&quot; liquidated a long position in ETH and made a profit of $6 million.In the past 9 hours, the whale withdrew $12.68 million from HyperLiquid and transferred it to Binance. It has purchased 2000 ETH at a price of $3839 per coin (approximately $7.68 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Meme Coin NEET Surges to Over $15 Million Market Cap Briefly Before Falling Back, Up Over 91% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22471</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to the GMGN market data, the meme coin NEET in the Solana ecosystem briefly exceeded a market capitalization of $15 million and then retreated. Currently, the market capitalization has reached $12.3 million, with a 24-hour increase of over 91%.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins have no practical use case and experience large price fluctuations. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22471</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Towns (TOWNS) on August 5th.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22470</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Binance Alpha is set to become the first platform to list Towns (TOWNS) on August 5th. Once the Alpha trading commences, eligible users can access the Alpha event page and utilize Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop. Further details will be provided at a later time.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22470</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Osaka Exchange in Japan is reportedly considering listing cryptocurrency derivatives.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22469</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to Bloomberg, the Osaka Exchange, which is a part of the Japan Exchange Group (JPX), is contemplating the listing of cryptocurrency-related futures and options. The president of the Osaka Exchange, Takasuke Yokoyama, stated in an interview that cryptocurrency-related products are &quot;potential candidate products&quot; and that they will conduct a thorough study of the specifications of overseas products while closely monitoring the regulatory trends of the Japanese Financial Services Agency. Yokoyama also mentioned that the company will give consideration to launching ETFs related to crypto assets. Since the Osaka Exchange mainly deals with derivatives, if this comes to fruition, the ETF will be listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22469</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum 10th Anniversary Torch NFT Holder Addresses Surpass 280,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22468</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to on-chain data, the address of the Ethereum Tenth Anniversary Torch Commemorative NFT holder has exceeded 280,000. The minting will end at 24:00 on July 31st (UTC+8).BlockBeats previously reported that Ethereum launched &quot;The Torch&quot; NFT to pay tribute to those who have shaped its development and values in the first decade of Ethereum and will support the future development of Ethereum. In the 10 days leading up to Ethereum&apos;s tenth anniversary, this The Torch NFT will symbolically pass between wallets. On July 30th, The Torch NFT will be burned to commemorate Ethereum&apos;s tenth anniversary. On that day, everyone can mint a commemorative NFT.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>