<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:39:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, Letsbonk has only minted 1 graduate token, causing its market share to shrink to 1%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25365</link>
      <description>On August 20th, BONK&apos;s Meme launchpad Letsbonk witnessed a notable decrease in token issuance and graduation tokens within the past 24 hours. It dropped from recent peaks and had once exceeded Pump.fun. In the past 24 hours, Letsbonk only had 1 graduation token, while Pump.fun had 166.According to Dune Analytics data, in the past 24 hours, the token issuance of Pump.fun was approximately 20,096, LetsBONK was 338, and BAGS was 920. It is noteworthy that the Launchpad platform Heaven has recently experienced a significant increase in market share, with a token issuance of 6,967 in the last 24 hours.In the past 24 hours, in the Solana token launch platform market share ranking, Pump.fun holds 63.6%, Heaven holds 28%, and Letsbonk&apos;s market share has contracted to 1%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25365</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Pre-market: Most Cryptocurrency Stocks Up, Bitmine Up 2.73%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25364</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on market data, pre-market cryptocurrency stocks in the US generally rose. These included:Circle (CRCL), which rose by 1.05%;Coinbase (COIN), with a rise of 0.8%;MicroStrategy (MSTR), increasing by 1%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET), rising by 2.01%;Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), up by 2.73%;BTCS Inc (BTCS), which saw a rise of 3.07%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25364</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Crown has been appointed as the President and CEO of the TON Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25363</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the TON Foundation announced today that Max Crown has been appointed as the President and CEO of the TON Foundation. Meanwhile, Manuel Stotz is stepping down in order to focus on his new role as the Executive Chairman of Verb Tech Company (which is soon to be renamed TON Strategy Co.).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25363</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A trader entered a long position with 25x leverage on ETH at $4,087.9, with a current unrealized profit of approximately $283,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25362</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as monitored by TheDataNerd, a trader initiated a 25x long position on ETH at $4,087.9 today. Currently, there is a floating profit of approximately $283,000.Since 2024, the address has been continuously taking long positions. There have been realized profits of about $8.5 million from taking long positions on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25362</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Smart Money trader has made over $48 million in profit over the past 4 months.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25361</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, a Smart Money trader whose address begins with 0x15b3 has achieved a profit of more than 48 million USD within the past 4 months.It is reported that since April, this address has taken long positions in 15 different tokens on Hyperliquid, including ETH, XRP, SOL, and LINK, with a total profit exceeding 38 million USD.In April, the trader also purchased 309 WBTC at an average price of 79,778 USD (approximately 24.68 million USD). Since June 16th, 199 WBTC have been sold at an average price of 110,687 USD (approximately 22.06 million USD). Currently, 110 WBTC (approximately 12.5 million USD) are held, with a profit of nearly 10 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25361</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashKey Capital has transferred 5,412,000 MNT to Bybit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25360</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, HashKey Capital transferred 5.412 million MNT to Bybit 15 minutes ago, with an approximate value of $7.42 million.It is reported that HashKey Capital withdrew these MNT from Bybit to an on-chain address 8 months ago. And now, within the past 15 minutes, it has been transferred back to Bybit. When withdrawn 8 months ago, the value of the MNT was $6.33 million, and now it is worth $7.42 million, indicating an increase in value of $1.09 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Stock Trading Platform StableStock Completes Seed Round Funding with Investment from YZi Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25359</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, the on-chain stock trading platform StableStock announced the completion of its seed round of financing. Participating in this round were YZi Labs, MPCi, and Vertex Ventures.StableStock is a trading-focused decentralized finance (TraDeFi) platform that is constructed around the on-chain stock ecosystem. Currently, StableStock is open to users for public testing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25359</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches RWA Index Perpetual Contract, with AAPL, NVDA, CRCL as the First Batch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25358</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, Bitget has officially launched RWA Index Perpetual Contracts. The initial assets to be listed are AAPL/USDT (RWA), NVDA/USDT (RWA), and CRCL/USDT (RWA). The underlying assets of the RWA contract are composed of stock-tokenized RWA index assets circulating in the market. Each index incorporates multiple RWA tokens to track prices from different third-party issuers. Its pricing mechanism is based on the encryption perpetual contract model. It dynamically adjusts index sources according to factors such as market activity, trading volume, liquidity, and regularly discloses weights to ensure pricing flexibility and fairness. In terms of trading rules, the RWA Index Perpetual Contract adopts a 5x24-hour trading system. There are price freezes during weekends and stock market holidays to avoid liquidation. It supports order cancellation but pauses new order submissions. Fund cost settlements resume with the resumption of trading. The product continues</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25358</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list XPIN Network (XPIN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25357</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, Binance Alpha is set to list XPIN Network (XPIN) on August 22nd. Once trading commences, eligible users will be able to claim an airdrop by utilizing Binance Alpha points on the Alpha activity page. Further details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25357</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Bitcoin Breaks Below $113,000, Cryptocurrency Stocks Tumble 6.45%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25356</link>
      <description>August 20th. In the evening, Bitcoin failed to break through the $116,000 mark and then witnessed a significant weakening of bullish momentum, resulting in a rapid price decline. It has now dropped below the $113,000 support level and briefly touched $112,000 intra-day. If the downward trend persists, it may test the key psychological level of $100,000. Ethereum is also under pressure and has fallen below $4,100.Affected by the weak cryptocurrency market, related stocks have also declined simultaneously. On August 19th, this sector as a whole fell by 6.45%, and on the 20th night session, most continued the downward trend: Bitmine Immersion Technologies dropped by nearly 4%, Bullish by more than 3%, Robinhood by 2%, and Coinbase by around 1%. This indicates that market risk appetite is decreasing, and investors need to remain cautious in the short term.In the context of intensified market volatility, investors need more flexible and secure trading tools. BiyaPay offers users over 20</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25356</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>