<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 01:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: US SEC Releases New Standards for Cryptocurrency ETFs, Coinbase Futures-Linked Asset Poised to Be First Approved</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22560</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bloomberg ETF Senior Analyst Eric Balchunas stated on social media that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has presented a new trading platform filing for cryptocurrency ETPs, outlining the &quot;listing standard.&quot;The main points are: any token listed on the Coinbase derivatives trading platform and having futures trading in progress for more than 6 months is likely to obtain approval. Currently, there are approximately a dozen mainstream coins that meet this standard, similar to those with a predicted probability of over 85% previously. The only remaining aspect is the timing, and these ETFs may potentially receive approval in a concentrated manner between September and October of this year.For altcoins or meme coins (such as BONK, TRUMP) that have not yet launched futures and are to be ETF-ized, they will need to rely on the path of the &quot;Investment Company Act of 1940&quot; and adopt a different product structure. However, based on historical experience, regula</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale/Institution Accumulates 5774 MKR, Approximately $11.84 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22559</link>
      <description>On July 31, according to ChainNews, a whale or institution has been continuously amassing 5774 MKR (approximately $11.84 million) through FalconX over the past 13 days. The average price is $2051.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22559</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades has been liquidated 4 times in a row, losing $1.93 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22558</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, trader AguilaTrades suffered consecutive liquidations for 4 times. However, they subsequently slightly augmented their Bitcoin position. As of now, in this trade, AguilaTrades has incurred approximately $1.93 million in losses. The total cumulative loss has exceeded $38.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin surpasses $120,000, the mainstream CEX cumulative short liquidation strength will reach 475 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22557</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to Coinglass data, if Bitcoin exceeds $120,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will amount to $475 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin falls below $116,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $86.25 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the precise number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows the extent to which reaching a certain price level will be influenced. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price reaching that level will trigger a stronger reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale/Institutional Investor has increased their holdings by 32,855 ETH, equivalent to approximately $124.07 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22556</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale or institution has once more received 32,855 Ethereum (ETH) from FalconX. This amount is approximately worth $124.07 million.The wallet address currently holds a total of 113,029 Ethereum, which is approximately worth $430.38 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22555</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin experienced a rebound and surpassed $11,800. It is currently trading at $118,063, with a 24-hour percentage change of 0.22%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22555</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cboe BZX and Arca Submit New Listing Standards Proposal to the US SEC to Streamline Cryptocurrency ETF Approval Process</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22554</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as reported by The Block, both the Cboe BZX Exchange and Arca have put forward listing standards for a cryptocurrency ETF with the intention of accelerating the approval process for its public trading.In a filing submitted to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Wednesday, Cboe BZX requested the SEC to make an amendment to a rule so as to &quot;enable commodity-based trust shares that meet the requirements of the proposed Rule 14.11(e)(4) to be listed and traded in a generic manner.&quot; This particular rule pertains to the trading and listing of commodity-based trust shares and stipulates specific requirements for the listing of certain shares on trading platforms.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22554</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Q2 Crypto Business Revenue Reaches $160 Million, Slightly Below Expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22551</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to Bloomberg, Robinhood Markets Inc. announced that its second-quarter revenue had exceeded the expectations of Wall Street, and this was due to the strong growth of its cryptocurrency trading business.In a press release on Wednesday, the company stated that the total net revenue for the quarter had increased by 45% year-on-year to $989 million, surpassing the average expectation of $9.215 billion surveyed by Bloomberg&apos;s analysts. The net profit also exceeded expectations, more than doubling to reach $386 million.The revenue related to cryptocurrency had increased by 98% to $160 million, which was slightly lower than the goal of achieving triple-digit growth for the sixth consecutive quarter. Analysts had previously expected the cryptocurrency revenue to be $162.1 million.In June of this year, Robinhood quickly attracted the attention of regulators in Europe after offering &quot;tokenized&quot; stocks to 150,000 customers in 30 countries, representing the company&apos;s</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House Proposes Legislation to Require U.S. Taxpayers to Report and Pay Taxes on Overseas Cryptocurrency Accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22553</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per Decrypt&apos;s report, on Wednesday in local time, the White House put forward to Congress the consideration of legislation that demands U.S. taxpayers to report their &quot;overseas digital asset accounts.&quot; The Trump administration indicated that this action would assist in preventing Americans from transferring cryptocurrency assets abroad.The policy proposal stated that this policy transformation would &quot;facilitate the development and utilization of digital assets in the United States and alleviate the concerns from the external world that the absence of reporting mechanisms could place the United States or U.S. digital asset trading platforms at a disadvantage.&quot;This proposal is one of several proposals within a 168-page crypto report released by the Digital Asset Market Working Group on Wednesday. The working group is headed by White House Director of Crypto and Artificial Intelligence David Sacks.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22553</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House Releases Digital Asset Report, Bitcoin Reserve Plan Without Substantial Update</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22552</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the White House made public the long-anticipated digital assets report. This report sketched out a national strategy intended to position the United States as a global leader in the blockchain, cryptocurrency market, and tokenized finance sectors. Although the report encompassed a broad range of digital asset policy areas, it did not offer a substantial update on the government&apos;s plans regarding a Bitcoin reserve as part of the strategy. Instead, it merely restated the language from President Trump&apos;s executive order in January and did not list specific follow-up steps or an implementation timeline.The release of this report originated from an executive order signed by President Trump in January. This order established an interagency working group on digital assets and other emerging technologies like artificial intelligence. This 166-page document was jointly written by White House Crypto and AI Czar David Sacks and Chief of Staff Bo Hines. It consolidated input from th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>