<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:55:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Exit of PoS Network Validators Drives Ethereum&apos;s Staking TVL Beyond $30 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26765</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as reported by The Block, Ethereum&apos;s liquidity restaking protocol has witnessed rapid expansion in recent years. The total locked value across various platforms has reached $30 billion, indicating a substantial shift in validators deploying ETH to obtain rewards. This growth occurs as native ETH staking activities have increased, leading validators to exit traditional staking mechanisms and seek more flexible opportunities.Leading protocols like EtherFi and Eigenpie have captured a significant portion of the market since the start of the year, and this sector continues to exhibit a sustained upward trend through the middle of 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26765</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares Submits Application to SEC to Launch SEI Spot ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26764</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per official channels, 21Shares has presented an SEI ETF S-1 Registration Statement to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In the prospectus, it is stated that they intend to investigate SEI staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26764</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Waller: Supports Fed 25 Basis Point Rate Cut in September Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26763</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Federal Reserve Governor Waller expressed that he is in favor of a 25-basis-point rate cut at the Fed&apos;s September meeting and anticipates further cuts within the next 3 to 6 months. He does not think there is a need for a larger rate cut in September unless the August jobs report indicates a considerable economic weakness while still maintaining good inflation control. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 22:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26763</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Powell Lawyer Says Mortgage Dispute May Be Due to &apos;Typographical Error&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26762</link>
      <description>August 29th. The attorney representing Federal Reserve Board Governor Lael Brainard contended that the mortgage dispute which led to Trump&apos;s request to fire her might have originated from an &quot;unintentional paperwork mistake.&quot; The aim was to undermine Trump and FHFA Director Mark Calabria&apos;s fraud allegations. The legal team stated that even if there was an error, it was not done with intentional deception and no one was harmed, in line with the legal &quot;substantive&quot; standard.&quot;The possibility exists that Brainard, long before joining the Board, might have mistakenly marked the home&apos;s use in the mortgage application. However, there was neither intent nor a substantive impact. This does not meet the &apos;just cause&apos; necessary for removal.&quot; The attorney wrote in a filing for a temporary restraining order. The legal team also pointed out that Trump and Calabria did not even explicitly claim that Brainard reaped any benefits from the error or that the error was intentional. (Golden Finance)Earl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI Launches Efficient Inference Model Grok Code Fast 1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26761</link>
      <description>August 29th, xAI made an announcement about the launch of the efficient inference model Grok Code Fast 1, which showcased remarkable performance in AI-assisted programming.During the next 7 days, Grok Code Fast 1 will be freely accessible on mainstream AI programming platforms such as Cursor, GitHub Copilot, Cline, opencode, Windsurf, Roo Code, and Kilo Code. (Gold10)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26761</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise: Bitcoin Expected to Reach $1.3 Million by 2035</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26760</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per Cointelegraph, the cryptocurrency asset management firm Bitwise has presented the latest Bitcoin price prediction. It is estimated that the price of Bitcoin will ascend to $1.3 million by 2035, primarily driven by institutional demand and Bitcoin&apos;s limited supply. This report was released as a part of Bitwise&apos;s &quot;Bitcoin Long-Term Capital Market Assumptions,&quot; forecasting that Bitcoin will attain a 28.3% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) over the next decade, which significantly outpaces traditional assets like stocks (6.2%), bonds (4.0%), and gold (3.8%).In the base case scenario, Bitwise anticipates that Bitcoin will reach $1.3 million by 2035. In the bullish scenario, Bitcoin might soar to $2.97 million (CAGR 39.4%). And in the bearish scenario, it could plummet to $88,005 (CAGR 2%).This price range showcases the notable volatility in the Bitcoin market despite the growing participation of institutions. Bitcoin is no longer a market dominated solely by reta</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Delays Decision on Grayscale Ethereum Trust Spot ETF&apos;s Proposal to Add Staking Feature</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26759</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on market information, the US SEC has postponed a decision regarding the authorization of GrayScale&apos;s Ethereum Trust (ETHE) to incorporate staking functionality.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Solana IDO Platforms by 24h Market Share: pump.fun, Letsbonk, Believe</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26758</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours, in the Solana issuance platform market share ranking, pump.fun holds the top position with 83.4%, Letsbonk comes in second with 6.99%, and Believe takes the third place with 2.43%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC has issued guidance on the Foreign Trading Platform Registration Framework, providing regulatory clarity for non-U.S. trading platforms seeking access to the U.S. market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26757</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the Market Oversight Department of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) issued guidance on a Foreign-Based Trading Platform (FBOT) registration framework today. This framework is applicable to non-U.S. entities that are legally formed and operate outside the United States and wish to provide direct trading platform access to individuals located in the United States. The CFTC&apos;s FBOT registration framework is applicable to all markets, regardless of asset class, including traditional and digital asset markets.Acting Chairman Caroline D. Pham stated: &quot;The release of today&apos;s FBOT guidance provides regulatory clarity for those who, due to the &apos;enforcement-based regulation&apos; of the past few years, have left U.S. trading activities and are now seeking a legal return to the United States. By reaffirming the CFTC&apos;s longstanding practices of providing U.S. traders with diverse options to access the world&apos;s deepest and most liquid markets, as well as a wide range</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26757</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC will issue guidance clarifying the rules for foreign trading platform registration.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26756</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Crypto journalist Eleanor Terrett disclosed that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is scheduled to issue guidance to clarify its Foreign Board of Trade (FBOT) registration rules. This provides a legal avenue for non-U.S. exchanges to enable U.S. users to trade on their platforms. Acting Chairman Caroline D. Pham stated that this is a means to bring crypto activities &quot;back to the U.S.&quot; as such activities had previously flowed out due to enforcement actions during the Biden administration. At the same time, it reaffirms the regulatory framework that has been in place since the 1990s. For U.S. traders, this implies that they can legally access more global liquidity. For the crypto industry, this is another step towards regulatory clarity and is also part of the Trump administration&apos;s &quot;crypto sprint&quot; strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26756</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>