<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has increased its holdings by 254.92 BTC, accumulating a total position of $249 million in BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26127</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale once more received 254.92 BTC from FalconX, which is valued at $28.57 million. Currently, within the past month, this whale has amassed a total of 2,219 BTC, and the total value is approximately $249 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26127</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $112,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26126</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $112,000 and is currently trading at $111,916, with a 24-hour decrease of 2.68%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26126</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XerpaAI makes its debut at WebX, unveiling the world&apos;s first AI Growth Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26125</link>
      <description>On August 25th, XerpaAI officially launched the world&apos;s first AI Growth Agent (AGA) and put forward the brand slogan &quot;Speed Up Your Growth.&quot; It is committed to providing an all-in-one intelligent growth solution for emerging projects.According to data, more than 70% of pre-listed Web3 projects lack dedicated growth personnel, and more than half of the budget is difficult to generate effective results. XerpaAI combines the Create-Distribute-Optimize growth model with an AI-driven system to help projects achieve real engagement. Through the Xerpa Index, complex influence metrics are quantified into standard scores to assist in data-driven decision-making.XerpaAI will also successively launch features such as Creative Labs 2.0 and Autonomous Agents to continuously expand the boundaries of AI-driven growth. The management team stated: &quot;Our goal is to be the &apos;Sherpa&apos; for emerging projects and guide them across the growth peak.&quot; The release of XerpaAI also marks the entry of Web3 growth</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26125</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Unveils New Brand Image at WebX Summit, Founder Dr. Han Delivers Keynote Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26124</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the WebX Summit commenced in Tokyo, Japan. The globally prominent cryptocurrency exchange Gate unveiled its novel brand image at this event, emphasizing its latest attainments in transaction security, compliance systems, and diversified ecosystem development. By means of interactive demonstrations, the event presented the platform&apos;s comprehensive strength in asset protection, innovative products, and global strategic planning to the participants. Additionally, Gate&apos;s founder and CEO, Dr. Han, delivered a keynote speech during the conference, sharing global cryptocurrency industry trends and platform strategic concepts.As the title sponsor of this conference, Gate will host an exclusive VIP Side Meeting in Tokyo on the evening of August 26th, serving as the official Side Meeting event of WebX. The event will invite project teams, capital institutions, and ecosystem partners from the Asia-Pacific region and around the world to have in-depth discussions on regional colla</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26124</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Profited $1.72 Million from a LINK Swing Trade and Reopened a $16.85 Million LINK Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26123</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale that had made a profit of $1.72 million from scalping LINK two years ago has resurfaced. It recently purchased 663,580 LINK (with a value of $16.85 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: ETH Leading the Market in the Short Term, Funds Will Eventually Flow Back to BTC to Realize Profits</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26122</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Wang Feng, the founder of Blueport Interactive, tweeted that the recent &quot;ETH outperforming while BTC is in a sideways movement&quot; is more of a difference in narrative rhythm. The opportunity window may be short-lived, and investors may not have enough time to complete position adjustments.In the medium to long term, both share the same pool of macro funds, the same set of regulatory dividends, and the same market value curve. ETH should be regarded as a β amplifier of BTC rather than a substitute.Historical experience has shown that during the 2017 ICO and the 2020 DeFi cycles, the heat of ETH actually enhanced the risk premium of BTC. ETH is leverage, and BTC is an anchor. Large funds will ultimately flow back to BTC to cash out profits after the carnival.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance&apos;s new Bonding Curve Participation Threshold: At least 241 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26121</link>
      <description>August 25th, Binance made an announcement about a novel Bonding Curve project named OVERTAKE (TAKE), with a participation threshold of at least 241 points.Subscription Period: August 25, 2025, from 4:00 to 6:00 PM (UTC+8). The subscription will demand 15 points.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun Appears at WebX2025 in Japan: Industry Consensus Drives TRON to Become the Core Network of Global Stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26120</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Justin Sun, the founder of the Tron Foundation, delivered a keynote speech entitled &quot;Tron TRON at the Core of Global Stablecoin Activities&quot; at the WebX Summit in Japan. In the speech, he disclosed that the supply of USDT on the Tron TRON blockchain has exceeded 82 billion US dollars, and the daily active users have exceeded 1 million. He pointed out that this is not a short-term spike but the result of long-term adherence to high speed, low cost, and stability. Stablecoins are at the core of global financial digitization, and Tron TRON has become one of the most reliable networks in this field. He also emphasized that the addition of USD1 shows that more issuers are recognizing the ecosystem advantages of Tron TRON.WebX is known to be one of the largest and most influential blockchain and crypto asset conferences in Asia. It is organized by the Japanese crypto media CoinPost. The conference is held annually in Tokyo and brings together blockchain enterprises, financia</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of a 25 basis point interest rate cut by the Federal Reserve in September has decreased to 87.3%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26119</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on the CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch Tool&quot;, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September has dropped to 87.3%, while the probability of keeping rates unchanged is 12.7%.Former Fed Vice Chair Richard Clarida previously indicated in a report that the Fed appears ready to cut the policy rate soon but will do it with caution. Powell&apos;s highly anticipated speech last week at the annual Jackson Hole symposium did not let the market down, and the Fed&apos;s revised monetary policy framework did not surprise Fed observers. Looking ahead, the Fed reaffirmed its commitment to its dual mandate and only made minor clarifications to its monetary policy framework.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale acquired an additional 2.94 million VIRTUAL tokens at an average price of $1.28, totaling over $3.7 million in value.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26118</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as monitored by OnchainLens, a whale utilized 785 ETH (valued at $3.76 million) to purchase 2.94 million VIRTUAL at a price of $1.28.Address: 0x4322fd98f95a219d2aae2bba6664e3574b4c3708.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26118</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>