<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:58:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem LST Protocol Sanctum Launches V2 Version</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26559</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the LST protocol Sanctum within the Solana ecosystem launched its V2 version. This includes new product updates as well as a brand new website and a dedicated landing page.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26559</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bankless Co-founder: ETH is an Institutional-Grade Investment Asset, Unlocking the Vast World of TradFi to New Heights</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26558</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Ryan Sean Adams, a co-founder of Bankless, stated, &quot;During this cycle, ETH has demonstrated itself to be a high-quality liquid asset (HQLA), similar to US treasuries, gold, and Bitcoin. This will unlock a vast world of traditional finance (TradFi) capital and drive ETH to new heights as an institutional-grade investment asset.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol is pleased to announce that the AUBRAI staking will soon be live.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26555</link>
      <description>August 27th. Bio Protocol made an announcement that the first BioAgent Launch project, AUBRAI staking, will become live on the Bio App within the next 24 to 48 hours. Stakers will obtain BioXP in the subsequent BioAgent and IP-Token sale.In addition, users who acquired more than 50% of their AUBRAI from the Ignition Sale during the first two weeks will be locked in the &quot;BioXP Prison&quot; for three weeks, and they will not receive any BioXP during this period.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26555</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created wallet has transferred 15 million DOLO to Binance, totaling $4.47 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26556</link>
      <description>August 27th. According to Arkham Data, 36 minutes ago, a newly established wallet transferred 15 million DOLO to Binance, with a value of $4.47 million.It is important to note that Binance will commence DOLO spot trading on August 28, 2025, at 0:00 (Beijing time).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Earn, One-Click Buy, Swap, and Margin Trading now support Dolomite (DOLO)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26557</link>
      <description>August 27th. As per an official announcement, Binance Launchpool, the one-click crypto purchase feature, the instant exchange service, and the margin trading option have listed Dolomite (DOLO).Thereafter, starting from August 28, 2025, at 00:00 (UTC +8), Binance Cross Margin and Isolated Margin will include DOLO as a borrowable asset. Additionally, DOLO/USDT and DOLO/USDC Cross Margin and Isolated Margin trading pairs will also be available.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Earnings Report Upcoming, Wall Street Focusing on AI Market Trends</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26554</link>
      <description>August 27th: Once the U.S. stock market closed on this day, NVIDIA is scheduled to release its second-quarter financial report. The market is closely observing its advancements in the U.S.-China AI competition, the chip supply-demand dynamic, and the participation of hyperscale customers. This financial report will also exert an impact on the overall stock market and the trend of the underlying artificial intelligence market. According to market data, NVIDIA is currently showing an intraday increase of 0.03%, and the NVIDIA concept stock CoreWeave is showing activity, currently rising by nearly 5%.Investors generally believed that the performance would exceed expectations prior to the release of the financial report. Based on FactSet data, NVIDIA is anticipated to announce revenue of $46.05 billion for the second quarter, which is higher than the $45 billion guidance provided in the previous quarter. The expected EPS is $0.95, and the net profit is $23.4 billion. The data center reve</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26554</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Treasury Mints 1 Billion USDT on the Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26553</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as monitored by Whale Alert, the Tether Treasury minted 1 billion USDT on the Ethereum blockchain 4 minutes ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26553</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC is planning to expand cryptocurrency regulation using a Nasdaq surveillance system.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26552</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as reported by TheBlock, the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) issued a statement today. It stated that the CFTC will expand cryptocurrency regulation by adopting Nasdaq&apos;s surveillance system in order to protect the market from fraud, abuse, and manipulation. If Congress passes the legislation currently under consideration in both houses, the CFTC&apos;s role in cryptocurrency regulation could be significantly enhanced.CFTC Acting Chairman Caroline Pham said that the new surveillance system will provide the agency with automatic alerts and &quot;cross-market analysis&quot; capabilities. This includes access to comprehensive order book data to support real-time analysis and decision-making for preventing and detecting abuse in both traditional and crypto asset markets. The CFTC is also getting ready for the growth of the cryptocurrency market. Earlier this month, the CFTC launched the &quot;CryptoSprint&quot; initiative, focusing on cryptocurrency futures trading and the recomme</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avail announces the acquisition of the Chain Abstract Protocol Arcana, where the XAR token will be exchanged for AVAIL at a 4:1 ratio.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26551</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Avail made an announcement regarding the acquisition of the chain abstraction protocol Arcana. All XAR tokens will be exchanged for AVAIL at a ratio of 4:1. The tools of Arcana will be integrated into the Avail stack, and a significant portion of its team members will also join Avail. The AVAIL unlocked from the exchange will be vested over a period of 6 to 12 months, while the tokens of the Arcana team will be vested over a period of 3 years.Avail is a modular blockchain infrastructure project that is supported by Peter Thiel&apos;s Founders Fund and other prominent investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoins USDT0 and XAUt0 Launched on the Polygon Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26550</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as reported by Cointelegraph, the operator of USDT0, Everdawn Labs, announced that the cross-chain liquidity USD stablecoin USDT0 and the gold stablecoin XAUt0, which are supported by LayerZero&apos;s Omnichain Fungible Token (OFT), will be launched on the Polygon blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>