<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:19:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A Bitcoin whale address has moved 343 BTC after 12 years of dormancy, worth $40.52 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22291</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a particular Bitcoin whale address made a transfer of 343 BTC after being dormant for 12 years and 18 hours ago. The value of these bitcoins is $40.52 million, with 130.77 BTC ($15.45 million) being deposited into Kraken.This whale address received 343 BTC 12 years ago, and at that time when the price of BTC was $86, the value was $29,600.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22291</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea has officially posted an image with the caption &quot;Something big is coming,&quot; hinting at an upcoming TGE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22290</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Linea officially put out an image accompanied by the caption &quot;Something Big Is Coming,&quot; suggesting that an upcoming TGE is on the way.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22290</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Asset Management Company K33 Acquires 5 Bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22289</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on the monitoring of @btcNLNico, the Bitcoin asset management company K33 increased its holdings by 5 bitcoins and now holds a total of 126 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22289</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Bitcoin Premium Disappears on Coinbase, Signaling a Slowdown in U.S. Institutional Buying Pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22288</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per CoinDesk, the &quot;premium&quot; of Bitcoin on Coinbase has mostly vanished. This premium is typically regarded as an indication of robust demand from U.S. investors, especially institutional ones. Since Coinbase is a cryptocurrency exchange platform listed on Nasdaq, it has a broad user base in the U.S. and is particularly preferred by large institutions. In contrast, Binance has a greater number of retail users globally.In past bull markets, the premium of Bitcoin on Coinbase was once substantial, and it was interpreted as a sign of increased buying pressure from experienced U.S. traders and institutions. The current decline in the premium might suggest a weakening in the activity of this type of capital.The emergence of a negative premium indicates a renewed weakening of the relative demand from U.S. investors, further reinforcing the assessment that the Bitcoin price may undergo a longer period of correction.Note: The Coinbase Bitcoin premium index measures the pe</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades closed an ETH long position with a profit of $1.67 million, and opened a 40x leveraged long position on BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22287</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, trader AguilaTrades liquidated his 25x leverage long position in ETH and achieved a profit of $1.67 million. Subsequently, he reopened a 40x leverage long position in BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22287</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURBOS, as the preferred DEX for the Sui Ecosystem&apos;s Ika TGE, initiates a multi-reward mechanism and early LP activity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22286</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to official information, the secure multiparty computation (MPC) network Ika of the Sui ecosystem announced the official launch of the IKA TGE today. At the same time, IKA-SUI was launched on TURBOS, a leading project in the Sui ecosystem. Both liquidity pools will simultaneously enjoy a dual reward mechanism: rewards of IKA tokens and USDC, with an initial Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of up to 5000%.At the same time, TURBOS has launched the TURBOS x IKA LP Incentive Activity. The first 100 users who provide at least $1000 of liquidity in this pool will have the opportunity to receive exclusive rewards and share a TURBOS token reward pool worth more than $5000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22286</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD1 on Binance experienced a mild depegging issue, briefly dipping to 0.9934 USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22285</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to market data, the price of USD1 on Binance deviated. It briefly dropped to 0.9934 USDT and has now rebounded to 0.9968 USDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22285</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Open Interest Reaches New High Since April 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22284</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Glassnode put out a post indicating that the market share of Ethereum&apos;s open interest contracts has risen to nearly 40%, reaching its highest level since April 2023. In history, only 5% of trading days have had a higher share. This alteration indicates a notable shift in speculative focus, with funds gradually transferring from Bitcoin to Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22284</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered Bank: Ethereum Poised to Break Above $4,000 in Treasury Purchase Trend</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22283</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Geoff Kendrick, the Head of Digital Asset Research at Standard Chartered Bank, stated that as cryptocurrency treasury companies continue to purchase Ethereum, Ethereum is anticipated to experience further growth. Cryptocurrency treasury companies, which are publicly listed companies holding digital assets on their balance sheets, have begun to integrate Ethereum into their asset allocations, and the institutional buying of Ethereum has even exceeded that of Bitcoin.He mentioned that due to the continuous restrictions on cryptocurrency asset investments in many jurisdictions, investors are increasingly turning to alternative channels such as public companies for allocation. &quot;If the inflow of funds can be sustained, Ethereum is expected to break through the key level of $4000 (our current end-of-2025 price prediction).&quot; (Kryptonian)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22283</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Quintenz&apos;s nomination vote to become chairman of the U.S. CFTC has been postponed again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22282</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Bitcoin.com, the progress of Trump&apos;s nomination of Brian Quintenz to serve as the new chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) might once more come to a standstill. His name has been wiped off the meeting agenda of the Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry.Quintenz, a former CFTC commissioner, is currently the policy head of the prominent venture capital firm a16z&apos;s crypto division. During another meeting of the same committee last week, his name was also unexpectedly removed from the voting list. Although the officials did not provide an explanation for the removal, there is widespread speculation that his nomination may be encountering difficulties.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22282</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>