<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:57:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday&apos;s US Spot Bitcoin ETF saw a net inflow of $157.1 million, while the Ethereum ETF saw a net inflow of $65.2 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22240</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Farside&apos;s monitoring, the net inflow of the US Spot Bitcoin ETF was $157.1 million yesterday, and the Ethereum ETF had a net inflow of $65.2 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong Monetary Authority is about to announce the regulatory details for a Stablecoin License.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22239</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the implementation of the Hong Kong &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; is drawing near. Multiple institutions have confirmed to reporters that the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) will hold a technical briefing on the stablecoin issuer regulatory regime at 4:30 pm on this day. It is reported that the technical briefing will be hosted by senior HKMA teams, including Vice President Eddie Cheng, Assistant Vice President (Regulatory Compliance and Anti-Money Laundering) Chan King Weng, Assistant Vice President (Monetary Management) Ho Hon Kit, and Director of Digital Finance Ho Wang Che. The HKMA had previously stated that it would release a stablecoin-specific implementation guidance this month, clarifying core regulatory details such as anti-money laundering and customer identification. The regulator has also reminded the market to adopt a rational attitude and avoid excessive speculation. The number of initial stablecoin issuer licenses will be strictly limited to single digits an</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22239</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $25.9 billion worth of ETH is currently staked on the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $9.8 billion worth of ETH is waiting to be staked.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22238</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per validatorqueue data, currently there are around 684,000 ETH (valued at approximately $25.9 billion at the present price) awaiting to exit the Ethereum PoS network, and the waiting time for exit is about 11 days and 21 hours. Meanwhile, there are approximately 259,000 ETH lined up waiting to join the network, which is about $9.8 billion, and the expected activation delay is about 4 days and 12 hours.Previously reported, this situation indicates the existence of two opposing forces in the market: on one hand, some stakers may have decided to cash out after Ethereum rebounded by more than 160% from its April low, resulting in a significant increase in the exit queue; on the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have increased their ETH holdings and are staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22238</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale sold 3 million Fartcoins approximately 9 hours ago, equivalent to $3.65 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22237</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale sold 3 million Fartcoin with an average price of $1.22 (a total value of $3.65 million) 9 hours ago.Previously, between February 26th and March 21st, the whale had purchased 8.89 million Fartcoin at an average price of $0.26 (with a total cost of $2.31 million).Currently, the whale holds 1.89 million Fartcoin (with a value of $2.16 million), and has a total profit of $8.07 million (+349%).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22237</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinDCX CEO Responds to Coinbase Acquisition Rumors: Will Not Sell Company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22236</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Sumit Gupta, the CEO of CoinDCX, declared that he would not sell the company.Previously, it was reported that Coinbase was in advanced negotiations with the Indian cryptocurrency exchange CoinDCX regarding a potential acquisition of the company.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22236</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An hour ago, a whale transferred 8231 ETH from the Blast Network back to the Ethereum Network and then moved it to Binance.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22233</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, a whale transferred 8,231 ETH ($31.23 million) from the Blast Network back to the ETH Network an hour ago and then moved it to Binance. The whale received airdrops and DeFi income exceeding $12 million on the Blast Network.In December 2023, the whale transferred 45,000 ETH ($102 million) into Blast mining. Since August 2024, it began to gradually withdraw ETH and transfer it to Binance. Today&apos;s withdrawal is basically the whale&apos;s final funds on the Blast Network.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22233</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX App Gets a Complete Makeover, Celebrating Its 12th Anniversary with a System-Wide User Experience Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22235</link>
      <description>On July 29th, on the occasion of its 12th anniversary, Huobi HTX officially launched a new version of its app, completing its first system-level experience upgrade since its establishment. The focus is on visual aesthetics and interaction efficiency, bringing a new &quot;lightweight advancement and ultimate experience&quot; operational feel.This upgrade encompasses all channels including the Web and App. It blends modern and classic color schemes and supports free switching between day and night modes, unifying the brand&apos;s visual identity. Core interfaces such as the homepage, asset page, and trading page have undergone pixel-level reconstruction. The interaction paths are more concise and clear, the information presentation is more focused, and the transaction efficiency is measured to increase by more than 20%.In the deposit/withdrawal and C2C trading scenarios, Huobi HTX has optimized the operation process and implemented one-click transaction mode switching, providing users with a smooth</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22235</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Succinct Open Airdrop Registration, First Round Airdrop Total Supply 5% Token</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22234</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Succinct Foundation tweeted that the registration for the Succinct airdrop has become live. The registration deadline is 3:00 AM Beijing time on August 4th. This airdrop rewards community members who have been actively engaged in the testnet for the past six months. It also recognizes open-source developers who have made contributions to the ZK, cryptography, and blockchain fields, as well as affiliated entities of collaboration agreements, collaborators of Succinct Labs, public goods organizations, and crypto Twitter influencers. Users with badges are eligible to participate in this airdrop.According to the Succinct official documentation page, the total token supply of the Succinct token PROVE is 1 billion. 25% is allocated to the public and future incentives (including 5% for the first airdrop), 25% to the ecosystem and research and development, 29.5% to core contributors, 10.5% to investors, and 10% to foundation operations. Investor and contributor tokens are s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22234</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abraxas Capital&apos;s Short Position Faces Unrealized Loss of Over $100 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22232</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to Arkham Monitoring, Abraxas Capital&apos;s short position is currently experiencing a loss of more than 1 billion US dollars. Abraxas Capital holds the largest short position in Hyperliquid for BTC and ETH. Their account is currently shorting a combined total of nearly 800 million US dollars worth of BTC, ETH, SOL, and HYPE.The account&apos;s current unrealized loss amounts to 106.3 million US dollars, and the liquidation price for Bitcoin is 156,000 US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the listing of a KRW trading pair on Bithumb, C experienced a sudden surge of over 20%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22231</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to HTX market information, Chainbase (C) experienced a short-term price surge of more than 20% because it was listed on Bithumb with a KRW trading pair. Currently, it is trading at $0.4433.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22231</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>