<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Security Report: At Least 3500 Websites Affected by Malicious Injection of Hidden Monero Mining Script</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21345</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, as per the report by Decrypt, researchers from the cybersecurity firm c/side stated that malicious Monero XMR mining software has launched an attack on multiple websites, marking a new surge of cryptojacking. At least 3,500 websites are currently operating with maliciously injected hidden Monero mining scripts. In contrast to traditional cryptojacking, these malicious software limit CPU usage and conceal traffic within WebSocket streams, thus evading the typical indicators of cryptojacking. Hackers are adhering to a &quot;keep a low profile and mine slowly&quot; strategy, targeting unpatched websites and e-commerce servers.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top holder of PUMP tokens deposited 17 billion PUMP tokens to the trading platform, worth $89.5 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21344</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, once the PUMP price dropped below its private/public sale price of 0.004 USD. The holder with the largest amount of PUMP, who had previously put in 100 million USDC to purchase 25 billion PUMP in a private sale round, has reloaded 17 billion PUMP onto the trading platform through FalconX, which is worth 89.5 million USD, and still holds 8 billion PUMP, with a value of 29.58 million USD.In addition, the second-largest holder of PUMP, who had previously spent 50 million USD to buy 12.5 billion PUMP, with a value of 71.37 million USD, has now transferred it all to the trading platform.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of Gyroscope: How Does Gyroscope&apos;s Dynamic Liquidity Pool Outperform Traditional Pools?</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21343</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, Ariah Klages-Mundt, a co-founder of Gyroscope, pointed out in a post that High Volume does not equal High LP Yield. Due to efficient utilization of capital and an intelligent pricing mechanism, Gyroscope&apos;s Dynamic Liquidity Pool is able to achieve a sustainable and relatively high native pool APR (Annual Percentage Rate). In contrast, some trading pools like Uniswap/Aerodrome, although they create high trading volume through &quot;slippage&quot;, this type of high trading APR masks arbitrage losses and does not truly bring actual returns to LPs. Metrics such as those from Dune Data - Markouts PnL are key indicators for measuring LP&apos;s real returns. As shown in the graph for the ETH/USDC trading pair, the yield of Gyroscope&apos;s Dynamic Liquidity Pool is significantly higher than that of other trading pools.Currently, many LPs are struggling to maintain a break-even point in Uni/Aero pools, while using Gyroscope&apos;s Dynamic Liquidity Pool (Dynamic E-CLP) model can easily achieve a more</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21343</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Yala (YALA) with an airdrop point threshold of 238 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21342</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, Binance Alpha is set to list Yala (YALA), and trading will commence on July 22, 2025, at 8:00 PM (UTC+8). Eligible users will be able to claim a 200 YALA token airdrop using Alpha Points on the event page within 24 hours after trading begins.The Binance Alpha airdrop will occur in two phases:Phase 1 (first 18 hours): Users with at least 238 Alpha Points can make the airdrop claim.Phase 2 (last 6 hours): Users with at least 200 Alpha Points can participate in the airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the rewards are not fully distributed, the points threshold will decrease by 10 points per hour.It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will cost 15 Alpha Points, and users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be considered a forfeiture.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21342</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit will launch the FARTCOIN Perpetual Swap Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21341</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, Bybit is set to launch the FARTCOIN U Perpetual Contract.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21341</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit to Launch INJ and HBAR USDT-Margined Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21340</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, Bybit is going to list INJ and HBAR USDT Perpetual Contracts.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21340</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Finance plans to withdraw all funds from CEX and establish a new Asset Transparency Page</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21339</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, the co-founder of DWF Labs and Andrei Grachev of Falcon Finance announced that Falcon Finance plans to withdraw all funds from centralized exchanges and has received a confirmation letter from their auditor. Falcon Finance will launch a new asset transparency page this week and is currently engaged in working on the design structure.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21339</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana-Powered Meme Coin Memecoin&apos;s Market Cap Surges Above $20 Million Briefly</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21338</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, according to GMGN data, the market capitalization of the Solana-based Meme coin briefly exceeded $20 million. Currently, it is reported at $17.3 million. The 24-hour trading volume is $15.9 million, and it has increased by 2236% in 24 hours.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21338</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafePal has partnered with 1inch to launch a WalletDrop collaboration, enhancing DeFi security and user experience.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21337</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, the Web3 wallet brand SafePal joined forces with the DEX aggregator 1inch to launch 300 sets of limited-edition co-branded hardware wallets. The purpose is to enhance the security and usability of DeFi. Against the backdrop of DEX global spot trading volume reaching a record 30% last month, this collaboration holds strategic significance.SafePal CEO and Co-founder Veronica Wong stated, &quot;In the increasingly competitive wallet market, continuous improvement and the implementation of effective user incentives and retention strategies are crucial. Due to the fact that airdrops are often associated with airdrop hunters and bot fake accounts, the Walletdrop activity with 1inch enables us to better identify and serve the user group with genuine DeFi security needs.&quot;1inch Co-founder Sergej Kunz said, &quot;Self-custody lies at the core of decentralization. As DeFi expands and attracts more mainstream users, advocating for secure self-custody practices becomes particularly importan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21337</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Resume Funding Rate Settlement Frequency for XTZUSDT and other Inverse Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21336</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, according to an official announcement, Binance Futures will resume the following U-based perpetual contract funding rate settlement frequency at 20:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, 2025. The funding rate settlement frequency will be adjusted to once every four hours for XTZUSDT, BROCCOLIF3BUSDT, MYXUSDT, MUSDT, and ERAUSDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>