<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:28:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Surges to Touch $3800, With a 24-hour Gain of 4.66%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23558</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum has witnessed a significant surge and reached $3800, showing a 24-hour percentage change of 4.66%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH/BTC Exchange Rate currently stands at 0.0328, with a 24-hour change of +3.31%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23557</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on HTX market data, the exchange rate of ETH to BTC is currently at 0.0328, and it has shown a 24-hour growth of 3.31%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: Trump to Sign Executive Order Allowing 401(k) Retirement Funds to Invest in Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23556</link>
      <description>On August 7th. According to Bloomberg, it is scheduled that Trump will sign an executive order on Thursday. This executive order would enable 401(k) retirement funds to make investments in alternative assets such as private equity, real estate, and cryptocurrency.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum&apos;s intraday gain widens to 4%, now trading at $3,770</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23555</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum&apos;s intraday increase expanded to 4%, and it is currently priced at $3770.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23555</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Caocao Mobility&apos;s Hong Kong Stock Soars Over 20%, Transitioning from Ride-Hailing to On-Chain Assets, Caocao Mobility&apos;s Real World Asset On-Chain Activation Ignites Robotaxi New Ec...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23554</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Caocao Mobility (Hong Kong Stock Code 02643) officially entered into a memorandum of understanding on virtual asset strategic cooperation with the Hong Kong-licensed institution Victory Securities. The cooperation focuses on three main aspects: the securitization of real-world assets (RWA), stablecoin payments, and compliant digital currency issuance. In response to this news, Caocao Mobility&apos;s Hong Kong stock price surged by more than 20% on August 7th, with the RWA concept becoming the focus of the market.This cooperation marks the first systematic exploration in the ride-hailing industry of the &quot;ride-hailing asset + RWA&quot; application scenario. Caocao Mobility CEO Gong Xin stated that through RWA technology, green mobility will be deeply integrated with digital finance, which may revitalize core assets such as Robotaxi and help the company establish a first-mover advantage in the autonomous driving field. Currently, Caocao has launched Robotaxi pilot operations in Han</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23554</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFINIT is launching the IN token along with staking functionality, ushering in an AI-powered Agentic DeFi economy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23553</link>
      <description>On August 7th, INFINIT announced that the core token IN of the platform was officially launched, and simultaneously opened the staking function. The aim is to build a growth flywheel centered around real utility. IN will serve as the engine of the Agentic DeFi economy and build long-term value around three core functions: protocol fee sharing, governance participation, and platform priority access.Users can now execute complex strategies with one click. By staking IN, they can earn rewards and support top strategy creators, which helps to form an intelligence-driven DeFi growth loop.Qualified users can claim tokens from August 7th at 10:00 UTC to September 6th at 10:00 UTC, including:- INFINIT Stones holders (Epoch 1-5)- Kaito Yappers- Community contributors- Ecosystem partners.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23553</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAY Surges 163% in 3 Hours, Price Retraces to 67.4% Gain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23552</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on market data, Binance&apos;s Alpha Zone token PLAY began a sharp ascent at 14:00 today. It reached a high of 0.092947 USD within 3 hours, showing a 163% increase. Now it has retraced to 0.0588 USD, with a narrowed gain of 67.4%. Its market capitalization on Binance Smart Chain is currently approximately 22 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Network&apos;s daily transaction volume hit a record high of 1.74 million on August 5th, with the July cumulative transaction volume also reaching an all-time high.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23551</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on The Block data, Ethereum&apos;s daily transaction volume (with a 7-day moving average) reached a record high of 1.74 million transactions on August 5th. This surpassed the previous record of 1.65 million transactions set on May 12, 2021.July also witnessed the largest monthly transaction volume in the history of the Ethereum network, with a total of 46.67 million transactions.Furthermore, on August 5th, the number of active Ethereum addresses surged to 683,520, approaching the historical high of 743,730 addresses on May 12, 2021.Presto Research analyst Min Jung stated, &quot;Ethereum&apos;s daily transaction volume has reached a record high, which reflects the significant increase in DeFi activity, with stablecoins being at the core. The market&apos;s growing interest in yield strategies, especially wagers on interest rate cuts, has led to more on-chain transactions, ranging from yield farming to capital deployment.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum On-Chain Activity Not Reflected in ETH Price, Staking ETF Approval Could Further Unlock Upside Potential</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23550</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Vincent Liu, the Chief Investment Officer of Kronos Research, stated that the United States&apos; clear stance on cryptocurrency regulation and the accumulation of institutional funds have also stimulated interest in Ethereum. Recently, dozens of companies have adopted Ethereum as part of their treasury strategy to achieve balance sheet diversification and attract investors seeking exposure to digital assets. The cumulative value of ETH held by publicly traded companies has exceeded $7.5 billion. The recent surge in on-chain activity on Ethereum has not yet been fully reflected in the ETH price.Vincent Liu further added, &quot;The price of ETH has been relatively cautious. Market confidence is on the rise, but a value reassessment is still in progress.&quot; If an Ethereum staking ETF is approved, it could further unlock the potential for price appreciation and on-chain activity, making ETH an interest-bearing asset that institutions can allocate to.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock ETH Strategy Stocks Surge in Pre-market Trading, BMNR and BTCS Up Over 5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23549</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on the market data from rockflow, the pre-market trading of US crypto stocks generally showed an increase. These included:Coinbase (COIN) with a pre-market increase of 0.83%.Circle (CRCL) with a pre-market increase of 1.46%.MicroStrategy (MSTR) with a pre-market decrease of 0.21%.Bitmine (BMNR) with a pre-market increase of 5.21%.BTCS (BTCS) with a pre-market increase of 5.48%.Bit Digital (BTBT) with a pre-market increase of 3.78%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) with a pre-market increase of 2.35%.CEA Industries (VAPE) with a pre-market increase of 1.95%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23549</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>