<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 15:53:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 15:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stablecoin Issuer Regulatory Regime Takes Effect, Vigilant Against Fraudulent Licensed Entity Scams</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22925</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) officially issued a security alert to be cautious of fraudulent stablecoin licensing scams. The Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation has come into effect, and the Stablecoin Issuer Regulatory Regime has also started to be implemented simultaneously. The regulatory regime is still in its initial stage, and the regulatory concept will adhere to the principle of &quot;being strict first and progressing steadily.&quot;With the implementation of the regulatory regime, market participants should act carefully when communicating with the public to avoid making statements that may be misinterpreted or create unrealistic expectations. According to the Stablecoin Regulation, falsely claiming to be a licensee or applicant is illegal.As of now, the HKMA has not issued any stablecoin issuer licenses. The public should be vigilant against any stablecoin or stablecoin issuer claiming to be &quot;regulated&quot; or &quot;licensed&quot; in Hong Kong. After licenses are issued, t</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22925</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell&apos;s Unexpected Resignation or Acceleration of Trump&apos;s Chosen Next Fed Chair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22924</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Federal Reserve Governor Quarles unexpectedly announced his resignation on Friday. This has presented President Trump with an opportunity to fill the Fed vacancy earlier than anticipated. It may also compel him to finalize his nominee for the next chair several months ahead of schedule.Derek Tang, an economist at the monetary policy analysis firm LH Meyer, said, &quot;Now the ball is in Trump&apos;s court. He has been putting pressure on the Fed and claiming that he wants to install his own people. Now the opportunity has arrived.&quot; While Powell&apos;s term as chair is set to expire in May next year, his term as governor extends until 2028. If Powell does not voluntarily resign from his governor position, Trump will not have another chance to fill the vacancy before 2028.In this situation, Trump may be forced to fill Quarles&apos; vacancy with his intended nominee for the chair. Tobin Marcus, the Director of U.S. Policy and Political Strategy at Wolf Research, pointed out that &quot;the key i</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 15:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22924</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean publicly listed company Bitmax&apos;s total Bitcoin holdings have surpassed 500 coins, ranking first in the South Korean market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22923</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, a Korean company listed on the KOSDAQ, Bitmax, announced that it has increased its holdings to 56.0445 bitcoins, raising its total holdings to 500.123 bitcoins and ranking first among Korean listed companies in terms of bitcoin holdings. The company stated that it will continue to adhere to its strategy of accumulating bitcoin.Bitmax is a listed company focusing on augmented reality technology development, providing AR software development tools and sensor fusion positioning solutions. It also integrates bitcoin into its financial reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 15:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22923</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Plunges Below $113,000 Temporarily</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22922</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin briefly fell below $113,000, with a 2.10% decline in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 14:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22922</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Tariffs Deal a Heavy Blow to Buffett&apos;s Berkshire Hathaway Consumer Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22921</link>
      <description>August 2nd. The company Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A.N, BRK.B.N), which is owned by Warren Buffett, declared that its consumer business has been affected by the trade policy of US President Trump. This is because the policy has imposed import tariffs. In the second quarter, the consumer goods division of this conglomerate (including brands like Fruit of the Loom, Jazwares, and Brooks Sports) witnessed a 5.1% year-on-year decrease in revenue, reaching $189 million. This mainly resulted from a decline in sales, the impact of tariffs, and business restructuring.Berkshire mentioned that the tariff policy has led to delays in the delivery of orders. Nevertheless, the company pointed out that the sportswear brand Brooks achieved a remarkable 18.4% revenue growth this quarter, which was driven by increased sales. Since Berkshire&apos;s business covers multiple economic sectors, its operational status is regarded as a microcosm of the US economy and has attracted significant attention from investors</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22921</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkshire&apos;s Q2 Cash Reserve Records First Drop in Three Years as Stock Market Investments Turn More Cautious</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22920</link>
      <description>August 2nd: The cash reserves of Berkshire Hathaway (BRK.A.N, BRK.B.N) decreased by 1% and reached $340 billion within the three months ending in June. This marks the first decline in cash reserves in three years.Previously, due to Buffett&apos;s difficulty in finding investment opportunities, the cash reserves repeatedly reached historical highs. In the second quarter, Buffett was more cautious about the stock market. He sold stocks worth approximately $3 billion net. Additionally, Berkshire suspended its stock buyback for four consecutive quarters despite a 12% decline in the stock price since the CEO transition was announced in May. (Jinse Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Insider Trader」 Adds XRP and SOL Short Positions, Total Position Shows Nearly $6 Million Unrealized Gain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22919</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio address has taken short positions of 3,333,333 XRP and 44,444.44 SOL respectively. The total value of these positions is $17.07 million, with opening prices of $2.93 for XRP and $164.18 for SOL. Currently, the total value of these four short positions exceeds $221 million, and the unrealized profit is $5.95 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22919</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether issued a total of 6 billion USDT in July, bringing the total circulating supply to increase by $20 billion since the beginning of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22918</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Tether issued a total of 6 billion USDT during July of this year. This occurred following the release of the Q2 2025 financial report. The report shows that as of June 30, 2025, the circulating supply of USDT has exceeded 157 billion dollars, with an increase of 20 billion dollars since the start of the year.The financial report discloses that Tether holds a combined total of 127 billion dollars in U.S. Treasury bonds. It directly holds 105.5 billion dollars and indirectly holds 21.3 billion dollars, representing an increase of approximately 8 billion dollars from the first quarter. The company achieved a net profit of 4.9 billion dollars in the second quarter, with a total profit of 5.7 billion dollars in the first half of 2025, including an operating profit of 3.1 billion dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22918</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caixin: Stablecoin Craze Cools Down, Hong Kong May Limit First Batch of Stablecoin Licenses to 3-4 Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22917</link>
      <description>August 2nd. According to the report by Caixin, from June to July of this year, the discussions on stablecoins across the Taiwan Strait once reached a fever pitch and then subsided. In Hong Kong, the scope of the first batch of stablecoin licenses may be narrowed down to three to four entities. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority realized in its communication with the People&apos;s Bank of China that, within the framework of the regulatory memorandum of understanding, the main regulatory responsibilities and risks are concentrated on the Hong Kong Monetary Authority.Several mainland Chinese banks with branches in Hong Kong and mainland Chinese securities firms with branches in Hong Kong are keen to participate in Hong Kong&apos;s compliant stablecoin business. These include Bank of China Hong Kong, Bank of Communications Hong Kong, China Construction Bank (Asia), Industrial and Commercial Bank of China (Asia), Guotai Junan International, etc., involving stablecoin issuance, custody, and other busi</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22917</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: Wall Street Quietly Accumulating Ethereum, Price Target to Reach $15,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22916</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Lee, the new chairman of BitMine, stated that traditional financial institutions are increasingly investing in cryptocurrency in a steady and quiet manner. He mentioned that ETH, the native asset of the Ethereum blockchain, is benefiting from the &quot;tokenization&quot; driven by Wall Street due to its advantages in legal clarity and technical reliability. &quot;Ethereum has never experienced downtime. This is important for banks,&quot; he said.BitMine currently holds 625,000 ETH, with total assets close to 2.8 billion US dollars and almost no debt. Lee also confirmed a $1 billion stock buyback plan and reiterated the company&apos;s goal of &quot;accumulating 5% of the total Ethereum supply.&quot;Regarding Bitcoin, the current price is $113,576.36, and it is also becoming a target for institutional investors&apos; regular purchases. Lee believes that if there is a shift in the Federal Reserve&apos;s monetary policy, especially with interest rate cuts in the coming months, Bitcoin could soar to $250,000. Lee st</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22916</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>