<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:13:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb has added a PROVE/KRW trading pair.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23335</link>
      <description>August 6th. According to official information, Bithumb has included the PROVE-KRW trading pair. The trading is set to begin on Wednesday, August 6th at 5:00 PM in the local time.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23335</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Sidekick (K) on August 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23334</link>
      <description>August 6th: According to official channels, Binance Alpha is set to become the first platform to initiate the launch of Sidekick (K) on August 8th.Users who are eligible can access the Alpha event page once Alpha trading commences and utilize Alpha Points to claim the airdrop. Further details will be provided separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23334</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Or possibly influenced by pump.fun&apos;s official Twitter account&apos;s &quot;Strong Milk&quot; meme, the related meme coin has seen a significant price increase recently.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23333</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to GMGN market information, some meme coins in the pump.fun ecosystem have witnessed significant gains recently. These include:TROLL has seen a 298.8% surge in the past week, and its market cap now stands at $171 million;HOUSE has surged by 88.5% in the past week, with a market cap of $25.78 million;neet has increased by 103.8% in the past week, and its market cap is now $16.84 million;BlockBeats&apos; new article today 《PUMP Rises Against the Trend, What Happened in the Meme Launchpad in the Past Two Weeks》 mentioned that the pump.fun official Twitter account posted a picture on July 23rd, which contained multiple meme coins in the pump.fun ecosystem.BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of these tokens are highly volatile, and users should invest cautiously.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23333</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow Traders to Serve as Market Maker for Binance&apos;s New Coin PROVE</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23332</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), Flow Traders received 2.5 million PROVE tokens from the project team&apos;s address 14 hours ago. This accounted for 1.28% of the total circulating supply. The tokens have now all been deposited into major CEXs such as Binance, Gate, Kucoin, and Bitvavo.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23332</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Quad-Stack ETH Whale with 75% Win Rate」 has realized a nearly $2.6 million profit.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23331</link>
      <description>On August 6th, on-chain data indicates that this morning, the &quot;Four-Battles ETH 75% Win Rate Whale&quot; increased its ETH short position to 70,000 ETH (approximately $252 million). Subsequently, its position is now showing a realized profit of $2.59 million. The liquidation price of its short position is $3,698.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23331</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: SEC Chair&apos;s &quot;Project Crypto&quot; Encompasses Multiple Key Opportunities, Yet to be Fully Priced</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23330</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Matt Hougan, the Chief Investment Officer of Bitwise, stated that the &quot;Project Crypto&quot; speech by SEC Chair Atkins is a &quot;roadmap for investment in the next five years.&quot; He pointed out three key opportunities: Ethereum/L1, super apps like Coinbase, and DeFi protocols. The speech mainly focused on public blockchains such as Ethereum.Atkins believes that all assets - stocks, bonds, the US dollar, etc. - will eventually migrate to public blockchains; DeFi will play a crucial role in the future; crypto assets and blockchain can create exciting new business models; the main obstacle to this &quot;revolution&quot; was a hostile regulatory environment, which has now completely reversed.Matt Hougan mentioned three immediate investment opportunities that stand out:The first and most obvious opportunity is to invest in Ethereum and other first-layer blockchains that support stablecoins and tokenization.The second is Coinbase, Robinhood, and other &quot;super apps.&quot; He boldly predicted that o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23330</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DOGE Department Employee Attacked, Trump Calls for Legislation to Prosecute Attackers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23329</link>
      <description>August 6th. As per the police in Washington D.C., a 19-year-old individual named &quot;Big Balls&quot; was assaulted in Washington over the weekend. He played a crucial role in the &quot;Department of Government Efficiency&quot; (DOGE) initiative aimed at downsizing the government and is currently still in government service.A police report indicates that around 3 a.m. on Sunday, Edward Coristine was attacked by approximately 10 teenagers near Dupont Circle.Trump posted a photo on his social media platform, showing Coristine without a shirt and with what seemed to be blood on his face, body, and pants. He called for a change in the law so that the teenagers who attacked him could be prosecuted as adults. He wrote: &quot;Perhaps this should have been done a long time ago, so that this remarkable young man, as well as many others, would not have to endure the terror of violent crime.&quot; (Kryptonite)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23329</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Continues Withdrawal, Over 36 million USDC Flowed Out in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23327</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight accessible at https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, while the market was experiencing fluctuations, whale addresses were still speeding up the withdrawal of USDC. In the past 24 hours, the total withdrawal volume exceeded 36 million US dollars. The whale withdrawal situation has been ongoing for more than three days, including:The whale address starting with 0x2326aD withdrew a total of 10.96 million USDC in the past 24 hours;The whale address starting with 0x5b5d51 made two withdrawals this morning: 8 million USDC and 5 million USDC;The whale address starting with 0xB83DE0 withdrew a total of 14.5 million USDC in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23327</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sidekick establishes Foundation and issues native token K</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23328</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Web3 live trading platform Sidekick announced the founding of the Sidekick Foundation and the issuance of its native token K. This token enables real-time interaction on the platform, creator monetization, and community engagement. It allows for seamless value exchange among hosts, viewers, and partners, facilitating various functions such as live gifting, staking, premium access, rewards, and decentralized governance.The tokenomics of the K token has a total token supply of 1 billion, which is distributed as follows: Ecosystem Growth (20%), Long-Term Community Incentives (20%), Liquidity Incentives (4%), Foundation (16%), Advisors (5%), Core Contributors (15%), Investors (20%).The initial circulating supply allocation of the tokens is 111,333,333 K (11.13% of the total token supply), including: Ecosystem Growth (6.883%), Long-Term Community Incentives (1.5%), Liquidity Incentives (2%), Foundation (0.75%).Lock-up Terms: The allocations of Investors, Advisors, a</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A User Loses Over $3 Million Due to Signing a Phishing Transaction</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23326</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of Scam Sniffer, 6 hours prior to this moment, a user suffered a loss of $3.05 million due to signing a phishing transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 02:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23326</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>