<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:55:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine acquires an additional 9613 ETH, worth $45 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25956</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on Arkham&apos;s monitoring data, the Ethereum treasury company Bitmine once again increased its holdings by 9613 ETH, which is worth $45 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 20:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25956</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Two Bitcoin Ancient Whale sold 9,142 BTC, bought 207,584 ETH, and is holding a long position of 135,263 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25955</link>
      <description>On August 24th, the latest updates regarding the reallocation of Ethereum by the two Bitcoin ancient whales in the current market are as follows:Ancient Whale 1:Sold: 6,000 BTC, with an approximate value of $690 million at a price of $115,000.Bought: 152,494 ETH, with an approximate value of $724 million at a price of $4,750.Ancient Whale 2:Sold: 3,142 BTC, with an approximate value of $360 million at a price of $115,000.Bought: 55,090 ETH, with an approximate value of $262 million at a price of $4,750.Long Position: 135,263 ETH perpetual contract, with a notional value of approximately $643 million at a price of $4,750.In total:Sold: 9,142 BTC, with an approximate value of $1.05 billion at a price of $115,000.Bought: 207,584 ETH in the spot market, with an approximate value of $986 million at a price of $4,750.ETH Total Position (Spot + Perpetual): 342,847 ETH, with a notional value of approximately $1.63 billion. P&amp;L: Currently, it has made a profit of approximately $1</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25955</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale has once again deposited 5,000 BTC into Hyperliquid to fund ETH accumulation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25954</link>
      <description>On August 24th, a certain Bitcoin &quot;ancient whale&quot; further deposited 5,000 BTC into Hyperliquid. The value of this deposit is approximately $5.7467 billion, and the purpose is to exchange it for ETH.Currently, this &quot;ancient whale&quot; holds 179,498 ETH, with a value of approximately $8.505 billion. It also maintains a long position of 135,265 ETH, which is worth approximately $6.4092 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25954</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale engaged in panic-selling and buying the dip of ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25953</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as monitored by lookonchain, the whale address 0x3c9E has always been panicking and selling ETH during market downturns, only to purchase it back at a higher price.From July 29th to August 3rd: Sold 38,582 ETH at an average price of $3,548 (approximately $136.9 million).From August 8th to August 15th: Bought back 16,800 ETH at an average price of $4,424 (approximately $74.3 million).From August 16th to August 20th: Sold 10,900 ETH at an average price of $4,369 (approximately $47.6 million).In the recent 20 hours: Bought back 7,500 ETH at an average price of $4,747 (approximately $35.6 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25953</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave Founder Responds to WLFI Protocol: Still in Effect</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25952</link>
      <description>August 23rd. Stani.eth, the founder of Aave, responded to questions on social media at 20:30 today regarding &quot;Is the WLFI and AAVE protocol still valid? Are they really building on Aave? There are many different rumors from the outside.&quot; He stated that the protocol is still valid.&quot;It is stated that at the current price, the Aave Treasury will receive WLFI worth $2.5 billion, making it one of the biggest winners in this cycle.&quot; In response to this view, Aave&apos;s founder prominently retweeted a comment saying, &quot;The art of the deal.&quot;BlockBeats previously reported that Aave will receive 7% of the total WLFI tokens and will receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by WLFI Aave v3. However, the related topic was later denied by an alleged WLFI Wallet team member, which sparked intense discussions on social media platforms and caused significant price fluctuations in the AAVE token.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital Founder: ETH&apos;s next target will surpass $10,000 and outperform BTC during the rate cut cycle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25951</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, Jack Yi, the founder of LD Capital, stated in a post, &quot;Just as we expected, after ETH broke through its all-time high, the next goal is to aim at challenging the all-time high of the BTC exchange rate. The target of ETH is above 10,000. During the interest rate reduction cycle, ETH has been consistently performing better than BTC, ushering in a rally of mainstream coins (including leaders in the ETH ecosystem such as ENA, AAVE, Pendle, UNI, as well as SOL, TON, LTC, etc.). Once again, remember not to go short. Add positions during pullbacks. In a bull market trend, ignore price fears and high prices. Avoid high leverage to prevent short-term pullbacks and spend more energy exploring off-chain income.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25951</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale withdrew 26,200 ETH from Hyperliquid, setting the platform&apos;s record for the largest single ETH withdrawal.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25947</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to Mlm Monitor, a Bitcoin ancient whale has just transferred 4,000 BTC (amounting to 460 million US dollars) to a new wallet. Subsequently, it is likely that he will swap it for ETH on Hyperliquid or sell it to over-the-counter (OTC) institutions.In addition, he also withdrew 26,200 ETH (with a value of 125 million US dollars) from Hyperliquid, setting a new record for the largest single ETH withdrawal on the exchange platform up to now.Today, the whale has deposited 2,520 BTC into HyperLiquid, which is worth 291.75 million US dollars, and is ready to sell it in exchange for ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25947</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAVE Short-Term Breaks Above $385, Surges Over 14% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25949</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on HTX market data, AAVE briefly soared above $385 and has now pulled back to $370. It has witnessed an increase of over 14% within 24 hours, and its market capitalization is $5.733 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25949</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave will receive 7% of the total WLFI token supply and will also receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by WLFI Aave v3.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25948</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on a previously disclosed proposal, Aave, as a WLFI lending ecosystem partner, within this Aave v3 instance, WLFI will adopt the same reserve factor mechanism as the main Aave instance.The AaveDAO will receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by the WLFI Aave v3 instance and will obtain approximately 7% of the total WLFI token supply to participate in future WLFI governance processes, liquidity mining, and promote the decentralization of the WLFI platform.Revenue distribution will be implemented through a trustless smart contract, which will directly allocate the corresponding proportion of the protocol fees to the AaveDAO treasury address and the WLFI treasury address.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25948</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected WLFI Wallet Team Member Denies Proposal-Related Message Regarding &quot;Aave Receiving 7% of WLFI Total Supply&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25950</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, the alleged WLFI Wallet team member Dylan_0x (@0xDylan_) posted a message denying any association with the &quot;Aave to Receive 7% of WLFI Total Token Supply&quot; proposal. Probably due to this, AAVE dropped from a high of $385.99 to $365, experiencing a short-term decline of more than 5%.Crypto KOL @Luyaoyuan1 expressed his opinion on this event, saying, &quot;I used to think that Aave would maintain a long position in AAVE&apos;s trading with this 7% and 20% protocol revenue. But in the weeks prior to the WLFI announcement, I noticed the weakness of AAVE/ETH and Aave&apos;s lagging price increase. There are precedents where, if WLFI does not fork, they have no intention of giving AAVE the 7% coins. There is no surprise here; there are precedents. SPK defaulted on the 10% revenue share and only provided 1% in the end, and this issue remained unresolved. During the WLFI public sale, they said it would be fully unlocke</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25950</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>