<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:49:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: The AI Companion is a rapidly growing field, let&apos;s combine it with cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28010</link>
      <description>September 7th: Binance founder CZ mentioned in a post that the field of AI companionship is growing rapidly, and users are also willing to make payments for it. We can introduce this into the cryptocurrency space or vice versa, bring cryptocurrency into the AI companionship space.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28010</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: During the SOL pullback, the majority of the volume entered above $144, with very few trapped chips remaining above.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28009</link>
      <description>On September 7th, on-chain data analyst Murphy released an analysis of SOL&apos;s on-chain structure. As depicted in the chart, the SOL chip distribution roughly assumes an olive-shaped structure, with a significant accumulation in the middle and slightly less at the extremities. With the current price of $203 as the center, SOL accumulated within the top 20% price range (that is, $203 to $242) makes up 7% of the total circulation, while SOL accumulated within the bottom -20% price range (that is, $162 to $203) accounts for 39.2% of the circulating chips.If the future SOL price continues to ascend and there are few trapped chips above, the main selling pressure will originate from the chips below engaging in profit-taking. Through recent repeated oscillations, SOL has achieved very thorough handovers within the -20% price range, elevating the average cost of all participants. Therefore, when there is a certain degree of unrealized profit, theoretically, the selling pressure will not be su</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28009</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Chain AI Game CAT Crew 2.0 &quot;Compute Power Era&quot; Officially Launched</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28008</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the first Web3+AI nurturing game on Solana launched by the CAT Terminal community - CAT Crew 2.0 &quot;Mining Power Era&quot; has officially been upgraded and launched.It is reported that the &quot;AI Meow Mine&quot; held its launch event in Dubai on August 16th, with the support of various Middle Eastern institutions such as OOKC and X3 Labs. Currently, the game has attracted more than 5,000 players, and the CAT feeding volume has exceeded 150 million tokens.This Meow Mine 2.0 upgrade introduces rare cat breed mining power bonuses and an adaptive feeding AI algorithm, and adds a CAT ecosystem burning mechanism. The launch of CAT Crew 2.0 has kicked off a new MEME 2.0 gameplay, bringing users an unprecedented on-chain interactive experience.As of the time of publication, the market value of CAT is approximately $18.6 million, and the number of holding addresses has reached 9,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will open airdrop distribution at 18:00, with a Phase 1 point threshold of 238 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28007</link>
      <description>September 7th. Binance Wallet will commence the Alpha Airdrop claim today at 18:00 (UTC+8), and the specific token remains undisclosed.The Alpha Airdrop will be dispensed in two stages:Stage One (first 18 hours): Users possessing at least 238 Alpha points will be qualified for the airdrop.Stage Two (last 6 hours): Users holding at least 220 Alpha points will participate in the airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the rewards are not completely distributed, the points threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points per hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28007</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador is celebrating the fourth anniversary of adopting Bitcoin as legal tender, currently holding 6,291.18 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28006</link>
      <description>September 7th: On September 7, 2021, El Salvador officially became the first country in the world to adopt Bitcoin as legal tender. President Nayib Bukele led the El Salvadoran Congress to pass the &quot;Bitcoin Law&quot; in June 2021. This law stipulates that Bitcoin can be used for payments of goods, services, taxes, etc., along with the US dollar as legal tender. The Salvadoran government then launched the digital wallet &quot;Chivo,&quot; enabling citizens to store and use Bitcoin. It provides a $30 Bitcoin reward to registered users and also deployed Bitcoin ATMs nationwide to facilitate transactions.According to data from the Salvadoran Ministry of Finance website, El Salvador has accumulated an additional 8 Bitcoins in the past 7 days, bringing its total Bitcoin holdings to 6,291.18 Bitcoins, with a value of over $690 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 05:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28006</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC and CFTC May Establish Joint Committee to End Cryptocurrency Regulation Dispute</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28005</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to TheBlock, a proposed draft of a market structure bill presented in the U.S. Senate indicates the establishment of a joint SEC and CFTC committee in order to resolve the cryptocurrency regulatory dispute. The draft encompasses provisions to safeguard decentralized finance (DeFi) developers, clarify the regulatory treatment of airdrops, exempt decentralized physical infrastructure networks (DePINs) from securities laws, and more. Additionally, the bill mandates the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) to set up a joint digital asset advisory committee to coordinate the two agencies&apos; distinct regulatory approaches to digital assets.In recent periods, the SEC and CFTC have enhanced their cooperation in cryptocurrency regulation and are scheduled to hold a public roundtable discussion on &quot;regulatory coordination priorities&quot; on September 29th. SEC Chairman Paul S. Atkins and Acting CFTC Chairwoman C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 05:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28005</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rate display indicates a bearish market sentiment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28004</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on Coinglass data, the current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rates suggest that the market has inclined towards bearishness. The specific funding rates are as presented in the following chart.BlockBeats Notes: The funding rate is a rate set by cryptocurrency exchanges to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price. It is usually applicable to perpetual contracts and is a fund exchange mechanism between long and short traders. The trading platform does not charge this fee. It is used to adjust the cost or profit of traders holding contracts to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the funding rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the funding rate is greater than 0.01%, it indicates a generally bullish market. When the funding rate is less than 0.005%, it indicates a generally bearish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 05:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28004</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea: Next Week&apos;s Liquidity Incentive Plan will Distribute 160 Million LINEA Tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28002</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Linea officially declared that the Linea Ignition liquidity incentive program in the next week will allocate 1.6 billion LINEA tokens as incentives. Previously, it was planned to be 1.5 billion tokens.The total reward for the Aave and Euler lending pools in USDC, USDT, and ETH is 1.28 billion LINEA tokens. And the total reward for trading on Etherex (trading pairs including USDC/ETH, WBTC/ETH, USDT/ETH, and ETH/REX) is 32 million LINEA tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28002</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOMI briefly broke through $1.15, with a 24-hour price increase expanding to 50.2%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28003</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on HTX market data, Somnia (SOMI) briefly rose above $1.15 and is now trading at $1.04. It has seen a 24-hour price increase of 50.2% and is currently valued at $160 million.Somnia (SOMI) was previously listed on Binance&apos;s spot trading on September 2nd.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28003</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC Establishes a Special Task Force to Combat Cross-Border Transaction Fraud Targeting U.S. Investors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28001</link>
      <description>September 7th. According to an official proclamation, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has declared the formation of a cross-border special task force with the aim of combating cross-border transaction fraud that poses a threat to U.S. investors. The initial emphasis of the cross-border special task force is to investigate potential violations of U.S. federal securities laws involving foreign companies, including potential market manipulation such as &quot;pump and dump&quot; schemes. The task force will also give special attention to &quot;gatekeepers,&quot; specifically auditors and underwriters that assist these companies in accessing the U.S. capital markets. Furthermore, the task force will review potential securities law violations related to companies in foreign jurisdictions.SEC Chairman Paul Atkins stated, &quot;We extend a warm welcome to companies from all over the world to access the U.S. capital markets. However, we will not show any tolerance for any bad actors - be it companie</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 04:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28001</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>