<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:22:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale held 2216.79 ETH on Ethereum throughout the bullish trend for three months, achieving an impressive 73% return on investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25718</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), on June X, the address 0x7C1...36FA7 withdrew 2216.79 ETH from Binance at a price of $2484 per ETH. The holdings remained idle for three months until all were transferred back to Binance three hours ago. If sold, the rate of return would be 73%, and a profit of $4 million was earned over the three-month period.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25718</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stock Exchange Listed Company Timely Resources Plans to Issue Tokenized Silver Digital Currency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25719</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per an announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, the Hong Kong-listed company Timing Resources (08028.HK) declared that it would cooperate with Edelweiss Securities Futures to issue a digital token supported by physical silver assets (Silver Token), thus propelling Hong Kong&apos;s first Silver Tokenization of Real World Assets (RWA) project. Edelweiss Securities Futures&apos; parent company, Edelweiss Financial, will aid the issuer in obtaining all the requisite approvals from the relevant regulatory authority (if any) prior to the launch of the Silver Token.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25719</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIO briefly touched $0.21, surging over 37% in the past 24 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25717</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to HTX market data, BIO briefly reached $0.21 and is currently trading at $0.2035, with a more than 37% increase in the past 24 hours.The DeSci protocol Bio Protocol recently launched a token launch platform. The first project is Aubrai. Users can obtain an issuance allocation by pledging BioXP. By investing in BIO, they can receive tokens. The final allocation depends on the BioXP staking share. The first BioAgent Launch project Aubrai sale will last for 24 hours, and the exact opening time will be announced separately. The AUBRAI token will be listed immediately after the sale.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25717</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&apos;s son Eric Trump will attend the Metaplanet shareholder meeting on September 1st.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25716</link>
      <description>August 22nd: The son of former U.S. President Donald Trump, Eric Trump, is scheduled to attend the shareholders&apos; meeting of Japan&apos;s Bitcoin financial company Metaplanet Inc. on September 1st.Metaplanet, a hotel operator, shifted to a Bitcoin treasury strategy in early 2024 and has up to now accumulated 18,888 BTC with a value of over $2.1 billion. In March, Eric Trump was appointed as a strategic advisor. Meanwhile, at the meeting on September 1st, Metaplanet shareholders will vote on a new financing method. Metaplanet CEO Simon Gerovich previously stated that the goal for this year to increase the BTC holdings to 30,000 coins remains unchanged.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25716</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroBit Bitcoin and Ethereum Spot ETF Listed on HKEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25715</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the two virtual asset spot ETFs of Hong Kong asset management company MicroBit Asset Management were officially listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange. They are the MicroBit Bitcoin Spot ETF (HKD counter stock code: 3430.HK, USD counter stock code: 9430.HK) and the MicroBit Ethereum Spot ETF (HKD counter stock code: 3425.HK, USD counter stock code: 9425.HK). The management fee for both ETFs is 0.5%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25715</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss asset management company Tyr Capital has launched a new cryptocurrency market-neutral hedge fund.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25714</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Swiss digital asset management company Tyr Capital announced the establishment of a new cryptocurrency market-neutral hedge fund. The fund is designed to generate returns for investors by employing market-neutral and arbitrage strategies. It aims to maintain independence from market trends through a meta-strategy portfolio.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Holdings Announces Acquisition of Over 50% Stake in Web3 Media Company CoinPost</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25713</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Japan&apos;s financial group SBI Holdings announced that an agreement on the transfer of stocks has been signed with some existing shareholders of the Web3 media company CoinPost. Under this agreement, SBI Holdings will acquire a majority stake in CoinPost and turn it into a wholly-owned subsidiary. The transaction is expected to be completed on October 1, 2025.CoinPost is one of Japan&apos;s largest cryptocurrency and Web3 professional media outlets and also operates the Asian Web3 conference &quot;WebX.&quot; After the acquisition, the two parties will collaborate in three areas: expanding media functions, providing support for the expansion of digital asset investment, and jointly hosting industry events. SBI Holdings stated that this move will accelerate the social implementation of Web3 through cooperation with group companies and help establish a new financial digital industry foundation in Japan.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25713</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell is set to deliver a speech tonight at 10 p.m. at the Jackson Hole Symposium, with the market focusing on rate cut expectations and successor selection.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25712</link>
      <description>August 22: The Federal Reserve Chair, Powell, is slated to deliver a speech on the economic outlook and the evaluation of the Fed&apos;s policy framework at the annual central bank symposium of the Kansas City Fed in Jackson Hole, Wyoming. The speech is scheduled to take place at 10 a.m. ET (10 p.m. Beijing time) today. Substantial market volatility is anticipated.This speech arrives at a crucial time. Recent data indicates that tariff measures have exerted a certain impact on inflation, while the labor market is decelerating. This intricate situation reinforces the market&apos;s expectation that the Fed may announce a 25-basis-point rate cut at the upcoming month&apos;s meeting. Meanwhile, U.S. President Trump continues to exert pressure on Powell to cut rates and is seeking a replacement. Powell&apos;s term as the Fed chair will come to an end in May of next year.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$38.2 Billion Worth of BTC and $9.5 Billion Worth of ETH Options Expiring Today, with Max Pain at $11.8k and $4250</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25711</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the analyst Adam of Greek.Live released today&apos;s options expiry data: 34,000 BTC options expired. The Put Call Ratio was 1.3, with a maximum pain point of $118,000 and a notional value of $3.82 billion. 220,000 ETH options expired. The Put Call Ratio was 0.82, with a maximum pain point of $4250 and a notional value of $9.5 billion. Analyst Adam stated that the theme of this week is price retracement. However, both BTC and ETH are hovering near their all-time highs, and market sentiment remains relatively optimistic. Nearly $5 billion in options expiry took place this week, accounting for 8% of the current total open interest. In terms of historical records, this is a relatively low weekly proportion, which is in sharp contrast to the current daily trading volume of nearly $5 billion. Looking at the key options data, there has been a significant rebound in implied volatility. BTC&apos;s mid-term IV has fully rebounded to above 35%, and ETH&apos;s major term IV is close to 70%, whil</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25711</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXC Exchange Coin MX has surged by 17.8% in the last 24 hours, currently trading at $3.13.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25710</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on market data, the price of the native exchange token MX of the crypto trading platform MEXC has witnessed a surge of 17.8% within the past 24 hours and reached $3.13. At present, its total market capitalization has reached $285 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25710</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>