<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:30:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>IPO Looms, Grayscale Founder Barry Silbert Returns as Chairman of the Board</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23135</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per The Block, following the submission of a confidential IPO application, Grayscale Investments announced the appointment of four executives and welcomed back founder Barry Silbert as the Chairman of the Board. The newly appointed executives are: Chief Operating Officer Diana Zhang, Chief Marketing Officer Ramona Boston, Chief Communications Officer Andrea Williams, and Chief Human Resources Officer Maxwell Rosenthal. All four executives will report to Grayscale CEO Peter Mintzberg and are from traditional financial giants such as Bridgewater Associates, Apollo Global Management, Goldman Sachs, and Castle Investment.Barry Silbert founded Grayscale in 2013 and stepped down as the Chairman of the Board at the end of 2023. He will now succeed Mark Shifke as the Chairman of the Board, with Shifke continuing to serve on the board. The board has now expanded to five members. The company has indicated that it is considering adding independent directors.Barry Silbert sta</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23135</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes: The next few months will usher in the Crypto Stock IPO Season, with funds expected to flow into native crypto projects rather than suffocating the season of copycats</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23134</link>
      <description>On August 4th, Forbes reported that the success of the Circle IPO will inspire those who are still on the sidelines. Since publicly traded crypto stocks present a highly attractive prospect for investors, especially for crypto newcomers, buying stock in a listed company is much easier than participating in a Curve Finance liquidity pool or trying to predict which memecoin will multiply by 100 in the future. Listed stocks can be purchased through traditional brokerage accounts or platforms like Robinhood, thus eliminating the barriers to entering the cryptocurrency ecosystem. Investors can enjoy the benefits of crypto with much less risk.Forbes stated that, similar to any free market, demand is expected to drive supply as well. This is good news for projects built in the crypto ecosystem. The launch of new projects indicates that capital is flowing into the digital asset economy. Undoubtedly, this capital is flowing into infrastructure projects, developer tools, Layer 1, and Layer 2 b</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23134</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pendle Co-founder: Pendle Achieves New $7 Billion TVL Peak as TVL Strengthens Post $1.5 Billion Locked Assets Expiry, Signaling Market&apos;s Deepening Trust in Pendle Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23133</link>
      <description>On August 4th, the co-founder TN of Pendle posted on social media that last week, Pendle witnessed one of its largest expiration events to date, with a total value locked (TVL) of over $1.5 billion expiring. Nevertheless, Pendle Finance&apos;s TVL still reached a new all-time high. Notably, $1.3 billion (87%) of the expiring TVL came from Ethena Labs&apos; assets. During the weekend, against the backdrop of a market downturn, Pendle and Ethena were the only projects among the top ten protocols to achieve a positive 7-day TVL growth. Currently, Pendle holds and contributes approximately 48% of Ethena&apos;s TVL.Even at this magnitude, the TVL retracement from the peak to the trough was minimal and only lasted for one day, falling from $6.827 billion to $6.638 billion, a decrease of just $189 million (-2.8%). Furthermore, in July 2025, the fee revenue of vePENDLE surged by 80% compared to the previous month, reaching $2.85 million. Even without airdrops, the July fee revenue remained at a healthy lev</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23133</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Quad-Short ETH Whale with 75% Win Rate] Closed Short Position of 20,000 ETH, Turning Unrealized Gain of $12.25M into Unrealized Loss of $840K</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23132</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per the on-chain data analyst Yujin Monitoring, the [Four-Battle ETH 75% Win Rate Whale]&apos;s short position of 50,000 ETH (approximately $170 million) was also liquidated by 20,000 ETH 20 minutes ago. It had a floating profit of $12.25 million yesterday and is currently floating at a loss of $840,000.Currently, they still maintain a short position of 30,000 ETH, which is worth $1.1 billion. The entry price is $3634 and the liquidation price is $3701.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23132</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Insider Trader」 @qwatio Closes XRP, SOL Shorts, Turns $12 Million Unrealized Gain into Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23130</link>
      <description>August 4th. As per on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio closed XRP and SOL short positions half an hour ago, incurring a total loss of $1.644 million. Yesterday, there was a realized gain of $12 million.Currently, there still remains a value of $105 million in BTC and ETH short positions. BTC is in a realized gain state as the entry price is $116,736.3, while ETH is already in a realized loss of $1.094 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23130</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midday Gains in Major U.S. Stock Indexes Expand, with SBET Soaring 15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23131</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to data from rockflow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), the three major U.S. stock indexes witnessed an expanded increase during intraday trading. The Nasdaq rose by more than 1.6%, the S&amp;P 500 rose by nearly 1.2%, and the Dow Jones Industrial Average rose by nearly 1%. Crypto stocks, which initially had mixed performances at the opening, turned into a general upward trend, including:Coinbase (COIN) increased by 1.83%.Circle (CRCL) decreased by 5.12%.MicroStrategy (MSTR) increased by 4.34%.MARA Holdings (MARA) increased by 1.57%.Riot Blockchain (RIOT) increased by 3.34%.BTCS (BTCS) increased by 2.83%.Bit Digital (BTBT) increased by 5.31%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) increased by 15.17%.CEA Industries (VAPE) increased by 10.73%.GameSquare (GAME) increased by 12.85%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23131</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun Test Website to Introduce &quot;Reward&quot; Functionality, Transaction Volume Incentive Program Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23129</link>
      <description>August 4th - As per market sources, the &quot;Reward&quot; feature of the pump.fun test website, which is a transaction volume incentive plan, is about to become operational.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23129</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $115,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23128</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin has shown a rebound and exceeded $115,000. It is currently trading at $115,218.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharplink Gaming Increases Holdings by 18,600 ETH, Bringing Total Holdings to Nearly 500,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23127</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on on-chain analysis, Sharplink Gaming (SBET) has increased its strategic ETH reserve address by an additional 18,680 ETH, which is valued at $66.3 million. Currently, it holds 498,884 ETH with a value of $1.8 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23127</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stock GameSquare (GAME) surges over 13%, announced today to increase its ETH holdings by 2717 coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23126</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to data from rockflow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), the stock price of GameSquare (GAME) in the US stock market increased by 13.15% and is currently trading at $0.9175.Previously, BlockBeats reported that GameSquare announced today the approval of a stock buyback program funded by Ethereum earnings. It spent $10 million to purchase an additional 2,717 ETH, increasing the treasury holdings to 15,630.07 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23126</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>