<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:58:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Noble, Eclipse, and Solana Top Cross-Chain Bridge Net Inflow in the Past Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22079</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the data from DefiLlama, during the past week, the net inflow of funds through the Noble cross-chain bridge amounted to $129 million, securing the top position among all public chains. Closely trailing behind are Eclipse and Solana, with net inflows of $112 million and $45.27 million, respectively.On Ethereum, Arbitrum, and Hyperliquid, there were net outflows of $223.9 million, $148.1 million, and $20.49 million, respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22079</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSC Ecosystem DeFi Tokens Experience Overall price Increase, with CAKE Surging by 13.2% in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22078</link>
      <description>On July 28th, along with BNB breaking through $840 to reach a new all-time high, the DeFi tokens in the BSC ecosystem generally saw an upward trend today. These include:CAKE with a 24-hour increase of 13.2%, currently priced at $3.22;XVS with a 24-hour increase of 7.8%, currently priced at $7.05;THE with a 24-hour increase of 9.6%, currently priced at $0.4232.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22078</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit 24-hour Trading Volume Ranking: XRP, Ethereum, GLM Take Top Three Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22077</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit reached 3.147 billion USD. The XRP/KRW trading pair took the lead in the Korean market with a 14.05% share and achieved a 24-hour trading volume of 440 million USD. Ethereum (8.24%, with a volume of 258 million USD) and GLM (5.02%, with a volume of 157 million USD) ranked 2nd and 3rd respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22077</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCTV&apos;s &quot;World Weekly&quot; Special Report on Trump&apos;s Crypto-Friendly Policy and Stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22076</link>
      <description>July 28th. In yesterday evening&apos;s &quot;World Weekly&quot; program on CCTV, a special report was featured on Trump&apos;s crypto policies and stablecoins. The report indicated that although Trump introduced a series of crypto-friendly laws, including the Genius Act, Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies still encounter issues such as significant price volatility and high security risks.The report lasted for approximately 20 minutes in total. It emphasized Trump&apos;s active promotion of stablecoin development in relation to Fed policy and the high level of U.S. debt. Stablecoins were described as a new generation of &quot;dollar hegemony.&quot; It was emphasized that in the current global context where various countries are accelerating the issuance of their own stablecoins, &quot;establishing a more stable international order is a brand-new challenge.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22076</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Ecоsy?tem Tokens Surge, NOICE Up 60% in One Day, Hits All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22075</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to the market information of GMGN, today the tokens of the Base ecosystem witnessed a rise. They include:NOICE witnessed a daily increase of 60.1%, with the current circulating market capitalization at $15.63 million and reaching a new all-time high;KTA saw a daily increase of 21%, with the current market capitalization at $459 million;VVV saw a daily increase of 16%, with the current market capitalization at $110 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22075</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Sues German Man, Accusing Him of Maliciously Domain Hijacking and Extortion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22074</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Coinbase initiated a lawsuit against a German man named Tobias Honscha in the California federal court. It accused him of maliciously squatting the domain name coinbase.de and attempting to extort the company.Coinbase alleges that Honscha utilized the domain to redirect users to a physical coin trading app and made profits through the Coinbase affiliate marketing program, which violated the prohibition in the affiliate agreement against using the term &quot;Coinbase&quot; in a domain name.More importantly, Coinbase accuses Honscha of threatening that if the company did not purchase the domain at a high price, there might be a phishing attack, including risks such as &quot;unauthorized submission of identification documents, passwords, and one-time two-factor authentication codes.&quot; Coinbase deems this as &quot;clear extortion behavior.&quot;Coinbase is seeking a court order to halt the use of the domain, transfer domain ownership, and seek compensation for losses. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22074</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Liquidity Platform Gyroscope&apos;s Dynamic Liquidity Pool is now live on Avalanche, releasing LP Yield Report</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22073</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Gyroscope released a report on Twitter, presenting the performance of LP Yield and Dynamic Liquidity Pool (Dynamic E-CLP) on the ETH/USDC trading pair on the Base chain. When measured by the Markouts metric, the pool&apos;s execution efficiency significantly surpassed that of mainstream DEXs. Specifically:- It outperformed Uniswap v2 by 3.5 times.- It outperformed Uniswap v3 by up to 33 times (based on total yield).Markouts are used to measure the transaction execution efficiency of liquidity pools. If assets are bought and sold at a price better than the market price, it is regarded as positive Markouts, indicating that LPs are actually earning spread income. This metric is independent of asset trends and can evaluate the quality of market-making strategies. Additionally, Gyroscope&apos;s Dynamic Liquidity Pool has now been deployed on Avalanche, initially supporting the AVAX/USDC and GYD trading pairs, and has initiated LP incentives with an APR of up to 107%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22073</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought $3.19M worth of VINE 6 hours ago, previously experiencing a $125K loss during a PUMP event.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22072</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale with the address 8RwxXR withdrew 17,082 SOL (valued at $3.19 million) from Binance six hours ago and used it to purchase 22.4 million VINE.This whale had previously suffered a loss of $125,000 in a PUMP trading.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has launched USELESS (BSC chain).</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22071</link>
      <description>July 28th. According to official channels, Binance Alpha has launched USELESS (on the BSC chain).Previous News: The meme coin USELESS in the Solana ecosystem has been bridged to the BNB Chain via the Chainlink CCIP.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22071</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaplanet increased its holdings by 780 bitcoins, bringing the total holdings to 17,132 bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22070</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Simon Gerovich, the CEO of the Japanese publicly traded company Metaplanet, tweeted that Metaplanet had made an average price purchase of 780 bitcoins at $118,622 each, totaling approximately $92.5 million.As of July 28, 2025, Metaplanet holds a total of 17,132 bitcoins. The cumulative purchase amount is around $1.73 billion, and the average purchase price per bitcoin is approximately $101,030.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22070</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>