<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:50:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Unveils New Brand Image at WebX Summit, Founder Dr. Han Delivers Keynote Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26124</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the WebX Summit commenced in Tokyo, Japan. The globally prominent cryptocurrency exchange Gate unveiled its novel brand image at this event, emphasizing its latest attainments in transaction security, compliance systems, and diversified ecosystem development. By means of interactive demonstrations, the event presented the platform&apos;s comprehensive strength in asset protection, innovative products, and global strategic planning to the participants. Additionally, Gate&apos;s founder and CEO, Dr. Han, delivered a keynote speech during the conference, sharing global cryptocurrency industry trends and platform strategic concepts.As the title sponsor of this conference, Gate will host an exclusive VIP Side Meeting in Tokyo on the evening of August 26th, serving as the official Side Meeting event of WebX. The event will invite project teams, capital institutions, and ecosystem partners from the Asia-Pacific region and around the world to have in-depth discussions on regional colla</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26124</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Profited $1.72 Million from a LINK Swing Trade and Reopened a $16.85 Million LINK Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26123</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale that had made a profit of $1.72 million from scalping LINK two years ago has resurfaced. It recently purchased 663,580 LINK (with a value of $16.85 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: ETH Leading the Market in the Short Term, Funds Will Eventually Flow Back to BTC to Realize Profits</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26122</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Wang Feng, the founder of Blueport Interactive, tweeted that the recent &quot;ETH outperforming while BTC is in a sideways movement&quot; is more of a difference in narrative rhythm. The opportunity window may be short-lived, and investors may not have enough time to complete position adjustments.In the medium to long term, both share the same pool of macro funds, the same set of regulatory dividends, and the same market value curve. ETH should be regarded as a β amplifier of BTC rather than a substitute.Historical experience has shown that during the 2017 ICO and the 2020 DeFi cycles, the heat of ETH actually enhanced the risk premium of BTC. ETH is leverage, and BTC is an anchor. Large funds will ultimately flow back to BTC to cash out profits after the carnival.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance&apos;s new Bonding Curve Participation Threshold: At least 241 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26121</link>
      <description>August 25th, Binance made an announcement about a novel Bonding Curve project named OVERTAKE (TAKE), with a participation threshold of at least 241 points.Subscription Period: August 25, 2025, from 4:00 to 6:00 PM (UTC+8). The subscription will demand 15 points.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun Appears at WebX2025 in Japan: Industry Consensus Drives TRON to Become the Core Network of Global Stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26120</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Justin Sun, the founder of the Tron Foundation, delivered a keynote speech entitled &quot;Tron TRON at the Core of Global Stablecoin Activities&quot; at the WebX Summit in Japan. In the speech, he disclosed that the supply of USDT on the Tron TRON blockchain has exceeded 82 billion US dollars, and the daily active users have exceeded 1 million. He pointed out that this is not a short-term spike but the result of long-term adherence to high speed, low cost, and stability. Stablecoins are at the core of global financial digitization, and Tron TRON has become one of the most reliable networks in this field. He also emphasized that the addition of USD1 shows that more issuers are recognizing the ecosystem advantages of Tron TRON.WebX is known to be one of the largest and most influential blockchain and crypto asset conferences in Asia. It is organized by the Japanese crypto media CoinPost. The conference is held annually in Tokyo and brings together blockchain enterprises, financia</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of a 25 basis point interest rate cut by the Federal Reserve in September has decreased to 87.3%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26119</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on the CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch Tool&quot;, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September has dropped to 87.3%, while the probability of keeping rates unchanged is 12.7%.Former Fed Vice Chair Richard Clarida previously indicated in a report that the Fed appears ready to cut the policy rate soon but will do it with caution. Powell&apos;s highly anticipated speech last week at the annual Jackson Hole symposium did not let the market down, and the Fed&apos;s revised monetary policy framework did not surprise Fed observers. Looking ahead, the Fed reaffirmed its commitment to its dual mandate and only made minor clarifications to its monetary policy framework.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale acquired an additional 2.94 million VIRTUAL tokens at an average price of $1.28, totaling over $3.7 million in value.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26118</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as monitored by OnchainLens, a whale utilized 785 ETH (valued at $3.76 million) to purchase 2.94 million VIRTUAL at a price of $1.28.Address: 0x4322fd98f95a219d2aae2bba6664e3574b4c3708.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26118</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citi expects the 10-year US Treasury bond yield to reach 4.10% by the end of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26117</link>
      <description>August 25th: Jason Williams, a strategist at Citigroup, stated in a report that Citigroup has made some minor updates to its year-end yield level forecast for US Treasuries. Nevertheless, the institution remains confident in its long-standing forecast for the 10-year bond yield.He pointed out that the institution still anticipates that the 10-year US Treasury bond yield will reach 4.10% by the end of the year, which is in line with its forecast since last year. However, Citigroup has moderately adjusted other benchmarks in order to better align with its view of a steeper yield curve and lower policy rate expectations for 2026. Citigroup&apos;s new base forecasts for the two-year US Treasury bond yield are 3.50%; the five-year bond yield is 3.65%, and the 30-year bond yield is 4.70%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26117</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Fed Vice Chair: Fed Expected to Cautiously Lower Policy Rate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26116</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Richard Clarida, Pimco&apos;s global economic advisor and former vice chairman of the Fed, stated in a report that the Fed appears to be prepared to cut policy rates soon but will do so cautiously.Powell&apos;s highly anticipated speech at last week&apos;s Jackson Hole annual symposium did not let the market down. The launch of the Fed&apos;s revised monetary policy framework did not surprise Fed watchers. In the long run, the Fed reaffirmed its commitment to its dual mandate while making only minor clarifications to its monetary policy framework. (IG)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26116</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list BIOUSDC Perpetual Futures Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26115</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Binance is going to list the BIOUSDC perpetual contract.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26115</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>