<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:18:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Amid escalating inflation concerns, the options market is showing bearish pre-signals.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23206</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per CoinDesk, worries regarding the economy, such as rising inflation and disappointing job figures, have resulted in a recent price decline of Bitcoin. Meanwhile, with indicators in the options market indicating a shift in market sentiment, Bitcoin&apos;s long-term bullish sentiment has transformed into a neutral one.Griffin Ardern, the Director of Options Trading and Research at the crypto financial platform BloFin, stated, &quot;I have noticed a rather worrying sign of a recent market retracement. The bullish sentiment for Bitcoin&apos;s far-month options has vanished and is currently firmly in a neutral position. This implies that the options market believes that BTC is unlikely to establish a long-term upward trend, and the probability of reaching new highs in the coming months is decreasing, similar to what occurred in January and February 2022.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23206</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will open Superp (SUP) trading at 6:00 PM today, with an airdrop threshold of 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23205</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to an official announcement, Binance Alpha is the first platform to list Superp (SUP). Alpha trading will commence on August 5th at 18:00 (UTC+8). After the trading starts, users who hold at least 200 Alpha points can claim a 500 SUP token airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet over, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23205</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Whale Holding Over Four Years Sells 50 WBTC, Realizing $2.91 Million in Profit 4 Hours Ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23202</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), address 0x21F...514b3 accumulated 176 WBTC from April to May 2021 at an average price of $56,410.89, with a total value of $9.92 million. The position once experienced a drawdown to $2.89 million. There has been no selling behavior during this period. Four hours ago, 50 WBTC were deposited into Binance; if sold now, a profit of $2.91 million would be realized. The remaining 138.25 WBTC still hold an unrealized gain of $8.03 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23202</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOCHK Completes Phase 2 Testing of DigiBond on In-house Built Consortium Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23204</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to the Aastocks report, Bank of China Hong Kong has announced the completion of the second stage trial of the pilot project under the &quot;e-Yuan+&quot; initiative of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority. This trial verified the programmability of digital currency in prepaid consumption and earmarked use cases. By using a self-built alliance blockchain, the concept of a &quot;unified wallet&quot; was tested, and more than 1500 transactions were completed at PacificCoffee.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23204</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: The current surge of altcoins may be difficult to sustain, and market sentiment still needs to be observed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23203</link>
      <description>August 5th. Matrixport shared today&apos;s market views as follows: Despite the continuous hype in the market regarding the &quot;altcoin bull run,&quot; there have only been two brief rebound rounds up to now, which were concentrated on a few projects. The overall market lacks sustainability. Although there was a phased activity in the fourth quarter of 2024, it did not lead to widespread diffusion.Overall, the rebound lacks fundamental support, making it difficult to drive the market into a sustained upward momentum. Matrixport remains cautious and believes that this round of gains may be difficult to maintain. The rapid drop in funding rates also indicates that bullish sentiment has not effectively converged, and market enthusiasm is still under observation.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23203</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Network has resumed normal block production.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23201</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per the information provided by the Base Explorer and OKLink Explorer, the Base network has resumed normal block production.Before this update, the Base network encountered a brief outage, during which the block height was frozen at 33,792,704 for more than 20 minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23201</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Network Experiencing Anomaly: No New Block Generated for Over 27 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23200</link>
      <description>On August 5th, based on Base Browser data, it is possible that the Base network encountered an anomaly where no new blocks were generated for more than 27 minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>《GENIUS Act》 Leads to Surge in Revenue-Sharing Stablecoin Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23199</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to Cointelegraph, since the enactment of the July &quot;GENIUS Stablecoin Act,&quot; the supply of yield-generating stablecoins has witnessed a significant surge. The data indicates that the primary beneficiaries are Ethena&apos;s USDe and Sky&apos;s USDS. Both of these stablecoins can earn yield when staked within their respective protocols.According to DefiLlama data, as of July 18th, the circulating supply of USDe has grown by 70% and reached $9.49 billion, ranking third among all stablecoins in terms of market capitalization. During the same period, the circulating supply of USDS has increased by 23% and reached nearly $4.81 billion, ranking fourth in terms of market capitalization.Anthony Yim, the co-founder of analytics firm Artemis, stated, &quot;Despite the &apos;GENIUS Act&apos; prohibiting the issuance of yield-bearing stablecoins in the United States, the supply of such stablecoins has grown substantially and has become an &apos;unexpected winner.&apos;&quot; Julio Moreno, the Head of Research a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23199</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CIO: Uniswap&apos;s current market cap is undervalued, equivalent to the size of the world&apos;s 400th largest financial services company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23198</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Matt Hougan, the CIO of Bitwise, said, &quot;Uniswap&apos;s current valuation of $6 billion appears to be too low. If it were a company, it would rank as the 400th largest financial services firm globally, approximately on a par in size with Norway&apos;s savings and insurance company Storebrand.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23198</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B increased its holdings by 62 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 2075 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23197</link>
      <description>August 5th: The European publicly traded company Capital B (formerly known as The Blockchain Group) enhanced its Bitcoin holdings by 62 coins, resulting in a total of 2075 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23197</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>