<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol: AUBRAI Staking Now Live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26712</link>
      <description>August 28th, Bio Protocol made an announcement. The first BioAgent Launch project, AUBRAI staking, has been initiated. Stakers will obtain BioXP in the subsequent BioAgent and IP-Token sale.Furthermore, users who purchased more than 50% of AUBRAI during the previous two weeks&apos; Ignition Sale will be locked in the &quot;BioXP Prison&quot; for three weeks, and they will not receive BioXP during this period.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four. Meme: The Creditlink (CDL) presale, which lasted 4 hours, raised 60 million USD1 and 1.1 million FORM, setting a new record for presale amount on the BNB Chain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26711</link>
      <description>August 28th. As per official channels, the decentralized identity and credit project Creditlink (CDL) has commenced its presale on the Four.Meme platform. In the initial 4 hours, it has raised around 60 million USD1 and 1.1 million FORM. This has set a new record for the presale amount on the BNB Chain. Creditlink is dedicated to establishing an AI-driven on-chain identity verification and credit scoring system, guiding Web3 finance towards the path of uncollateralized and inclusive finance.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26711</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZKWASM and UnicornX AMA Recap: Focusing on the Long-Term Value of ZKWASM post UniCall Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26710</link>
      <description>On August 28th, during a recent AMA hosted by UnicornX, Anna Ann, the founder of the investment firm UnicornVerse, Sinka, the project lead, and community representatives engaged in an in-depth discussion. They shared insights on five main aspects: the technical accumulation of ZKWASM, its development journey, the future roadmap, as well as UnicornX&apos;s investment logic and the UniCall mechanism.UnicornVerse founder Ann stated that the reason for choosing ZKWASM is due to the team&apos;s long-term perspective, the WASM+ZK technical moat, and the strong alignment with UnicornX&apos;s investment philosophy. ZKWASM founder Sinka introduced the complete path of the project from technical breakthroughs to ecosystem construction, emphasizing the future focus on performance optimization, ecosystem expansion, and community building.Several community members shared their experiences in participating in UniCall, acknowledging UnicornX&apos;s project selection and guidance while also providing suggestions for</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26710</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn, the &quot;ETH Long Whale,&quot; currently holds a long position in the &quot;Ant Farm&quot; while continuing to trade using rebates and remaining funds.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26709</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, &quot;insider trader&quot; James Wynn (@qwatio), AguilaTrades, and the &quot;ETH long liquidation roller&quot; have now reduced their positions. Only James Wynn and the &quot;ETH long liquidation roller&quot; are still engaged in &quot;ant trading&quot;.James Wynn obtained a $114,000 commission through the Hyperliquid referral link. He used this commission funds to open some ant trades. For example, he has $10,000 in his address and opened a 10x long position on DOGE.The &quot;ETH long liquidation roller&quot; was continuously liquidated the day before yesterday. It still held a long position in ETH with the remaining $60,000 in the address. After two days, it has now grown to $90,000.Previously reported, on August 26th, &quot;insider trader&quot; James Wynn (@qwatio), AguilaTrades, and the &quot;ETH long liquidation roller&quot; collectively reached a peak profit of $197.7 million. Since then, they have returned most of the profits and even lost their initial capital.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26709</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of initial unemployment claims in the United States dropped last week, with layoffs remaining low.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26708</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the initial jobless claims in the United States for the previous week showed a slight decline. However, weak job growth may lead the August unemployment rate to reach 4.3%. The data released by the Labor Department on Thursday indicated that the seasonally adjusted state unemployment insurance initial claims decreased by 5,000 to 229,000 people in the week ending August 23rd. Driven by President Trump&apos;s protectionist trade policy, the average import tariffs in the US have reached the highest level in a century, resulting in the labor market being stuck in a &quot;neither hiring nor firing&quot; dilemma. A report from the US government in early August showed that the average monthly employment growth in the past three months was 35,000, which was much lower than 123,000 in the same period in 2024. Domestic demand has also slowed down significantly, partly due to tariff policies. Federal Reserve Chairman Powell hinted last week that the Fed may cut interest rates at the September p</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26708</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Initial Jobless Claims Data Strong, Highlighting Resilience of the US Labor Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26707</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Analyst Giuseppe Dellamotta&apos;s analysis of US initial claims data showed that the data exhibited strength. This was particularly the case when considering the downward revision of continuing claims. Unemployment claims data continue to affirm the resilience of the labor market. Now, the market focus will shift to the employment sub-index of the ISM Purchasing Managers&apos; Index, ADP private employment data, and the US non-farm payroll report. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26707</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. second-quarter real GDP annualized growth rate revised to 3.3%, expected 3.10%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26706</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the revised annualized real GDP growth rate for the second quarter in the United States was 3.3%, which was higher than the expected 3.10% and the previous value of 3.00%. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26706</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending August 23rd totaled 229,000, compared to the expected 230,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26705</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the number of initial jobless claims in the United States for the week ending August 23 was 229,000. The expected value was 230,000. The previous value was revised from 235,000 to 234,000. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26705</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AirNet Technology has completed a $180 million private placement fundraising, with the proceeds paid in BTC and ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26704</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the Nasdaq-listed company AirNet Technology announced that it has successfully completed a private placement fundraising. A total of 80,826,225 common shares and accompanying warrants were issued, raising approximately $180 million. The proceeds were all paid in digital assets, which included around 819.07 Bitcoins and 19,928.91 Ethereums.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The United States, Japan, and South Korea have issued a joint declaration regarding North Korean IT personnel, pledging to collectively address the threat posed by North Korean IT personnel.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26703</link>
      <description>August 28th: The United States, Japan, and South Korea jointly issued a statement regarding North Korean IT personnel. It was stated that the three countries will remain united in addressing the threat posed by North Korean IT personnel. North Korea has been constantly sending IT personnel worldwide to make profits. The funds obtained are used to finance illegal large-scale weapons of mass destruction and ballistic missile programs in violation of United Nations Security Council resolutions. The United States, Japan, and South Korea expressed serious concerns about the increasingly malicious activities of North Korean IT personnel.North Korean IT personnel use various means to disguise themselves as non-North Korean IT workers. They use false identities and addresses for deception, including the use of artificial intelligence tools and collusion with foreign accomplices. They take advantage of the existing demand for advanced IT skills in the market and obtain freelance contracts fro</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26703</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>