<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:54:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>$4.6 billion worth of BTC and $1.3 billion worth of ETH options are set to expire today, with the maximum pain point at $11,800 and $4,000 respectively.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24751</link>
      <description>August 15th. Greek.Live analyst Adam disclosed today&apos;s options expiry data:39,000 BTC options reached their expiration. The Put Call Ratio was 0.95. The max pain was at $118,000, and the nominal value was $4.6 billion.280,000 ETH options expired. The Put Call Ratio was 1.04. The max pain was at $4000, and the nominal value was $1.3 billion.This week, BTC hit a new high, and ETH also reached a historical high near $4800. The market sentiment is extremely bullish. Nearly $6 billion in options expired this week, accounting for 9% of the current total open interest. On Thursday, Deribit&apos;s single-day options volume reached $10.9 billion. Looking at the major options data, in terms of implied volatility, BTC&apos;s IV remains low. The medium to short-term IV stays below 35%. While ETH&apos;s main term IV remains high at 70%, which matches the current potential volatility expectations for ETH. There have been many large trades recently. A significant number of large trades have been made for both bu</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24751</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s latest PUBLIC Airdrop single-ticket profit is approximately $31</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24750</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on market information, PublicAI (PUBLIC) has been listed on Binance Alpha. It is currently trading at $0.072, and its market capitalization is $14.3 million. Each eligible user can receive 430 PUBLIC tokens through an airdrop. The estimated value of the airdrop per eligible recipient at the current price is approximately $31.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24750</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catizen is releasing its Mid-Year 2025 Recap and will launch the TON L2 GameChain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24749</link>
      <description>August 15th. Catizen unveiled its 2025 mid-year data: The total user base of the platform reached 63.4 million. Over 50 million CATI were collected this year, accounting for 15% of the total circulation. In May of this year, Catizen also secured a strategic investment from Animoca Brands. In the second half of the year, the ecosystem&apos;s Web3 games Cattea and Capybobo will undergo significant updates. Catizen will launch the TON L2 chain game public chain and hundreds of games, aiming to establish the world&apos;s largest game public chain.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24749</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 2 hours, a newly created wallet withdrew 17,591 ETH from Kraken, worth $81.62 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24747</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, in the past 2 hours, there has been another new wallet making a withdrawal of 17,591 ETH from Kraken, which is worth $81.62 million.During the past 3 days, a total of two newly created wallets have withdrawn a combined total of 71,025 ETH from Kraken, with a value of $330 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24747</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: Grok Soon to Have Speech Output Ability</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24748</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Musk tweeted that &quot;Grok will shortly possess speech output capabilities.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24748</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market Crypto Stocks in US Market Show Mixed Performance, with Bullish Up by 2.44%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24746</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the market data from RockFlow, the pre-market cryptocurrency stocks in the US showed mixed trends. These included:- The mining firm TeraWulf (WULF) decreased by 0.11%.- The cryptocurrency exchange platform Bullish (BLSH) increased by 2.44%.- Circle (CRCL) decreased by 0.77%.- Coinbase (COIN) increased by 0.55%.- MicroStrategy (MSTR) increased by 0.25%.- SharpLink Gaming (SBET) increased by 0.3%.- Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) increased by 2.06%.- The &quot;IP Treasury Strategy&quot; company Heritage Distilling (CASK) increased by 9.98%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24746</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow Futures Up 0.7%, Intel Continues Pre-market rally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24745</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the market data from RockFlow, the S&amp;P 500 Index Futures increased by 0.2%, the Nasdaq 100 Index Futures rose by 0.04%, and the Dow Jones Index Futures went up by 0.7%. Intel maintained its pre-market rally, rising by more than 4%. It closed up by 7.38% yesterday, with a market value of $104.4 billion.Earlier, according to informed sources, the Trump administration is in negotiations with Intel (INTC.O) with the aim of seeking a U.S. government stake.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24745</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midgame and OSL Group Reach Strategic Partnership to Jointly Promote Stablecoin Payment Collaboration New Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24744</link>
      <description>August 15th, the global IP game operator Century Huatong and the compliant digital financial infrastructure platform OSL Group (0863.HK) have entered into a strategic cooperation. They will deeply integrate OSL Group&apos;s compliant virtual asset financial infrastructure capabilities with Century Huatong&apos;s rich global IP game application ecosystem in order to jointly promote the application scenarios of compliant stablecoin ecosystem cooperation.This strategic cooperation between the two parties is based on the complementarity of their businesses and aims to bridge the value loop of Web3 technology from the underlying infrastructure to the upper-layer compliant applications within a multi-jurisdictional license network. By leveraging Century Huatong&apos;s own technological capabilities and industry influence, and based on OSL&apos;s provision of compliant digital asset custody and a unified settlement layer tool supporting multiple chains and currencies, they will provide 24/7 global cross-border</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Reveals Justin Sun&apos;s &quot;$24.6 Billion&quot; Asset List, the Latter Sues Alleging Privacy Breach</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24743</link>
      <description>August 15th. According to the data disclosed in the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, as of August 15, 2025, the assets of Justin Sun were nominally valued at approximately $24.6 billion. After discounting based on liquidity, it was around $12.4 billion. The majority of his net worth comes from his cryptocurrency holdings, which include:· 600 billion TRX, accounting for 63.3% of the total TRX supply, with a nominal value of $21.6 billion. Due to concerns about illiquidity, Bloomberg discounted this part of assets by 75%;· Approximately 17,000 Bitcoins (worth about $20.4 billion), 224,000 Ethereums (worth about $10.52 billion), and 700,000 USDT. The analysis only covers on-chain tokens; tokens held by Justin Sun on exchanges such as HTX and Binance are not included in the analysis as their holdings could not be verified;In response to this information, Justin Sun has filed a lawsuit against Bloomberg, claiming that the latter &quot;recklessly and inappropriately disclosed his highly co</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24743</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list TCOM Global (TCOM) with a minimum airdrop threshold of 200 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24742</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Binance Alpha will list TCOM Global (TCOM), and trading will commence on August 15, 2025, at 20:00 (UTC+8). Users who have at least 200 Binance Alpha points can receive an airdrop of 600 TCOM tokens on a first-come, first-served basis.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24742</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>