<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 01:05:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 01:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>First YZY Buyer&apos;s Identity Revealed, Once Profited Over $100 Million with TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25661</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to the on-chain analysis conducted by Bubblemaps, the first purchaser of YZY was Naseem. Naseem spent $1.1 million this year on investing in TRUMP and ultimately reaped a profit of over $100 million.YZY was deployed on the blockchain on August 17th, and the first actual transaction took place on August 21st. The address starting with AwY1V purchased $250,000 worth of YZY. Bubblemaps discovered on the blockchain that the address starting with AwY1V is closely related to wallets that were previously linked to Naseem, including addresses that had previously bought Libra and Trump. Based on this evidence, there is a reason to believe that the address starting with AwY1V is Naseem.As of now, Naseem has cashed out $800,000 from the initial purchase and still holds $600,000 worth of YZY. He may have used other addresses for transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25661</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Roll-over Long on ETH」 Whale opens 25x leveraged long position with 4026 ETH, worth $17.1 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25660</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to Ashes Monitoring, the &quot;Long ETH with $125k Liquidation&quot; whale transferred 740,000 USDC to Hyperliquid two hours ago. Currently, this whale has opened a 25x leveraged long position with 4,026 ETH (valued at $17.1 million), and the average entry price per ETH is $4,247.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25660</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AERO briefly surged above $1.4, jumping over 7% in 5 minutes.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25659</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to GMGN market data, AERO briefly broke through $1.4 and is currently trading at $1.39, with a 5-minute price increase of 7.29%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25659</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Upbit will list AERO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25658</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per an official announcement, Upbit is set to list the trading pairs of AERO in KRW, USDT, and BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25658</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain ancient whale has sold 3100 BTC and bought 50,522 ETH, going long with 5x leverage on 135,000 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25657</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to Chainalysis, a whale or institution that has been holding 10,606 BTC for as long as 7 years has achieved a profit of $1.12 billion. Currently, this whale or institution has sold 3,100 BTC (valued at $348 million) and purchased 50,522 ETH (valued at $213 million) in spot transactions.In addition, it has spent $120 million on margin to take a long position of 135,000 ETH with a 5x leverage, and it still holds 7,537 BTC (worth $846 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25657</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Justice Policy Shift: Decentralized Software Developers to Be Protected from Certain Liability</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25656</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per Decrypt, a high-ranking official from the U.S. Department of Justice informed a group of cryptocurrency industry lobbyists and leaders during a gathering in Jackson Hole, Wyoming. The official stated that the U.S. government will no longer prosecute decentralized software developers under specific charges. Just a bit earlier this month, federal prosecutors managed to secure a conviction of Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm on these very charges.This charge originates from Title 18 U.S. Code § 1960(b)(1)(C), which stipulates that any unlicensed money transmitting business operator involved with funds known to be derived from illegal activities or intended for unlawful use is regarded as illegal. Just a few weeks ago, a Manhattan jury found Storm guilty of violating this law, which has a maximum sentence of 5 years in federal prison. However, the jury was unable to reach a verdict on all other charges.During today&apos;s Jackson Hole policy summit, Matthew Galeott</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Central Bank Digital Currency provision included in US House-approved defense policy bill</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25655</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as reported by The Block, an anti-Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) provision has been incorporated into a defense appropriations bill that is regarded as &quot;must-pass&quot; legislation. This provision has been added to the latest version of the United States House of Representatives&apos; National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA).The newly added chapter in the bill is named the &quot;Anti-CBDC Surveillance Act,&quot; and its contents are in line with a bill previously introduced by House Majority Leader Whip Tom Emmer. Earlier this summer, the full House passed Emmer&apos;s bill with a vote of 219 to 210. The bill intends to prohibit the Federal Reserve from directly issuing a central bank digital currency to individuals.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25655</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC Announces Launch of New Round of &apos;Crypto Sprint&apos; Initiative</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25654</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per an official announcement, Caroline D. Pham, who is the Acting Chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), declared that the CFTC will initiate a new round of Crypto Sprint in order to implement the recommendations of the President&apos;s Working Group on Financial Markets.Pham stated that at the federal level, advancing real-time digital asset trading is a top government priority, and the CFTC&apos;s spot cryptocurrency trading listing plan aligns with the SEC&apos;s Project Crypto in response to President Trump&apos;s call. She emphasized that public feedback will be beneficial for the CFTC to formulate policies related to leverage, margin, and retail trading.The CFTC also extended an invitation to the industry to submit comments on the recommendations in the &quot;Enhancing U.S. Leadership in Digital Financial Technologies&quot; report.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25654</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Collins: Rate Cut Might Be Appropriate in the Short Term if Labor Market Outlook Worsens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25653</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Federal Reserve&apos;s Collins said that if the outlook of the labor market deteriorates, a rate cut may be appropriate in the short term. We cannot wait until inflation becomes completely clear before considering a rate cut. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25653</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million Followers KOL Andrew Tate Shorting YZY, with a Position Size of $175,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25652</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per the monitoring of @mlmabc, KOL Andrew Tate, who has tens of millions of followers on the X platform, has just placed a short position worth $175,000 on YZY (Kanye West&apos;s Meme coin) with an opening price of $0.8523 and a liquidation price of $1.0306.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25652</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>