<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:52:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Staking Armageddon」 is Coming, Over $5.38 Billion ETH Staked has Exited and Moved to a Centralized Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25921</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, as per EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, 111,456 ETH (valued at $538 million) has withdrawn from staking in Eigenlayer over the past 20 hours. Subsequently, it was transferred to Matrixport in the last 3 hours. And in the most recent 1 hour, it was further moved from Matrixport to Binance and OKX.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25921</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: &quot;Macrohard&quot; Project by &quot;Giantsoft&quot; is Real, a Pure AI Software Company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25920</link>
      <description>August 23rd. Musk tweeted yesterday and said, &quot;Join xAI to jointly build a purely AI software company named Macrohard. The name has a bit of a humorous meaning, but the project is completely genuine. In principle, software companies like Microsoft do not produce any physical hardware themselves. Therefore, theoretically, they can be entirely simulated by AI.&quot;In response, Grok under xAI stated, &quot;Macrohard&quot; is a fun project name of xAI (paying tribute to Microsoft). The goal is to establish a fully AI-simulated software company. Since enterprises like Microsoft do not produce any hardware, AI can theoretically replicate their entire operation, ranging from programming to management. &quot;This is true, and we are hiring!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Websea&apos;s Second Anniversary Celebration is about to kick off, with Five Major Welfare Benefits in full swing.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25919</link>
      <description>August 23rd - In celebration of its two-year anniversary, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Websea will launch a themed event from August 26th to September 4th, titled &quot;Two-Year Journey: Borderless Trading, Co-Creating the Web3 Wealth Map.&quot; This celebration encompasses Early Bird Airdrops, Lucky Koi Fish, Social Red Envelopes Rain, Game Interaction, Card Collection Exploration, and other multi-faceted gameplay. Users have the chance to win prizes such as Contract Trial Funds, VIP Experience Cards, iPhone 16, Moutai Liquor, Gold, and other magnificent prizes. The event covers all core sections of the website and is designed to reward users, witnessing together Websea&apos;s growth and breakthroughs over the past two years. Users can participate in the anniversary celebration on the Websea official website.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25919</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shangri-La Group will establish a cryptocurrency strategic reserve, with a priority on BTC, ETH, and USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25918</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, AMTD IDEA Group (「AMTD IDEA Group」), which is dual-listed on the New York Stock Exchange and the Singapore Stock Exchange and is a subsidiary of AMTD Group; AMTD Digital Inc. and The Generation Essentials Group (「TGE」) jointly announced that cryptocurrency will be an essential part of the corporate treasuries of these three companies as a &quot;strategic reserve.&quot;This &quot;strategic reserve&quot; encompasses bank deposits and other uncollateralized, unencumbered, and liquid investments, totaling approximately $240 million as of June 30, 2025. Specifically, the planned cryptocurrency investment portfolio will center around Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and USDT.Among the three NYSE-listed companies under the AMTD Group, TGE will be in charge of expanding and concentrating on cryptocurrency-related opportunities and development. The name TGE has held genetic significance since its inception, representing not only &quot;The Generation Essentials&quot; but also symbolically referring to &quot;Toke</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25918</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: OTC Platforms and Market Makers Show Stronger Demand for ETH than BTC; ETH May Continue to Outperform BTC in the Future</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25917</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, following Federal Reserve Chairman Powell&apos;s dovish signal at the Jackson Hole Economic Symposium, which went against market expectations of a tougher stance, cryptocurrencies witnessed a surge on Friday night. Consequently, asset managers anticipate that Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and certain altcoins will reach new highs.Analysts from Monarq Asset Management project that the price of Ethereum will ascend to above $5,000 in the forthcoming days. Sam Gaer, the Chief Investment Officer of the Monarq Direction Fund, informed CoinDesk, &quot;We maintain an overall bullish outlook. The market&apos;s internal structure remains in good health with little indication of overheating. As you mentioned, the path to new highs for BTC and ETH is quite evident.&quot;Gaer stated that over-the-counter desks and market makers have a greater demand for ETH compared to BTC, suggesting that Ethereum may outperform Bitcoin in the future. Nevertheless, BTC itself is also demonstrating strong impetus</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25917</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale has once again moved 2520 BTC to ETH, now holding a total of over 153,000 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25916</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, as monitored by Onchain Lens, within the past 6 hours, a particular Bitcoin ancient whale deposited 2,520 BTC into HyperLiquid. The value of these BTC is $291.75 million, and they are intended for selling and exchanging into ETH. This OG currently holds 153,320 ETH, with a value of $724.1 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25916</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: WLFI&apos;s pre-market price reached a peak FDV of $55 billion, equivalent to the total FDV of LINK, UNI, ENA, and ONDO.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25915</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to the analysis of on-chain analyst AI Auntie @ai_9684xtpa, the highest price of WLFI at the opening of the Binance pre-market contract was $0.55, corresponding to a Fully Diluted Valuation (FDV) of $55 billion. This data is equivalent to the sum of the FDVs of four projects: LINK, UNI, ENA, and ONDO.At the time of this writing, the pre-market contract price of WLFI has dropped to $0.3771.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25915</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XDOG Surges Over 90% in 24 Hours, Market Cap Reaches $12.5 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25914</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on GMGN data, the X Layer on-chain Meme coin XDOG witnessed a surge of over 90% in the past 24 hours. Its market value rebounded to $12.5 million.BlockBeats alerts users that Meme coin prices are highly volatile. It is necessary to be cautious about asset protection and avoid the FOMO (Fear of Missing Out) phenomenon.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25914</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum briefly dropped below $4,700, now rebounded to $4,723</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25913</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to HTX market data, Ethereum briefly fell below $4,700. It is now rebounding to $4,723, with a 24-hour change of 8.82%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25913</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: Cautiously Optimistic About Starship&apos;s Full Reusability Next Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25912</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, SpaceX CEO Musk stated that constructing a fully reusable orbital rocket is one of the most challenging engineering issues that humanity has faced to date. It is even more difficult than going to the moon, which is why it has not been achieved yet. He is cautiously optimistic that Starship will achieve full reusability next year. Another crucial technology is orbital refueling, which is relatively simpler. If they are fortunate, it may also be achieved next year. By then, human consciousness and life will be able to expand to other planets and even stars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>