<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21935</link>
      <description>On July 26th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin has rebounded and is now above $118,000, with a 24-hour increase of 1.46%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21935</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Past 7 days CEX Net outflow of 99,500 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21934</link>
      <description>On July 26th, according to Coinglass data, during the past 7 days, CEX has witnessed a total net outflow of 99,500 Ethereum. The top three exchanges with outflows are as follows:· Binance, with an outflow of 24,200 ETH;· Bitfinex, with an outflow of 23,100 ETH;· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 9,387.90 ETH.In addition, OKX saw an inflow of 8,607.98 ETH and ranked first on the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21934</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEX Net Outflow of 17,117.49 BTC in the Last 7 Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21933</link>
      <description>On July 26th, according to Coinglass data, during the past 7 days, the total net outflow of BTC from CEXs was 17,117.49 BTC. The top three exchanges with the largest outflows are as follows:· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 8,701.25 BTC;· Kraken, with an outflow of 5,668.80 BTC;· Binance, with an outflow of 2,635.99 BTC.In addition, Bitfinex saw an inflow of 501.41 BTC and ranked first on the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21933</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Once Considered Splitting NVIDIA, Now Engaging in Mutual Praise with Jensen Huang, Trump&apos;s AI Stance Takes a Subtle Turn</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21932</link>
      <description>On July 26th, during an Artificial Intelligence summit held in Washington D.C., U.S. President Trump declared that he had earnestly contemplated breaking up NVIDIA in order to disrupt the company&apos;s AI chip monopoly and boost industry competition. Trump recollected, &quot;Before I grasped the facts, I remarked, &apos;We are going to disassemble this company.&apos;&quot; Nevertheless, after receiving a briefing from his staff, he became aware that NVIDIA had already achieved a prominent advantage in technology and the ecosystem, making it challenging to be replaced in the short run.Ultimately, he conceded, &quot;This is not a simple matter.&quot; More significantly, Trump subsequently publicly commended NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang and engaged with him on the spot. Huang responded in kind on the stage, stating, &quot;The unique advantage of the United States is something that other countries do not possess, that is President Trump.&quot; The mutual &quot;praise&quot; between the two regarding AI policy implies Trump&apos;s pursuit of a more bal</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21932</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This month, the buyback of tokens by pump.fun has been severely &quot;halved,&quot; with the $19.5 million PUMP now only worth $8.2 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21931</link>
      <description>On July 26th, as monitored by OnchainLens, 8 to 10 days ago, pump.fun allocated 120,450 SOL (valued at $19.5 million at that time) to purchase 3.07 billion PUMP tokens. However, currently, the total value of these tokens amounts only to $8.2 million.Related wallet addresses:3vkpy5YHqnqJTnA5doWTpcgKyZiYsaXYzYM9wm8s3WTiG8CcfRffqZWHSAQJXLDfwbAkGE95SddUqVXnTrL4kqjm</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 09:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21931</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「LUNA/UST Flash Crash Shorting Whale」 Acquires 80.2623 WBTC at an Average Price of $118,174</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21930</link>
      <description>On July 26th, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;Whale Who Shorted BTC to Earn $5.16 Million During the LUNA/UST Flash Crash&quot; has once again entered the market, this time focusing on WBTC.In the past half an hour, he spent $9.485 million to purchase 80.2623 WBTC at an average price of $118,174. &quot;The bearish impact of the ancient whale&apos;s sell-off has become a reality, and it seems that this smart money is optimistic about the future performance.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 09:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21930</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week, the net inflow into the US Ethereum spot ETF was $18.465 billion, while during the same period, the Bitcoin ETF saw only $72.3 million in inflows.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21929</link>
      <description>On July 26th, as reported by Farside Monitor, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF this week reached $18.465 billion. In contrast, during the same period, the net inflow of the Bitcoin spot ETF was only $72.30 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21929</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink has spent approximately $12.5 million to hire former BlackRock executive Joseph Chalom as the company&apos;s Co-CEO.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21928</link>
      <description>On July 26th, according to SharpLink Gaming, Inc. as stated in an 8-K filing disclosed in July 2025, Joseph Chalom, a former executive of BlackRock, was appointed as the Co-CEO of the company, with the appointment taking effect on July 24, 2025. Joseph Chalom had previously been involved in the launch of BlackRock&apos;s Bitcoin Spot ETF IBIT, BlackRock&apos;s Ethereum Spot ETF ETHA, and BUIDL (the first tokenized sovereign debt fund on Ethereum). The current CEO, Rob Phythian, will share this position with Chalom, and the details of Chalom&apos;s new hiring agreement are as follows:An annual salary of $750,000, a target bonus equivalent to 100% of the annual salary, 7 million restricted stock units (RSUs) with a two-thirds time-based vesting and one-third performance-based vesting, a Long-Term Incentive Plan (LTIP) for the 2026 fiscal year of not less than $4 million, immediate vesting with a &quot;double-trigger&quot; upon a Change in Control (CIC), and a severance package of two times the annual salary an</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin breaks $119,000, the mainstream CEX aggregate short liquidation pressure will reach $948 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21927</link>
      <description>On July 26th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin surges above $119,000, the total short liquidation strength on mainstream CEXs will amount to $948 million. In contrast, if Bitcoin drops below $116,000, the total long liquidation strength on mainstream CEXs will reach $588 million.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of the contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, strength.Consequently, the liquidation chart shows the extent to which the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price, when reached, will have a more pronounced reaction due to a liquidity avalanche.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21927</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSC Ecosystem Meme Coin Totakeke&apos;s Market Cap Once Reached $15 Million, with a 24-hour Growth of 420%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21926</link>
      <description>On July 26th, according to GMGN market data, the Meme coin Totakeke in the BSC ecosystem briefly reached a market capitalization of 15 million US dollars. Currently, it stands at 12.97 million US dollars, with a 24-hour price increase of 420% and a 24-hour trading volume of 5.8 million US dollars.Furthermore, Totakeke has officially announced its partnership with the well-known Meme project CHEEMS in the BSC ecosystem.BlockBeats Note: Meme coins typically exhibit significant price volatility, often driven by market sentiment and hype surrounding a concept and lacking actual value or a practical use case. Investors should be cautious of the risks involved.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21926</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>