<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:56:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list CYBER/USDC, MAV/USDC, and SKL/USDC spot trading pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25021</link>
      <description>August 18th. According to an official announcement, Binance announced that it will list the CYBER/USDC, MAV/USDC, and SKL/USDC spot trading pairs on August 19th, 2025, at 4:00 PM (UTC+8).In addition, Binance will provide trading bot services for the following trading pairs starting on August 19th, 2025, at 4:00 PM (UTC+8).Spot Algo Orders: CYBER/USDC, MAV/USDC, and SKL/USDC.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25021</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Bitcoin to Revisit $112,000 or Lower, Market Awaits Fed FOMC Meeting as Key Catalyst</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25020</link>
      <description>On August 18th, Matrixport issued a new report indicating that Bitcoin was unable to hold the downtrend line. This initially signaled a breakout but recently dropped below the former support. Although not overly worried about further downside risks, due to the market remaining cautious ahead of the September Fed rate decision, the Bitcoin price may once again test the $112,000 level.Matrixport does not anticipate that this year&apos;s Jackson Hole meeting will release any significant signals as it is more of a discussion platform rather than a market driver. Currently, the market is awaiting a real catalyst, with the September 17th FOMC meeting being the most crucial event.Technically, Bitcoin is currently in a &quot;no man&apos;s land&quot; between $112,000 and $117,292. This leaves traders with two distinct strategies: buying on a breakout above the range or accumulating on a pullback near $112,000. In other words, the market is in a period of observation, waiting for a clear direction.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25020</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit WSOT 2025&apos;s first Trader’s Camp livestream kicks off today, with a total prize pool of 10 million USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25019</link>
      <description>On August 18th, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Bybit announced that the annual trading extravaganza World Series of Trading (WSOT) 2025 has officially begun, with a huge prize pool reaching up to 10 million USDT. The first Trader&apos;s Camp live event will commence today at 8:00 AM UTC.The live lineup consists of renowned traders and KOLs such as Chart Champions, David Tech, Dusty BC, Crypto Rover, and Forfiles, who will share exclusive strategies and interact with participants. During the live broadcast, viewers will also get the chance to share a 10,000 USDT reward.As the highlight of the WSOT 2025 ten-day prelude event, this series of activities will include leaderboard sprints, mystery box missions, and a total of 20,000 USDT in cryptocurrency learning course challenges. Live broadcast benefits involve a sneak peek at new features, a 5,000 USDT airdrop, and iPhone 16 Pro Max and other luxury gifts.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25019</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch crypto service provider Amdax establishes Bitcoin Treasury company AMBTS, aiming to hold 210,000 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25018</link>
      <description>On August 18th, according to @btcNLNico, the Dutch cryptocurrency service provider Amdax has set in motion the establishment of AMBTS B.V. (referred to as &quot;AMBTS&quot;). It is planned to list as a Bitcoin treasury company on the pan-European securities trading platform Amsterdam Market. The long-term goal of AMBTS is to gradually transform into a treasury company holding 1% of the global Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25018</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Long ETH Liquidation」 Whale has taken profits, realizing a 53.92x return in 4 months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25017</link>
      <description>August 18th. Based on the on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;125K USD Long Liquidation Whales&quot; has realized profits. It has finally earned 6.865 million USD. The profit is 84% lower than the peak of 42.987 million USD, and the four-month return on investment (ROI) is 53.92 times.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25017</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMBI Securities International Commences Offering Virtual Asset Trading Services</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25016</link>
      <description>August 18th. According to official channels, CMB International Securities declared the formal launch of its virtual asset trading service. The mobile app of CMB International Securities has initiated the virtual asset trading function, offering 7x24-hour virtual asset trading services to eligible investors. Eligible investors can directly engage in Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and USDT trading through a virtual asset account.CMB International Securities is the first Hong Kong-based Chinese-funded bank-owned brokerage firm to obtain a license for virtual asset trading services. In the future, within the framework of risk control and compliance management, CMB International Securities will gradually expand the scope of virtual asset trading and enhance its functionalities.Note: Eligible investors refer to those possessing professional investor qualifications and being residents in regions where there are no restrictions on virtual asset sales. Investors must first successfully open</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Reservoir (DAM) and open up airdrop claiming for eligible users.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25015</link>
      <description>August 18th. As per official information, Binance Alpha is set to launch Reservoir (DAM).Alpha Trading Commences: August 18th, 2025 at 19:00 (UTC + 8).Spot Trading Commences: August 18th, 2025 at 20:30 (UTC + 8).Once trading begins, users who hold at least 200 Binance Alpha Points can claim 320 DAM tokens as an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.Claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as giving up the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25015</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain day trader panic-sold 2277 ETH, securing a $4.04 million profit.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25014</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a certain scalper sold 2277 ETH (valued at $9.57 million) in a panic. The average transaction price was $4203. Along with a high on-chain slippage, it ultimately locked in a profit of $4.04 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25014</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin briefly drops below $115,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25013</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin briefly fell below $115,000 and is now trading at $115,077, with a 24-hour decrease of 2.49%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25013</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: RiceAI (RICE) TGE participation threshold is 230 Alpha Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25012</link>
      <description>August 18, as per an official announcement, Binance has declared that Binance users possessing 230 points or more of Binance Alpha Points are eligible to participate in the RiceAI (RICE) TGE event via the Alpha event page. Participating in this event will result in a deduction of 15 points.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25012</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>