<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:15:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Putin&apos;s Meeting Failed to Deliver Substantial Positive News, BTC Stuck in Range-Bound Trading, Resistance at $120,600, Limited Upside Potential</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24879</link>
      <description>August 16th: The &quot;Putin-Biden Summit in Alaska&quot; came to an end. Although it was the longest face-to-face interaction between the two leaders, it ultimately failed to yield specific results. Trump characterized it as &quot;productive but no agreement reached yet,&quot; while Putin emphasized a constructive atmosphere and mentioned &quot;reaching some undisclosed agreements.&quot; However, the market found it difficult to obtain clear signals in such an &quot;upbeat atmosphere with empty content.&quot; This has intensified concerns in Europe and Kyiv, and global markets still maintain a high level of sensitivity to geopolitical risks.The short-term performance of the crypto market has been characterized by fluctuating back and forth. BTC has been oscillating repeatedly within the range of 119,200–116,400, forming a support zone. The concentrated liquidation area above is around 119,600, and there is even greater pressure at 120,000. Order book data shows that the chips have not yet made a significant breakthrough,</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24879</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Buddy」 Goes Long on PUMP and HYPE, Overall Account Unrealized Loss Reduced to $5.34 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24878</link>
      <description>On August 16th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, &quot;Big Brother Whale&quot; Huang Lizheng took a long position on PUMP and HYPE with a leverage of 5 times. The position size was 25,000.00 HYPE and 300,000,000.00 PUMP. The opening prices were 46.5996 USD and 0.0034 USD respectively.In addition, he still holds long positions in ETH (with a leverage of 25 times) and BTC (with a leverage of 40 times). Currently, the total unrealized loss in the account amounts to 5.4 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24878</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinGecko Executive Team Update, CEO TM Lee to Transition to President</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24877</link>
      <description>August 16th - The cryptocurrency data aggregation platform CoinGecko announced a series of strategic leadership alterations today to fuel its next phase of expansion. Bobby Ong, a co-founder and the Chief Operating Officer, has been designated as the Chief Executive Officer, succeeding TM Lee, another co-founder and the former CEO. TM Lee will transition to the position of President.During his 11-year tenure as the Chief Operating Officer, Ong has played a crucial role in formulating CoinGecko&apos;s business strategy, expanding its global footprint, and augmenting its global influence. On the other hand, TM Lee will concentrate on promoting the long-term product vision and guiding greenfield research and development projects. This transition enables him to redirect his focus towards fundamental innovation while ensuring strategic continuity.Moreover, Cedric Chan will be appointed as the Chief Technology Officer, taking charge of leading CoinGecko&apos;s technical roadmap and infrastructure</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 12:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24877</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Sets &quot;First 10 Big Goals&quot; to Long Ethereum, Currently Facing Unrealized Loss of Over $640,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24876</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on the &quot;First Set of 10 Major Goals&quot; position screenshot shared by the Whale at 20:24 today, the Whale established a long position with more than 31,000 ETH at a leverage of 5x at a price of $4399.13. The liquidation price is $2655.41. The current unrealized loss is more than $640,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 12:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24876</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Macro Outlook: Powell&apos;s &quot;Battle&quot; Against Market Rate Cut Expectations, Fed Releases Monetary Policy Meeting Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24875</link>
      <description>Update, August 16th. During the past week, U.S. economic data has been a combination of positive and negative, resulting in continuous market volatility in the anticipation of a Fed rate cut. The data released on Friday showed that driven by robust auto sales and extensive online promotions, U.S. retail sales experienced broad-based growth. However, a subsequent report indicated an unexpected decrease in consumer confidence, which was the first since April, along with a rise in inflation expectations.Previously, the U.S. July CPI and PPI reports seemed to convey conflicting signals regarding whether the economy is withstanding the impact of Trump&apos;s comprehensive import tariffs, but both pointed to persistent service inflation, with PPI reaching a three-year high on a monthly basis. Meanwhile, there is evident internal disagreement within the Fed regarding a September rate cut.At 11:00 PM on Wednesday, Fed Governor Waller gave a speech at a blockchain seminar in Wyoming; at 2:00 AM</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 12:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24875</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Treasury Holdings Surpass 3.7M, Ethereum ETF Holdings Exceed 6.5M</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24874</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on the data from strategicethreserve, the total holdings of the Ethereum Treasury Reserve have reached 3.7 million ETH, which accounts for 3.06% of the total supply; the total holdings of the Ethereum ETF have reached 6.56 million ETH, accounting for 5.42% of the total supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24874</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week&apos;s net inflow into the US Ether ETF was $28.521 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24873</link>
      <description>On August 16th, according to Farside Investors, a net inflow of $2.8521 billion into the US Ethereum Spot ETF occurred this week.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 11:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24873</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem AI Game &quot;AI Nyan Mine&quot; Officially Launched</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24872</link>
      <description>On August 16th, the first Web3 + AI nurturing game launched by the CAT Terminal community - CAT Crew &quot;AI Meow Mining&quot; - officially went live.The CAT Terminal community held the global launch event of &quot;AI Meow Mining&quot; in Dubai, with the support of well-known Middle Eastern crypto organizations such as OOKC and X3 Labs. It attracted hundreds of Web3 enthusiasts from around the world to participate.Before the official launch, &quot;AI Meow Mining&quot; had completed two rounds of public testing. Over 3,000 players participated and the total feeding amount exceeded 100 million CAT tokens. The debut of CAT Crew has brought in a new MEME 2.0 gameplay, providing users with an unprecedented on-chain interactive experience.As of the time of writing, CAT&apos;s market capitalization is approximately $18 million and the number of holders has reached 6,900.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian President&apos;s Advisor: Ending the Russia-Ukraine Conflict Requires Ceasefire Before Negotiation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24871</link>
      <description>August 16th. Serhiy Leshchenko, the Chief Advisor to the Office of the President of Ukraine, made a statement on social media on August 16th about the ways and means to end the Russia-Ukraine conflict. Leshchenko stated that Ukraine is firmly convinced that a ceasefire must be achieved first before moving on to further negotiation processes.Leshchenko explicitly pointed out that Ukraine&apos;s stance is very clear, that is, ceasefire first and then other discussions. The reason for this is that if negotiations are begun before a ceasefire, Ukraine will be exposed to a huge ransom risk. Only by successfully achieving a ceasefire can the necessary space for diplomatic activities be created. (Sina Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24871</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over the last 24 hours, CEX net outflow of 1,435.75 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24870</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on Coinglass data, in the past 24 hours, CEX has witnessed a total net outflow of 1,435.75 BTC. The top three exchanges with outflows are as follows:· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 1,023.19 BTC;· OKX, with an outflow of 585.67 BTC;· Gemini, with an outflow of 482.79 BTC.In addition, Bitfinex saw an inflow of 242.98 BTC and ranked first in the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24870</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>