<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:29:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>GEN Market Cap Surpasses $60 Million, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25989</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on GMGN data, the price of the GEN token exceeded its previous high and briefly soared to $0.06040. Currently, its market value exceeded 60 million US dollars.It is reported that GEN is the native token of the General Impressions (GI) project. GI is constructing the core infrastructure of the Agentic AI era, which is a Rust-driven intelligent body network providing underlying support for the trusted execution of autonomous AI, low-cost reusability, and multi-agent collaboration. As a key driver of the rise of the Agentic Paradigm, GI is gradually becoming a key algorithmic protocol for decentralized intelligent systems.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investments should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25989</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Whenever the cumulative rate cut reaches 2%, the S&amp;P 500 tends to rise by an average of 13.9%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25988</link>
      <description>On August 24th, analysts claim that the U.S. labor market is deteriorating at a rapid pace. The latest data has revised down a whopping -258,000 job positions for May and June alone. This number is even greater than the total population of Scottsdale, Arizona. Up to now this year, 461,000 U.S. job positions have been revised downwards, and many leading indicators of the labor market are collapsing.All of this indicates that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates in order to curb inflation. However, as inflation rebounds, those without assets will find themselves in a situation similar to that in the post-pandemic era. Wage growth will lag behind inflation, and the wealth gap will widen. When the Fed has lowered rates to within 2% historically, as has occurred in the past 20 times, the S&amp;P 500 index has on average seen a +13.9% increase over the next 12 months, and asset owners will be in a party mood just like they were in 2021.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25988</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 15 minutes, 3 new addresses have accumulated 10,600 ETH, worth $51.04 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25987</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, within the past 15 minutes, 3 new wallet addresses have come into existence. These addresses have accumulated a total of 10,600 ETH from Galaxy Digital, with a value of $51.04 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25987</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Powell has effectively caved, September rate cut a &apos;done deal&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25986</link>
      <description>August 24th. The Kobeissi Letter disclosed its most recent market analysis, indicating that Fed Chair Powell has essentially yielded. The Fed is scheduled to cut rates one month from now, attributing it to the &quot;weak labor market.&quot; Meanwhile, the PPI inflation rate has reached its highest level in 3 years, and the CPI inflation rate has remained above 2% for 53 consecutive months. At this moment, not holding assets will lag behind the market.To gain a better understanding of what is transpiring, it is necessary to initially comprehend the Fed&apos;s responsibilities: The Fed&apos;s objective is to reduce unemployment and prevent inflation/deflation, which constitutes the Fed&apos;s &quot;dual mandate.&quot; Since 2021, the Fed has been extremely attentive to inflation. However, Fed Chair Powell&apos;s Friday speech brought about a significant transformation: &quot;A change in the balance of risks might necessitate a readjustment of our policy stance.&quot; In other words, the Fed now deems the risk of unemployment to be gre</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25986</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bitcoin OG Whale Keeps Reallocating to ETH, Ethereum&apos;s Total Holdings Valued at $1.06 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25985</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as monitored by OnchainLens, within the past 3 hours, a certain Bitcoin OG whale once more carried out a swap where 1,276 BTC were exchanged for ETH. This transaction was valued at $1.4709 billion. Currently, the OG whale holds 221,600 ETH, with a value of $1.06 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25985</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Coinbase User Funds Theft Hacker」 Buys 38,126 SOL at an average price of $208.7</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25984</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, within the past hour, the &quot;hacker who stole funds from Coinbase users&quot; swapped 7.957 million DAI for USDC and conducted a cross-chain transfer to Solana, purchasing 38,126 SOL at a purchase price of $208.7.The hacker:In May, sold 26,347 ETH and received 68.18 million DAI, with an average selling price of $2,588.In July, spent 14.865 million DAI to repurchase 5,513 ETH at a price of $2,696.Today, used 7.957 million DAI to buy 38,126 SOL at a price of $208.7.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: The bull market cycle is coming to an end, and my own ETH trading journey has effectively concluded</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25983</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio shared in his personal channel that it appears we have reached the climax of the bull market cycle that began in January 2023. I expect this phase to last no more than a few months. Every global marginal buyer is to some extent turning towards and investing in cryptocurrency. Both Bitcoin and Ethereum have reached new all-time highs. The high target I set for myself of an Ethereum/Bitcoin exchange rate of 0.04 has also been accomplished, indicating to me that the trading of ETH has effectively come to an end.I will no longer adopt an aggressive approach - no more large-scale Martingale momentum trades. The strategy focus is shifting from capital accumulation to capital preservation. I may miss out on any subsequent market frenzy, but that&apos;s fine because these fluctuations no longer match my trading system. This does not mean I have exited all positions and gone short (on the contrary, I am still holding long positions), but the net position siz</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25983</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Major &quot;Bankruptcy&quot; Contract Whales Current Positions Overview, AguilaTrade 40x Long on Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25981</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on the monitoring of HyperInsight, the current positions of the three major contract trading whales who had previously gone through a &quot;bankruptcy&quot; event (losing tens of millions of dollars on the books and ending up with zero), namely James Wynn, AguilaTrades, and the &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio, are as follows:James Wynn has liquidated his 25x long position in ETH and currently holds approximately $240,000 worth of DOGE with a 10x long position. The entry price was $0.23963, and he has incurred a net loss of $226,000 in the past 30 days.AguilaTrades has closed the 25x short position he opened at the all-time high of ETH. Currently, he holds around $2.82 million worth of BTC with a 40x long position. The entry price was $115,077, and the liquidation price was $113,640. He has suffered a net loss of $6.69 million in the past 30 days.The &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio has closed his 3x short position in XPL and is</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25981</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea: Status Network will first offer LINEA token yield farming</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25982</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Linea&apos;s official blog announced that Status Network, which combines native ETH rewards, stablecoin rewards, and native application fee commissions, will be the first to provide LINEA token staking. Users are able to deposit LINEA and SNT tokens to obtain increased LINEA token rewards.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 20, 2024, Status was collaborating with Linea, supported by Consensys, to launch a Layer 2 rollup solution. The two parties are jointly developing a Layer 2 network that will operate in parallel with Linea&apos;s zkEVM chain, named Status Network. Status contributors will interact with Linea&apos;s open-source code and actively participate in managing its codebase to maintain a parallel version.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25982</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Launches WLFI Perpetual Contract Pre-market Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25980</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to official information, Gate has now initiated the pre-market trading of WLFI perpetual contracts (settled in USDT), with support for leverage ranging from 1 to 10 times.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25980</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>