<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:57:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Testnet 2.1 Goes Live, Mainnet Launch Imminent</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24247</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Sonic Labs made an announcement that Sonic Testnet 2.1 has been officially launched. It is compatible with the Ethereum Pectra upgrade and has expanded Sonic&apos;s capabilities. The mainnet is set to arrive shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24247</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed&apos;s Signal Booster」: Rate Cut Threshold Shifts, but July CPI Still Insufficient to Prevent September Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24246</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Nick Timiraos, a Wall Street Journal reporter renowned as the &quot;Fed Whisperer&quot;, declared that the rate cut threshold had undergone a transformation following the release of today&apos;s CPI data. The rate cut plan for September might be impeded by today&apos;s CPI data, which was higher than expected. The CPI data from July did not suggest &quot;no inflation&quot;, yet it might not be sufficient to prevent a rate cut in September.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24246</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Urges Rate Cut Again, Threatens Major Lawsuit Against Powell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24245</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Trump once more posted on Truth Social and urged a rate cut, saying, &quot;Jerome, it&apos;s too late. Powell must immediately lower interest rates. He is always &apos;too late&apos;, resulting in immeasurable losses. Fortunately, the economic situation is excellent. We have completely gotten rid of Powell and the complacent Federal Reserve. However, I am considering allowing a major lawsuit against Powell because he has done a terrible job in managing the construction of the Fed. He is extremely incompetent. This project should have only needed a $50 million repair, but it ended up costing $3 billion. It&apos;s truly awful!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24245</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market-listed company Bit Origin has disclosed holding approximately 70.5 million DOGE coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24243</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Bit Origin, a US-listed company (stock code: BTOG), announced that by August 11th, it possessed 70,543,745 DOGE, and the average acquisition cost was $0.2268. Additionally, it had completed a rights offering of 20 million shares of Class A common stock to support the previously announced $500 million equity acquisition and convertible note financing.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24243</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Stock Market&apos;s Three Major Indexes Open Higher, &quot;Top Stablecoin Stock&quot; Circle Soars 17%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24244</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on the market data from RockFlow, the U.S. stock market opened with the three major indices showing an upward trend. The Dow increased by 0.4%, the S&amp;P 500 rose by 0.4%, and the Nasdaq went up by 0.5%. &quot;The First Stablecoin Stock&quot; Circle witnessed a surge of 17%, with its second-quarter revenue witnessing a 53% year-on-year increase. Crypto-related stocks witnessed an overall rise, including:The new ETH Treasury company ETHZilla (ATNF) surged by more than 70%, with Peter Thiel and his investment team having previously acquired a 7.5% stake;Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) rose by 3.3%, announcing today its plans to raise $20 billion in financing to increase its ETH holdings;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) rose by 3.76%;Coinbase (COIN) rose by 1.4%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) fell by 0.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24244</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address has once again accumulated 21,000 ETH, bringing its total accumulation to approximately 86,000 ETH since June 22nd.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24242</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as monitored by EmberCN, the address &quot;0x395...500&quot; continued to make a withdrawal of 21,000 ETH from Binance within the past half hour, with a value of $90.16 million.Since June 22nd when the price of ETH was $2,280, this address has been constantly withdrawing ETH from Binance. It has now accumulated as much as 86,001 ETH ($3.78 billion) at an average price of $3,023, and currently has an unrealized gain of $120 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24242</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) saw a pre-market turnaround from a decline to an increase, planning to raise $20 billion in funding to increase its ETH holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24241</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on the market data from RockFlow, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) reversed its pre-market decline and rose, currently showing an increase of 4.95%.Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) announced today its plan to raise the fundraising scale by 20 billion US dollars in order to increase its ETH holdings. The maximum total offering price specified in the prospectus of Bitmine Immersion can reach up to 20 billion US dollars. The maximum offering price specified in the first prospectus supplement can reach up to 25 billion US dollars. And the maximum offering price specified in the newly released second prospectus supplement can reach up to 200 billion US dollars, with a total of 245 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24241</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUI Postpones Robinhood Listing After Blog Post</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24240</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the SUI Network deleted a blog post this evening that announced the listing on Robinhood or prematurely released a draft document with a confidential date.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transak has completed a $16 million strategic fundraising round, with Tether and IDG Capital co-leading the investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24239</link>
      <description>August 12th. The Web3 payment infrastructure company Transak secured $16 million in a strategic financing round. IDG Capital and Tether took the lead in this round, with Primal Capital, 1kx, Protein Capital, and Fuel Ventures also participating. Transak intends to utilize this funding to expand its stablecoin payment stack and enter new markets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24239</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrade increased its long position in ETH to approximately $66.02 million, with an average entry price of $4,309.19.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24238</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), following the reaching of $4400 on the ETH price, the contract transaction whale AguilaTrades&apos;s Hyperliquid long position is now up by $1.38 million.This evening, AguilaTrades increased its long position to 15,000 ETH (approximately $66.02 million) with an average entry price of $4,309.19.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24238</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>