<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:30:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected WLFI Wallet Team Member Denies Proposal-Related Message Regarding &quot;Aave Receiving 7% of WLFI Total Supply&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25950</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, the alleged WLFI Wallet team member Dylan_0x (@0xDylan_) posted a message denying any association with the &quot;Aave to Receive 7% of WLFI Total Token Supply&quot; proposal. Probably due to this, AAVE dropped from a high of $385.99 to $365, experiencing a short-term decline of more than 5%.Crypto KOL @Luyaoyuan1 expressed his opinion on this event, saying, &quot;I used to think that Aave would maintain a long position in AAVE&apos;s trading with this 7% and 20% protocol revenue. But in the weeks prior to the WLFI announcement, I noticed the weakness of AAVE/ETH and Aave&apos;s lagging price increase. There are precedents where, if WLFI does not fork, they have no intention of giving AAVE the 7% coins. There is no surprise here; there are precedents. SPK defaulted on the 10% revenue share and only provided 1% in the end, and this issue remained unresolved. During the WLFI public sale, they said it would be fully unlocke</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25950</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale withdrew 26,200 ETH from Hyperliquid, setting the platform&apos;s record for the largest single ETH withdrawal.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25947</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to Mlm Monitor, a Bitcoin ancient whale has just transferred 4,000 BTC (amounting to 460 million US dollars) to a new wallet. Subsequently, it is likely that he will swap it for ETH on Hyperliquid or sell it to over-the-counter (OTC) institutions.In addition, he also withdrew 26,200 ETH (with a value of 125 million US dollars) from Hyperliquid, setting a new record for the largest single ETH withdrawal on the exchange platform up to now.Today, the whale has deposited 2,520 BTC into HyperLiquid, which is worth 291.75 million US dollars, and is ready to sell it in exchange for ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25947</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave will receive 7% of the total WLFI token supply and will also receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by WLFI Aave v3.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25948</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on a previously disclosed proposal, Aave, as a WLFI lending ecosystem partner, within this Aave v3 instance, WLFI will adopt the same reserve factor mechanism as the main Aave instance.The AaveDAO will receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by the WLFI Aave v3 instance and will obtain approximately 7% of the total WLFI token supply to participate in future WLFI governance processes, liquidity mining, and promote the decentralization of the WLFI platform.Revenue distribution will be implemented through a trustless smart contract, which will directly allocate the corresponding proportion of the protocol fees to the AaveDAO treasury address and the WLFI treasury address.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25948</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAVE Short-Term Breaks Above $385, Surges Over 14% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25949</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on HTX market data, AAVE briefly soared above $385 and has now pulled back to $370. It has witnessed an increase of over 14% within 24 hours, and its market capitalization is $5.733 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25949</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Traded Company Vault Ventures Increases Ethereum Holdings to 771 Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25946</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, Vault Ventures plc (AQSE: VULT), a UK-listed company, made an announcement. It stated that Ethereum has been added to the company&apos;s treasury reserve assets. Currently, the Ethereum holdings have increased to 771 ETH.Previously, as reported by BlockBeats on June 26th, Vault Ventures plc (AQSE: VULT) announced that after its recent financing plan, ￡750,000 was allocated to purchase Ethereum (ETH) and ￡150,000 was allocated to purchase Bitcoin (BTC).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25946</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHZilla has announced a plan to issue up to $10 billion in common stock to purchase more ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25945</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, the US stock Ethereum reserve company ETHZilla (formerly 180 Life Sciences) announced that, in accordance with the amended and restated sales agreement with Clear Street LLC, the company intends to periodically issue and sell common stock through Clear Street as a sales agent. The maximum total amount to be raised is up to $10 billion.As of this announcement, the company has issued and sold 5,001,310 shares of common stock under the initial sales agreement, raising a total of approximately $34.4 million. Starting from the date of this prospectus supplement, the company will no longer sell common stock in accordance with the market issuance prospectus submitted on August 13, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25945</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week, Bitdeer mined a total of 91.1 BTC, surpassing a total holding of 1800 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25944</link>
      <description>August 23rd. Bitdeer, a Bitcoin mining company, disclosed the latest Bitcoin holding data. By August 22nd, its total Bitcoin holdings had risen to 1,818.2 BTC (It should be noted that this quantity represents pure holdings and does not encompass Bitcoin deposited by customers). Furthermore, this week&apos;s Bitcoin mining output was 91.1 BTC, yet 37.0 BTC were sold.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has now launched WLFI pre-market trading and futures trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25943</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, as per the official announcement, Bitget has now initiated pre-market trading and futures trading, with a leverage range spanning from 1 to 25 times.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25943</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Macro Outlook: July Core PCE on the Horizon, &quot;Don&apos;t Get Too Excited About Rate Cuts&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25942</link>
      <description>August 23rd. For the majority of this month, Wall Street traders thronged to the stock and bond markets, wagering that the Fed was ultimately prepared to cut rates once again. The sole thing they were awaiting was the green light from Fed Chair Powell to sustain this rally. Their wish was fulfilled on Friday as Powell adopted a dovish stance in a highly anticipated speech, giving rise to the largest cross-market rally since April.On Friday, Powell hinted at the Fed&apos;s readiness to modify its policy direction, which brought to mind the situation at the Jackson Hole conference a year ago. In his Jackson Hole speech, Powell opened the door to a rate cut in September, clearly indicating that the Fed will reduce rates by 25 basis points at the September meeting.On Tuesday at 03:15, 2026 FOMC Voter and Dallas Fed President Logan participated in a panel discussion at the 100th Anniversary of the Bank of Mexico;On Tuesday at 07:15, FOMC Permanent Voter and NY Fed President Williams deliver</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25942</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Falls Below $115,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25941</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $115,000, and its 24-hour growth rate narrowed to 2.40%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25941</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>