<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 21:18:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Signs Executive Order, Officially Enacting US-Japan Trade Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27775</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the White House of the United States announced that President Trump signed an executive order to officially commence the implementation of the U.S.-Japan trade agreement.Based on the U.S.-Japan trade agreement, the United States will impose a 15% basic tariff on nearly all Japanese imports. At the same time, separate industry-specific treatments will be provided for automobiles and auto parts, aerospace products, generic drugs, and natural resources that the United States is unable to naturally obtain or produce domestically.The Japanese government will make efforts to expedite the implementation of the rice &quot;minimum access&quot; scheme, increasing the purchase of U.S. rice by 75% and purchasing U.S. agricultural products such as corn, soybeans, fertilizers, bioethanol (including bioethanol for sustainable aviation fuel), and other U.S. products, with a total annual amount of up to $8 billion.The Japanese government also aims to enable the sale of U.S.-made passenger</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27775</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed Megaphone」: Federal Reserve Board nominee Milan&apos;s Consideration of Term Appointment While Retaining White House Role Seen as Unusual Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27774</link>
      <description>On September 5th, in an article by the &quot;Fed Whisperer&quot; Nick Timiraos, it was reported that Tomas Philipson, the governor of the Riksbank and a nominee for the U.S. Federal Reserve Board, indicated that after fulfilling a short-term role at the Fed, he plans to return to his original position at the White House next year. This arrangement has no precedent since Congress tried to separate the executive branch from the Fed decades ago.During Thursday&apos;s Senate confirmation hearing, Philipson stated that his legal team advised him that he could take unpaid leave from his current position as the Chair of the White House Council of Economic Advisers, enabling him to return next year without the need for a new round of Senate confirmation. Philipson was nominated to fill the term left by Kudlow, who unexpectedly resigned last month, and the term will last until January 31, 2026.Democratic lawmakers questioned whether this arrangement might affect his ability to maintain independent judgmen</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27774</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Administration Submits New Evidence, Seeks Court Support to Impeach Federal Reserve Board Member Powell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27773</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the U.S. Department of Justice presented new evidence to support the claim that President Trump should be allowed to remove Federal Reserve Board member Lisa Cook. It was stated that her assertion of a &quot;rate cut excuse&quot; is baseless. Cook has been accused of mortgage fraud and is currently contesting the decision to dismiss her. On Thursday, U.S. government lawyers once more urged the judge to reject Cook&apos;s request to prevent her dismissal during the lawsuit, reinforcing the arguments put forward during last week&apos;s hearing.A few hours before this filing, reports indicated that the Department of Justice had launched a criminal investigation into Cook. The U.S. government argues that the fraud charges initially raised by FHFA Director Puert now serve as a sufficient &quot;reason&quot; under U.S. law for Trump to fire her.In Thursday&apos;s filing, the Department of Justice emphasized that the judge must not &quot;question&quot; Trump&apos;s judgment regarding having a valid reason for dismissal.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27773</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Board Nominee Miller: Did Not Consult White House on Long-Term Tenure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27772</link>
      <description>September 5th. Stephen Moore, a nominee for the Federal Reserve Board by US President Trump, stated on Thursday that he had not engaged in any discussions with anyone at the White House regarding the possibility of being nominated for a long-term position. He had previously informed senators that only a nomination for a long-term position would lead him to resign from his current position as a White House economic advisor, rather than simply taking a leave of absence.When questioned by reporters on this matter, Moore initially raised his eyebrows and refused to respond. When asked again, &quot;Really none at all?&quot; he briefly replied, &quot;None.&quot; During Moore&apos;s nomination hearing, Democratic senators expressed concerns that his failure to resign from the Economic Advisory Committee would cause him to yield to pressure from President Trump during interest rate votes. Moore denied these concerns. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27772</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun&apos;s Response to Being Blacklisted: The address in question was only used for small-scale testing and was not involved in any buying or selling.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27771</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Justin Sun responded on social media regarding the incident of &quot;World Liberty blacklisting Justin Sun&apos;s address and freezing 5.4 billion unlocked tokens and 24 billion locked tokens&quot;. He stated, &quot;Our address only carried out a few general exchange deposit tests with very low amounts, and then conducted an address dispersion. There was no buying or selling involved, and it could not have any impact on the market.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI briefly surged by nearly 10% before pulling back, with a current market cap of $4.418 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27770</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on HTX market data. Possibly due to the &quot;WLFI Blacklists Justin Sun&apos;s Address&quot; news, WLFI witnessed a short-term surge of nearly 10% and then retraced. Currently, its market cap is $4.418 billion.World Liberty has placed Justin Sun&apos;s address on a blacklist, seizing 540 million unlocked tokens and 2.4 billion staked tokens. They declared that they believe a certain exchange has been continuously selling user tokens in an attempt to suppress the price.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27770</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Blacklists Justin Sun Address</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27769</link>
      <description>September 5th. Based on on-chain data, World Liberty has placed Justin Sun&apos;s address on a blacklist, immobilizing 540 million unlocked tokens and 2.4 billion staked tokens. They claimed that they think a certain exchange has been continuously selling user tokens in an attempt to suppress the price.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27769</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s &quot;Big Three&quot; Official Williams: Timely Rate Cut Is Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27768</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the President of the New York Fed, Williams, stated that he anticipates that a rate cut will become &quot;appropriate in due course.&quot; However, he did not specify the timing or pace of such an action. Williams said on Thursday in remarks prepared for the New York Economic Club event: &quot;Looking forward, if our dual-mandate goals continue to be achieved in accordance with my baseline outlook, I expect that over time, a shift to a more neutral policy stance will be appropriate.&quot; Williams pointed out that the Fed is facing a &quot;subtle balance&quot; in terms of risks to employment and inflation.He said: &quot;On one hand, we need to maintain a balanced labor market to ensure that the impact of tariffs does not spread to a more persistent and widespread inflation. On the other hand, adopting a stance of &apos;being overly tight for too long&apos; could pose a risk to our maximum employment mission.&quot; He also stated that so far, the impact of tariffs on inflation has not been as severe as initially expe</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Previously Minted 2 Billion USDT Moved Chain Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27767</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Paolo Ardoino, the CEO of Tether, responded to a &quot;Whale Alert&quot; tweet from 1 hour ago which claimed that Tether had minted 2 billion USDT on the Ethereum blockchain. He stated, &quot;Binance has transferred 2 billion USDT from the Tron chain to the Ethereum chain as a replacement.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27767</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump family-backed crypto projects WLFI and ABTC both dropped over 20% today.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27766</link>
      <description>September 5th: The cryptocurrency projects World Liberty Financial (WLFI) and American Bitcoin (ABTC), which are endorsed by Donald Trump, both witnessed a more than 20% decline today. WLFI dropped by 24% and ABTC by 21%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>