<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Benet: The implementation of the GENIUS Act is crucial to ensuring the United States&apos; leadership in the digital asset space.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25179</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the U.S. Treasury Department issued a Notice of Proposed Rulemaking in line with the requirements of the GENIUS Act today.In response, U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson declared that the implementation of the GENIUS Act is of great significance in ensuring America&apos;s leadership in the digital asset field. Stablecoins will widen the usage channels of the U.S. dollar to billions of people worldwide and lead to a substantial increase in the demand for U.S. bonds that support stablecoins. &quot;For all parties involved, this is a situation that is beneficial to all - stablecoin users, stablecoin issuers, and the U.S. Treasury Department.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25179</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investment Bank Outlook for Jackson Hole Conference Shows Significant Rate Cut Expectation Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25178</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is scheduled to deliver a speech on the economic outlook and the assessment of the Fed&apos;s policy framework at the annual central bank symposium of the Kansas City Fed in Jackson Hole, Wyoming at 10 am Eastern Time (10 pm Beijing Time) on August 22nd. Major investment banks hold the following expectations for Powell&apos;s speech:UBS: It is anticipated that Powell may lay the groundwork for a rate cut commencing in September and persisting through the end of the year.UBS: Considering last week&apos;s data, Powell may be inclined to hint at the Fed&apos;s propensity to cut rates during the September meeting.Russell Investments: The Jackson Hole meeting may temper expectations for a Fed rate cut. A September rate cut is &quot;possible&quot; rather than &quot;certain&quot;, with a 25-basis-point cut rather than a 50-basis-point cut.ING: Recently, three Fed officials (Daly, Cook, and Kashkari) expressed concerns about the deterioration of the labor market, which seems to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25178</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish cryptocurrency exchange company Safello will launch a physically-backed TAO ETP.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25177</link>
      <description>August 19th. According to Marketscreener, the Swedish crypto exchange company Safello declared that it is going to launch the first physically-backed TAO exchange-traded product (ETP) in the European market. This ETP is scheduled to be listed on the SIX Swiss Exchange, the Paris and Amsterdam pan-European exchanges, as well as the Xetra exchange in Germany, thus enabling institutional and retail investors to gain exposure to the Bittensor native token TAO.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25177</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Exchange LBank May Launch Plan to Go Public in the US</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25176</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to the crypto KOL @_FORAB, a certain exchange (as shown in the attached image, which might be LBank) is going to launch a plan to list in the United States. The platform &quot;issued 250 shares of common stock to invited employees and asked them to register with their passports and identification. However, due to regulatory reasons, employees with mainland Chinese passports are unable to participate in the common stock incentive.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese 3D Printing Construction Company Lib Work has announced its intention to adopt a Bitcoin reserve, planning to purchase $3.3 million worth of BTC as an inflation hedge.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25174</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as reported by Cointelegraph, the Japanese 3D printing construction company Lib Work announced that it will incorporate Bitcoin into its corporate reserves and intends to purchase $3.3 million worth of BTC as a tool for hedging against inflation. The company focuses on the research and application of 3D printing construction technology.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25174</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: In September, the Ethereum ETF&apos;s share of total holdings will exceed that of the Bitcoin ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25175</link>
      <description>On August 19th, based on the calculation by Dragonfly data analyst hildobby, the current Bitcoin ETF holding accounts for 6.38% of the total BTC supply. Meanwhile, the Ethereum ETF holding accounts for 5.08% of the total ETH supply. If this rate is sustained, by September, the percentage of the Ethereum ETF&apos;s total ETH supply held will surpass that of the Bitcoin ETF.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25175</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean Regulators Require Domestic CEXs to Halt Lending Services Starting Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25173</link>
      <description>August 19th: As per The Block, the Financial Services Commission (FSC) of South Korea has given an order to local cryptocurrency exchanges to halt their lending services starting from August 19, 2025. The Financial Supervisory Service mentioned that the suspension will continue to be in force until the official guidelines regarding cryptocurrency lending are formulated.The regulatory body pointed out that lending services have legal uncertainties and risks of user losses. It was emphasized that around 27,600 investors borrowed 15 trillion Korean won (10 billion USD) in the first month after a digital asset company initiated its lending service. The Financial Supervisory Service stated that 13% of these borrowers were compelled to liquidate their positions due to price fluctuations.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25173</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaneck Market Outlook: Maintains Bitcoin End-of-Year Target Price of $180,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25172</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Vaneck put out a post summarizing the key market points from mid-July to mid-August as follows:1. Bitcoin (BTC) achieved a historical high rebound to $124,000, and the CME benchmark reached a yearly high; maintaining a year-end Bitcoin target of $180,000.2. Bitcoin miner differentiation: APLD increased; although U.S. miners account for 31.5% of the global hashrate, most miners have underperformed.3. The Digital Assets Treasury Company (DATS) mNAV decreased: Low volatility suppressed financing and growth.In addition, Vaneck stated that as autumn is approaching, a large amount of open options positions has increased. Even a slight amount of volatility may trigger significant price fluctuations through trader hedging. For DAT, prolonged low volatility may limit financing capacity, further compressing mNAV. Macro-economic developments and the re-engagement of seasonal investors may sustain Bitcoin&apos;s momentum and may also potentially trigger profit-taking. Nevertheless,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25172</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&apos;s Ningbo Busts &quot;Express Delivery Maotai&quot; Fraud Case, Illicit Funds Transferred in Cryptocurrency Form</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25171</link>
      <description>August 19th. According to Legal Daily, a virtual currency remote ordering &quot;Flash Delivery Moutai&quot; fraud case was detected in Ningbo City, Zhejiang Province, China. The defendant targeted a tobacco and liquor store and committed fraud. He used fake receipts to deceive and steal real Moutai and transferred the proceeds through virtual currency to the upstream accomplice.After the prosecution by the Yinzhou District People&apos;s Procuratorate of Ningbo City, the defendant Zhou was sentenced to one year and six months in prison for the crime of concealing and concealing the proceeds of crime and was fined. Currently, the public security organs are further investigating the upstream fraudsters.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25171</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pumped by Upbit Listing News, API3 Surges Over 70% Short-Term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25170</link>
      <description>On August 19th, based on HTX market data, driven by the news of being listed on Upbit, API3 witnessed a short-term surge of more than 70% and is currently priced at $1.5048.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25170</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>