<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:31:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Willy Woo: Bitcoin Network Sees First Inflow of Funds in Weeks, Signaling Structural Support Buildup</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26980</link>
      <description>On August 30th, Crypto analyst Willy Woo put out a post indicating that following several weeks of declining inflows, the Bitcoin network witnessed its first day of inflow growth, which signaled the first indication of Bitcoin&apos;s structural bottoming. Bitcoin is currently in a state of stabilization. For a bullish structure to form, investors need to continuously buy the dips. This process has already commenced.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26980</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue reduced to around 1.024M ETH, while Entry Queue increased to around 0.808M ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26979</link>
      <description>August 30th. According to the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, it is reported that the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is 1,024,545 ETH. Based on the current price, approximately $4.45 billion worth of ETH is leaving the PoS network, and the withdrawal delay is currently 17 days and 19 hours.At the same time, there has been a growth in staking demand from new validators. The staking queue for today has increased to 808,910 ETH, with a value of around $3.51 billion. The current queuing time for admission is 14 days and 1 hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26979</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Wong: Hong Kong is actively building an international hub for digital assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26978</link>
      <description>August 30th. A member of the Hong Kong Legislative Council, Wu Jiezhuang, posted on social media, stating that Hong Kong is actively establishing an international digital asset center. He emphasized that enterprises should focus on both innovation and compliance. He also believed that the integration of the capital market and the digital asset industry would bring new impetus to the market. DePIN, which combines blockchain with the real economy, is expected to transform traditional industries such as the Internet of Things, energy, and transportation, and is an important direction for the implementation of Web3.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26978</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Official: Trump in Good Health, About to Go Play Golf</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26977</link>
      <description>On August 30th, Barak Ravid, a reporter from Axios Global Affairs, wrote that a U.S. official stated that President Trump is in a good physical state and will go play golf this morning in the local time. At the moment when this news was released, widespread speculation about Trump&apos;s health was still circulating on social media.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26977</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White Whale Trader&apos;s long position is currently down over $13 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26976</link>
      <description>August 30th. Based on on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the positions of trader The White Whale in five addresses currently have a total unrealized loss of more than 13.37 million USD. One of the addresses is experiencing a loss of 13.31 million USD from long positions in BTC and ETH. Nevertheless, the collateral in this address is as high as 52.25 million USD, and the current collateral utilization rate is only 10%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 12:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Quack AI (Q) and open airdrop claims to eligible users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26975</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per official channels, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list Quack AI (Q) on September 2nd.Alpha Trading Opening Time: 15:00 (UTC+8) on September 2, 2025.Contract Trading Opening Time: 15:30 (UTC+8) on September 2, 2025.Qualified users will be able to participate in the Alpha event and receive an airdrop by using Binance Alpha points once the Alpha trading commences. Specific details will be disclosed separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 12:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26975</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week, the United States Ethereum Spot ETF recorded a total net inflow of $10.829 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26974</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per the monitoring data from Farside, this week the US Ethereum spot ETF witnessed a cumulative net inflow of $10.829 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 12:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26974</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The high-profile ETH whale has once again transferred 2120 BTC to HyperUnit for swapping ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26973</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the highly visible BTC whale that swapped a significant amount of ETH has once again deposited 2120 BTC (valued at $230 million) into HyperUnit for the exchange of ETH, and 1120 BTC is currently still unsold.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26973</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperscale Data is planning to sell common stock to raise $125 million to purchase BTC and XRP</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26972</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per PR Newswire, the U.S. listed company Hyperscale Data (NYSE: GPUS) declared that it had set up a &quot;market issuance&quot; equity issuance plan. The company may from time to time sell its common stock in order to raise a total of up to 125 million U.S. dollars. A portion of the proceeds from this fundraising will be utilized to purchase Bitcoin and expand its Michigan data facility. Another part will be used to purchase XRP. The rest will be allocated for working capital and general corporate purposes, which may include repaying, refinancing, redeeming, or repurchasing future debt or equity.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26972</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI: Protocol governance power will be fully controlled by a multisig during security risks or major adverse events</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26971</link>
      <description>August 30th. As per the official website, World Liberty Financial (referred to as the WLF Protocol) declared in a governance statement that the WLF Protocol or any associated protocols might encounter &quot;significant adverse events,&quot; meaning any event that obstructs the intended and prolonged normal operation of the WLF Protocol or any related protocols. Or it might encounter &quot;security risks,&quot; referring to any event that leads to the cessation of the WLF Protocol&apos;s operation or endangers the security of users utilizing the WLF Protocol.During a period of significant adverse events or security risks, the governance control of the WLF Protocol will be solely in the hands of a multi-signature until the normal governance operations of the WLF Protocol can be restored.Previously reported, the unlocking of the WLFI token is scheduled to officially start at 8:00 AM EST on September 1st, and the relevant functionality page is now available.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26971</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>