<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:24:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Everything Blockchain to Launch Diversified Cryptocurrency Treasury</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25195</link>
      <description>August 19th, In the off-exchange trading market, the listed company Everything Blockchain announced that it will launch a diversified cryptocurrency treasury. This treasury will consist of three types of cryptocurrency assets. One type is blue-chip cryptocurrencies that provide long-term stability support (such as BTC, ETH, SOL, XRP, etc.). Another type is tokens related to blockchain infrastructure. The third type is speculative assets (like Meme coins, AI-related tokens, and game / metaverse project tokens).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25195</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Accumulates 2318 ETH Again After Six Months, Worth $9.94 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25194</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, within the past 20 hours, a whale withdrew 2318 ETH from Wintermute and Kraken after a period of 6 months. The value of this withdrawal is $9.94 million.The whale currently holds 5191 ETH, with a value of $22.31 million. It has achieved current profits of $4.45 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25194</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Jr: Crypto Will Be the Future of Finance, It Will Be a Trillion-Dollar Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25193</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Donald Trump Jr., the son of former President Donald Trump, said in an interview with Bloomberg that their participation in the cryptocurrency field was not because of a deep understanding of crypto but out of necessity. (The Trump family) was being &quot;debanked&quot; by the traditional financial system. &quot;A few years ago, in this city, with just one phone call, almost no one would refuse to lend to my real estate project. But after we were labeled as &apos;political,&apos; overnight we became &apos;unwelcome individuals&apos;.&quot;&quot;Consequently, cryptocurrency represents the future of finance; we must make laws to establish the necessary &apos;guardrails&apos; for this industry to remain here. This will be a trillion-dollar industry that should be based in the United States. The US should benefit from the tax revenue, innovation, and growth it brings and should also have that strategic vision.&quot;&quot;So, I am extremely excited about that bill because it will ensure that the United States becomes the home of futur</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25193</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch AriaAI (ARIA) on August 21.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25192</link>
      <description>August 19th. According to official information, Binance Alpha is set to list AriaAI (ARIA) on August 21st. Once trading commences, eligible users will be able to utilize Alpha Points to claim the airdrop on the Alpha Activity Page. Further details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Update: Tether Appoints Former White House Crypto Council Executive Director Bo Hines as Chief of Digital Assets and US Strategic Advisor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25191</link>
      <description>August 19: According to market intelligence, the issuer of USDT, Tether, has appointed Bo Hines, who was previously the Executive Director of the White House Crypto Council, as the Digital Assets and US Strategy Advisor.August 10: Bo Hines, the Executive Director of the White House Crypto Council, resigned and returned to the private sector.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25191</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernstein: Crypto Bull Market Could Last Until 2027, Bitcoin&apos;s Price Could Reach $200,000 in the Next Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25190</link>
      <description>On August 19th, a recent report from Bernstein analysts indicated that although the recent price has cooled down, the current cryptocurrency bull market may persist until 2027, which is driven by U.S. policy support and the increasing institutional adoption.The analysts anticipate that Bitcoin will rise to $150,000 to $200,000 within the next year. At the same time, they have also raised the price targets for Coinbase, Robinhood, and Circle. (The Block)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25190</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renowned analyst claims that during this bull run, Bitcoin will not drop below $100,000, having accurately predicted Bitcoin&apos;s new all-time high in 2024.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25189</link>
      <description>August 19th: The renowned analyst BitQuant, who had previously made a successful prediction of Bitcoin&apos;s all-time high in 2024, holds the view that during the remaining period of this bull market, the price of Bitcoin will not fall below $100,000.At the same time, his latest prediction indicates that the BTC price still has the potential to reach $145,000 within the year. In his forecast from December of last year, he had projected that the price in this bull market could reach $250,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25189</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit has announced support for an airdrop of SpaceCoin to Creditcoin holders</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25188</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per an official announcement, Upbit has declared that it will provide support for an airdrop of SpaceCoin (SPACE) tokens to Creditcoin (CTC) holders.The first snapshot will occur on: August 22nd, 2025, at 09:00 to 10:00 local time (Ethereum block height 23,193,117).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25188</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Trump Propels Late-August &quot;Puzi Summit&quot; Tripartite Talks, Geopolitical News Pressure, Bitcoin Support Seen at $112,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25187</link>
      <description>On August 19th, during a meeting at the White House, US President Trump stated that he had reached a preliminary agreement with European leaders on the security guarantee for Ukraine. Subsequently, he had a phone call with Russian President Putin after the meeting. Trump disclosed that he is actively making arrangements for a direct meeting between Putin and Ukrainian President Zelensky, which is scheduled to take place before the end of August. After this meeting, a trilateral talk involving himself will be promoted. US Vice President Pence, Secretary of State Pompeo, and Special Envoy Volker are currently working closely with both Russia and Ukraine.BiyaPay analysts believe that this round of diplomatic actions has sent a strong signal of relaxation, which may have an impact on the global capital market&apos;s risk appetite and thereby affect the price trend of Bitcoin. After the news was released, the price of Bitcoin briefly dropped to $114,400 but quickly rebounded above $115,000. Ho</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25187</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Mitosis (MITO) Booster Event Season 1 BNB Pool TVL Reaches $77.71M</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25186</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to the information on the relevant page, the first season of the Binance Mitosis (MITO) Booster event has a TVL of $77.71 million in the BNB pool and $111 million in the USDT pool.Before this news, Binance launched the first season of the Mitosis (MITO) Booster event, which went live at 8:00 today. As of the time of this writing, the current APY in the BNB pool is reported to be 40.24%, and the APY in the USDT pool is reported to be 21.14%. This event enables users to deposit BNB or USDT into the Simple Yield Mitosis Treasury through the Binance Wallet to receive MITO rewards. The total reward is 15 million MITO, and the event does not set an Alpha point threshold. Users can redeem assets through the Mitosis DApp. It is important to note that the BNB redemption process may take up to 10 days, and the USDT redemption process may take up to 5 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25186</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>