<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:40:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Powell Lawyer Says Mortgage Dispute May Be Due to &apos;Typographical Error&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26762</link>
      <description>August 29th. The attorney representing Federal Reserve Board Governor Lael Brainard contended that the mortgage dispute which led to Trump&apos;s request to fire her might have originated from an &quot;unintentional paperwork mistake.&quot; The aim was to undermine Trump and FHFA Director Mark Calabria&apos;s fraud allegations. The legal team stated that even if there was an error, it was not done with intentional deception and no one was harmed, in line with the legal &quot;substantive&quot; standard.&quot;The possibility exists that Brainard, long before joining the Board, might have mistakenly marked the home&apos;s use in the mortgage application. However, there was neither intent nor a substantive impact. This does not meet the &apos;just cause&apos; necessary for removal.&quot; The attorney wrote in a filing for a temporary restraining order. The legal team also pointed out that Trump and Calabria did not even explicitly claim that Brainard reaped any benefits from the error or that the error was intentional. (Golden Finance)Earl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise: Bitcoin Expected to Reach $1.3 Million by 2035</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26760</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per Cointelegraph, the cryptocurrency asset management firm Bitwise has presented the latest Bitcoin price prediction. It is estimated that the price of Bitcoin will ascend to $1.3 million by 2035, primarily driven by institutional demand and Bitcoin&apos;s limited supply. This report was released as a part of Bitwise&apos;s &quot;Bitcoin Long-Term Capital Market Assumptions,&quot; forecasting that Bitcoin will attain a 28.3% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) over the next decade, which significantly outpaces traditional assets like stocks (6.2%), bonds (4.0%), and gold (3.8%).In the base case scenario, Bitwise anticipates that Bitcoin will reach $1.3 million by 2035. In the bullish scenario, Bitcoin might soar to $2.97 million (CAGR 39.4%). And in the bearish scenario, it could plummet to $88,005 (CAGR 2%).This price range showcases the notable volatility in the Bitcoin market despite the growing participation of institutions. Bitcoin is no longer a market dominated solely by reta</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI Launches Efficient Inference Model Grok Code Fast 1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26761</link>
      <description>August 29th, xAI made an announcement about the launch of the efficient inference model Grok Code Fast 1, which showcased remarkable performance in AI-assisted programming.During the next 7 days, Grok Code Fast 1 will be freely accessible on mainstream AI programming platforms such as Cursor, GitHub Copilot, Cline, opencode, Windsurf, Roo Code, and Kilo Code. (Gold10)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26761</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Delays Decision on Grayscale Ethereum Trust Spot ETF&apos;s Proposal to Add Staking Feature</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26759</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on market information, the US SEC has postponed a decision regarding the authorization of GrayScale&apos;s Ethereum Trust (ETHE) to incorporate staking functionality.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Solana IDO Platforms by 24h Market Share: pump.fun, Letsbonk, Believe</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26758</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours, in the Solana issuance platform market share ranking, pump.fun holds the top position with 83.4%, Letsbonk comes in second with 6.99%, and Believe takes the third place with 2.43%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC has issued guidance on the Foreign Trading Platform Registration Framework, providing regulatory clarity for non-U.S. trading platforms seeking access to the U.S. market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26757</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the Market Oversight Department of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) issued guidance on a Foreign-Based Trading Platform (FBOT) registration framework today. This framework is applicable to non-U.S. entities that are legally formed and operate outside the United States and wish to provide direct trading platform access to individuals located in the United States. The CFTC&apos;s FBOT registration framework is applicable to all markets, regardless of asset class, including traditional and digital asset markets.Acting Chairman Caroline D. Pham stated: &quot;The release of today&apos;s FBOT guidance provides regulatory clarity for those who, due to the &apos;enforcement-based regulation&apos; of the past few years, have left U.S. trading activities and are now seeking a legal return to the United States. By reaffirming the CFTC&apos;s longstanding practices of providing U.S. traders with diverse options to access the world&apos;s deepest and most liquid markets, as well as a wide range</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26757</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC will issue guidance clarifying the rules for foreign trading platform registration.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26756</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Crypto journalist Eleanor Terrett disclosed that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is scheduled to issue guidance to clarify its Foreign Board of Trade (FBOT) registration rules. This provides a legal avenue for non-U.S. exchanges to enable U.S. users to trade on their platforms. Acting Chairman Caroline D. Pham stated that this is a means to bring crypto activities &quot;back to the U.S.&quot; as such activities had previously flowed out due to enforcement actions during the Biden administration. At the same time, it reaffirms the regulatory framework that has been in place since the 1990s. For U.S. traders, this implies that they can legally access more global liquidity. For the crypto industry, this is another step towards regulatory clarity and is also part of the Trump administration&apos;s &quot;crypto sprint&quot; strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26756</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB surges over 1.5% in a short period, as Eleanor Terrett previously mentioned that the US CFTC will issue guidance to clarify rules for foreign trading platform registration.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26755</link>
      <description>On August 29th, BNB experienced a brief surge of more than 1.5% and is currently trading at $875.Earlier, the crypto journalist Eleanor Terrett posted that the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is going to issue guidance to clarify its Foreign Board of Trade (FBOT) registration rules, thus providing a legal way for non-U.S. exchanges to enable U.S. users to trade on their platforms.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26755</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Pre-market Price Surges Over 19% in 24 Hours, Currently Trading at $0.317</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26754</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on HTX market data, the pre-market price of WLFI (World Liberty Financial) witnessed a surge of more than 19% within the past 24 hours. It is currently trading at $0.317.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26754</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberKongz: 2% of the total supply of KONG is airdropped to addresses that have purchased Ethereum-based NFTs on OpenSea since 2023, with a total amount of $10,000 or more.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26753</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to official channels, the Ethereum NFT and gaming project CyberKongz announced that 2% of the total supply of KONG will be airdropped to OpenSea users who have been active since 2023 (during the bear market). Addresses that have purchased a total of 10,000 US dollars worth of Ethereum NFTs on OpenSea since January 1, 2023, are eligible to participate in the airdrop. More details will be disclosed shortly.Previously reported, on August 20th, CyberKongz announced the launch of a new token, KONG, serving as the liquidity layer of its ecosystem and completely replacing the original token BANANA. The token will only be issued on the Ethereum mainnet, with a total supply of 1 billion tokens. BANANA can be converted to KONG at a ratio of 1:25 (opening at TGE). The airdrop plan is to airdrop 2% of the total token supply to the Ethereum NFT community, with specific details to be announced.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26753</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>