<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Listed Company on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange Establishes Joint Venture for International Business Settlement, Engaging in Crypto Asset-Related Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23738</link>
      <description>August 8th, International Business Settlement (00147.HK) declared that on August 8, 2025, the company&apos;s wholly-owned subsidiary, Chengtai, and Mr. Chen Sanming signed a joint venture agreement to set up a joint venture. After going through the registration process, the joint venture will be held by Chengtai and Mr. Chen Sanming with 70% and 30% equity respectively. The joint venture will mainly be involved in cryptocurrency-related business. (Sohu Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23738</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Quad-Stacking ETH with 75% Win Rate Whale」 is currently holding positions with an unrealized loss of $6.26 million, resulting in a total loss of over $10.46 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23735</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on on-chain information, the &quot;Four-Battles ETH 75% Win Rate Whale&quot; added $5.53 million in collateral this morning. Its 15x short position in Ethereum is currently facing an unrealized loss of $6.26 million, with a total historical loss of more than $10.46 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23735</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solayer: To Distribute 50,000 WCT Tokens to Active Ecological Users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23737</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to official information, Solayer is going to hold a joint event with WCT to give rewards to active users in the ecosystem. The top 100 consumers of Jade Card and the top 100 holders of sUSD, sSOL, and LAYER will obtain a distribution of 50,000 WCT tokens. The eligibility will be determined based on a snapshot taken on August 18th.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23737</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rating Agency S&amp;P: DeFi Protocol Sky Credit Rating on Par with Congo Debt, at a Lowly B-</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23736</link>
      <description>August 8: The rating agency S&amp;P Global carried out its initial credit rating on the DeFi protocol Sky (formerly known as MakerDAO). It assigned a B- rating to Sky, which is on a par with the sovereign debt rating of the Republic of the Congo and is classified as a high-risk &quot;speculative grade.&quot; S&amp;P pointed out that the current risks of Sky mainly include high depositor concentration, excessive reliance on the founder Rune Christensen, and the uncertainty of DeFi regulation. However, it also recognized that Sky has had low credit losses and stable revenue since 2020.This rating does not cover the governance token SKY and only pertains to USDS, DAI, and their savings derivatives. Sky is the fourth-largest stablecoin issuer on Ethereum, with a circulating supply of $7.9 billion.Sky responded that this rating is the first step towards integrating with the traditional financial system. In the future, as DeFi awareness grows, the ratings may be upgraded. Analysts believe that although th</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian July Employment Data Below Expectations, Increased Likelihood of September Interest Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23734</link>
      <description>August 8th. In Canada, the employment change in July was -40.8K people. The expected value was 13.5K people, and the previous value was 83.1K people. After the data was released, the probability of a rate cut by the Bank of Canada in September indicated by the Canadian futures market rose to 38% from 33% before the employment data was announced.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23734</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP Futures Trading Volume Surges 208% in 24 Hours, Open Interest Up 15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23733</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to glassnode, the trading volume of XRP futures witnessed a significant surge. The 24-hour trading volume increased by 208% and reached $12.4 billion, surpassing SOL&apos;s $9.6 billion. The open interest rose to $5.9 billion (+15%).glassnode&apos;s analysis stated that the current positive funding rate in the market indicates a large number of long positions. This could potentially increase the liquidation risk in case of a price decline.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23733</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperion Launches $100k &quot;Proof of Trade&quot; Airdrop Event, Pioneering Post-TGE Reward Mechanism Based on Trade P&amp;L</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23732</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Aptos&apos; largest decentralized exchange platform, Hyperion, officially launched a brand new airdrop event named &quot;RION The Trading King.&quot; Users who sold RION between July 17th and August 16th and shared their profit and loss (PnL) screenshots on Twitter are eligible to unlock a $100,000 USD airdrop with no threshold. The rewards will be distributed on August 16th.This event began at 8:00 PM (Beijing time) on August 8th and will last until August 16th. All airdrop rewards will be distributed uniformly after the event concludes. As the first interactive airdrop gameplay introduced after the TGE, &quot;RION The Trading King&quot; not only shows gratitude to early supporters but also attracts more new users to participate in trading and promotion through a gamified approach. It is reported that Hyperion has been performing strongly since the TGE, with high community engagement and trading activity. The introduction of this new airdrop gameplay is expected to further enhance user engage</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23732</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LM Funding: In July, Bitcoin Production Increased by 7% Month-over-Month, Holding a Total of 150.4 Bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23730</link>
      <description>August 8th. The Nasdaq-listed company LM Funding America (LMFA) presented its July 2025 operational data. During the reporting period, the company&apos;s monthly Bitcoin net production reached 5.9 coins, which was a 7% increase compared to the previous month. The energy revenue witnessed a 20% growth compared to the previous month.As of July 31st, the company held 150.4 bitcoins, and the total value of these bitcoins was approximately $17.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23730</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink: Conference Call Scheduled for August 15 to Discuss Recent Company Performance and Release Financial Report</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23731</link>
      <description>On August 8th, SharpLink announced that a conference call and webcast will be held on Friday, August 15th, 2025, at 8:30 AM Eastern Time. The purpose is to discuss the company&apos;s financial and operating performance for the three and six months ending June 30th, 2025. The executive team of SharpLink will host this event and will release a press release with the financial results prior to the conference call.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23731</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumulative Profits of Nearly $54 Million: Whale Smart Money Increased Bitcoin Long Position by Over 40x in Less Than Half an Hour, and Shorted SOL and XRP by 20x Each</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23729</link>
      <description>August 8th. Based on on-chain data, a whale has recently increased their Bitcoin long position by more than 40 times within less than half an hour, raising their holdings by 158.32 BTC. The current value of their holdings is $30.46 million, and the average entry price is $117,170. Meanwhile, the whale opened a 20-times short position on SOL and XRP, with holdings amounting to $13.66 million and $1.19 million respectively.This address still holds a 10-times long position on BNB at present. The whale has achieved a nearly $54 million profit on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23729</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>