<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:27:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>4 Whale Addresses withdrew a total of approximately 123,000 SOL from CEXs within a day</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22149</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, 4 whale addresses collectively withdrew approximately 123,269 SOL from CEX within a day. These include:· The address 7VbjYZ withdrew 58,700 SOL from Binance 16 hours ago (with a value of $11 million).· The address BnwZvG withdrew 38,000 SOL from Binance in the past 5 hours (with a value of $7.3 million).· The address 2AbHLS withdrew 14,569 SOL from Binance 2 hours ago (with a value of $2.8 million).· The address KMhcqN withdrew 12,000 SOL from Kraken 14 hours ago (with a value of $2.25 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22149</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the Purchase of 14,000 ETH, BTCS Pre-market Gain Expanded to 10.24%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22147</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on Rockflow data, likely influenced by the news of acquiring an extra 14,000 ETH, the pre-market gain of BTCS expanded to 10.24%, with a pre-market price of $5.60.Previously, BTCS Inc. announced the acquisition of 14,240 ETH, raising its total holdings to 70,028 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22147</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTCS announced that it has increased its holding of 14,240 ETH, surpassing a total of 70,000 ETH held.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22148</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per official information, BTCS Inc. made an announcement regarding an increase in its holdings by 14,240 ETH, raising its total holdings to 70,028 ETH. Given an Ethereum price of $3,850, the current holdings are valued at around $270 million.Furthermore, the official statement pointed out that BTCS has successfully completed a $10 million convertible note offering. The conversion price for this financing is $13 per share, which represents a 198% premium over BTCS&apos;s closing price on July 18, 2025.Influenced by this news, the pre-market trading of BTCS in the US stock market witnessed an extended increase of 10.24%, with a pre-market price of $5.6.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22148</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs has increased its BNB holdings to 128,000 tokens, with a total value exceeding $100 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22145</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the US-listed company Nano Labs announced that it has boosted its holdings of BNB to 128,000 coins. With the current price of BNB at $850 per coin, the total value of the company&apos;s BNB strategic reserve has exceeded $108 million. This represents the latest move made by Nano Labs in its long-term BNB reserve strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22145</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Nano Labs Surges Over 10% in Pre-market Trading, Currently Trading at $8.03</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22146</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to Rockflow market data, the pre-market trading of US stock Nano Labs surged by more than 10% and is currently at $8.03.Previously, Nano Labs announced that it has raised its holdings of BNB to 128,000 coins. Based on the current price of $850 per BNB, the total value of the company&apos;s BNB strategic reserve has exceeded $108 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22146</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Foundation Buys $25,000 of SOLV and CA</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22144</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the BNB Chain Foundation provided incentives to certain addresses, with these addresses purchasing $25,000 worth of SOLV and CA tokens respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit, Bithumb, and other South Korean DAXA member platforms will delist the PUNDIAI token</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22143</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Upbit declared that the member exchanges of the Korea Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) planned to stop trading support for Pundi AI (PUNDIAI). &quot;Just based on the explanatory materials provided by the foundation regarding the reasons for being designated as a trading alert project, the related concerns cannot be dispelled. After a comprehensive examination of the project&apos;s legitimacy, sustainability, security, and other aspects, it was determined that the project did not meet the standards to maintain trading support. Therefore, the decision was made to terminate trading support.&quot;Both Upbit and Bithumb will cease trading support for PUNDIAI on August 28th.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22143</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab Launches Cryptocurrency Payment Option in the Philippines, Partners with Triple-A and PDAX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22142</link>
      <description>July 28th: The Southeast Asian super app platform Grab announced that Grab users in the Philippines can now add funds to their GrabPay wallet using cryptocurrency. This service became feasible through Grab&apos;s cooperation with the payment service provider Triple-A and the local digital asset exchange PDAX.As early as 2024, Grab initially partnered with Triple-A in Singapore to launch the service of topping up the GrabPay wallet with cryptocurrency. Triple-A is a company focused on assisting businesses in achieving cryptocurrency payments. Building on the success in Singapore, Triple-A has now collaborated with PDAX to introduce this innovative top-up method to the Philippines, providing greater convenience and flexibility to Grab users. Users can now utilize various cryptocurrencies to top up their GrabPay wallet, including:· Bitcoin· Ethereum· USD Coin (USDC)· Tether (USDT)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22142</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXC is about to launch the StablR USD (USDR) Launchpool event, sharing a total prize pool of 85,000 USDT</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22141</link>
      <description>July 28th. According to official channels, in celebration of the listing of StablR USD (USDR), MEXC has initiated a Launchpool event. Through staking USDT, MX, and USDR, participants are able to share a reward of 70,000 USDT. Inviting new users to participate can also enable them to share an additional 15,000 USDT.Event Duration: July 28, 2025, 19:00 (UTC + 8) - August 1, 2025, 19:00 (UTC + 8)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22141</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Sequans increased its Bitcoin holdings by 755, bringing the total number of Bitcoins it holds to 3072.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22140</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Sequans, a publicly traded company in the US, has acquired 755 bitcoins, raising its total holdings to 3072 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22140</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>