<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:56:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Ethereum is currently in a digestion phase after being overbought, with limited potential to retest $5000 in the short term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27295</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, Matrixport presented a market outlook indicating that Ethereum&apos;s transaction volume sharply decreased from $122 billion to $57 billion as speculative long positions underwent liquidation. Despite several technical supports existing below, the funding rate has retreated back to below 10%, suggesting a slowdown in ETF capital inflows.At present, Ethereum is in a digestion stage following being overbought, and the implied volatility still remains at a high level. For aggressive investors, selling covered call options can enable them to capture volatility premiums, and the short-term possibility of returning to $5,000 is limited. Overall, risk control remains of key importance, and Matrixport still maintains a cautious stance after the price breaks below a crucial support.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27295</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Holoworld AI (HOLO) Exclusive Pre-TGE Event Point Threshold is 240 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27294</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to an official announcement, Binance Wallet is going to hold a brand new exclusive Pre-TGE event for HOLO. The event will be carried out on September 2nd, 2025, from 08:00 to 10:00 (UTC). Users who possess 240 Alpha points can participate in this Pre-TGE event by clicking on the Pre-TGE event banner within the wallet. To participate in this event, 10 points need to be spent.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27294</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: ETH May Retrace to $3,350 Support in September, Start Rebound in October Towards New High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27293</link>
      <description>September 2nd. As per Cointelegraph, analyst Johnny Woo declared: &quot;ETH might initially present a bearish outlook. However, if the trend unfolds as anticipated, this could potentially be the most significant bear trap I have ever witnessed.&quot;He further added that the chart suggests that ETH might form a &quot;head and shoulders&quot; pattern in September and then experience a breakout in an &quot;October rally.&quot; In this situation, Ethereum could decline to around $3,350 as a support level in September and subsequently rebound in October, surging to a new all-time high in November.A comparable situation took place in September 2021 when ETH dropped by 30% from $3,950 to $2,750 only to rebound to a new all-time high in November.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27293</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Short-Term Breakthrough of $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27292</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, based on HTX market data, Ethereum briefly exceeded $4400, and it saw a 0.26% increase in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27292</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Executive Board Member Schnabel: Central Bank Should Keep Rates Unchanged, Inflation Could Still Be Higher Than Expected</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27291</link>
      <description>September 2nd - Fabio Panetta, who is a member of the Executive Board of the European Central Bank, expressed that the ECB should keep the interest rate at the present level. This stance is founded on the Eurozone economy&apos;s ability to withstand U.S. tariffs and the potential that the inflation rate might still be higher than anticipated. The ECB previously concluded a one-year period of loose monetary policy and is currently evaluating the comprehensive impact of the July agreement on U.S. tariffs to determine whether further interest rate cuts are required. Panetta is one of the most significant hawks at the ECB and holds the view that there is no necessity for additional rate cuts. The current policy rate of 2% may &quot;moderately&quot; stimulate the already vibrant economy. She stated: &quot;I think we may have already implemented a slightly accommodative policy, so I do not perceive a reason for further rate cuts in the current circumstances.&quot; (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27291</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaplanet announces that the Special Shareholders&apos; Meeting has passed resolutions, including increasing the authorized share capital, etc.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27290</link>
      <description>September 2nd: The publicly traded Japanese company Metaplanet announced that its extraordinary general meeting of shareholders has approved a resolution. This resolution encompasses an increase in authorized shares (to 2,723,000,000 shares), a location-independent shareholders&apos; meeting (enabling fully online shareholder meetings), and the establishment of authorized share classes, namely Class A shares and Class B shares.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27290</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will open Quack AI (Q) airdrop claim today at 15:00 UTC, with a minimum threshold of 220 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27289</link>
      <description>September 2nd, Binance Alpha will commence the claim process for the Quack AI (Q) airdrop at 15:00 UTC. Users possessing at least 220 Alpha points will be eligible to claim a first-come, first-served airdrop of 6000 Quack AI (Q) tokens. In the event that the rewards are not fully distributed, the point threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points every hour. Claiming the airdrop will result in the consumption of 15 Binance Alpha points.· Binance Alpha trading will become active at 15:00 UTC on September 2, 2025;· Binance Futures trading will commence at 15:30 UTC on September 2, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27289</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Since Bitcoin broke $100,000 earlier this year, hodlers have been continuously selling their Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27288</link>
      <description>September 2nd: The Coindesk analyst Omkar Godbole pointed out that Bitcoin long-term holders, including those wallets that have remained inactive for many years, have been continuously selling ever since Bitcoin exceeded $100,000 earlier this year. Investors considered that the $100,000 Bitcoin price was too high and thus chose to realize profits, suggesting that the market might require some time to adjust to $100,000 as the new standard for Bitcoin. We are likely to continue to witness volatile trading in order to assist investors in gradually getting accustomed to this elevated valuation level.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 05:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After spending a day at a golf course near Washington, Trump has returned to the White House and pushed back against &quot;critically ill&quot; rumors.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27287</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, after spending a day at a golf course near Washington, President Trump of the United States returned to the White House and refuted the &quot;critical condition&quot; rumors.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 05:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27287</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Accumulated 260,000 ETH in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27286</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, cryptocurrency analyst @ali_charts presented on-chain data indicating that within the past 24 hours, whales have amassed 260,000 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 05:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27286</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>