<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:18:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has increased its holdings by acquiring 2000 ETH at an average price of $3839, totaling approximately $7.68 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22472</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per the monitoring of Spot On Chain, yesterday the whale &quot;0x720&quot; liquidated a long position in ETH and made a profit of $6 million.In the past 9 hours, the whale withdrew $12.68 million from HyperLiquid and transferred it to Binance. It has purchased 2000 ETH at a price of $3839 per coin (approximately $7.68 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Meme Coin NEET Surges to Over $15 Million Market Cap Briefly Before Falling Back, Up Over 91% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22471</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to the GMGN market data, the meme coin NEET in the Solana ecosystem briefly exceeded a market capitalization of $15 million and then retreated. Currently, the market capitalization has reached $12.3 million, with a 24-hour increase of over 91%.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins have no practical use case and experience large price fluctuations. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22471</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Towns (TOWNS) on August 5th.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22470</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Binance Alpha is set to become the first platform to list Towns (TOWNS) on August 5th. Once the Alpha trading commences, eligible users can access the Alpha event page and utilize Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop. Further details will be provided at a later time.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22470</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Osaka Exchange in Japan is reportedly considering listing cryptocurrency derivatives.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22469</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to Bloomberg, the Osaka Exchange, which is a part of the Japan Exchange Group (JPX), is contemplating the listing of cryptocurrency-related futures and options. The president of the Osaka Exchange, Takasuke Yokoyama, stated in an interview that cryptocurrency-related products are &quot;potential candidate products&quot; and that they will conduct a thorough study of the specifications of overseas products while closely monitoring the regulatory trends of the Japanese Financial Services Agency. Yokoyama also mentioned that the company will give consideration to launching ETFs related to crypto assets. Since the Osaka Exchange mainly deals with derivatives, if this comes to fruition, the ETF will be listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22469</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Perpetual Contract DEX Superp Completes Second Round of Funding, Led by UOB Ventures and Brooker Group</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22467</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Meme coin perpetual contract DEX project Superp (formerly Vanilla Finance) on BSC announced the completion of a seed round financing. It was led by UOB Ventures and Brooker Group, with the participation of Sei Network, Pluto Studio, UXLINK, 071Labs, and strategic angel investors including the core founders from Tapbit, Oobit, Kyber, CaliberBuild, KiloEx, etc. The amount of this seed round financing has not been disclosed.Superp was selected for the 8th phase of the BNB Chain MVB Accelerator Program and received incubation support from CoinMarketCap. Superp aims to create a Hyperliquid for Meme coins, supporting mainstream Meme asset long and short trading.Superp is expected to launch the NoLiquidation Perp trading competition at 10:00 UTC on July 30th as a pre-event for Superp Pre-TGE, encouraging users to try out Superp&apos;s innovative Perp product. The event will provide each user with 1000U in test funds, and user trades will not cause real losses. Based on the pr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22467</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum 10th Anniversary Torch NFT Holder Addresses Surpass 280,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22468</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to on-chain data, the address of the Ethereum Tenth Anniversary Torch Commemorative NFT holder has exceeded 280,000. The minting will end at 24:00 on July 31st (UTC+8).BlockBeats previously reported that Ethereum launched &quot;The Torch&quot; NFT to pay tribute to those who have shaped its development and values in the first decade of Ethereum and will support the future development of Ethereum. In the 10 days leading up to Ethereum&apos;s tenth anniversary, this The Torch NFT will symbolically pass between wallets. On July 30th, The Torch NFT will be burned to commemorate Ethereum&apos;s tenth anniversary. On that day, everyone can mint a commemorative NFT.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Increases Holdings Again with an Additional 56.9 BTC, Bringing Total Holdings to 685.1 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22466</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Swedish listed company announced the acquisition of an additional 56.9 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 685.1 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22466</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Spent $2.25 Million Betting on No Change in July Fed Rate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22463</link>
      <description>Update: On July 30th, based on the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the whale named &quot;bobe2&quot; spent $2.25 million on Polymarket to make a bet that the US Federal Reserve will not adjust interest rates in July 2025. Meanwhile, the whale also spent $144,700 to purchase 149,000 shares of the &quot;no&quot; outcome for &quot;the Fed will cut rates by 25 basis points after the July 2025 meeting.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22463</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs announces investment in the BNB Strategic Reserve Company CEA INDUSTRIES INC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22465</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Nano Labs made an announcement regarding an investment in the BNB Strategic Reserve Company, CEA INDUSTRIES INC, with the aim of further bolstering the BNB Strategic Reserve.According to the terms and conditions of the agreement, Nano Labs subscribed to 495,050 shares of Class A common stock of CEA INDUSTRIES INC at a price of $10.10 per share. Additionally, this investment encompassed an equal number of 495,050 warrants, each with an exercise price of $15.15 per share. In the event that all warrants are exercised, Nano Labs will hold up to 990,100 shares of the company.This round of investment involved the subscription of 495,000 shares of common stock and an equal number of warrants to support its $500 million PIPE financing plan. As of the date of this announcement, Nano Labs holds approximately 128,000 BNB.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22465</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Finance Receives $10M Strategic Investment from Trump Family Crypto Project WLFI</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22464</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Synthetic USD protocol Falcon Finance secured a $10 million strategic investment from the crypto project WLFI affiliated with the Trump family. Falcon has taken USD1 as collateral.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>