<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:59:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Quintenz&apos;s nomination vote to become chairman of the U.S. CFTC has been postponed again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22282</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Bitcoin.com, the progress of Trump&apos;s nomination of Brian Quintenz to serve as the new chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) might once more come to a standstill. His name has been wiped off the meeting agenda of the Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry.Quintenz, a former CFTC commissioner, is currently the policy head of the prominent venture capital firm a16z&apos;s crypto division. During another meeting of the same committee last week, his name was also unexpectedly removed from the voting list. Although the officials did not provide an explanation for the removal, there is widespread speculation that his nomination may be encountering difficulties.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22282</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spheron unveils the SPON Tokenomics, with an Airdrop and Incentive allocation of 9.01%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22281</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to official channels, the decentralized computing protocol Spheron has made the tokenomics of the SPON token public. Once the TGE (Token Generation Event) is completed, the internal accounting token uSPON will be gradually phased out, and SPON will be fully adopted as the primary economic token in the network. Users who hold uSPON will receive a 100% unlocked allocation of SPON at the TGE. Users without uSPON but with points will have to endure a 2-month lock-up period, followed by a 6-month linear release.In the distribution of the total token supply of SPON: Liquidity makes up 5.00%; the Pre-Seed Round accounts for 12.66%; the Seed Round accounts for 8.60%; the Strategic Round accounts for 1.33%; Network Rewards accounts for 24.00%; Ecosystem Projects accounts for 8.00%; Airdrops and Incentives account for 9.01%; the Foundation accounts for 10.00%; the Team and Advisors account for 21.40%.After the TGE, 41.75% of the airdrop rewards will be released immediate</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22281</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: Bitmain Plans to Establish First Factory in the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22280</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as reported by Bloomberg, Bitmain Technologies Ltd., which is the world&apos;s largest manufacturer of cryptocurrency mining rigs, intends to open its first factory in the United States within the next few months. This action is part of its strategic shift towards embracing the &quot;Made in America&quot; trend in digital assets.According to Irene Gao, the head of Bitmain&apos;s global business, the company plans to set up its new headquarters and assembly line in either Texas or Florida by the end of the third quarter of 2025. The first batch of production is anticipated to commence in early 2026, and then it will gradually increase to full-scale production within that year.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures and Alpha Finance will list PlaysOut (PLAY)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22279</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will list and commence trading for PlaysOut (PLAY) on July 31st, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). Furthermore, the Binance Futures platform will initiate the PLAYUSDT perpetual contract on July 31st, 2025, at 17:30 (UTC+8), with a maximum leverage of up to 50 times.All eligible Binance users will be entitled to a Binance exclusive token airdrop. Eligible users are required to claim the airdrop through the BinanceAlpha event page by using Binance Alpha points from July 31st, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8) to August 1st, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22279</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater&apos;s Ray Dalio: Advises Investors to Allocate 15% of Assets to Bitcoin or Gold</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22278</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the report by CoinDesk, Ray Dalio, the founder of Bridgewater Associates, recently advised investors to allocate 15% of their portfolios to Bitcoin or gold. He did this by citing the growing debt burden in the United States and the risks associated with long-term currency devaluation.Dalio stated on the &quot;Master Investor&quot; podcast, &quot;If you aim to optimize the risk-return ratio of your portfolio, then approximately 15% of your funds should be allocated to gold or Bitcoin.&quot;This perspective represents a notable shift from his 2022 recommendation of only a 1–2% Bitcoin allocation, which reflects his increasing worry about the so-called &quot;debt crisis loop.&quot; He pointed out that the United States is projected to issue an additional $12 trillion in new national debt within the next year in order to address the current $36.7 trillion national debt.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22278</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Uncertain Outlook for US-India Trade Agreement, BTC $118,000 Forms Short-Term Support, $120,000 Still a Resistance Level</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22277</link>
      <description>July 29th: The U.S. Trade Representative, Grier, stated that the U.S. and India need to engage in more negotiations prior to the tariff deadline on August 1st and approach with caution regarding the possibility of reaching an agreement. Although India had previously expressed a willingness to impose zero tariffs on certain goods, it has set red lines for core industries such as agriculture and dairy. In the event that trade frictions escalate, it may have an impact on global market risk sentiment. In the crypto market, the price of BTC rebounded after testing 117,400 multiple times yesterday and is currently fluctuating within the range of 118,000 - 120,000.Bitunix analyst&apos;s suggestion: The deadlock in U.S.-India negotiations has heightened the demand for safe-haven assets, and BTC still has short-term support; however, the upward momentum is limited. It is recommended that investors focus on the support level near 118,000 and strictly manage stop-loss; if the price fails to effectiv</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22277</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IKA is about to be listed on Bitget PoolX, with 14 million locked IKA tokens to be unlocked upon ETH staking.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22276</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to an official announcement, Bitget PoolX is set to launch the IKA project. 14,000,000 IKA will be unlocked by locking ETH. The lock-up limit is 300 ETH per person, and the lock-up period is from 6:00 PM on July 29th to 6:00 PM on August 5th (UTC+8).In addition, users who participate in ETH subscription and have a positive net deposit will also receive a 10% ETH financial management interest coupon. The net deposit opening time is from 12:00 PM on July 29th to 12:00 PM on August 5th (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22276</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority: Stablecoin Issuers Regulatory Framework to Take Effect on August 1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22275</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) released several guidelines and explanatory documents regarding the stablecoin issuer regulatory regime today, which is set to take effect from August 1, 2025. The &quot;Licensed Stablecoin Issuer Regulatory Guidance Consultation Summary&quot; and &quot;Guidance on Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Financing of Terrorism (Applicable to Licensed Stablecoin Issuers) Consultation Summary&quot; will be officially published on August 1, 2025. With the implementation of the regulatory regime, market participants are required to comply with the Stablecoin Ordinance and relevant guidelines.The HKMA encourages institutions planning to apply for a license to get in touch with the HKMA through the official email address by August 31, 2025, or even earlier, so that the HKMA can communicate regulatory expectations and offer appropriate feedback. The licensing process is an ongoing one. If individual institutio</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22275</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 11,370 ETH from Coinbase, approximately $40 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22274</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Arkham Monitoring, a whale has just made a withdrawal of 11,370 ETH from Coinbase (approximately $40 million), with an average price of $3,811. In the past hour, it has already achieved a profit of $400,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22274</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit will list the OMNI/KRW trading pair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22273</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, Upbit is going to list the OMNI/KRW trading pair.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22273</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>