<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:45:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: If Tariff Decision is Unfavorable, Will Have to Return Trillions of Dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27430</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, US President Trump stated, &quot;If the tariff appeal is rejected, I will have no choice but to withdraw the tariff. If the tariff ruling is unfavorable to us, we will be compelled to refund trillions of dollars. The tariff ruling lacks legal foundation. If the tariffs are cancelled, we may ultimately end up as a third-world country.&quot; (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple&apos;s AI Talent Continues to Decline as Head of Robotics Research Defects to Meta</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27429</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as per foreign media reports, the lead of Apple&apos;s (AAPL.O) AI robot research has resigned and joined Meta Platforms (META.O), which represents the latest instance of talent loss in AI at the company. Meta confirmed on Tuesday that Jian Zhang has joined its Robotics Lab.According to sources, three other AI researchers are also scheduled to leave Apple&apos;s internal large language model team. The recent wave of resignations that took place last week is said to have included John Peebles, Nan Du, and Zhao Men. These individuals all come from Apple&apos;s base model team, and around 10 members have resigned from this team in recent weeks, including the team lead. This team is a crucial force in developing Apple&apos;s AI platform, which was launched last year as a significant step for the company to keep up with the AI trend. (Jinse)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27429</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Deposit Trend Continues, with CEX Net Inflow of 2,178.12 BTC in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27428</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, the total net inflow of BTC on CEX exchanges was 2,178.12 BTC. The top three exchanges in terms of inflow volume are as follows:· Binance with a net inflow of 1,370.04 BTC;· OKX with a net inflow of 731.08 BTC;· Bitfinex with a net inflow of 564.15 BTC.In addition, Coinbase Pro witnessed a net outflow of 348.74 BTC and ranked first in the outflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27428</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Responds to &quot;Death Rumors&quot;: Didn&apos;t See It</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27427</link>
      <description>September 3rd: Regarding the &quot;death hoax&quot; about him, US President Trump stated, &quot;I didn&apos;t see it.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27427</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Appears on Live Camera at End of White House Press Conference, Dispelling Speculation About His Health</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27426</link>
      <description>September 3rd. Towards the end of a White House press briefing, President Trump emerged on live camera to quash speculation regarding his health. During the first half of today&apos;s White House press briefing, live broadcasts from major U.S. mainstream media outlets like Fox News, NBC, CNBC, etc. presented the exterior of the White House without showing President Trump at the briefing. Recent social media has been in full swing with speculation about his health.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27426</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum drops below $4200, the cumulative long liquidation strength of major CEXs will reach $1.53 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27425</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the cryptocurrency market remains on a downward trajectory. According to Coinglass data, in the event that Ethereum drops below $4200, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation in mainstream CEXs will reach $1.553 billion.Conversely, if Ethereum surges above $4400, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation in mainstream CEXs will reach $0.940 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not precisely depict the number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent clusters, that is, intensity. Consequently, the liquidation chart showcases the degree to which the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it attains a certain level. Higher &quot;liquidation bars&quot; indicate that when the price reaches that level, it will experience a more pronounced reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27425</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Losing the Tariff Appeal Would Be an Economic Disaster</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27424</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, President Trump of the US stated that if he lost the tariff appeal, it would be an economic disaster. An &quot;emergency meeting&quot; is going to be held tomorrow regarding the tariff ruling.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Shows Up at White House Press Briefing as Scheduled, But Does Not Appear on Camera Live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27423</link>
      <description>September 3rd. President Trump was present at the White House press briefing as scheduled at 2 a.m. today. It is noteworthy that up to now, live broadcasts from major U.S. media outlets such as Fox News, NBC, CNBC, etc., only display the exterior of the White House and have not shown Trump&apos;s attendance at the briefing.In recent days, there has been extensive speculation on social media regarding his health condition. On August 30th, Pence stated that if a &quot;serious tragedy&quot; were to occur to Trump, he would be prepared to assume the presidency. Subsequently, Pence mentioned that the 79-year-old Trump is in good health and, despite recent inquiries about his health, he still retains &quot;remarkable energy.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27423</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Will Appeal Tariff Ruling, To Hold &quot;Emergency Meeting&quot; Tomorrow on Tariff Ruling</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27422</link>
      <description>September 3rd: President Trump declared that he will file an appeal regarding the tariff ruling.Trump emphasized once again that global tariffs pose an economic emergency and that &quot;if the tariff war fails to achieve victory, it will set off a chain reaction.&quot; An &quot;emergency meeting&quot; concerning the tariff ruling will be held tomorrow.BlockBeats had previously reported that on August 31st, U.S. Trade Representative Grille stated that after the tariff ruling (by a U.S. court), trade negotiations would continue.On June 2nd, Trump made remarks related to tariffs again, stating, &quot;If the court in some manner issues a ruling on tariffs that is unfavorable to us (which is not anticipated), then other countries will take advantage of this situation to hold us hostage with anti-American tariffs and utilize these tariffs against us, which means the destruction of the U.S. economy!&quot;The U.S. International Trade Court prohibited Trump&apos;s &quot;Liberation Day&quot; tariffs from coming into effect, ruling</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27422</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Withdrawal Trend Continues, with CEX Net Outflow of 10,600 ETH in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27421</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to Coinglass data, in the past 24 hours, the cumulative net outflow of CEX was 10,600 ETH. The top three exchanges with the largest outflows are as follows:· Bitfinex, with an outflow of 14,500 ETH;· Binance, with an outflow of 6,437.45 ETH;· KuCoin, with an outflow of 1,028.80 ETH.In addition, Bybit witnessed an inflow of 8,572.40 ETH and ranked first on the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27421</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>