<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun: $12,192,383 worth of PUMP tokens were bought back in the past week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27749</link>
      <description>On September 4th, pump.fun tweeted that during the past week, a total of $12,192,383 worth of PUMP tokens were purchased. This accounted for 98.23% of the total revenue during the same period (from August 28th to September 3rd). This PUMP purchase has led to a reduction in the total circulating supply by 5.363%, which is an increase of 1.102% compared to the previous week.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27749</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$13.29M Bet Placed on BLOCK and WLFI Address」 Withdraws $2.09M Worth of WLFI Again from Bybit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27748</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the value of WLFI continues to decline. &quot;Invested $13.29 million in BLOCK and WLFI address&quot;, 50 minutes ago, it once again withdrew $2.09 million worth of WLFI from Bybit; currently, he holds a total of 62.78 million WLFI. The average price for the additional 52.56 million WLFI is $0.2313, resulting in an unrealized loss of $3.436 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27748</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stocks Crypto Reserve Companies Experience General Decline, ABTC Drops More Than 17%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27747</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the stock prices of US crypto reserve companies generally declined. These included:American Bitcoin (ABTC), which decreased by 17.2%;MicroStrategy (MSTR), down by 2.62%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET), with a decline of 7.77%;Bitmine (BMNR), down 7.2%;BTCS (BTCS), falling 3.79%;ALT5 Sigma (ALTS), down 15.18%.Previously reported, Nasdaq is intensifying its scrutiny of listed companies&apos; investments in cryptocurrency. Previously, some companies had raised funds to purchase crypto assets, which had boosted their stock prices. However, Nasdaq has expressed concerns about this behavior, believing that it may pose risks of misleading investors. Therefore, it has decided to strengthen regulatory efforts. Currently, Nasdaq has not publicly disclosed specific regulatory measures. However, it is expected that relevant companies will be required to disclose detailed information about their crypto asset investments, including investment size, strategy, and potential risks. In addi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27747</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Board Nominee Milan: President Has Right to Comment on Monetary Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27746</link>
      <description>September 4th. Milan, the nominee of the Federal Reserve Board, stated that the President has the prerogative to express viewpoints on monetary policy. (Xinhua Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27746</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jito Foundation announces four updates to the JTO Tokenomics and has completed the first round of a $1 million JTO buyback.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27745</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the Jito Foundation announced four updates to the JTO tokenomics:· The completion of the first round of a $1 million JTO buyback and future plans: It was completed in four parts within ten days with a $1 million JTO buyback. The foundation will continue to utilize the TWAP buyback strategy and develop other mechanisms like an auction system to achieve the automatic accumulation of JTO value.· The approval of the JIP-24 proposal, doubling the DAO block engine fee.· The launch of the JTO Economic Hub page.· The hosting of the first JTO holder conference call.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27745</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland withdrew 22,086 ETH from Coinbase Prime</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27744</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to Arkham&apos;s monitoring, 43 minutes ago, the liquidity provider Cumberland withdrew 22,086 ETH from the hot wallet address of Coinbase Prime. The value of this withdrawal is $96.99 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venus $13 Million Phishing Attack Victim Retrospective: Attack by Lazarus Hacker Group, Originating from a Spoofed Zoom Meeting Invitation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27743</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Kuan Sun, the founder of EurekaTrading, tweeted a summary of his nearly $13 million loss resulting from a phishing attack.Around 13 million dollars&apos; worth of assets in his wallet were nearly stolen by the Lazarus hacking group on September 2, 2025. The security team took immediate emergency actions and finally recovered the funds.The incident was triggered by what appeared to be a normal Zoom meeting invitation, but it was actually a meticulously planned phishing trap. The hacker utilized a &quot;familiar stranger&quot; relationship, deepfake video, and a forged Rabby plugin to customize an attack based on the victim Venus&apos;s position. Due to mistakenly trusting the fake plugin, a withdrawal was carried out, exposing the assets to the risk of being transferred along with debt.PeckShield, SlowMist, Venus, and multiple security teams responded quickly. They paused the protocol to investigate the risk and ultimately prevented the fund theft. It should be noted that hardware w</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27743</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Board Nominee Milan: The Fed&apos;s independence is crucial to the economy, and the President nominated me because he agrees with my policy views</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27742</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the nominee Milan of the Federal Reserve Board stated that the independence of the Fed is crucial to the economy. The President nominated me because he is in agreement with my policy viewpoints. If confirmed for this position, I will act in an independent manner. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27742</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market&apos;s Three Major Indexes Turn Lower, S&amp;P 500 Index Erases Opening Gains</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27741</link>
      <description>September 4th: The three major U.S. stock indexes witnessed a downward trend. The Dow decreased by 0.06%. The S&amp;P 500 wiped out its opening gains. And the Nasdaq dropped by 0.1%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27741</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In August, CEX Platform Ethereum Spot Trading Volume Surpasses Bitcoin for the First Time in Seven Years</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27740</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to The Block. Based on The Block&apos;s data, the August and weekly spot trading volume of centralized exchanges (CEX) Ethereum exceeded that of Bitcoin (BTC) for the first time in at least seven years.Throughout August, Ethereum consistently outperformed Bitcoin in the seven-day cumulative spot trading volume of centralized exchanges, bringing an end to Bitcoin&apos;s long-term dominance in global spot trading volume. The total Ethereum trading volume on CEX platforms reached approximately $480 billion, while Bitcoin was around $401 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27740</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>