<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:55:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The crypto gaming startup PlaysOut is considering raising $15 million in funding at a $150 million valuation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26862</link>
      <description>August 29th. The GameTech startup company PlaysOut is contemplating a fresh round of equity financing. It aims to raise approximately $15 million, and the valuation is anticipated to surpass $150 million. Insiders disclosed that the company has initiated discussions with potential investors. The target investors comprise Middle Eastern sovereign wealth funds and top global venture capital firms. It is reported that PlaysOut intends to utilize the funds obtained from the financing to expedite its commercialization process. (Bloomberg)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26862</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Bitcoin Treasury Company AMBTS Completes $23.4 Million First Funding Round to Launch Bitcoin Strategic Reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26861</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to BitcoinTreasuries.NET, the Bitcoin treasury company of Amdax, AMBTS, has successfully completed a first-round fundraising of $23.4 million. This fundraising will be employed to initiate a Bitcoin accumulation strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26861</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sei-to-Tree Protocol Yei Finance Launches Cross-Chain Settlement and Execution Layer Product Clovis</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26860</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to official information, Sei&apos;s leading protocol, Yei Finance, launched a full-chain settlement and execution layer product called Clovis. Within just 1 hour of its launch, the first reserve vault reached the deposit cap. The official announcement stated that the next opening will commence on September 1st.Clovis is dedicated to integrating fragmented inter-chain liquidity to construct a unified clearing and settlement architecture. The core on-chain Clearing Layer executes global logic, while the lightweight vaults connected on-chain are responsible for custody and on-chain settlement, thereby forming a shared liquidity pool. This mechanism can support multiple scenarios such as lending, trading, and cross-chain transactions, enabling each deposit to earn additional yields in various products.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26860</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares is planning to list in the United States, with a second-quarter net profit of $32.4 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26859</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per The Block, the European cryptocurrency asset management firm CoinShares announced a net profit of $32.4 million in the second quarter. This was due to the rise in cryptocurrency prices, which drove record inflows into its physically backed exchange-traded products, resulting in a significant surge in its assets under management. With the boost from the increase in cryptocurrency prices and the record inflows into the company&apos;s ETP, the assets under management grew by 26% quarter-on-quarter and reached $3.5 billion.The report indicated that CoinShares is getting ready for a listing in the United States, and the specific timing of the U.S. listing for this quarter will be made clear. CoinShares is headquartered in the British Crown Dependency of Jersey but is currently listed on the Nasdaq Stockholm in Sweden.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26859</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Pre-TGE and Booster Event will be launched for Pieverse (PIEVERSE)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26858</link>
      <description>August 29th. As per an official announcement, the Binance Wallet&apos;s Pre-TGE and Booster event is set to go live for Pieverse (PIEVERSE). The Booster event will commence on September 1, 2025, at 5:00 PM (UTC+8). Eligible users will be required to possess Alpha Points to participate. (The points threshold has not been made public yet.)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26858</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: Multiple Bitcoin Technical Indicators Suggest Short-Term Top Is In</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26857</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to analyst @ali_charts, several Bitcoin technical indicators suggest that a short-term top is approaching:1. RSI Divergence: Although the price keeps reaching new highs, the RSI continues to hit new lows. This divergence is similar to the trend from April to November 2021, indicating the end of this cycle.2. Bearish MACD Cross: This week, the MACD has turned bearish, coinciding with the price drop and increasing the downside risk.3. MVRV Momentum: The Bitcoin MVRV momentum indicator has recently witnessed a &quot;death cross,&quot; suggesting that the macro momentum will change from positive to negative. Historically, this has been a reliable signal of a cyclical top.Key Support Levels: The current significant level to monitor is $108,700. If the weekly closing price drops below this level, it will confirm a deeper trend shift. Further down, there is the initial on-chain accumulation support at $104,500. There is also a major historical demand zone at $97,000. A</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26857</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list Portal To Bitcoin (PTB) Alpha and Futures Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26856</link>
      <description>August 29th. As per official channels, Binance Alpha is set to launch the Portal To Bitcoin (PTB) trading. Binance Alpha trading will commence on 2025-09-03 at 12:00 (UTC). Contract trading will open at 2025-09-03 at 12:30 (UTC). Eligible users can utilize Alpha Points on the Alpha event page to receive airdrops once trading commences. Further details will be disclosed shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: PCE Forward Guidance Points to Third Consecutive Hike, September Rate Cut Sentiment Unchanged; BTC Faces Resistance at 114600, Support at 107600 Likely to be Tested</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26855</link>
      <description>August 29th: The market anticipates that the core PCE will grow by 0.3% in July, with a year-on-year growth reaching 2.9% to 3.0%, marking the third consecutive increase. Tariff transmission has driven up inflation. However, Powell has alleviated inflation concerns at the Jackson Hole Symposium and shifted the focus to employment. This indicates that the probability of a &quot;insurance rate cut&quot; in September remains high. Nevertheless, if the PCE shows signs of overheating, the number and pace of future rate cuts for the rest of the year may be restricted. The consumer side may have reached its peak, with a focus on wages and core services.On the crypto market front, the BTC liquidation heat map shows a concentration of liquidations around 114,000, with further support at 116,800; the downside support is observed at 107,600.Advice from Bitunix analysts:This round of PCE data will have a greater impact on the subsequent easing pace rather than the September decision itself. If the data</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26855</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: Hong Kong Has the Potential to Become a Major Hub for Virtual Assets, but Regulatory Action is Needed to Unlock Its Potential</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26854</link>
      <description>August 29th. In an interview with the South China Morning Post, CZ said that Hong Kong has the capability to become a significant hub for virtual assets, on a par with markets such as the United States and the UAE. Nevertheless, Hong Kong&apos;s regulatory authorities need to act promptly in order to fully tap into this potential.CZ proposed expanding the variety of cryptocurrencies that licensed exchanges in Hong Kong can trade and following the model of Japan by enabling exchanges to decide which tokens can be traded.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26854</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL &quot;Price Manipulator&quot; or Top Individual Holder of WLFI Token</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26853</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to on-chain analyst Ai姨 (@ai_9684xtpa), the WLFI TOP1 holding address, moonmanifest.eth, was identified by Arkham today as belonging to TechnoRevenant (XPL &quot;Price Manipulator&quot;). This address had made an investment of $15 million (13 million USDC + 2.01 million USDT) during the first public sale round seven months ago and currently holds 1 billion WLFI tokens, accounting for 1.0007% of the total supply.It is crucial to note that this address is marked on Debank as belonging to the X account @moonmanifest47. There is a discrepancy in the platform tags. However, after cross-validation by Nansen, Ai姨 is of the opinion that the probability of it belonging to TechnoRevenant is relatively higher.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26853</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>