<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:31:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela&apos;s annual inflation rate reaches 229%, USDT and other stablecoins become a daily payment tool for the public</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28041</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to Cointelegraph, with Venezuela&apos;s annual inflation rate skyrocketing to 229%, stablecoins like USDT have turned into the de facto currency for millions of Venezuelans.Mauricio Di Bartolomeo, the co-founder of Ledn, stated that USDT, which was once limited to users familiar with cryptocurrency and commonly known as the &quot;Binance USD&quot; locally, is now widely used in daily transactions in Venezuela, including buying groceries, paying condo fees, and making salary and supplier payments.Venezuela&apos;s national currency, the Bolivar, has almost no practical value in daily commerce. Rampant inflation, strict capital controls, and a fragmented exchange rate system have led an increasing number of people to prefer using stablecoins rather than cash or local bank transfers.Di Bartolomeo commented: &quot;People and companies prefer to price goods and services in dollars and receive dollars.&quot; He pointed out that USDT is now regarded as the &quot;better dollar.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28041</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Withdrawal Trend Continues, with CEX Net Outflow of 6544 ETH in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28040</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to Coinglass data, in the past 24 hours, CEX accumulated a net outflow of 6544 ETH. This includes:· Coinbase Pro had an outflow of 8,576.65 ETH and ranked first in the outflow list;· Kraken had an inflow of 2,007.13 ETH and ranked first in the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 10,366,000 DOGE from Binance, worth $2.25 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28039</link>
      <description>On September 7th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale withdrew 10,366,000 DOGE from Binance after being dormant for 2 years. The amount withdrawn was worth $2.25 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28039</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: BTC Key Support Level at $108,250</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28038</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the cryptocurrency analyst @ali_charts presented a chart analysis indicating that the crucial support level for BTC is $108,250. The lower support levels are $104,520 and $97,050 respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28038</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerai Founder: Most websites displaying NMR TVL data are incorrect, actual value is around $20 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28037</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Richard Craib, the founder of Numerai, tweeted, &quot;Because of the unique characteristics of our staking mechanism, most websites display incorrect Total Value Locked (TVL) for NMR. For instance, CoinMarketCap shows $4 million, but it is actually approximately $20 million.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28037</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cango mined 150.3 BTC this week, increasing its total holdings to 5277.1 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28036</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the Bitcoin mining firm Cango announced on the X platform that the company mined 150.3 bitcoins during this week. Up to now, Cango&apos;s total holdings of bitcoins have reached 5,277.1 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28036</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol Founder: to Launch Aubrai Terminal, Initiate IP-NFT Minting, and Smart Proxy System</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28035</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Paul Kohlhaas, the founder of Bio Protocol, tweeted that &quot;In the 8 days since the release of AUBRAI, $180,000 in fees were generated, and the transaction volume exceeded $20 million.&quot;The next step is to release the aubr.ai terminal, enabling IP-NFT minting from the terminal, launching Aubrai IPTs on Bio Protocol to fund experiments, and initiating RMR2 research.Cooperating with top scientists from around the world to launch intelligent agent systems for them, while hoping to enable all new DeSci builders and DAOs to succeed. Once Aubrai becomes fully autonomous, there will be multiple synchronous ignition sales in the future with permissionless openness.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28035</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: ETH Key Support Level is $4,260, Watch $4,000 if Broken</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28034</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the cryptocurrency analyst @ali_charts released a chart analysis which said, &quot;The key support level of ETH is $4260. If it is broken, we need to pay attention to $4000.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28034</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has launched Saros (SAROS). Eligible users can claim a 100 SAROS token airdrop.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28033</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Binance Alpha has now launched Saros (SAROS).Users who are eligible can use Alpha Points to claim a 100 SAROS token airdrop on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours after the trading starts.It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a forfeiture of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28033</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Adam Weitsman Teams Up with Gabriel to Take Over HV-MTL Series for Future Development and Ownership</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28032</link>
      <description>On September 7th, billionaire Adam Weitsman made a post on social media, stating, &quot;In collaboration with Gabriel, we are set to take charge of the future development and ownership of the HV-MTL series. Our objective is not merely to leave a lasting mark in the realm of Digital Art but also to facilitate the usage and experience of it by a greater number of people. In the days to come, we will join hands with top-notch artists, developers, and engineers from across the globe.&quot;Adam Weitsman is an American entrepreneur, investor, and philanthropist. Currently, he serves as the CEO of Upstate Shredding – Weitsman Recycling, which is one of the largest private scrap metal processing companies on the East Coast of the United States, handling more than 1 million tons of steel and 25 million pounds of non-ferrous metal annually. In 2021, he founded Viridium LLC and entered the cryptocurrency mining field.Earlier reports: On August 5th, Adam Weitsman posted on social media, saying, &quot;I am ma</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>