<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:00:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: Solana On-Chain DeepSeekAI, SPARK New Coin Climbing; Base Chain Blue Chips ZEN, Billy, and Others Emerging</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23353</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to GMGN data, in the &quot;Hot&quot; sector on the Solana chain, the top five tokens in terms of market capitalization within the past 6 hours are Fartcoin, DeepSeekAI, USELESS, TROLL, and SPARK. It should be noted that DeepSeekAI and SPARK have been listed for less than 24 hours, which poses relatively higher risks. Therefore, please trade with caution.On the other hand, on the Base chain, in the &quot;Next Blue Chip&quot; sector within the past 6 hours, the top five tokens in terms of market capitalization are ZEN, XTTA, Billy, SPARK, and BOSS. Tokens in this sector have a short listing time and an unstable trading volume. Please be aware of the risks.BlockBeats reminds users that many Meme coins lack practical use cases and have significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23353</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland, Abraxas Capital continue to accumulate over 44,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23352</link>
      <description>August 6th. Based on The Data Nerd&apos;s monitoring, 10 hours ago, Cumberland withdrew 36,918 ETH from Coinbase (around $132.86 million).4 hours ago, Abraxas Capital kept on accumulating 7,191 ETH from Binance (about $25.97 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Foundation Update on Scaling Efforts: Addition of L1 Scaling Lead Member</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23351</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Ethereum Foundation issued a blog post to update the latest work progress in the &quot;Scale L1 / Layer 1 Scalability&quot; area. This includes the following 3 points:1. Marius van der Wijden joins Ansgar Dietrichs and Tim Beiko to jointly lead the L1 scaling work.2. Following Berlinterop, the mainnet gas limit has been increased to 45 million, marking the first step towards 100 million Gas and beyond.3. All major execution layer clients have deployed the pre-merge history pruning feature, which significantly reduces node disk usage.It is understood that in order to address the growing demand on the Ethereum network, the Foundation reorganized the research and development team in June and renamed it to &quot;Protocol&quot;, focusing on three key strategic goals: L1 Scalability (Scale L1), Blob Scalability, and User Experience/UX Improvement while ensuring security and decentralization.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23351</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONK Token Experiences Significant Pullback, GP and USELESS Both Drop Over 25%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23350</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to the GMGN market information, today the mainstream token of the BONK protocol experienced a significant pullback. Specifically:The 24-hour price drop of GP reached 30.4%, and the current market value is $125 million.The 24-hour price drop of USELESS reached 27.2%, and the current market value is $185 million.The 24-hour price drop of ANI reached 23.6%, and the current market value is $28.93 million.BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of these tokens are highly volatile, and users should invest with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23350</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 1.25 billion PUMP tokens to Kraken 10 minutes ago, potentially facing a loss of nearly $1 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23349</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the whale address BfL4vh deposited 1.25 billion PUMP tokens ($4.09 million) into Kraken 10 minutes ago.Previously, this whale had spent 5 million USDC in public sales through 5 wallets to acquire the 1.25 billion PUMP tokens. If it sells now, it would lead to a loss of nearly $1 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23349</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital stakes 250,000 SOL and deposits it into Binance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23348</link>
      <description>On August 6, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, 3 hours ago, Galaxy Digital undelegated 250,000 SOL tokens (amounting to $40.7 million) and deposited them into Binance.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23348</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF saw a net outflow of $196 million, marking the fourth consecutive day of outflows.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23346</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as monitored by Farside Investors, yesterday there was a net outflow of $196 million from the US Bitcoin spot ETF, marking the fourth consecutive day of net outflows. Among them, the BlackRock IBIT witnessed a net outflow of $77.4 million, and the Fidelity FBTC saw a net outflow of $99.1 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23346</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale that had been quiet for 2 months undelegated over 30,000 SOL and deposited it into Binance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23345</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, following a period of two months of inactivity, a whale carried out the action of unbonding 30,010 SOL, which is equivalent to 4.9 million US dollars. Subsequently, it deposited 30,050 SOL into Binance.During the past four months, this whale, after staking for four years, has already unbonded 205,072 SOL coins with a value of 30.07 million US dollars. Currently, the whale still holds 1,108,368 SOL, which is worth 179 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the US Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $73.3 million, breaking a two-day streak of outflows.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23344</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as monitored by Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF yesterday was $73.3 million. Among them, BlackRock&apos;s ETHA witnessed a net inflow of $88.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic Observer: Recently, multiple illegal projects have utilized the concept of &quot;Stablecoin Mining&quot; for illegal fundraising and rebate activities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23347</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Economic Observer released an investigation report entitled &quot;Annualized Yield Up to 540%? Investigation of Chaos in Virtual Asset Investment.&quot; The report pointed out that through journalists&apos; investigations, it was found that there are currently some virtual asset investment platforms active in the market with keywords such as decentralization, blockchain, and virtual assets. They package their projects with terms like blockchain technology, smart contracts, DeFi, and Defai (DeFi + AI).Many illegal projects are packaged with concepts such as &quot;DeFi Decentralized Finance,&quot; &quot;DApp Financial Management,&quot; and &quot;Stablecoin Mining,&quot; but in essence, they are still fundraising and rebate activities, merely using technological shells to cover up risks.From a legal perspective, investors need to bear responsibility for their own civil legal actions. They should carefully identify and participate in virtual asset investment projects, be vigilant against illegal activities disg</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23347</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>