<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:52:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A criminal group in Fujian, China is using USDT for money laundering, with involved transactions totaling over 13.3 billion RMB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27839</link>
      <description>September 5th. In the first half of this year, the People&apos;s Court of Hanjiang District, Fujian Province, China, handed down a ruling in a criminal case related to virtual currency. Yan, Zheng, Lin and others established an underground foreign exchange trading network using the virtual currency USDT (Tether). They solicited customers through overseas chat applications and illegally exchanged RMB and foreign currency using &quot;U coins&quot; as a medium. The bank account transactions involved exceeded 13.3 billion RMB. It was found that the amount of illegal foreign exchange transactions was 25.62 million RMB. The group also withdrew cash exceeding 478 million RMB from banks in various places in Fujian Province, purchased &quot;U coins&quot;, transferred them to upstream criminal wallets to &quot;launder&quot; cross-border crime proceeds and earned the price difference.Suspect Lin denied all criminal facts after being brought to justice. The court guided the public security organs to extract three key voice record</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27839</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Strategy&apos;s profitability level has met the S&amp;P 500 inclusion criteria. If included, it will bring in $16 billion in liquidity.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27838</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to Bloomberg, with regard to Strategy, as it recorded $14 billion in unrealized gains in the last quarter, it has theoretically met the profitability requirement for inclusion in the S&amp;P 500. If included, passive funds tracking the index would be required to passively purchase around 50 million shares, which would amount to approximately $16 billion at the current price. This would lead institutional passive holders to hold around $70 billion of its Bitcoin reserves.Although Strategy had already been included in the Nasdaq 100 by the end of 2024, the S&amp;P 500 has more stringent requirements regarding liquidity, market capitalization (no less than $227 billion), earnings history, and industry balance. The final decision still depends on the committee&apos;s judgment.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27838</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha New Airdrop BOOST Point Threshold is 220 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27837</link>
      <description>September 5th. As per an official announcement, the trading for the Binance Alpha new airdrop project BOOST is set to commence on September 5, 2025, at 08:00 (UTC). Once trading begins, users possessing at least 220 Alpha points will be qualified to receive an airdrop of 640 BOOST tokens on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the reward pool is not fully distributed, the points threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27837</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC: Hong Kong May See a Renminbi Stablecoin in the Future, with Some Large State-owned Enterprises Actively Exploring Stablecoin Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27836</link>
      <description>September 5th. According to the Hong Kong Economic Times, Liu Jing, the Chief Economist of HSBC Global Asset Management in the Greater China region, stated in his speech at the Lujiazui Forum in June that PBOC Governor Pan Gongsheng mentioned the establishment of an international operation center for the digital RMB. Meanwhile, some large central enterprises are actively exploring the applications of stablecoins. When Chinese enterprises invest in Belt and Road emerging markets, they often face issues such as local currency volatility and a lack of hedging tools. In such cases, these enterprises may explore issuing their own RMB stablecoins to assist in investing in emerging markets.Liu Jing pointed out that when multiple Chinese enterprises issue RMB stablecoins, the digital RMB may serve as an intermediary connecting various RMB stablecoins, which will contribute to the expansion of the international usage of the RMB.She further stated that Hong Kong, considering its cooperation</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27836</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: SOL long position has been closed, market still in consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27835</link>
      <description>On September 5th, trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio said in his personal channel, &quot;I have closed a relatively small long position on SOL. I originally expected a bullish trend, but it seems to be in a consolidation stage for the time being.&quot;On September 3rd, trader Eugene stated that he had established a small long position on SOL and set a stop-loss if Bitcoin dropped below $110,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 05:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27835</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI partnered with RaveDAO to host its first offline event, bringing to life the world&apos;s first USD1 offline payment scenario.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27834</link>
      <description>On September 5th, WLFI (World Liberty Financial) is going to partner with RaveDAO, the world&apos;s largest Web3 Rave community. They will hold their first offline event during the Korea Blockchain Week 2025 on September 24th, thus establishing the world&apos;s first offline payment scenario driven by USD1. At that time, tickets and on-site purchases can be directly settled in USD1.It is reported that in this cooperation, RaveDAO will join hands with ecosystem partners such as AWE, Aptos, MUKU, Umy, Gradient, Sidekick, etc. to jointly create a cross-border experience covering payment, travel, fashion, and entertainment. This event also marks the official launch of RaveDAO&apos;s Korea station. Continuing with its &quot;Rave for Good&quot; charity model, RaveDAO will donate 20% of its on-chain revenue to charity projects, truly integrating &quot;crypto payments + entertainment + charity&quot;.Over the past year, RaveDAO has held immersive electronic music events in places like Dubai, Miami, Brussels, Seoul, Singapore</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 05:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27834</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea Network DeFi TVL Surpasses $1.2 Billion, Setting a New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27833</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to data from DefiLlama, the DeFi TVL of Linea Network has exceeded $1.2 billion and is currently at $1.214 billion. It has seen a nearly 71.14% increase in the past week and reached a new all-time high.The top three DeFi protocols on the network in terms of TVL are Aave ($723 million), Etherex ($266 million), and Renzo ($229 million) (some protocols may have overlapping calculations).In a previous announcement, Linea revealed the launch of the Ignition liquidity incentive program, distributing 1 billion LINEA tokens as rewards. Etherex, Aave, and Euler are designated partners for this event.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27833</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jia Yueting: Faraday Future Currently Has No Plans to Increase Treasury Stock by Issuing Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27832</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Jia Yueting tweeted that the core principle of Faraday Future (FFAI) has always been &quot;shareholder first.&quot; The company has no intention of issuing FFAI shares for treasury holdings. If a new policy mandates the issuance of shares for this purpose, the company will strictly adhere to it after formal implementation.On August 17th, Faraday released the C10 Treasury, a treasury product based on the &quot;C10 Index&quot; allocation. The first phase aims to purchase $5 to $10 billion of cryptocurrency assets after obtaining the requisite funding. The initial allocation amount is $30 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Alert: AI Programming Tool Cursor at Risk of New Virus Hijacking</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27831</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as reported by Cointelegraph, the cybersecurity firm HiddenLayer stated that the AI programming tool Cursor possesses a &quot;CopyPasta License Attack&quot; vulnerability. Hackers are able to conceal malicious commands within the LICENSE.txt and README.md files, thereby inducing the AI tool to infuse the vulnerability into the codebase. This tool is widely utilized by cryptocurrency exchanges such as Coinbase.The attack makes use of Markdown comment hiding to inject prompts, resulting in the AI automatically propagating the malicious payload while editing files. Tests have demonstrated that AI programming tools like Windsurf, Kiro, and Aider also share the same vulnerability. The malicious code has the potential to create backdoors, steal sensitive data, or disable systems, all while remaining deeply concealed to evade detection.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27831</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Invites Tech Giant CEOs to Dinner, Musk Absent, Tim Cook, Sam Altman, and Others Attend</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27830</link>
      <description>September 5th. According to reports from NBC and other media, last evening local time in the United States, President Trump invited several CEOs of tech giants to a dinner at the White House. The guests comprised: Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella, Google CEO Sundar Pichai, Apple CEO Tim Cook, AMD CEO Lisa Su, OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, and others.It is worth noting that Musk did not attend the dinner; however, the White House stated that a representative for Musk would be in attendance.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27830</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>