<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Mainstream Cryptocurrencies Continue to Surge, Bitcoin Breaks $115,000, Ethereum Breaks $4,500</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25792</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to HTX market data, mainstream cryptocurrencies continued to surge following Powell&apos;s dovish remarks. Bitcoin briefly exceeded $115,000 and is currently trading at $114,771, with a nearly 2.05% increase in the past hour. Ethereum briefly exceeded $4,500 and is currently trading at $4,482.21, with a nearly 4.6% increase in the past hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the last hour, a total of $128 million has been liquidated across the network, with the main position being a short liquidation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25791</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to data from Coinglass, nearly $128 million was liquidated within one hour, with $119 million in short positions being liquidated.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25791</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yi Li Hua: ETH Ends Week-Long Bear Market, Gearing Up for Next Bull Run</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25790</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the founder of Liquid Capital (formerly LD Capital), Li Hua, published an article on Platform X, stating: &quot;ETH has concluded a one-week bear market, which is in line with our expectation of a confirmed rate cut. Those who heeded the advice and bought at the dip, raise your hands. Let&apos;s jointly welcome the new round of growth.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25790</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Powell &quot;Joins&quot; Dovish Camp, States Economic Risks Provide Greater Rationale for Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25789</link>
      <description>August 22nd. Federal Reserve Chairman Powell expressed that the continuously &quot;evolving&quot; economic risks have provided the Fed with a more solid foundation for cutting interest rates. This assertion indicates that Powell has joined the &quot;dovish&quot; camp within the Federal Open Market Committee responsible for setting rates and signals his potential endorsement for a 25-basis-point rate cut at the Fed&apos;s next meeting in September. Although Powell acknowledged that the impact of the government&apos;s trade war on consumer prices is now &quot;apparently visible,&quot; he suggested that this impact is unlikely to endure and may instead be a one-time shock that the central bank can disregard.He stated: &quot;Given that the labor market is not overly tight and is facing increasing downside risks, this outcome does not seem probable.&quot; He further added, &quot;Inflation is facing upside risks, while employment is facing downside risks, presenting a challenging situation.&quot; (ChainDD)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25789</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: No Need to Tighten Policy Above Sustainable Employment Level, New Framework Aims to Adapt to Various Economic Conditions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25788</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell stated that the Fed still holds the view that relying solely on employment being above its maximum sustainable level is an uncertain estimate and may not necessarily call for policy tightening. If a tight labor market poses risks to price stability, proactive measures may be needed. The previous framework placed excessive emphasis on specific economic conditions, which may have caused some confusion; the new framework is intended to adapt to various economic situations.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25788</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: Fed Abandons 2020 Flexible Inflation Target Framework, Cannot Take Stable Inflation Expectations for Granted</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25787</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell stated at the Jackson Hole Symposium that the Fed is giving up the 2020 flexible average inflation targeting framework. We cannot assume stable inflation expectations automatically, and the impact of tariffs on consumer prices is now evident.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25787</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Powell&apos;s Speech, Traders Fully Price In Two Rate Cuts by Fed Before Year-End</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25786</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on market reports, following Powell&apos;s speech, traders had fully factored in two additional rate cuts by the Fed prior to the end of the year.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25786</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: Shift in Risk Balance May Warrant Policy Adjustments</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25785</link>
      <description>August 22: At the Jackson Hole Symposium, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell stated that a change in the risk balance might necessitate policy adjustments as the circumstances suggest an increasing downside risk to employment.Market Interpretation: It seems that Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is getting prepared for a rate cut in September.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25785</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by Powell&apos;s Speech, Mainstream Cryptocurrencies Experience a Short-term Surge, with Bitcoin Breaking $114,000 and Ethereum Breaking $4,400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25784</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin exceeded $114,000 and is currently trading at $114,145, with a 1-hour price increase of 1.3%. Ethereum briefly reached above $4,400 and is currently priced at $4,400.88, with a 1-hour price increase of 2.71%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the eve of Powell&apos;s speech, traders continue to lower interest rate cut bets.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25783</link>
      <description>August 22nd: The forex options data indicates that the bullish sentiment towards the US dollar has reached a three-week high. This shows that traders are wagering that Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will not adopt an overly dovish stance on rate cuts.In recent days, traders have been reducing their bets on rate cuts. Currently, the market anticipates that the Fed will implement a cumulative 47 basis point rate cut by the end of the year, in contrast to 63 basis points just over a week ago.&quot;With a 25 basis point rate cut in September - this possibility exists,&quot; said Sonja Marten, the Director of Forex and Monetary Policy Research at DZ Bank AG, in an interview with Bloomberg TV. &quot;However, I don&apos;t think he will adopt a more aggressive stance than that.&quot; (FX678)According to the CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch Tool,&quot; the current probability of the Fed keeping rates steady in September is 24.5%, while the probability of a 25 basis point rate cut is 75.5%. The probability of the Fed keeping rates ste</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25783</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>