<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: Has Not Yet Met the Right Business Partner or Life Partner</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26403</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Justin Sun recently stated in an interview with the LatePost team that he has not yet come across a suitable business partner or life partner. He remarked, &quot;It would be splendid to have such a person at the appropriate time. Currently, the individuals who love me the most are my parents.&quot;Regarding Justin Sun&apos;s company, there is no true &quot;second in command.&quot; All departments report directly to Justin Sun alone. He brought up, &quot;This is typical. Many companies do not have a second in command. I believe leaders like Musk also do not have a second in command.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26403</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Withdraws Another 10,000 ETH from Kraken, Worth $45.6 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26402</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale withdrew 10,000 ETH from Kraken, with a value of $45.6 million.Previously, this whale address had made a withdrawal of 10,000 ETH from Kraken on August 24th. Currently, the whale holds a total of 20,000 ETH.Address: 0x3f0D4d2A42dd577CA0F604Dc330335a50179ab794.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26402</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rex is applying for a BNB staking ETF, based on the &quot;40 Act.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26401</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per Bloomberg&apos;s Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas, Rex is in the process of seeking approval for a BNB Staking ETF in accordance with the Investment Company Act of 1940. This is similar to the &apos;REX-Osprey SOL Active ETF (SSK)&apos;.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26401</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud is launching L1 Network GCUL, which is currently in the private testnet phase.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26400</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Rich Widmann, Google&apos;s Web3 Strategy Lead, wrote that the recent discussions about Layer 1 blockchains have brought Google&apos;s own Layer 1 - known as the Google Cloud Universal Ledger (GCUL) - into the spotlight. As a product lead in the crypto space, you are aware that to build a Layer 1, it must have differentiation.GCUL combines Google&apos;s years of research and development and is currently in the private testnet stage, providing a new Layer 1 for financial institutions: it is high-performance, trust-neutral, and supports Python-based smart contracts. In addition to utilizing Google&apos;s distribution capabilities, GCUL is also a neutral infrastructure layer. Tether will not use Circle&apos;s blockchain, and Adyen is also unlikely to use Stripe&apos;s blockchain. However, any financial institution can build on GCUL. Stay tuned for more technical details in the coming months!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address fell for a YZY investment scam, losing $710,000, then bought the genuine coin, currently facing an unrealized loss of $424,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26399</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to crypto KOL Kakashi, a wallet address made an investment in the Meme token YZY. It bought fake tokens and incurred a loss of $710,000. Subsequently, it purchased genuine YZY tokens, spending $740,400. Currently, it is sitting on an unrealized loss of $424,000 and has not yet made a sale.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26399</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI surged pre-market on Hyperliquid to &quot;wickedly&quot; spike at $0.42, then quickly retraced.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26398</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on on-chain data, WLFI on the Hyperliquid pre-market contract platform reached as high as $0.42 at 6:27 this morning. It then quickly dropped back and is now trading at $0.28359, with a 24-hour increase of 18.85%. According to Coinglass data, in the past 4 hours, a total of $370,900 worth of WLFI was liquidated across the entire network, including $73,800 in long liquidations and $297,100 in short liquidations.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26398</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-profile ETH Whale Swaps BTC Once Again, Sells 3,968 BTC, and Acquires 96,533 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26397</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, the BTC ancient whale that had previously made a highly publicized switch from ETH has sold another 3,968 BTC (approximately $437.02 million) within the past 13 hours. Additionally, it has acquired an extra 96,533 ETH at an average price of $4,588.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26397</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HLP earned approximately $47,000 this morning during the XPL price surge, after previously losing nearly $12 million during the JELLY price anomaly.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26396</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to on-chain data, HLP earned approximately $47,000 during an XPL anomaly this morning. The monthly annualized return rate reached 14%. A whale made a long position of several million XPL from 5:00 to 6:00 this morning. It directly swept the entire order book and squeezed out all short positions. Then, it began to close part of the long positions, making a profit of $16 million in just one minute. XPL soared to $1.80 within 2 minutes, with an increase of more than 200%.BlockBeats previously reported that on March 26th, a whale holding 126 million JELLY tokens was manipulating the price of JELLY. The address first sold off JELLY to cause the price to crash, enabling HLP to have a passive short position of 398 million JELLY (worth about $15.3 million). Then, the address bought back JELLY, resulting in the price surging and HLP losing nearly $12 million.Subsequently, users of Hyperliquid holding long positions on JELLY at settlement time will be refunded by th</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26396</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL Soars 200% on Hyperliquid, Whale Liquidates Order Book with Long Position in Just 1 Minute to Pocket $16 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26394</link>
      <description>August 27th. According to the monitoring of @mlmabc, a specific wallet address initiated a long position on Hyperliquid at 5:35 this morning. During this process, it purchased millions of XPL and directly cleared the entire order book, squeezing out all short positions. Subsequently, the trader began to close some of the long positions, achieving a profit of $16 million within just one minute. XPL soared to $1.80 within 2 minutes, indicating a more than 200% increase.He currently still holds 15.2 million XPL (with a value of approximately $10.2 million). Mlm described it as &quot;one of the most insane liquidation events I have ever witnessed on Hyperliquid.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26394</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYPE briefly surged to $49.7, marking a 12.88% increase in the last 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26395</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on HTX market data, HYPE briefly surged to $49.7 and is now retracted to $48.5, with a 24-hour gain of 12.88%. The market capitalization rose to $16.241 billion.Earlier today, on Hyperliquid, XPL saw a 200% surge. A whale went long and &quot;liquidated&quot; the order book, earning $16 million in just 1 minute.During the same period, on Hyperliquid, HLP made around $47,000 during the price anomaly of XPL. It had previously lost nearly $12 million due to the price swing of JELLY.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26395</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>