<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:21:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit&apos;s daily trading volume surges over 45%: ETH, XRP, and PROVE currently hold the top three positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23903</link>
      <description>On August 10th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit surged to $3.879 billion, experiencing a daily increase of 45.7%. The ETH/KRW trading pair accounted for 16.1% of the volume and ranked first. Next came XRP, PROVE, BTC, and SOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23903</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale withdrew 274.22 BTC from a CEX after one month of dormancy, worth $32 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23902</link>
      <description>On August 10th, as monitored by OnchainLens, a whale address withdrew 274.22 BTC from Binance after being dormant for a month. The value of this withdrawal is $32 million. Currently, the whale holds 587.24 BTC, with a value of $69.24 million.Address: bc1qk2c3usel9wqcccxgrzcnmys3ry57algan3tsmx</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23902</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Expert: Russian-American Summit in Alaska Could See Proposal for Ukraine Ceasefire Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23901</link>
      <description>On August 10th, Dmitry Suslov, the Deputy Director of the European and International Studies Department at the Higher School of Economics in Russia and an expert at the Valdai Club, informed Sputnik News that after the meeting between Russian President Putin and US President Trump in Alaska, they might propose a ceasefire plan for Ukraine. Suslov stated, &quot;We shouldn&apos;t anticipate an immediate ceasefire agreement directly. Instead, we should concentrate on a ceasefire conditions plan that is jointly agreed upon by Russia and the US. Then, we should strive to enter into final negotiations in order to thoroughly resolve the conflict.&quot;This plan may comprise the complete withdrawal of Ukrainian forces from the territory of the Donetsk People&apos;s Republic. Meanwhile, the current line of contact in Zaporizhia and Kherson oblasts would be maintained as the final border. And Russian forces might withdraw from certain parts of Sumy, Kharkiv, and Dnipropetrovsk oblasts. (Finance 10)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23901</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn admits to overleveraging, succumbing to the spotlight effect, leading to a meltdown in the end.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23900</link>
      <description>August 10th, James Wynn put out a post and summed it up like this: &quot;In this world, there is no such thing as a mistake. There are only lessons. Whenever I encounter what others might call a mistake or a failure in my life, I always manage to learn from it. The most significant lesson recently was when I turned 3 million dollars into 100 million dollars but then lost it all in front of everyone.&quot;&quot;That time was extremely intense - with adrenaline pumping, chaos all around, and a complete madness. I faced it with a smile and a laugh. This is another lesson - I got overly leveraged and was blinded by all the &apos;attention,&apos; losing complete control of my emotions. I don&apos;t want to change anything that has happened. Even if you were to send me back to that moment and give me the choice to cash out, I wouldn&apos;t. I value this lesson more. Money is boundless; it is everywhere and easy to make.&quot;&quot;When I reached 100 million dollars, you cheered for me. And when I fell to the bottom, you laughed at</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23900</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOON surges over 100% in 24 hours, reaching a market capitalization of $1.24 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23899</link>
      <description>On August 10th, based on HTX market data, SOON witnessed a surge of more than 100% within the past 24 hours. It is currently trading at $0.518 and has a market capitalization of $124 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23899</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Pelosi Couple Used Insider Information to Beat All Hedge Funds in 2024, Investigation Needed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23897</link>
      <description>On August 10th, U.S. President Trump took to his personal social media platform and stated, &quot;Sneaky Nancy Pelosi and her &apos;quite intriguing&apos; husband outperformed all the hedge funds in 2024. In other words, these two rather ordinary &apos;minds&apos; managed to defeat all the super geniuses on Wall Street, which amounts to thousands of people. This is all insider information! Is anyone looking into this??? She is an extremely nauseating disgrace, having impeached me twice without any valid reason and failed! Nancy, how do you feel now???&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23897</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORM Token Surges to $4.19, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23898</link>
      <description>On August 10th, based on HTX market data, FORM briefly exceeded $4.19 and reached a new all-time high. It is currently trading at $4.12, indicating a 24-hour price increase of 2.93% and having a market capitalization of $1.579 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23898</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital Deposits 224,000 SOL to CEX, Worth Over $410 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23896</link>
      <description>On August 10th, according to the monitoring of Lookonchain, 3 hours ago, Galaxy Digital deposited 224,000 SOL (valued at $41.12 million) into Binance and Coinbase.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P Global: July U.S. CPI Data to Be Key Economic Indicator for New Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23895</link>
      <description>On August 10th, Standard &amp; Poor&apos;s Global indicated that the July U.S. CPI data would be a key economic indicator in the new week. Due to tariff policies causing inflation expectations to rise, the market is eagerly anticipating this report. Despite the current tariff developments (such as the higher tariffs imposed on August 7th and the latest threat of 100% chip tariffs), which suggest a possible increase in inflation, the overall U.S. second-quarter consumer price increase has remained below 3.0%.It is worthy of note that the Standard &amp; Poor&apos;s Global U.S. PMI data, as a leading indicator of CPI trends, has hinted that inflation may pick up in the second half of 2025. Therefore, the upcoming CPI data will confirm whether prices in July have begun to accelerate. This is crucial for the Fed&apos;s monetary policy as there is potential price volatility, and the Fed is currently maintaining a wait-and-see stance. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23895</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Net Inflow of 99,300 Ethereum to CEX in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23894</link>
      <description>On August 10th, according to Coinglass data, during the past 24 hours, the total net inflow of Ethereum on CEX was 99,300 ETH. The top three CEX inflows are as follows:· Binance, with an inflow of 128,900 ETH;· OKX, with an inflow of 12,100 ETH;· Bybit, with an inflow of 4,232.97 ETH.In addition, Bitfinex witnessed an outflow of 35,000 ETH, ranking first on the outflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23894</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>