<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 22:56:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 22:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Reserve Asset Stocks Experience Broad Decline, SBET and BMNR Both Drop Over 9%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25256</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on market data, the Ethereum Reserve concept stocks in the US stock market witnessed a general decline. These included:- SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US), which dropped by 9.42%;- Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US), with a decrease of 9.97%;- BTCS (BTCS.US), down by 13.45%;- GameSquare (GAME.US), falling by 10.53%;- Bit Digital (BTBT.US), declining by 8.16%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor: Fed&apos;s Views on AI and Cryptocurrency &apos;About to Change&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25255</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Federal Reserve Board Governor Bowman expressed that banks and regulatory agencies must embrace the advantages of new technologies like artificial intelligence and cryptocurrency. Otherwise, their role in the economy could be weakened.In her speech, she stated, &quot;Change is approaching.&quot; She proposed that ideally, regulatory agencies would enable new use cases to &quot;soar in a manner that benefits the banking system.&quot; She further added, &quot;If we do not adopt this approach, we may run the risk of the banking system&apos;s relevance to consumers, businesses, and the overall economy decreasing.&quot;Bowman called on the industry to assist regulatory agencies in better understanding blockchain and digital assets, as well as the potential of new technologies to address issues such as fraud. She also indicated that she would strive to reduce regulatory oversight related to reputational risk, suggesting the possibility of new rulemaking. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25255</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Includes 407 Steel and Aluminum Derivative Products in Tariff List</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25254</link>
      <description>August 20th: On August 19th in the local time zone, the U.S. Department of Commerce announced that 407 product categories have been included in the steel and aluminum tariff list, and the tariff rate is 50%.The Department of Commerce declared that the new list encompasses a wide variety of products, such as wind turbines and their components, mobile cranes, railway vehicles, furniture, compressors, pumps, and hundreds of other products. (CCTV)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25254</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: The Presidents of Russia and Ukraine have expressed their willingness to sit down for negotiations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25253</link>
      <description>August 20th: On August 19th in the local time, the White House Press Secretary Levi declared that the U.S. military will not be deployed within Ukraine but can offer assistance through coordination and security. Trump has given instructions to the National Security Council to collaborate with Europe.Levi stated that Trump has put forward a solution for NATO to purchase American weapons. Levi also mentioned that Russian President Putin and Ukrainian President Zelensky have shown a willingness to have negotiations. Trump hopes for direct diplomatic talks between Russia and Ukraine. Currently, arrangements are being made for Zelensky to meet with Putin. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25253</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: US Treasury Secretary&apos;s Rate Cut Stance Contradicts Fed&apos;s Model</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25252</link>
      <description>On August 20th, a Deutsche Bank interest rate strategist expressed that the view of the U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen on the appropriate level of the Fed rate compared to the model is incorrect by more than one percentage point. Yellen had previously stated that &quot;regardless of any model,&quot; the rate &quot;should be reduced by 150 to 175 basis points.&quot; However, subsequent attempts to search for a model to support this statement have been unsuccessful, and the Deutsche Bank strategist team led by Matthew Raskin has recently joined this verification effort.Former Fed economist and advisor Raskin and his team stated in a report on Tuesday that the rule used by the Fed in its semi-annual monetary policy report &quot;does not clearly indicate a rate cut, let alone a cut of 150 to 175 basis points.&quot;They pointed out: &quot;It should be noted that the current federal funds rate is precisely within the relatively narrow range specified by the rule,&quot; approximately between 4% and 4.65%, which suggests that a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25252</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn Ethereum Long Liquidation Event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25251</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as monitored by lookonchain, James Wynn&apos;s long position in Ethereum experienced partial liquidation, and it took only 10 hours. Now only 71.6 ETH in long position remains (approximately $300,000).Previously, after receiving a 19,206.72 USDC referral reward, he opened a 25x leveraged long position on ETH. The opening price was $4,239.5, and the liquidation price was $4,143.8.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25251</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Withdrawal Momentum Rebounds, with a CEX Net Outflow of 9457.52 ETH in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25250</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, CEX has witnessed a total net outflow of 9,457.52 ETH. The top three CEX with outflows are as follows:· Bybit, with an outflow of 26,300 ETH;· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 18,800 ETH;· Kraken, with an outflow of 3,303.03 ETH.In addition, OKX saw an inflow of 18,700 ETH and ranked first on the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25250</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum falls below $4,000, the mainstream CEX cumulative long liquidation intensity will reach $1.223 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25249</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on Coinglass data, if Ethereum drops below $4000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEX will reach 1.223 billion.Conversely, if Ethereum rebounds above $4300, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEX will reach 1.336 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not precisely display the number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of the contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it reaches a certain position. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will have a more intense response due to a liquidity cascade once it reaches that level.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25249</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Falls Below $113,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25248</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $113,000, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 2.99%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the last 1 hour, the total liquidation across the network was $61.9545 million, with only short positions liquidated totaling $0.7009 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25257</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to Coinglass data, within the past 1 hour, the total liquidation across the network was $61.9545 million. The total long liquidations were $61.2536 million, and the short liquidations were $0.7009 million.The liquidations of Bitcoin amounted to $13.9272 million, while the liquidations of Ethereum reached $18.9156 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25257</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>