<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:45:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bit Digital&apos;s AI Infrastructure Subsidiary Whitefiber Seeks to Raise $132.8 Million Through IPO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22340</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the U.S. listed company Bit Digital (BTBT)&apos;s artificial intelligence infrastructure subsidiary, Whitefiber Inc., is aiming to raise up to $132.8 million through an initial public offering (IPO). The company intends to issue 7.8 million shares of stock with a price ranging from $15 to $17 per share and is projected to determine the IPO pricing during the week commencing August 4th. Whitefiber was separated from Bit Digital and possesses high-performance computing data centers, offering cloud-based High Performance Computing (HPC) Graphics Processing Unit (GPU) services. The company provides cloud services for applications in the development of artificial intelligence and machine learning.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22340</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by &quot;Order System Failure,&quot; HYPE Plunges Over 7% in Nearly 2 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22339</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on market data, HYPE witnessed a drop of over 7% in the past 2 hours and is currently trading at $43.Previously, the Hyperliquid team responded on Discord to the &quot;order system malfunction preventing users from placing trades&quot; by stating that the issue is being investigated and they will promptly share any updates.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22339</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity deposited 12,981 ETH to Coinbase in the past hour, worth approximately $49.7 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22338</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Fidelity transferred 12,981 ETH to Coinbase within nearly 1 hour, with a value of approximately $49.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22338</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyth Network is pleased to announce its support for real-time price data for 85 publicly listed companies in the Hang Seng Index in Hong Kong.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22337</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Pyth Network declared its backing for the real-time price data of 85 listed companies within the Hang Seng Index of Hong Kong. The data source is furnished by institutional-grade market participants and is updated every 400 milliseconds, being published on-chain in real time.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22337</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eToro to Launch Tokenized Stocks on the Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22336</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the online trading platform eToro announced that it will launch a tokenized US stock service on the Ethereum blockchain. This enables users to buy and trade tokenized US stocks on the blockchain as a strategic step towards a tokenized future. During a webinar held on Tuesday, eToro disclosed that it will offer a 24/5 trading service for the initial 100 popular US-listed stocks and ETFs (serving as underlying assets), allowing users to trade outside of traditional market hours. eToro has also formed a partnership with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange Group to launch spot price futures. These futures are currently available in some European markets, with plans to further expand their coverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s PEPE Long Position Partially Liquidated 8 Times in a Row, Losing Nearly $1 Million in the Past Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22334</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, James Wynn&apos;s 10x PEPE long position has consecutively undergone liquidation 8 times. In the past week, he has lost nearly $1 million, and there is only $32,000 left in the wallet.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22334</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Simply buying ETH and holding for three months will be simpler than chasing hot coins on-chain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22335</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio expressed his views on the market trend for the upcoming months. He stated, &quot;In my opinion, after a risk adjustment, the number of coins that can outperform BTC and ETH in the coming months will be quite limited. Certainly, there may be some unexpected meme coins that experience a sudden surge. However, betting on these coins in advance is similar to playing a highly difficult game. Now that the market has reached a relatively high level, I may be more inclined to hold mainstream coins and reduce high-risk speculative trading. Instead of chasing the next hot coin on-chain and experiencing significant volatility, it is much simpler to simply buy and hold ETH for three months without taking any action and then sell it to earn a 50% profit.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22335</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase Raises Robinhood Stock Price Target for 2026, Doubles It to $98</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22333</link>
      <description>July 29th: The price target for Robinhood stock at JPMorgan Chase has been doubled to $98 in 2026. Meanwhile, Robinhood is scheduled to announce its second-quarter earnings on Wednesday. JPMorgan Chase retains a Neutral rating on Robinhood and anticipates that Robinhood will earn $0.31 per share, which is an increase from $0.21 in the same period of the previous year. JPMorgan Chase holds the view that Robinhood&apos;s initiatives in cryptocurrency and tokenized finance will enhance its operational leverage and generate long-term profit potential.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22333</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve July Meeting Voter Count Drops to 11</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22332</link>
      <description>July 29th: Due to personal reasons, Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard will be absent from this week&apos;s policy meeting. As a result, the number of voting members for this interest rate decision will be decreased to 11. Governors Waller and Bowman may have different views and support a rate cut, yet the committee still has a substantial majority to maintain the interest rate at its current level. There is no one to take Governor Brainard&apos;s seat as a substitute. However, the President&apos;s vote can act as a replacement. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22332</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL drops below $180, with a 24-hour decrease of 4.23%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22331</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on HTX market data, SOL dropped below $180, showing a 24-hour percentage change of -4.23%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22331</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>