<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Contract Transaction Whale AguilaTrades Reallocates 4.6M USDT to Open Long Positions for BTC and ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23545</link>
      <description>July 8th. According to on-chain analyst Ai (@ai_9684xtpa), the contract trade whale AguilaTrades deposited 4.6 million USDC as collateral to Hyperliquid 15 minutes ago and has since opened long positions for BTC and ETH. The total position is worth 98.29 million US dollars, with a realized profit of 308,000 US dollars. The specific position information is as follows:BTC: 40x long, holding 530.7497 BTC, entry price $114,856.1ETH: 25x long, holding 10,000 ETH, entry price $3,706</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23545</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB announced the completion of a $9.5 million funding round, with participation from Amber Group.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23544</link>
      <description>July 8th. As per techinasia, BOB, a project focused on constructing a Bitcoin and Ethereum hybrid DeFi chain, declared that it has secured $21 million in funding starting from December 2023.It is reported that BOB obtained $9.5 million in the latest fundraising round. The new investors involved are Anchorage, Amber Group, and Sats Ventures, along with the existing supporters Castle Island Ventures, Ledger, and RockawayX.Castle Island Ventures had previously led BOB&apos;s $10 million seed round of funding.The company recently launched its testnet and collaborated with institutions like Lombard, Amber Digital, and RockawayX to facilitate native Bitcoin DeFi transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Listed Company DL Holdings Plans to Raise Approximately $83 Million to Expand into the Blockchain Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23543</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to The Block, the stock price of Hong Kong-listed financial services group DL Holdings fell by more than 8% on Thursday. The company announced plans to raise 653.3 million Hong Kong dollars (approximately $83.2 million) through a rights issue to finance its blockchain business development.Based on the filings submitted to the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, DL Holdings has entered into subscription and subscription agreements. Selling shareholders will sell shares to at least six buyers at a price of 2.95 Hong Kong dollars per share through a placement agent. Subsequently, the company will immediately repurchase an equal number of new shares at the same price.The shares to be sold in this placement account for approximately 13.58% of the company&apos;s current issued share capital. After the issuance of new shares is completed, this proportion will decrease to around 11.96%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23543</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALLINDOGE Launches Ultra Edition, AI Smart Assistant Enters Utility Stage</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23542</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the AI tool platform ALLINDOGE launched its new Ultra version today. This new version is upgraded with Web3 user needs in mind. It focuses on introducing the MCP module, which supports one-line command completion for on-chain data queries, market analysis, project retrieval, document parsing, and other tasks. It has evolved from a &quot;capable of conversation&quot; intelligent assistant to an &quot;able to execute&quot; one. The main highlights of this update are as follows:· Integrated the MCP module to achieve integrated research and market analysis.· Added historical conversation records to support continuous context interaction.· Supported one-click sharing of conversation content.· Gained access to the document upload and parsing system, and the AI automatically extracts key points.· Optimized the interface for clearer and smoother operation.The ALLINDOGE team stated that the Ultra version is a turning point from &quot;passive queries&quot; to &quot;active service&quot; and will continue to i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23542</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Strategies has released its July report: Total holding of 428,000 SOL tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23541</link>
      <description>July 7th, SOL version. SOL Strategies has officially presented its July funding and validator node operation update report. By July 31st:SOL Holdings: 396,717 SOL (approximately 91.4 million USD)JitoSOL Staked Holdings: 26,440 (approximately 7.4 million USD)Total SOL Holdings: 428,995 SOL (approximately 98.8 million USD)Total Delegated SOL: 3,551,797 SOLNumber of Service Independent Wallets: 5,537Validator Node Continuous Operation Record: The Laine node has achieved a 100% online rate and has been operating smoothly for over 500 days.Highest Achieved Annual Percentage Yield (APY): 7.704% (Orangefin node)Network-wide Average Yield: 7.41%</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: Solana&apos;s OG Token TROLL Holds the Line, New Coin on Base Chain SWIF Surges</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23540</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to GMGN data, within the past 24 hours on the Solana blockchain, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume in the &quot;Hot&quot; section are DeepSeekAI, BOSS, TROLL, SPARK, and MLP. Except for TROLL, all of them are newly listed meme tokens with a low market capitalization and a small number of holders, presenting a higher risk.On the other hand, on the Base chain, in the past 24 hours, the top five in terms of trading volume are mostly well-established projects, namely ZORA, EURC, wstETH, SWIF, and VIRTUAL. Since SWIF has been listed for less than 24 hours, it should be used with caution due to its low market capitalization and potential significant risk.BlockBeats reminds users that most meme coins lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Bitcoin is currently in a post-ATH adjustment phase, with no sufficient evidence to suggest a forming trend of structural fund outflow</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23539</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Glassnode referred to data in its latest Crypto Week in Review report. From a macro perspective, Bitcoin&apos;s current price is above the Short-Term Holder (STH) Cost Basis ($106,000), placing it in a &quot;mild but not overheated&quot; range. This structure is in line with typical bull market characteristics because the STH Cost Basis has always been a key threshold for distinguishing short-term bull/bear trends.Glassnode believes that the market has now entered a post-historic high correction phase. Key level contention will determine the future trend. Investor behavior indicators show that the market is currently in a relatively balanced state. Multiple metrics based on Short-Term Holders (STH) still align with typical bull market trends. Although Bitcoin ETFs have experienced significant outflows, these outflows have been short-term events so far, and there is insufficient evidence to indicate a forming trend of structural fund outflows.The current support below is at the prev</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RWA Register Platform Officially Launches in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23538</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the RWA Registration Platform was officially launched in Hong Kong. This platform was initiated by the Hong Kong Web3 Standardization Association and will offer a full-process service system for the digitization, securitization, and financialization of RWA asset tokenization. On the same day, three Web3 standards were established, namely the &quot;RWA Tokenization Business Guide,&quot; the &quot;RWA Tokenization Technical Specification,&quot; and the &quot;Blockchain-based Stablecoin Cross-border Payment Technical Specification.&quot; (Jinse)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: If Bitcoin&apos;s buying pressure continues to accumulate at a low level, it may set the stage for the next rally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23537</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Glassnode referred to data in its latest crypto weekly report. It indicated that Bitcoin&apos;s price in July retraced from a high of $12.3K to $11.3K. This led to recent new investors being underwater and formed a significant supply cluster with a cost basis above $11.6K. The lower bound of this cluster has been tested multiple times and triggered bounces. However, the decisive breakdown on July 31st caused the price to enter the previously mentioned &quot;empty zone.&quot;Historical data shows that such low liquidity ranges often develop into new accumulation zones. By comparing the UTXO Realized Price Distribution (URPD) on July 31st and August 4th, it can be observed that when the price rebounded from a low of $11.2K, about 120K BTC were absorbed by investors, driving the price back above $11.4K. Nevertheless, the total supply in the range of $11K to $11.6K remains low. Continued accumulation may set the stage for the next upward movement.Despite the accumulation seen over the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address holding 188.2 WBTC for 4 years has been transferred to Binance in the last 2 days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23536</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on on-chain data analyst ChainInfo, a whale address transferred 188.2 WBTC (approximately $21.55 million) that it had been hoarding for 4 years to Binance in the past 2 days, realizing a profit of $10.93 million.It is reported that the address withdrew WBTC from Binance in April 2021 when the price was $56,420. After holding it for 4 years, the whale began to transfer WBTC to Binance 2 days ago, and the final transfer took place 20 minutes ago. The average price at which it transferred to Binance was $114,498.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>