<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:46:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Coin Innovation Technology, HashKey Group, Beosin, and SlowMist jointly launched the Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Professional Committee</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25153</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Yuan Coin Innovation Technology, HashKey Group, Beosin, and SlowMist jointly declared the establishment of the Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Professional Committee (DAAMC). This committee was formed with the support of the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Industry Association (HKVAIA). It is an industry-leading non-profit organization committed to promoting cooperation among regulated financial institutions to formulate and promote first-class Anti-Money Laundering and Combating the Financing of Terrorism (AML/CFT) standards and practices. The aim is to drive the compliant issuance of stablecoins in Hong Kong and enhance the financial integrity within the digital asset ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25153</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odin.fun Co-founder: Hacked Funds Frozen, Audit and Remediation in Progress</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25152</link>
      <description>August 19th, for Odin.fun co-founder Bob Bodily, he stated that certain funds in CEX and tokens have been frozen. Currently, they are collaborating with the authorities to investigate the individuals involved and make efforts to recover the assets. The platform is nearing the completion of audit fixes. Once the audit party gives confirmation, a public report will be released. Before resuming trading, the platform will ensure that user funds are 1:1 fully covered. The team is also dealing with the impact caused by the attacker, removing abnormal transactions and preserving legitimate user transactions. Bob indicated that the resumption of trading will depend on the confirmation of funds, the completion of audits, and the readiness of platform cleanup on three fronts. The timeline has not been determined yet, but the progress is good.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index Drops to 56, Market Still in &apos;Greed&apos; Sentiment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25151</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to Alternative Data, the Crypto Fear and Greed Index for today dropped to 56 (yesterday it was 60), with a weekly average of 68, suggesting that the market still maintains a &quot;greedy&quot; sentiment.Note: The Fear and Greed Index has a threshold ranging from 0 to 100 and encompasses the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Hype (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25151</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Withdraws 361,118 LINK from Binance Again, Worth $8.77 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25150</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale once more withdrew 361,118 LINK from Binance, with a value of $8.77 million.In general, over the past 4 days, this whale has accumulated 1.29 million LINK from Binance, which is worth $31 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25150</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After a Bitcoin Pullback, Market Awaits Fed&apos;s Powell Speech This Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25149</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per Forbes, analyst Ryan Rabaglia mentioned that due to Bitcoin&apos;s recent decline, &quot;everyone&quot; will be observing Federal Reserve Chairman Powell&apos;s speech on Friday, August 22nd, in order to seek clues regarding the central bank officials&apos; policy direction during the September meeting.Ryan Rabaglia, who is a General Partner at Rise Capital Venture Capital Fund, said: &quot;With some mainstream coins reaching or getting close to all-time highs, there has been a substantial profit-taking. There is a crucial event this week - the Jackson Hole Summit - and all attention will be focused on it. In previous summits, we have witnessed the Fed Chairman taking decisive actions, and even explicitly hinting at an interest rate hike or cut. This time as well, it is expected that he will clearly indicate a stance. This summit will lay the groundwork for actions in September, and the market currently generally anticipates a 25 basis point rate cut.&quot;Analyst Bruni stated: &quot;If the comment</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25149</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-chain Yield: Mitosis USDT Pool APY reaches 37.71%, Syrup USDC Pool APY reaches 9.18%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25148</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per the data from DefiLlama, the Total Value Locked (TVL) of SUSDE (Ethena USDe) currently stands at $55.53 billion, having an Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of 7.28% and a unstaking period of 7 days. The TVL of Maple Finance&apos;s Syrup USDC is $22.09 billion with an APY of 9.18%. SUSDS (Sky Lending) has a TVL of $17.47 billion and an APY of 4.75%.In addition, Binance has initiated the first season of the Mitosis (MITO) Booster event today at 8:00. The APY for the BNB pool is as high as 72.91%, and for the USDT pool, it is as high as 37.71%. This event enables users to deposit BNB or USDT into the Simple Yield Mitosis Treasury via the Binance Wallet to receive MITO rewards, with a total reward of 15 million MITO. The event does not have an Alpha Point threshold. Users can redeem assets through the Mitosis DApp. It is important to note that the BNB redemption process may take up to 10 days, and the USDT redemption process may take up to 5 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 05:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25148</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: In a bull market, fluctuations are inevitable. If there is a pullback, consider buying in tranches to lower your cost.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25147</link>
      <description>August 19th: The founder of Linekong Interactive, Wang Feng, tweeted that during a bull market, market fluctuations are an inevitable part. He suggested preparing sufficient funds, entering the market gradually in stages, buying when the price dips, and aiming to accumulate more chips.Previously, Wang Feng declared that he had been buying the dip in Ethereum for three consecutive days.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 04:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25147</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Treasury Corp increased its holdings by 1565 SOL, bringing the total position to 14194 SOL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25146</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the wholly-owned subsidiary SOL Treasury Corp of the French publicly listed company Acheter-Louer.fr increased its holdings by 1565 SOL. As a result, its total holdings reached 14194 SOL, which is approximately worth 2.7 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 04:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25146</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbeat launches aggregator Masterswap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25145</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the native reward layer of the Hyperliquid ecosystem, Hyperbeat, launched the aggregator Masterswap.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 04:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25145</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the U.S. Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net outflow of $1.966 billion, while the Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net outflow of $1.217 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25144</link>
      <description>On August 19th, based on the data from Farside Investors, yesterday the net outflows of the US Ethereum spot ETF and the Bitcoin spot ETF were $1.966 billion and $1.217 billion respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 04:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>