<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:54:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A certain new wallet withdrew 1.35 million ONDO and 1.6 million ENA from Binance.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25389</link>
      <description>August 20th. Based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, a newly established wallet withdrew 1.35 million ONDO from Binance within the past hour. The value of this withdrawal was $1.26 million. Additionally, the wallet withdrew 1.6 million ENA, with a value of $1.03 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25389</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opening: Cryptocurrency Stocks Show Mixed Performance, SharpLink Gaming Up by 0.88%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25387</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on market data, the three major U.S. stock indexes opened in a mixed manner. The Dow Jones Index increased by 0.13%, the S&amp;P 500 Index decreased by 0.08%, and the Nasdaq Composite Index decreased by 0.28%. The stock prices of U.S. crypto companies showed differences. Most Ethereum Treasury companies were trading in an upward trend, including:Circle (CRCL) decreased by 0.27%;Coinbase (COIN) decreased by 0.02%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) decreased by 0.04%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) increased by 1.2%;Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) increased by 0.88%;BTCS Inc (BTCS) increased by 1.04%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25387</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Acquires No-Code Trading Company Capitalise.ai</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25388</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per CoinDesk, the cryptocurrency exchange Kraken has made an acquisition of the no-code trading company Capitalise.ai in order to expand its professional platform. Capitalise.ai is an Israel-based enterprise that focuses on no-code and natural language-based trading automation. The financial details of this transaction have not been made public.This acquisition will enable Kraken Pro users to create, backtest, and automatically execute trading strategies by using everyday language without the need to write code. Kraken intends to launch these new features on the Pro platform later this year.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25388</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: Once interest rates reflect the Fed&apos;s dovish stance, the market will end the year strong in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25386</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Tom Lee, the newly appointed Chairman of the Board of BitMine, released the latest market outlook report. He stated, &quot;As we enter the final third of 2025, the most significant change is the Fed&apos;s transformation towards dovishness. The ISM index is expected to rebound above 50, laying the groundwork for a strong year-end in the market of 2025. The S&amp;P 500 index has already increased by 9% year-to-date, which is an astonishing performance in any year. Looking ahead to the last few months of 2025, it is anticipated that the market will generally continue to maintain a strong momentum.&quot;&quot;In fact, 2025 can be divided into three phases: the first phase is tariff concerns from January to April; the second phase is a V-shaped rebound from April until now; and the third phase is a dovish Fed combined with the recovery of the ISM. Tom Lee believes that the S&amp;P 500 index will reach 6800-7000 points by the end of the year. However, this will not be a linear path. Once interest rat</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25386</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cointel, an AI-native platform, has completed a $7.4 million strategic financing round with Avalanche and Sugafam leading the investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25385</link>
      <description>August 20th: The Cointel, an AI-native platform, has successfully completed a strategic financing round of $7.4 million. This round was led by Avalanche and the Japanese Web3 innovation company Sugafam Inc. Cointel intends to construct a globally scalable platform that focuses on the convergence of artificial intelligence, crypto, and education in order to fulfill the requirements of new users and data-driven traders.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25385</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LazAI Ecosystem AI Agent Launch Platform Lazpad First Batch of AI Companion DAT Asset Lazbubu Open for Minting</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25384</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the Web3-native AI infrastructure protocol LazAI announced that the first batch of AI Companion Data Anchoring Tokens (DAT), Lazbubu, launched on its ecosystem&apos;s AI Agent Launchpad Lazpad, has officially concluded the whitelist event and started minting. Lazbubu Companion DATs, as the first entry point into the LazAI internal ecosystem, are AI intelligent agents with memory, personality, and evolutionary capabilities designed for long-term interaction and value creation. In the &quot;Exploration Zone&quot;, these unminted DATs await users to collectively shape their growth story through on-chain decisions, conversations, and adventure logs.This one-month whitelist event attracted more than 50,000 users. Whitelisted users could unlock DAT blind boxes, randomly revealing Lazbubu DATs with four rarities: Common, Advanced, Rare, and Legendary.It is reported that Lazpad is an on-chain AI Agent Launchpad supported by the LazAI internal incentive ecosystem. It transforms complex AI</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Powell to Uphold Cautious Stance, Potentially Supporting US Dollar in the Short Term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25383</link>
      <description>August 20th. Jane Foley, the foreign exchange strategist at Rabobank, stated in a report that if Federal Reserve Chairman Powell shows caution regarding a rate cut in his forthcoming speech, speculators may unwind their previously held short positions on the US dollar in the short term. Both the market and Rabobank anticipate that the Fed will cut rates in September, which indicates a weakening labor market. However, Foley pointed out that Powell may still be cautious about easing policy when delivering a speech at the Jackson Hole central bank symposium this Friday. This attitude could offer support to the dollar in the short run. Nevertheless, Rabobank still expects the Euro to US Dollar (EUR/USD) to reach 1.20 in the spring of next year as the market anticipates more rate cuts. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25383</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capybobo debuts at WebX 2025, unveiling Web3-native Collectible NFT Apparel IP.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25382</link>
      <description>On August 20th, from the 25th to the 26th of this month, Catizen&apos;s Web3 game Capybobo will be present at the main venue of WebX 2025 in Tokyo and deliver a keynote speech mainly focusing on its upcoming Web3-native trendy IP. Meanwhile, Capybobo will showcase the PYBOBO trendy outfits created based on in-game skins, presenting a brand-new experience that integrates online and offline elements.In addition, Capybobo will also participate in the LINE NEXT &amp; BGW event on August 24th and the OKJ event on August 26th simultaneously. Participants can interact at the booth and have the opportunity to obtain limited Labubu and PYBOBO outfits.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25382</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish publicly listed company PixelFox AB initiates Crypto Reserve Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25381</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the publicly listed company PixelFox AB in Sweden announced the start of a crypto reserve strategy. It plans to gradually allocate a part of its remaining liquidity to investments in blockchain technology and digital assets. The largest share will be allocated to BTC, ETH, and BNB. The company has completed its first investment of 250,000 Swedish Krona in cryptocurrencies. The specific allocation is 50% to staked Ethereum, 20% to Avalanche, 15% to XRP, and 15% to staked Solana.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25381</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Plasma Fixed Savings Quota of 250 million USDT Sold Out, More Quotas May Be Opened Soon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25380</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Binance&apos;s Launchpool launched the earn-as-you-go coin Plasma USDT fixed-term product (with limited time and quantity) at 20:00 (GMT+8) tonight. Within approximately 50 minutes, the $250 million USDT quota was sold out. Binance announced that more quota may be opened soon, and participating users can receive daily USDT rewards and XPL rewards (after TGE).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25380</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>