<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Schiff: Trump Allowing Retirement Funds to Invest in Cryptocurrency Will Worsen America&apos;s Retirement Savings Deficiency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23659</link>
      <description>August 8th, Economist and cryptocurrency critic Peter Schiff tweeted, &quot;Most Americans possess far too little savings to sustain their retirement. By allowing Americans to invest their meager retirement savings from their 401(k) accounts into Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, Trump will only exacerbate this problem.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23659</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb Adds TreeHouse (TREE) KRW Trading Pair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23658</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to official channels, Bithumb has incorporated the TreeHouse (TREE) KRW trading pair.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23658</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the listing of the Korean Won trading pair on Bithumb, TREE experienced a sudden 17% price surge.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23657</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to HTX market data. Because a KRW trading pair was listed on Bithumb, TreeHouse (TREE) witnessed a short-term surge of more than 17% and is now trading at $0.4762.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23657</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Foundation Executive Director: Greater Emphasis Should Be Placed on Any Potential Delay in the Fusaka Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23656</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Tomasz K. Stańczak, the Executive Director of the Ethereum Foundation, tweeted, &quot;The Glamsterdam Upgrade (Q1/Q2 2026) might draw some attention. However, at the same time, we should place more emphasis on any potential delays to the Fusaka Upgrade (Q4 2025). As I have repeatedly stated, if we are unable to achieve a consistent level of coordination to meet milestones on time, then discussing Ethereum&apos;s roadmap and vision becomes meaningless. I am aware that some very talented individuals are working hard to address the issues that are causing the proposed changes to the team&apos;s dates. I hope to see widespread acknowledgment that the timeline is of great importance. Of great importance.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAGS Founder Spends Approximately $800,000 at Auction to Acquire Original Hat Wearing Dog Meme Hat</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23655</link>
      <description>August 8th. Finn, the founder of BAGS, spent 6.8 BTC (about $800,000) to auction off the original hat of the Dogwifhat Meme.The Shiba Inu Achi is the protagonist behind the &quot;Dogwifhat&quot; meme. This is the very first and sole time that the physical hat from this meme has been made accessible to the public. This collectible had never been previously put up for sale before and may not have another chance to be sold in the future. In order to ensure its authenticity and heritage, before the auction, a photo of Achi sitting with its owner while wearing the hat was inscribed onto the Bitcoin blockchain through Ordinals to verify its origin.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23655</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana-based Token V2EX Market Cap Surpasses $20 Million, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23654</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to GMGN data, the on-chain token V2EX on Solana has exceeded a market capitalization of $20 million and reached a new all-time high. Currently, it is valued at $21.6 million with a 24-hour trading volume of $430,000.BlockBeats previously reported that on July 8th, Livid, the founder of the Chinese programmer community V2EX, stated that the $V2EX token would have further interactions with the V2ex community. Currently, about 75% of the total supply is held and has not been sold. The current circulating supply in the market accounts for about 25% of the total supply. The token was created 9 months ago to explore the product Pump.fun. The reason for the token&apos;s graduation (moving to an external exchange) was to add Solana wallet login functionality to the V2EX website to meet the demand for viewing on-chain addresses, inadvertently causing the internal exchange to be filled up and moved to an external exchange.Livid stated that Solana-logged-in or bonded users</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23654</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About $1.75 billion worth of ETH is currently queued to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $150 million worth of ETH is waiting to join.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23653</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, it is reported that the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is 445,845 ETH, which is approximately worth $1.75 billion. The recent peak of the exit queue was 744,000 ETH. The waiting time for the exit queue is approximately 7 days and 18 hours.Meanwhile, there are about 39,370 ETH queued to join the network, which is approximately worth $150 million. This is a significant decrease from the recent peak of 435,000 ETH. The anticipated activation delay is around 16 hours and 24 minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23653</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has accumulated 171,015 ETH in the past 4 days, equivalent to around $670 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23652</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to on-chain analyst Wu Ji, a whale has accumulated a total of 171,015 ETH, which is worth an astonishing $670 million within the past 4 days through 6 addresses. In just the past 1 hour alone, they have received 23,424 ETH ($91.65 million).They utilized the address 0x0c3...40e to create a wallet via BitGo and then purchased and received ETH from institutional business platforms like FalconX, Galaxy Digital, and BitGo. Currently, they have created a total of 6 wallets to receive the accumulated 171,015 ETH ($670 million), with an average price of $3,669 per ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23652</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase: Expects the Federal Reserve to begin cutting interest rates in September 2025, with three 25 basis point reductions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23651</link>
      <description>On August 8th, JPMorgan Chase announced that it anticipates the Fed to commence cutting interest rates in September 2025, with three reductions each of 25 basis points. This contrasts with the previous forecast of only one rate cut in December. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 05:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23651</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Bets Against the Trend by Increasing ETH Short Position, Single Address Faces Unrealized Loss of Over $16 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23650</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight, as ETH once again rose to $4000, some whales chose to increase their short positions against the trend, and their current unrealized losses continued to expand. These include:The whale with the address starting with 0x20c2d9 added $870,000 to their ETH short position, and the current unrealized loss is -$16.78 million (liquidation price $4,903).The whale with the address starting with 0x507561 added $830,000 to their ETH short position, and the current unrealized loss is -$2.16 million (liquidation price $4,488).The whale with the address starting with 0x8af700 added $950,000 to their XRP short position, and the current unrealized loss is -$7.75 million (liquidation price $5.693).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 04:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23650</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>