<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:31:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance HODLer Airdrop Goes Live on OpenLedger (OPEN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27845</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Binance is glad to declare that the 36th project to be launched on the HODLer Airdrops page is OpenLedger (OPEN), an AI blockchain project aiming to unlock liquidity for the monetization of data, models, and intelligent agents.During the time from 2025-08-18 00:00 (UTC) to 2025-08-21 23:59 (UTC), users who have staked BNB in Simple Earn (either flexible or locked) and/or on-chain staking products will receive the airdrop distribution. The details of the HODLer Airdrops will be announced within 24 hours, and the new tokens will be delivered to users&apos; spot accounts at least 1 hour before trading begins.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain new address has acquired 309,000 HYPE tokens and staked them, totaling over $14 million in value.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27844</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on on-chain data, a newly established wallet has just withdrawn 309,000 HYPE tokens (approximately $14.2 million) from KuCoin and pledged them with the FalconX &lt;&gt; Chorus One validator.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27844</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha New Airdrop SHARDS Point Threshold Announcement: At Least 220 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27843</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to official information, Binance Alpha is the first platform to list WORLDSHARDS (SHARDS), and Alpha trading will commence on September 5, 2025, at 19:00 (UTC+8).After the trading begins, users who hold at least 220 Binance Alpha Points can claim 4,000 SHARDS tokens as an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s &apos;Pump Signal&apos; Meme Coin, with a market cap of only $157,000, has now surged over 240%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27842</link>
      <description>On September 5th, James Wynn made a post on a social media platform, stating, &quot;Can someone come and serve as the CTO of this coin? $WIFE. I will assist in promoting it. I truly like this narrative. However, the team has ceased posting and responding.&quot; At the moment he made the post, the meme coin had a market capitalization of only $157,000. Approximately 40 minutes later, the token&apos;s market capitalization surged by more than 240% to $459,000.James Wynn then said, &quot;I hold $WIFE and $GOAT on Solana. I firmly believe that I will never purchase any shitcoin on Solana again. I will continue to hold them and provide support at the appropriate time, whether they reach the moon or return to dust. My current main focus will be on AI trading bots, my personal trading, and the Ethereum ecosystem.&quot;Currently, James Wynn is actively attempting to obtain the X account of the meme coin $WIFE.BlockBeats reminds users: Most meme coins have no practical applications and experience significant pric</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27842</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Past $112,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27841</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin has rebounded and exceeded $112,000, registering a 24-hour gain of 1.67%. Ethereum has surpassed $4,350, and the 24-hour loss has narrowed to 0.43%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27841</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US August non-farm payroll data and unemployment rate will be released tonight at 8:30 PM.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27840</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics will announce the U.S. August seasonally adjusted nonfarm payroll data and the U.S. August unemployment rate data at 20:30 this evening. The details include:· The U.S. August Seasonally Adjusted Nonfarm Payrolls (in thousands): Expected is 7.5, and the previous value was 7.3. This data reflects the changes in the number of people employed in the U.S. nonfarm sector, excluding the agricultural sector. It is obtained through sampling surveys of U.S. businesses, government agencies, and nonfarm sectors. On the first Friday of each month, the U.S. Department of Labor releases the nonfarm payroll data for the previous month.· The U.S. August Unemployment Rate: Expected is 4.30%, and the previous value was 4.20%. This data represents the percentage of the unemployed population in the labor force during a specific period (the number of job seekers who are willing to work but still do not have a job within the total employed population du</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A criminal group in Fujian, China is using USDT for money laundering, with involved transactions totaling over 13.3 billion RMB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27839</link>
      <description>September 5th. In the first half of this year, the People&apos;s Court of Hanjiang District, Fujian Province, China, handed down a ruling in a criminal case related to virtual currency. Yan, Zheng, Lin and others established an underground foreign exchange trading network using the virtual currency USDT (Tether). They solicited customers through overseas chat applications and illegally exchanged RMB and foreign currency using &quot;U coins&quot; as a medium. The bank account transactions involved exceeded 13.3 billion RMB. It was found that the amount of illegal foreign exchange transactions was 25.62 million RMB. The group also withdrew cash exceeding 478 million RMB from banks in various places in Fujian Province, purchased &quot;U coins&quot;, transferred them to upstream criminal wallets to &quot;launder&quot; cross-border crime proceeds and earned the price difference.Suspect Lin denied all criminal facts after being brought to justice. The court guided the public security organs to extract three key voice record</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27839</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Strategy&apos;s profitability level has met the S&amp;P 500 inclusion criteria. If included, it will bring in $16 billion in liquidity.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27838</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to Bloomberg, with regard to Strategy, as it recorded $14 billion in unrealized gains in the last quarter, it has theoretically met the profitability requirement for inclusion in the S&amp;P 500. If included, passive funds tracking the index would be required to passively purchase around 50 million shares, which would amount to approximately $16 billion at the current price. This would lead institutional passive holders to hold around $70 billion of its Bitcoin reserves.Although Strategy had already been included in the Nasdaq 100 by the end of 2024, the S&amp;P 500 has more stringent requirements regarding liquidity, market capitalization (no less than $227 billion), earnings history, and industry balance. The final decision still depends on the committee&apos;s judgment.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27838</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha New Airdrop BOOST Point Threshold is 220 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27837</link>
      <description>September 5th. As per an official announcement, the trading for the Binance Alpha new airdrop project BOOST is set to commence on September 5, 2025, at 08:00 (UTC). Once trading begins, users possessing at least 220 Alpha points will be qualified to receive an airdrop of 640 BOOST tokens on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the reward pool is not fully distributed, the points threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27837</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC: Hong Kong May See a Renminbi Stablecoin in the Future, with Some Large State-owned Enterprises Actively Exploring Stablecoin Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27836</link>
      <description>September 5th. According to the Hong Kong Economic Times, Liu Jing, the Chief Economist of HSBC Global Asset Management in the Greater China region, stated in his speech at the Lujiazui Forum in June that PBOC Governor Pan Gongsheng mentioned the establishment of an international operation center for the digital RMB. Meanwhile, some large central enterprises are actively exploring the applications of stablecoins. When Chinese enterprises invest in Belt and Road emerging markets, they often face issues such as local currency volatility and a lack of hedging tools. In such cases, these enterprises may explore issuing their own RMB stablecoins to assist in investing in emerging markets.Liu Jing pointed out that when multiple Chinese enterprises issue RMB stablecoins, the digital RMB may serve as an intermediary connecting various RMB stablecoins, which will contribute to the expansion of the international usage of the RMB.She further stated that Hong Kong, considering its cooperation</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27836</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>