<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:04:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea will share cryptocurrency trading information starting next year, with data of overseas investors included in the supervision of the National Tax Service.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27249</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to South Korean media reports, the South Korean government is set to commence from next year. Based on the Common Reporting Standard for Crypto-Asset Financial Account Information (CARF), it will promote domestic cryptocurrency exchanges to share transaction information with foreign (non-resident) investors. Meanwhile, the transaction details of domestic investors on foreign exchanges will also be reported to the National Tax Service. Tax authorities in each country will be able to access the overseas transaction information of their domestic investors through the OECD system. Although the official start date for information sharing is 2027, transaction data from next year has already been incorporated into the sharing and reporting scope.The National Tax Service of South Korea has stipulated that overseas financial accounts holding stocks, deposits, or cryptocurrency with a total value of over 500 million Korean won need to be declared voluntarily. The am</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27249</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 133.33 million WLFI to Binance, equivalent to around $32.21 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27248</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale deposited 133.33 million WLFI tokens into Binance, with an approximate value of $32.21 million.The whale used 10 million USDT to participate in the WLFI presale on January 19, 2025, and obtained 666.66 million WLFI tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 3,158,000 USDC into Hyperliquid to short HYPE with 1x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27247</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale deposited 3.158 million USDC into Hyperliquid and initiated a HYPE short position with a leverage of 1x.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27247</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot Gold Breaks $3500/oz, Hits Another All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27246</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, based on market data, physical gold surged to $3,500 per ounce, reaching a new record high. It has gained approximately $875 year-to-date. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27246</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale moonmanifest sold 10 million WLFI tokens, with an average price of $0.21 each</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27245</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to on-chain data analyst Yanjing Monitoring. WLFI investor @moonmanifest47 claimed the unlocked 200 million WLFI tokens (approximately $59.45 million) last night. And 5 hours ago, they sold 10 million WLFI, exchanging it for $2.1 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27245</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global WLFI Contract Position: $9.79 BillionLargest Liquidation in 24h: $27.81 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27244</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to Coinglass data, the present total WLFI contract position throughout the network is currently reported to be $9.79 billion, and $27.81 million has been liquidated within the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27244</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;The Smiths&quot; Director to Helm New Film &quot;Killing Satoshi Nakamoto,&quot; Expected to Release in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27243</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per the report from financefeeds (https://www.financefeeds.com), Pete Davidson and Casey Affleck are set to star in &quot;Killing Satoshi&quot;, a conspiracy thriller film directed by Doug Liman, who is renowned for &quot;The Bourne Identity&quot;. This film draws inspiration from the enigmatic story surrounding the anonymous founder of Bitcoin and is anticipated to be released in 2026.According to the producers, the movie will merge political intrigue, advanced espionage, and global power struggles, depicting a confrontation among governments, Wall Street, and Silicon Valley for the control of the world&apos;s monetary system. Producer Ryan Kavanaugh has characterized the project as a fintech-themed drama similar to &quot;The Social Network&quot;.&quot;Killing Satoshi&quot; will witness director Liman returning to this genre following &quot;Mr. &amp; Mrs. Smith&quot; and &quot;Edge of Tomorrow&quot;. Filming is scheduled to commence in 2025. The project is being showcased at film markets in Toronto and Berlin, with insiders dis</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27243</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>glassnode: Bitcoin HODLers Sell-off Accelerates in Recent Weeks, But Remains Below Last Year&apos;s Peak</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27242</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, glassnode put out an article indicating that Bitcoin Long-Term Holders (LTH) have sped up their selling in recent weeks, and the 14-day Simple Moving Average (SMA) is continuously going up. Nevertheless, the overall activity remains within the normal range for this cycle, which is much lower than the peak witnessed in October-November 2024.This latest increase in selling is mainly due to a single event: last Friday, long-term holders sold around 97,000 BTC, setting the highest single-day selling volume this year and causing a notable spike in smoothed selling activity.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27242</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider: Revolut Launches Employee Secondary Share Sale, Company Valuation Reaches $75 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27241</link>
      <description>September 2nd. According to Reuters, sources disclosed on Monday that the UK financial technology giant Revolut has initiated an employee secondary stock sale, which has boosted its valuation to $75 billion. The London-based company is intensifying its expansion efforts in order to challenge larger traditional banks.A Revolut spokesperson stated in an email on Monday: &quot;The employee secondary stock sale is in progress, and we will not provide any further comments until it is completed.&quot; Bloomberg News reported that in this round of transactions, Revolut was priced at $1381.06 per share.In April of this year, the fintech company reported that its annual profit more than doubled, mainly driven by strong cryptocurrency trading, interest income, and card fees, and it indicated plans to operate as a UK bank starting from this year.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 01:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27241</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>《Financial Times》: Trump Family Criticized by Democrats for Involvement in Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27240</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as reported by the Financial Times, the Trump family has come under criticism from Democrats and others due to their involvement in cryptocurrency.U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren and Congressman Maxine Waters previously stated in a letter: &quot;The Trump family&apos;s financial interest in World Liberty Financial presents an unprecedented conflict of interest.&quot;They further added that this has given the Trump administration a &quot;clear incentive&quot; to direct regulatory bodies, such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), to adopt a pro-cryptocurrency stance, which would directly benefit the president&apos;s family.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>