<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Traders Trim Bets on Fed Rate Cut, Still Expect Cut in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24780</link>
      <description>August 15: Traders reduced their wagers on a Fed rate cut; however, they still anticipate a rate cut in September and another one in 2025. (FX Street)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24780</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Mester: Latest PPI, CPI Inflation Data Cause for Concern</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24779</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the Fed&apos;s Gullspie stated that the recent PPI and CPI inflation data are of concern. (Xinhua Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24779</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Retail Sales MoM July 0.5%, Expected 0.5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24778</link>
      <description>On August 15th, in the US, July Retail Sales Month-on-Month was 0.5%, which was in line with the expected 0.5%. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24778</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays: Powell&apos;s Hawkish Stance Will Not be Changed by Jobs Data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24777</link>
      <description>On Friday, Barclays Bank stated that although the market anticipates a Fed rate cut in September, the recent US employment data is unlikely to influence Fed Chair Jerome Powell&apos;s cautious attitude towards interest rates. The bank expects only a 25-basis-point cut in December this year and believes that investors are overly optimistic about a September rate cut, misinterpreting the Fed&apos;s perspective on the strength of the labor market.Powell recently indicated that monetary policy is &quot;only moderately restrictive&quot; and the labor market is &quot;robust.&quot; Even with the deceleration in July job growth and a 4.2% unemployment rate, Barclays has not detected any indications of a change in stance from hawkish Fed officials. The decision on a September rate cut remains uncertain, and the bank will pay attention to speeches at the Jackson Hole conference for clues.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24777</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink Announces Q2 Performance Report: Currently Holding 728,804 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24776</link>
      <description>August 15th. As per official channels, SharpLink Gaming, Inc. (Nasdaq: SBET) announced today its quarterly financial results as of June 30, 2025, and gave an update on the swift expansion of the company&apos;s Ethereum asset strategy.SharpLink has raised more than $2.6 billion by means such as PIPE, At-The-Market (ATM) offerings, and Registered Direct offerings to finance the ETH acquisitions. The company has acquired and now possesses 728,804 ETH.SharpLink has nearly completely staked all of the company&apos;s held ETH and has accumulated around 1326 ETH in rewards up to now.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetix to Return to Ethereum Mainnet, Introducing Layer 2 Order Matching for a Perpetual Contract DEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24775</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Kain Warwick, the founder of Synthetix and Infinex, posted on social media, indicating that Synthetix is speeding up its return to the Ethereum mainnet. The goal is to build a modern and high-performance perpetual contract decentralized trading platform. After two years of development, the team has confirmed that the off-chain order matching combined with a batch settlement engine and with funds fully reserved on the mainnet is currently the optimal design solution.The Synthetix team has completed the integration, significantly improved coordination capabilities, and rekindled entrepreneurial enthusiasm. They are committed to reshaping Synthetix into one of the top decentralized trading platforms in the EVM ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24775</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Reservoir (DAM) and open airdrop claiming to eligible users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24774</link>
      <description>On August 15, according to official channels, Binance Alpha is set to list Reservoir (DAM).The Alpha spot trading will become operational on August 18, 2025, at 11:00 (UTC).The Alpha contract trading will commence on August 18, 2025, at 12:30 (UTC).Qualified users can participate in the airdrop of Alpha tokens by leveraging Alpha Points on the Binance Alpha activity page once trading gets underway. Further details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24774</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey: Majority of Economists Expect the Fed to Cut Interest Rates in September, with Another Cut Later This Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24773</link>
      <description>August 15th - The majority of economists surveyed by Reuters anticipate that the Federal Reserve will initiate the first interest rate cut this year in September. It is followed by another cut before the end of the year, which is regarded as the base case scenario. In the current market environment, concerns about the well-being of the U.S. economy are on the rise.Among the 110 respondents, 67 individuals (61%) foresee that the Fed will reduce the benchmark interest rate by 25 basis points to 4.0% - 4.25% in September, marking the first cut this year. This is an increase from 53% in the July survey, with one person expecting a 50 basis point hike. The remaining 42 participants believe that the Fed will maintain the interest rates unchanged. More than 60% of the respondents (68 out of 110) expect one to two rate cuts this year, similar to the previous month. However, there is no agreement on the level of the federal funds rate by the end of 2025.Furthermore, 68% of the respondents a</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24773</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Analyst: Bitcoin and Ethereum Spot ETFs&apos; Total Trading Volume Yesterday on Par with Apple Stock</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24772</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas stated on social media that the combined trading volume of Ethereum and Bitcoin spot ETFs the previous day was $11.5 billion, which was on a par with the trading volume of Apple&apos;s stock.According to Rockflow data, the trading volume of Apple the previous day reached $12.083 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24772</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital has completed a $1.4 billion project financing to accelerate the development of the Helios AI data center.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24771</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as per official channels, Galaxy Digital Inc. (Nasdaq: GLXY) declared that it has successfully completed a $1.4 billion project financing. This is intended to support the continuous development of its Helios data center campus located in western Texas. The financing will cover the initial renovation and expansion work at Helios and provide the initial power supply for its Artificial Intelligence (AI) and High-Performance Computing (HPC) business. This supply will be delivered through a long-term agreement with CoreWeave Inc.Galaxy has allocated $350 million to fulfill the equity requirements, while the remaining construction costs will be financed through debt. The $1.4 billion debt financing amounts to 80% of the loan-to-cost ratio and has a term of 36 months. It is secured by all assets related to the first-phase construction of Helios.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>