<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:33:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan Governor: The spread of stablecoins has a significant impact, such as affecting transactions outside of traditional banking</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22604</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bank of Japan Governor Kuroda stated: The spread of stablecoins has a significant impact. For instance, it affects transactions that take place outside traditional banks. (Xinhua News)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22604</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Move: Over 34.7M USDC Withdrawn in a Single Transaction, One Address Reversed Deposited 20.53M USDC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22603</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight at https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/trade, multiple whales have carried out large-scale withdrawal operations within the past 24 hours. One whale address has deposited 20.53 million USDC:The whale with the address starting with 0x6fCaD3 has withdrawn a total of 3.47 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0x477296 has withdrawn a total of 7.277 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0x2BDF1a withdrew approximately 1.5 million USDC in the last 1 hour;The whale with the address starting with 0x47729 has withdrawn a total of 5.776 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0x8d0E34 has withdrawn approximately 5 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0xECB63c has deposited approximately 20.53 million USDC in the last 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22603</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Fed Sees First Dual Dissent in 30 Years, BTC Quickly Rebounds After Fed Statement, $117,000 Holds as Short-Term Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22602</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as was anticipated, the Federal Reserve maintained the interest rates at their current levels. Nevertheless, during the FOMC meeting, two governors appointed by Trump (Waller and Bowman) surprisingly cast dissenting votes, which had not occurred for more than 30 years. These two individuals believe that the current policy is overly restrictive. Chairman Powell stated that no decision has been made regarding the September meeting yet, but the inflation pressure caused by tariffs may be a short-term occurrence. The language of the Fed still maintains a hawkish stance but also emphasizes that economic growth is decelerating and that policy risks coexist.On July 31st, in the early morning, the price of BTC plummeted to below 116,000, breaking through a significant liquidity band before rebounding rapidly. Within a few hours, it regained the lost ground and rose above 117,000, indicating strong buying support below. Currently, the price has entered a high-density liquidity z</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22602</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 wallets from the Satoshi era were activated after 15.3 years of dormancy, consolidating 250 BTC to 2 new addresses</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22601</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as monitored by OnchainLens, 5 wallet addresses from the Satoshi era (which are likely owned by the same entity) that had been inactive for 15.3 years consolidated 250 BTC with a value of $29.64 million into 2 new addresses.Addresses:- bc1qng4nps9ye7e5pfnd9hy687fygjgr3pq5xhsu4a- bc1q6n53469l6evqs05apy49pm7r0df0rxhv8cxndj</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22601</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin Poised to Hit $125,000 Based on Short-Term Holder Cost Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22600</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the crypto analyst @ali_charts presented a chart analysis indicating that as long as Bitcoin&apos;s support level of $105,450 is maintained. According to the short-term holder cost basis, it is anticipated to keep rising to $125,230, and there is even a possibility of reaching $141,770.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list PlaysOut (PLAY) with an airdrop threshold of 200 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22599</link>
      <description>July 31st. Binance Alpha is set to launch PlaysOut (PLAY). Users possessing at least 200 Alpha points will be eligible to receive an airdrop of 1600 PLAY tokens. In case the rewards are not completely distributed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. The act of claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points.Binance Alpha exchange platform will list PlaysOut (PLAY) on July 31, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). Binance Futures platform will list PlaysOut (PLAY) on July 31, 2025, at 17:30 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22599</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish publicly listed company Fragbite Group increases its holdings by 2.7 BTC, bringing the total holding to 7 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22598</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per NLNico&apos;s monitoring, the Swedish-listed company Fragbite Group augmented its holdings of BTC by 2.7 coins, resulting in a total holding of 7 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22598</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address containing 50 BTC has just been activated after 15.3 years of dormancy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22597</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as monitored by Whale Alert, an address holding 50 BTC (approximately $5.91 million) has just been activated following 15.3 years of being dormant.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22597</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Over the past year, BTC whales have locked in significant profits, but strong demand from new entrants has supported the market&apos;s continued growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22596</link>
      <description>On July 31st, CryptoQuant analyst Axel released data on social media, stating that over the past year, large holders have locked in substantial profits. Whale addresses holding more than 1000 bitcoins have seen a decrease of 502,000 bitcoins. Meanwhile, institutional investor demand has played a supporting role in market resilience and continued growth. In essence, over the past year, we have constantly witnessed strong demand for tokens from newly entered funds.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22596</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fosun-backed Finloop Completes Multi-Million Dollar Series A Funding Round with Participation from Solana Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22595</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to Finloop, a technology firm under Fosun&apos;s Star Road Technology. It has recently completed a nearly multimillion-dollar Series A financing round. The investors include the Solana Foundation and other Web3 industry organizations.This round of financing will be utilized to swiftly build and enhance the company&apos;s Web5 new business ecosystem - RWA (Real World Assets). It will also enhance its comprehensive ability to integrate fiat currency, stablecoins, and digital assets. Furthermore, it will provide financial institutions with a one-stop technology solution that connects the traditional financial and digital asset worlds.According to the introduction, the strategic concept of Star Road Technology is based on Web5. Its business model mainly supports B2B service platforms for all types of financial products. It achieves this by supporting full-category products from Web2 (such as cash management, public funds, private funds, bonds, bills, insurance, etc.) and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22595</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>