<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:55:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>One week after &quot;selling the top,&quot; the ETH whale has increased their position by $20 million in ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24510</link>
      <description>On August 14th, according to Ember Monitor, an ETH Whale purchased an extra 4,201 ETH with 20 million USDT in the past half an hour.A week ago, after selling ETH at a price of $3,835, the whale has now repurchased 14,931 ETH with 70.596 million USDT today. The average price is $4,728.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase DEX has first opened up to 1% of users, and will gradually expand coverage in the future</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24509</link>
      <description>On August 14th, the newly appointed listing team leader of Coinbase, shaaa, declared that Coinbase DEX has already been made accessible to 1% of users and will gradually expand to a greater number of users in the future.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: Standard Chartered&apos;s Ethereum Year-End Target of $7500 is &apos;Lowball&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24508</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Tom Lee, the newly appointed chairman of BitMine, responded on the X platform regarding &quot;Standard Chartered Bank raising Ethereum&apos;s year-end price expectation to $7500&quot;, stating that this price target might be conservative.Before this news, Tom Lee had stated that based on the fundamental valuation of the Ethereum network, the fair price of ETH is $15,000, while the current price is $3,700.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&apos;s company SpaceX&apos;s holdings of Bitcoin have surpassed $1 billion in value</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24507</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on Arkham data, the value of BTC held by Elon Musk&apos;s SpaceX has exceeded $1 billion.The data indicates that SpaceX holds a total of 8,285 BTC. It first acquired BTC on December 31, 2020, and has been holding it since completing its last purchase on June 10, 2022.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>spacex</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenidge Mining Company recorded a net loss of $4.1 million in the second quarter, producing 110 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24504</link>
      <description>On August 14th, the Nasdaq-listed Bitcoin mining company Greenidge Generation Holdings disclosed its second-quarter financial results. The total revenue reached $12.9 million. It had a net loss of $4.1 million. The total Bitcoin production was 110 BTC. The cryptocurrency mining revenue was $4.2 million, and the data center hosting revenue was $6 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit&apos;s 24-hour Trading Volume Drops by 15.6%: XRP, ETH, BTC Currently Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24506</link>
      <description>On August 14th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit has dropped to $3.906 billion, experiencing a 15.6% decrease. Among them, the XRP/KRW trading pair held the largest trading volume share at 15.57%, and the other top five were: ETH, BTC, SOL, DOGE.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jump Crypto announces its participation as an engineering and network contributor to DoubleZero</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24505</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Jump Crypto made an announcement that it has now become a contributor to DoubleZero&apos;s engineering and network.Furthermore, Jump Crypto indicated that it is actively contributing to the launch of the DoubleZero network by taking part in the DoubleZero testnet and the mainnet Beta network. The network is scheduled to officially go live this fall.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24505</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethereum Whale Who Shorted 20x Liquidates Shorts to Avoid Liquidation, Currently Facing $18 Million in Unrealized Losses</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24502</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a 20x short Ethereum whale this morning managed to avoid liquidation by reducing its short position. As of the time of this writing, its short position reached 10,000 ETH, and the liquidation price was $5680.It is reported that this whale has already incurred a loss of $9.88 million in this ETH (20x) short position and still has approximately $18 million in unrealized losses.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins CEO: The brand will collaborate with a Fortune Global 100 company, and will also announce six major partnership deals this year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24503</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Luca Netz, the CEO of Pudgy Penguins, stated in an interview with Odaily BlockBeats that the &quot;next partner of Pudgy Penguin is a top 100 global company, which is extremely explosive. You definitely can&apos;t guess, but I can guarantee that this will definitely be explosive news.&quot; Additionally, within the remaining time of this year, Pudgy Penguins is likely to announce six heavyweight collaborations.Furthermore, regarding the timing of Abstract Chain&apos;s coin issuance, Luca Netz said, &quot;When Abstract is officially launched, everyone should be able to clearly sense that this is a Top 4 public chain in the crypto space. If we can&apos;t achieve that, there is no need to issue coins. For us, the token must be able to create a wealth effect and take us to a new level instead of issuing just for the sake of issuing.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit operator partners with Vietnam&apos;s MB Bank to build the country&apos;s first cryptocurrency exchange platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24501</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to The Korea Herald, on August 13th in Seoul, South Korea&apos;s largest cryptocurrency exchange platform operator Dunamu and the Vietnam Military Commercial Joint Stock Bank (MB Bank) signed a Memorandum of Understanding. This is to collaborate on establishing Vietnam&apos;s first local digital asset exchange.Based on the agreement, Dunamu will serve as MB Bank&apos;s key strategic partner, providing technological and infrastructure support. It will also offer advice on regulatory compliance, investor protection, and talent development. This move comes after a significant development in Vietnam following the country&apos;s passage of the &quot;Digital Technology Industry Law&quot; in July this year.Data indicates that Vietnam currently has more than 20 million digital asset holders, with a trading volume exceeding $800 billion, making it the fifth-largest recipient of blockchain asset inflows globally. As one of Vietnam&apos;s top five banks, MB Bank has 33 million users and total asse</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>