<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:07:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Bank of Japan Keeps Interest Rate Unchanged, in Line with Market Expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22578</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the Bank of Japan maintained its benchmark interest rate at 0.5%, having remained unchanged for four consecutive meetings, which was in line with market expectations. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22578</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale address has withdrawn a total of 113,000 ETH from FalconX over the past 6 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22576</link>
      <description>On July 31, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a whale address has withdrawn a cumulative total of 113028.97 ETH from FalconX within the past 6 days. The value of these withdrawals is $424 million. The average transfer price was $3752, and the current unrealized profit amounts to $12.044 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will support the Injective (INJ) network upgrade and hard fork</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22577</link>
      <description>July 31st. According to an official announcement, Binance is anticipated to halt the deposit and withdrawal of tokens for the Injective (INJ) Network on July 31, 2025, at 21:00 (UTC+8) in order to support its network upgrade and hard fork. This measure is designed to offer users a better experience. The project team will carry out the network upgrade and hard fork at block height 127,250,000 (estimated to be at 22:00 on July 31, 2025, UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22577</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Layer AI Token BNKR Surpasses $85 Million Market Cap, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22575</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to GMGN data, the Base Layer AI token BankrCoin (BNKR) has exceeded a market capitalization of $85 million. It is currently at $85.24 million, reaching an all-time high, with a 24-hour growth rate of 41.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22575</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cryptofinance Company&apos;s cumulative market value has surged to $160 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22574</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as reported by The Block, as of the present time, the cumulative market value of publicly traded companies that hold cryptocurrency has reached $160 billion. This is a notable increase from approximately $90 billion in early 2024, indicating a new trend where investors are obtaining crypto exposure through equities.This six-month growth reflects a general shift in corporate treasury management strategies. An increasing number of companies are regarding digital assets as legitimate assets on their balance sheets. As the market adjusts to this emerging trend, many companies have witnessed a substantial double-digit increase in their stock prices after announcing their crypto asset allocations.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22574</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Swing Whale Sells All ETH, Profits $1.62 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22572</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a particular swing trader liquidated their ETH holdings on June 25th. These holdings were purchased at an average price of $2451.6. The sell order was carried out at an average price of $3268.19, thereby achieving a profit of $1.62 million in this swing trade.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22572</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American singer George Jones&apos;s widow targeted in theft plot by ex-boyfriend, loses 17 million XRP</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22571</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to FinanceFeeds, Nancy Jones, the widow of the American country music legend George Jones, became a victim of a scam masterminded by her ex-boyfriend Kirk West, losing XRP worth $17 million.West was arrested in July 2025. It is reported that he took advantage of his access to Nancy Jones&apos;s assets to steal cash and a hardware wallet. Court documents indicate that on June 26, 2025, West stole more than $400,000 in cash and a Ledger hardware wallet containing over 5.5 million XRP tokens from two safes in Nancy Jones&apos;s Franklin residence.Kirk West, 58 years old, met Nancy Jones shortly after George Jones&apos;s death in 2013. He pretended to be wealthy and quickly got into a romantic relationship with Nancy, moving into her residence. Court documents reveal that West had a history of financial deception. He was convicted of bank fraud in 2016, and at that time, Nancy covered his debts. West pretended to be very knowledgeable about cryptocurrency and persuaded</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22571</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both co-founders of Samourai Wallet face up to 5 years in prison</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22573</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per Decrypt&apos;s report, Keonne Rodriguez and William Lonergan Hill, the two co-founders of the cryptocurrency mixing service Samourai Wallet, admitted on Wednesday that they had conspired to operate an unlicensed money transmitting business and were facing a maximum prison term of 5 years.As part of a plea agreement, the U.S. Department of Justice agreed to drop more serious money laundering charges. According to the DOJ&apos;s sentencing guidelines, these charges could have carried a maximum sentence of 20 years in prison. The charge of operating an illegal money transmitting business has a maximum sentence of 5 years in prison.Both individuals initially pleaded not guilty to the charges, but court documents indicate that they have since changed their pleas to guilty.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22573</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun will take a Blue Origin spaceship to complete a space flight on August 3rd.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22570</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, announced on the X Platform that he has confirmed his spaceflight on Blue Origin&apos;s New Shepard, which is scheduled for August 3, 2025. He is set to become the youngest Chinese astronaut in history.In 2021, Justin Sun successfully bid $28 million for a seat on the first crewed flight of New Shepard and donated all the proceeds to Blue Origin&apos;s &quot;Club for the Future&quot; to support STEM education for young people worldwide.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22570</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado Cash Co-founder Lawsuit Enters Jury Deliberation Phase, Could Redefine Developer Legal Liability</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22569</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as reported by Cointelegraph, following the completion of the prosecution and defense&apos;s closing arguments on Wednesday, the jury will determine the outcome for Roman Storm, the co-founder of the cryptocurrency mixing service Tornado Cash.Closing arguments represent the final stage of a trial. During this stage, both parties summarize the case in front of a judge or jury, present their stances, and make a final attempt to persuade the decision-maker to rule in their favor.Storm is currently on trial in the federal court of the Southern District of New York. This case has the potential to set a legal precedent regarding the extent of responsibility that developers should bear when their created decentralized software is used illegally.The U.S. prosecution has accused Storm of conspiracy to launder money, violating U.S. sanctions, and operating an unlicensed money transmitting business. If convicted, he could face a maximum prison term of 40 years. The judge has provid</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22569</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>