<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Binance Whale Community Shows Consistent Preference for ETH, Diverges on BTC&apos;s Outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27798</link>
      <description>September 5th: On-chain data analyst Murphy released an article clarifying the divergence and consensus among Binance whales after the mainstream stablecoin balance on Binance witnessed a rapid growth. From August 13th to September 3rd, Binance&apos;s BTC balance increased by 7,709 coins. There exist two whale groups on Binance, with transaction sizes ranging from $1 million to $10 million and over $10 million respectively. Currently, these two groups are in a &quot;conflict.&quot; In April this year, these two forces were in alignment during withdrawals, but differences emerged after August 13th. Smaller whales have been continuously depositing BTC into Binance, while larger whale groups have been withdrawing BTC. In terms of fund size, both groups are not ordinary retail investors and are evenly matched in strength. The former represents potential selling pressure, while the latter represents buying demand, and the former currently holds the upper hand.Interestingly, the data for ETH is completel</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27798</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine-Related Address Receives 10 BTC Donation, Equivalent to $1.1 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27797</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as monitored by Whale Alert, a cryptocurrency donation of 10 BTC was transferred to a Ukraine-related address approximately 5 minutes ago. This is equivalent to around $1.108 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27797</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Big Brother」 Huang Licheng opens 5x WLFI long position with a position value of $1.82 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27795</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), after the address of &quot;Brother Big Whale&quot; Justin Sun was blacklisted by WLFI this morning, Huang Lizheng initiated a 5x long position on WLFI. Currently, he is holding 10 million tokens with a value of $1.82 million, and the entry price is $0.1822.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27795</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Total Market Capitalization Down 1.8% in the Last 24 Hours, Altcoins Experience a Broad Decline</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27796</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to Coingecko data, the cryptocurrency market continues to decline. The total cryptocurrency market capitalization has dropped to $3.896 trillion, with a 24-hour decrease of 1.8%. Bitcoin is remaining above $110,000. Meanwhile, ETH and SOL have both seen a decrease of about 3% in the past 24 hours. ETH is currently trading at $4,320, and SOL is at $202. Shitcoins are generally in a downtrend, including:SLF down 17.6% in the last 24 hours;WLFI down 16.3% in the last 24 hours;TREE down 15.4% in the last 24 hours;BAKE down 12% in the last 24 hours;DOLO down 11.7% in the last 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27796</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address received 14,000 MKR from FalconX, worth $24.74 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27794</link>
      <description>September 5th. As per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a novel address received 14,000 MKR from FalconX, with a total value of $24.74 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27794</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump: Major Announcement to Be Made Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27793</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, posted a picture and said, &quot;I will be making a significant announcement tomorrow.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27793</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s ETH long position has been liquidated for the sixth time in a row, with the current liquidation price at $4,257.29.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27792</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, James Wynn&apos;s 25x long position in ETH has been liquidated for the sixth consecutive time. The current remaining position was opened at $4378.62, with the liquidation price at $4257.29, and the position is now only worth approximately $130,000.Previously reported, James Wynn has recently been liquidated at a high position after making multiple attempts to go long on ETH:On September 2nd, when ETH rose above $4400, James Wynn fully entered a long position. On September 3rd, when ETH fell below $4280, James Wynn was liquidated.From the evening of September 3rd to this morning, James Wynn added to his long position near $4440. After that, ETH fell back to around $4370, and James Wynn was partially liquidated again. The remaining position&apos;s liquidation price is $4339, and he is holding a position worth about $320,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Economic RWA Protocol Pluralk Completes $7M Seed Round, Led by Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27791</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to Reuters, Plural, an RWA protocol with a focus on the electricity economy, announced the successful completion of a $7 million seed round of financing. This round was led by Paradigm, and Maven11, Volt Capital, and Neoclassic Capital also participated, bringing the total funding to nearly $10 million.Plural is a blockchain technology company committed to promoting the electricity economy. By leveraging tokenization and smart contract automation technology, Plural transforms real-world energy assets like solar power, batteries, and data centers into scalable and programmable investment products.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27791</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Proposes Safe Harbor for Cryptocurrency and Amends Broker-Dealer Risk Assessment Rules</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27790</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) put forward a proposal to offer a safe harbor for cryptocurrency and reform the broker-dealer rule. The proposed rule changes may have an impact on the SEC&apos;s guidance on broker-dealers, custody, and reporting. It may also allow cryptocurrency companies to operate in the United States with relatively less regulatory oversight and reduce the risk of legal actions. The proposed rules involve amending the &quot;Exchange Act&quot; to &quot;consider trading crypto assets on alternative trading systems and national securities exchanges&quot; and amending the &quot;broker-dealer financial responsibility rules&quot;, which may relieve the burden on cryptocurrency companies in reporting data. Although the impact of each proposal on the cryptocurrency industry is different, many proposals indicate that the Commission will continue to soften its enforcement approach, establish a safe harbor, and restructure existing regulations to benefit relevant crypto proje</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27790</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto-Friendly Bank Lead Bank Raises $70 Million in Funding at a $1.47 Billion Valuation, Led by a16z</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27789</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the cryptocurrency-friendly bank Lead Bank, which is valued at $1.47 billion, successfully completed a $70 million financing round. This round was spearheaded by a16z and Khosla Ventures. Existing investors such as Ribbit Capital, Coatue, and Zeev Ventures also took part in the round. Additionally, new investors including Iconiq Capital and Greycroft joined in.The extra funds will be utilized to fortify the balance sheet in order to facilitate its business expansion in the fintech sector. Lead Bank&apos;s clients encompass the &quot;buy now, pay later&quot; company Affirm Holdings Inc., the corporate spending management platform Ramp Business Corporation, and the stablecoin business unit of Stripe Inc., which was recently acquired.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27789</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>