<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Christie&apos;s Subsidiary Establishes Cryptocurrency Real Estate Department</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21759</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as reported by The New York Times, one of the largest luxury real estate brokerage firms in the United States is setting up a dedicated department to enable buyers to use digital currency to purchase real estate.This company is Christie&apos;s International Real Estate, becoming the first mainstream real estate brokerage firm to establish a dedicated team to handle transactions solely through cryptocurrency payments. The team consists of lawyers, analysts, and cryptocurrency experts, and is specifically responsible for transactions where both buyers and sellers use digital currency exclusively without relying on banks. As cryptocurrency continues to rapidly enter the mainstream financial sector, Christie&apos;s move represents a significant shift.The CEO of Christie&apos;s Los Angeles subsidiary, Aaron Kirman, stated that he is currently in negotiations with several major banks to facilitate the acceptance of cryptocurrency as a payment method for property transactions that req</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>510 billion BONK tokens were transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase last night, totaling around $18.75 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21758</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as per Ashes Monitor, last night following the Bonk team&apos;s announcement of a buyback and burn of 500 billion BONK (approximately $18.47 million), 510 billion BONK (approximately $18.75 million) were transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase half an hour later.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 8.47 million USDC into Hyperliquid and went long on ETH with 3x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21757</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale transferred 8.47 million USDC to Hyperliquid and initiated a 3x leveraged long position in ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21757</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn Closed Long Position at over $650,000 Loss and Opened Short Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21756</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, James Wynn has liquidated his long positions in BTC (with 40x leverage) and PEPE (with 10x leverage), incurring a loss of $657,172. He has also opened a short position in PEPE (with 10x leverage).He has deposited 1.25 million USDC into Hyperliquid. Currently, he only has $214,000 left.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21756</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin falls below $116,000, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach $677 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21755</link>
      <description>On July 25th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin drops below $116,000, the cumulative liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will reach 677 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin exceeds $120,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will reach 259 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the relative significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent ones, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree reaching a certain price level will have an impact. Higher &quot;liquidation bars&quot; indicate that once the price reaches that level, a more intense reaction will occur due to a liquidity avalanche.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21755</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Temporarily Drops Below $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21754</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin briefly fell below $118,000 and is currently trading at $118,001, showing a 24-hour decrease of 0.65%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21754</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSL Group Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.355 Billion through a Rights Issue for Strategic Acquisitions, Stablecoin Business, etc.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21753</link>
      <description>On July 25th, OSL Group announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that prior to the trading session on July 25, 2025, the company had entered into a placing and subscription agreement, a general mandate subscription agreement, and a specific mandate subscription agreement. The total estimated proceeds from these transactions are approximately 23.5503 billion Hong Kong dollars, with an estimated net proceeds of approximately 23.3610 billion Hong Kong dollars. The placing price is HKD 14.90 per placing share, which represents a discount of about 15.34% compared to the closing market price of the shares on the last trading day on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange.The company intends to utilize the total net proceeds for the following purposes: approximately 50% for supporting the company&apos;s strategic acquisition initiatives; approximately 30% for the development of global business and new business initiatives (including payment and stablecoin initiatives); and approximately 20% for the group&apos;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21753</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Son Retweets and Endorses &quot;ETH Severely Undervalued&quot; Point of View</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21752</link>
      <description>On July 25th, Eric Trump, the son of former U.S. President Donald Trump, retweeted a comment regarding the value potential of Ethereum (ETH) on social media and publicly declared his &quot;complete agreement.&quot;The original post noted: &quot;Ethereum is catching up with global liquidity. When compared with M2 money supply growth, the current price of ETH should already be above $8,000. This shows how undervalued ETH currently is and is likely one of the most promising trading opportunities at present.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injective Launches On-Chain Tokenized SharpLink Gaming Stock Asset SBET</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21751</link>
      <description>July 25th. According to official channels, Injective has officially initiated the on-chain tokenization of SharpLink Gaming&apos;s stock asset SBET. This indicates that the first on-chain Digital Asset Treasury (DAT) has come into being.The SBET digital asset treasury is constructed based on Injective&apos;s iAssets framework, enabling the creation of real assets with &quot;ready-made&quot; functionality. By means of SBET, Injective offers holders staking rewards, real-time trading, and the utility to be used as collateral in DeFi strategies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21751</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Demands Powell to Cut Interest Rates</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21750</link>
      <description>July 25th: During a visit to the headquarters of the Federal Reserve, U.S. President Trump participated in a media interview with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell. Regarding how he would retract his criticism of Powell, Trump expressed his hope for a rate cut and stated that he would pay attention to the Committee&apos;s rate decision.Trump also said, &quot;In general, I would fire a project manager who exceeds the budget.&quot; As Trump referred to the renovation budget data of the Federal Reserve headquarters, Powell kept shaking his head nearby. Trump also made a sarcastic remark that the building renovation was a challenging task.After Trump said to Powell, &quot;I want him to lower the interest rates,&quot; he forcefully patted Powell on the back, and then Powell awkwardly laughed. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21750</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>