<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster Capital partner deposited 1260 ETH into Coinbase 10 hours ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22058</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), Winslow Strong, a partner of Cluster Capital, deposited 1260 ETH into Coinbase 10 hours ago. The value of this deposit is $4.82 million and it is suspected to have been sold. ETH only accounts for a small part of his on-chain holdings. He has over $41.55 million in assets in sUSD, followed by Wrapped BTC and GRT.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22058</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: BNB All-Time High Could Signal Accelerated Growth for Total3</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22057</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio stated in a post on his personal channel that &quot;The reaching of a new all-time high by BNB is a significant signal. This is the first mainstream coin to break through the resistance of the historical high point, aside from BTC. I don&apos;t hold any myself, but this is a very positive signal for the acceleration of the rise of Total3 (the total market value excluding BTC and ETH). Now, we are patiently waiting for ETH to break through $4000.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22057</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $25.4 billion worth of ETH is currently queued to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while around $10.1 billion worth of ETH is waiting to join.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22056</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the validatorqueue data, there are currently around 660,000 ETH (which is approximately equivalent to $25.4 billion at the current price) awaiting to exit the Ethereum PoS network. The exit waiting time is approximately 11 days and 11 hours. Meanwhile, there are about 263,000 ETH queued to join the network, approximately $10.1 billion, with an expected activation delay of about 4 days and 14 hours.Previously reported, this situation indicates the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On one hand, some stakers may have decided to cash out after Ethereum rebounded by more than 160% from the April low, resulting in a significant increase in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also raising the entry queue. Publicly traded companies like SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have been increasing their ETH holdings and engaging in staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courtyard Completes $30 Million Series A Funding Round, Lead by Forerunner</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22054</link>
      <description>July 28th. As per the report in Fortune, the New York-based startup Courtyard has concluded a Series A funding round worth $30 million. This round was led by Forerunner Ventures and involved the participation of NEA and Y Combinator. Courtyard was established in 2021. Its main business is to sell &quot;blind box&quot; trading cards and comic books in a digital vending machine format via its website. Users make a certain payment, and the algorithm randomly distributes the cards or comics. Users have the option to resell at 90% of the market price, resell on the platform without incurring any fees, or store for free in Courtyard&apos;s warehouse. The company intends to enhance its market-leading position by expanding the team, increasing marketing investment, and broadening the product line.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22054</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun&apos;s Solana Launchpad Market Share in the last 24 hours has dropped to 9.01%, placing it below Jup Studio at third place.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22055</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours, in the Solana launchpad market share ranking, Letsbonk took the first place with 76.9%, Jup Studio came in second with 9.8%, and pump.fun ranked third with 9.01%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22055</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US lending institution Divine Research uses World ID to enable uncollateralized cryptocurrency loans</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22053</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per Cointelegraph, the San Francisco-based lending institution Divine Research has extended around 30,000 unsecured short-term cryptocurrency loans since December. It utilizes OpenAI CEO Sam Altman&apos;s iris scanning platform World ID to verify the identities of borrowers. Divine Research mainly provides sub-$1,000 USDC stablecoin loans to overseas borrowers who are not served by traditional financial services. By using World ID, it ensures that users cannot open multiple accounts in case of default. The company&apos;s founder, Diego Estevez, stated that the borrowers include high school teachers, fruit vendors, and other ordinary individuals.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22053</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HK Stock Stablecoin Concept Stocks Soar Across the Board, Golden Surge Investment Up Nearly 6%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22052</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Hong Kong stock concept stocks related to stablecoins witnessed a general upward trend. Loto Interactive (01328.HK) rose by nearly 6%, Matrix Holdings (01911.HK) increased by more than 5%, and Guotai Junan International (01788.HK) went up by nearly 4%. The Hong Kong &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; is set to take effect officially on August 1st, and the issuance of stablecoins has entered the &quot;countdown&quot; stage.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22052</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX Recovery Hot Wallet received 20,000 ETH redeemed from Lido in the past hour, which has now been deposited into Aave.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22051</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the HTX Recovery hot wallet received 20,000 ETH redeemed from Lido within the past 1 hour. The value of these ETH is $76.57 million, and they have currently been deposited into Aave.Since July 16th, this address has queued a total of 50,000 ETH for redemption. It is one of the top addresses during this &quot;unstaking wave&quot; and still holds 40,283 ETH in Lido.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22051</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCTV reported last night on &quot;Trump Coin, WLFI, and Stablecoins&quot; content</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22050</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the CCTV-13 (CCTV News Channel) World Weekly program reported last night on relevant content such as &quot;TrumpCoin (TRUMP), WLFI, and Stablecoin&quot;.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22050</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale is long on BTC and ETH with 15x leverage, currently sitting on a $21 million unrealized gain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22049</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale carried out 15 times leveraged longing on BTC and ETH. The position value exceeded $270 million. Currently, the unrealized profit is $21 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22049</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>