<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:53:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered: Ethereum Treasury Company Now &apos;Very Investible,&apos; Superior to U.S. Spot Ethereum ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23468</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as reported by The Block, Geoffrey Kendrick, the Global Head of Digital Assets Research at Standard Chartered Bank, stated that Ethereum Treasury Companies are currently &quot;very worthy of investment&quot; and are more attractive to investors compared to a U.S. spot Ethereum ETF. The Net Asset Value (NAV) multiple of Ethereum Treasury Companies, which is the market cap divided by the held ETH value, is currently &quot;starting to normalize&quot; and is expected to remain above 1, making it a better investment target than a U.S. spot ETH ETF. Kendrick said: &quot;I see no reason why the NAV multiple should be below 1.0, as I believe these companies present investors with a regulatory arbitrage opportunity.&quot; With the normalization of the NAV multiple, Ethereum Treasury Companies can provide better opportunities for Ethereum price appreciation, staking rewards, and per-ETH growth compared to a U.S. spot ETH ETF, which currently cannot participate in staking or decentralized finance (DeFi).Kendr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Powell: July Employment Data Cause for Concern, Significant Data Revision Possible as Economy Approaches Turning Point</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23466</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Federal Reserve Governor Powell expressed that caution should be exercised when interpreting data. The July employment data was a cause for concern, and significant data revisions may take place as the economy reaches a turning point. (Xinhua Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23466</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Powell: Labor Market Slowing, Tariffs Only Have Short-Term Impact, Fed Will Soon Cut Interest Rates</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23465</link>
      <description>July 8th. The President of the San Francisco Fed, Daly, stated on Wednesday that given the moderating labor market and her assessment that tariffs pose only a short-term threat to inflation, she is of the view that the Fed will soon be required to cut interest rates. &quot;In the absence of tariffs, inflation has been gradually declining. Along with the economy slowing down and monetary policy remaining restrictive, inflation is expected to continue to fall.&quot; She further added that although tariffs have pushed up inflation in the short term, it is unlikely to have a lasting influence. Meanwhile, the labor market has exhibited signs of weakness. &quot;I believe that further slowing would be a cause for concern. Once the labor market begins to waver, it typically deteriorates rapidly and severely. All of this indicates that we are likely to need to adjust policy in the coming months.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23465</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says He Will Nominate an Acting Fed Board Member in the Coming Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23467</link>
      <description>On August 7th, President Trump stated that he might nominate an interim member of the Federal Reserve Board in the following days to fill a vacancy instead of taking the chance to promote his preferred candidate for the next Fed chair. &quot;We may make the interim appointment first, and then we&apos;ll make the permanent appointment,&quot; Trump told reporters at the White House on Wednesday. &quot;I think the interim will be announced within the next two to three days, and then we will make the permanent appointment.&quot;Trump said he is considering &quot;probably&quot; three candidates for this position, and they may come from Wall Street. He further added that Commerce Secretary Lighthizer, Treasury Secretary Mnuchin, and Vice President Pence are each advisors in this process. Trump reiterated that he still regards former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh and National Economic Council Director Kevin Hassett as leading candidates for the chairmanship in case of a vacancy. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23467</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitlight Labs is pleased to announce that the RGB mainnet is now live, allowing open testing of asset issuance.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23464</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the infrastructure developer Bitlight Labs of the RGB Protocol announced that the RGB mainnet is now live. It supports access to the RGB Faucet, enabling the minting of test assets on RGB and the exploration of Bitcoin&apos;s on-chain native smart contract capabilities.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale @ParallelAiRev Tops Hyperliquid Weekly $PUMP Profits With $1.26M Gain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23459</link>
      <description>Whale investor @ParallelAiRev is holding a 2.3B $PUMP($7.85M) long position with over $1.26M in unrealized profit — making him the top $PUMP earner on Hyperliquid&apos;s leaderboard over the past week.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23459</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the Tornado Cash Case Reached a Partial Settlement, TORN Experienced a Short-Term Drop of Over 18%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23463</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to HTX market data, after the &quot;Tornado Cash Partial Settlement&quot;, TORN witnessed a short-term drop of more than 18% and reached $11.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23463</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitalik: Ethereum will eventually achieve instant cross-L2 native asset transfers via L1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23462</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Vitalik Buterin, the founder of Ethereum, stated in a post that he was very pleased to witness many mainstream Layer 2 solutions entering Stage 1, which is the &quot;limited training rounds&quot;. The next objective is to achieve fast withdrawals through a zero-knowledge proof system. He considers this to be more significant than reaching Stage 2, which is &quot;without training rounds&quot;. Fast withdrawal times are of great importance as they will lower the capital costs for liquidity providers. If the native withdrawal time can be shortened to less than 1 hour in the short term and to 12 seconds in the medium term, Ethereum Layer 1 will further enhance its position as the default platform for issuing assets and as the economic center of the Ethereum ecosystem.For this to be achieved, we need to give up the Optimistic proof system, which essentially requires waiting for several days to make a withdrawal. Historically, zero-knowledge proof technology was immature and costly, making the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23462</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado Cash Case Reaches Partial Settlement: Guilty of Operating Unlicensed Money Transmitting Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23461</link>
      <description>On August 7th, during the trial of Roman Storm, the co-founder of Tornado Cash, a partial verdict was reached. The charge of operating an unlicensed money transmitting business was sustained. The charge of money laundering conspiracy remains undetermined. And the third charge (evading sanctions) resulted in an acquittal.Roman Storm stood trial in the federal court of the Southern District of New York. This case could potentially set a legal precedent regarding the extent of responsibility that developers should bear when the decentralized software they created is used illegally. The U.S. prosecutors accused Storm of conspiracy in money laundering, violating U.S. sanction regulations, and operating an unlicensed money transmitting business. If found guilty, he could face a maximum prison term of 40 years.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23461</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Halt Trading Stay Away from the Market, Wait for a Clear Case of Mispricing</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23460</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio declared in a post on his personal platform that he has temporarily ceased trading in order to stay away from the market for a brief period. He is waiting for a clear instance of significant mispricing before coming back. He believes that this is the season to cut down on trading activities.Previously, it was reported that on August 5th, Trader Eugene had already realized profits from his long position in ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23460</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>