<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Listed Company Sharps Technology&apos;s SOL Holdings Exceed 2 Million Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27350</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per the Associated Press, the US-listed company Sharps Technology, Inc. (STSS) announced today that it has carried out its first SOL purchase. As of now, the holdings of SOL tokens have exceeded 2 million, and the market value of the SOL Treasury has exceeded $4 billion.On August 29th, Sharps Technology announced the completion of a private placement of common stock and warrants, raising more than $4 billion in this transaction. If all warrants are exercised, an additional $6 billion can be raised, bringing the total fundraising amount to potentially $10 billion. The new funds will support its launch of a digital asset treasury strategy, with the main holding of this treasury being SOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27350</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Launches First-ever US Stock Market IPO, Ticker Symbol &quot;GEMI&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27349</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as reported by the Associated Press, the cryptocurrency platform Gemini announced that it has submitted an S-1 registration statement to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission in order to conduct an initial public offering of 16,666,667 shares of Class A common stock. In relation to this offering, Gemini and its selling shareholders intend to grant the underwriters a 30-day option to purchase up to an additional 2,396,348 shares and 103,652 shares of Class A common stock respectively to cover over-allotments. The initial public offering price is currently anticipated to be between $17.00 and $19.00 per share of Class A common stock.Gemini has applied to list its Class A common stock on the Nasdaq Global Select Market under the symbol &quot;GEMI&quot;. Goldman Sachs, Citigroup, Morgan Stanley, and Cantor are serving as lead underwriters, while Evercore ISI, Mizuho, Truist Securities, Cohen &amp; Company Capital Markets, Keefe, Bruyette &amp; Woods, a Stifel Company, Needham &amp; Com</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27349</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowMist Cosmos Update on Venus Security Incident: Compromised Whale Account Targeted with a Spear Phishing Attack, Related Wallet Extension Replaced</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27347</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, SlowMist Cosmos updated the Venus security incident on the X platform in the following manner: In this whale theft incident, both the Venus protocol and the front end are supposed to be in good condition. Currently, the joint partner analysis by SlowMist tends to believe that the whale was the target of a pinpoint attack. Although the whale used a hardware wallet, the relevant wallet extension on the computer (used in combination with the hardware wallet) was replaced. When the user issued a normal redeemUnderlying operation, it was replaced with an updateDelegate operation, ultimately leading to the theft of assets in their Venus.The hacker targeted the funds of this whale through a pinpoint attack. The Gas came from the privacy token Monero XMR exchange, and other related funds traced back to eXch, which is the previously sanctioned dark web trading platform and also a platform that was favored by North Korean hackers in the past.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27347</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starknet experiences downtime again, and the engineering team has started working on the fix</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27348</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the Starknet team officially made an announcement that Starknet had encountered another outage. The engineering team has initiated the repair process, and the specific cause has not been disclosed yet. Further updates will be provided as the work progresses.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27348</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Somnia (SOMI) with a Phase 1 threshold of 235 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27346</link>
      <description>September 2nd. Binance Alpha will list Somnia (SOMI) on September 2, 2025, at 21:30 (UTC+8). Trading on Alpha will commence. Eligible users will be able to claim a 100 SOMI token airdrop on the Alpha event page within 24 hours after the start of trading.The airdrop will be distributed in two stages:Stage 1 (first 18 hours): Users who hold at least 235 Alpha Points can make a claim.Stage 2 (last 6 hours): Users holding at least 220 Alpha Points can participate in the second-stage airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is not yet over, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27346</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cango Inc. mined 663.7 bitcoins in August, bringing its total holdings to 5,193.4 bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27345</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the Bitcoin mining firm Cango Inc. presented its August 2025 update on Bitcoin production and mining operations. During August, 663.7 bitcoins were mined, and the Bitcoin treasury exceeded 5,000 bitcoins, reaching 5,193.4 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market Cryptocurrency Stocks Mixed, WLFI Finance Company ALTS Plunges 9.3%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27344</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, which was the first trading day of the week, during the pre-market trading of the US stock market, there were mixed movements in cryptocurrency stocks. These included:The WLFI Treasury Company ALT5 Sigma (ALTS) plummeted by 9.3%. On August 11th, it announced the launch of a $1.5 billion private placement WLFI Treasury Strategic Launch. Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, joined the board.Bitmine (BMNR) rose by 0.62%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) fell by 0.06%.Coinbase (COIN) fell by 0.14%.Circle (CRCL) fell by 0.34%.MicroStrategy (MSTR) rose by 1.08%.Bullish (BLSH) rose by 0.14%.BTCS (BTCS) fell by 0.48%.ETHZilla (ETHZ) fell by 0.71%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: WLFI Underperforms on First Day of Trading, Drives U.S. ALTS Pre-market Down Nearly 12%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27343</link>
      <description>September 2nd. On the listing day of WLFI, the stock price of Alt5 Sigma Corporation once dropped by nearly 12% in the pre-market. The market remains cautious about the volatility of emerging coin stock companies. Nevertheless, in the long term, the strategy of holding tokens as reserve assets is anticipated to establish a closer linkage between cryptocurrencies and traditional capital markets, bringing new investment opportunities to investors.Previously, the U.S.-listed company Alt5 Sigma Corporation intended to include the WLFI token in its company&apos;s reserve assets, creating a growth model similar to a &quot;MicroStrategy-style flywheel.&quot; The company also announced that it would expand its crypto payment business, covering almost all popular sectors in the market, providing new insights for the integration of digital assets and traditional finance.The BiyaPay multi-asset trading wallet will continuously provide you with one-stop services such as global remittances, 0% Maker fee trans</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27343</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company Sequans increases its BTC holdings by 34 coins, bringing its total holdings to 3,205 coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27342</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per an official announcement, the publicly traded company Sequans in the US purchased 34 BTC, resulting in its total BTC holdings reaching 3,205.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27342</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowMist Cosmos Updates Venus Security Incident: Protocol Should Be Fine, Large Holders&apos; Computers Possibly Compromised</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27341</link>
      <description>September 2nd. SlowMist Cosmos updated the Venus security incident on the X platform as follows:1. The Venus Protocol is likely to be in good condition. However, we do not exclude the possibility that the Venus frontend may have been compromised, resulting in phishing attacks against large holders (the Venus team can also conduct investigations in this regard).2. The computers of large holders may be targeted with poisoning attacks (under investigation).3. The hacker was well-prepared. The source of funds is somewhat complex, and the gas source was converted from XMR.4. Large holders are in communication with SlowMist. Many details have not been disclosed yet. Additionally, the actual loss may be less than $20 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27341</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>