<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:21:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Leaderboard Update: Whale AndreIsBack Joins WLFI Genesis Sale, Contributing 170 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27299</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the Ethena Leaderboard Whale AndreIsBack, who invested 170 ETH (approximately $580,000) eight months ago and received 38.71 million WLFI tokens at a cost of $0.015 per token. Yesterday, he received 7.74 million unlocked tokens that have not been sold yet (approximately $1.85 million). However, he is currently sitting on a $585,000 unrealized gain from his 3x short hedge position on Hyperliquid.This whale is extremely enthusiastic about participating in DeFi projects. The address 0x9cb...c06ce holds over $41.69 million in assets and has participated in a total of 21 DeFi projects. Currently, it is leading the Ethena Season3 Leaderboard with an astonishing 1.28 trillion points, accounting for 3.57% of the total reward pool.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27299</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT has disclosed the fee structure and wallet address for over 200 crypto Key Opinion Leaders (KOLs), with most KOLs not clearly stating the promotional nature of their tweets.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27300</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, ZachXBT disclosed the charging standards and wallet addresses of more than 200 crypto KOLs on the X platform yesterday. ZachXBT stated that among the more than 160 paid promoters, fewer than 5 clearly marked their posts as advertisements.ZachXBT believes that in many jurisdictions, failing to disclose the promotional nature of information may even be illegal. &quot;I have said many times that if you disclose paid promotion information for a project that you truly believe in, then paid promotion is acceptable. If you think that influential people should be allowed to secretly accept money to promote projects and mislead fans, then this indicates many problems.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27300</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Union (U) on September 4th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27298</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per an official announcement, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list Union (U) on September 4th. Eligible users can access the Alpha event page once the Alpha trading commences and claim the airdrop by using Alpha Points. Additional details will be provided separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27298</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fujian-based Group in China Organized a Pyramid Scheme in the Name of Virtual Currency and NFTs; Court of Second Instance Rejects Their Appeal</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27297</link>
      <description>September 2nd, 2023. From May to August 2023, Li and others, under the guise of issuing a certain cryptocurrency, established a hierarchical reward mechanism based on invitation relationships. They formed groups through social platforms, carried out online and offline promotions, and publicly promoted to the general public. They enticed participants to qualify for membership through activities such as purchasing cryptocurrency, staking assets, and auctioning NFTs, and received rebates based on developing a downline. By the time of the October 2023 incident, the organization had developed multiple levels and had raised funds equivalent to more than 20 million RMB.The Shishi City Procuratorate of Fujian Province determined through its review that although this organization used new concepts such as cryptocurrency and NFTs for packaging, its operating model still met the criteria of the crime of organizing and leading MLM activities as stipulated in the Criminal Law of the People&apos;s Repu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27297</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lxuan.eth entered a long position on cbBTC during today&apos;s rebound, with an average price of $110,230</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27296</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), lxuan.eth has spent $8.51 million in the past 1 hour during a rebound trend. It has gone long for 77.21 cbBTC with an average price of $110,230. Currently, it is holding an unrealized profit of $18,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Ethereum is currently in a digestion phase after being overbought, with limited potential to retest $5000 in the short term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27295</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, Matrixport presented a market outlook indicating that Ethereum&apos;s transaction volume sharply decreased from $122 billion to $57 billion as speculative long positions underwent liquidation. Despite several technical supports existing below, the funding rate has retreated back to below 10%, suggesting a slowdown in ETF capital inflows.At present, Ethereum is in a digestion stage following being overbought, and the implied volatility still remains at a high level. For aggressive investors, selling covered call options can enable them to capture volatility premiums, and the short-term possibility of returning to $5,000 is limited. Overall, risk control remains of key importance, and Matrixport still maintains a cautious stance after the price breaks below a crucial support.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27295</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Holoworld AI (HOLO) Exclusive Pre-TGE Event Point Threshold is 240 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27294</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to an official announcement, Binance Wallet is going to hold a brand new exclusive Pre-TGE event for HOLO. The event will be carried out on September 2nd, 2025, from 08:00 to 10:00 (UTC). Users who possess 240 Alpha points can participate in this Pre-TGE event by clicking on the Pre-TGE event banner within the wallet. To participate in this event, 10 points need to be spent.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27294</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: ETH May Retrace to $3,350 Support in September, Start Rebound in October Towards New High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27293</link>
      <description>September 2nd. As per Cointelegraph, analyst Johnny Woo declared: &quot;ETH might initially present a bearish outlook. However, if the trend unfolds as anticipated, this could potentially be the most significant bear trap I have ever witnessed.&quot;He further added that the chart suggests that ETH might form a &quot;head and shoulders&quot; pattern in September and then experience a breakout in an &quot;October rally.&quot; In this situation, Ethereum could decline to around $3,350 as a support level in September and subsequently rebound in October, surging to a new all-time high in November.A comparable situation took place in September 2021 when ETH dropped by 30% from $3,950 to $2,750 only to rebound to a new all-time high in November.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27293</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Short-Term Breakthrough of $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27292</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, based on HTX market data, Ethereum briefly exceeded $4400, and it saw a 0.26% increase in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27292</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Executive Board Member Schnabel: Central Bank Should Keep Rates Unchanged, Inflation Could Still Be Higher Than Expected</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27291</link>
      <description>September 2nd - Fabio Panetta, who is a member of the Executive Board of the European Central Bank, expressed that the ECB should keep the interest rate at the present level. This stance is founded on the Eurozone economy&apos;s ability to withstand U.S. tariffs and the potential that the inflation rate might still be higher than anticipated. The ECB previously concluded a one-year period of loose monetary policy and is currently evaluating the comprehensive impact of the July agreement on U.S. tariffs to determine whether further interest rate cuts are required. Panetta is one of the most significant hawks at the ECB and holds the view that there is no necessity for additional rate cuts. The current policy rate of 2% may &quot;moderately&quot; stimulate the already vibrant economy. She stated: &quot;I think we may have already implemented a slightly accommodative policy, so I do not perceive a reason for further rate cuts in the current circumstances.&quot; (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 06:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27291</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>