<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance HODLer Airdrop Launches Mitosis (MITO) and Spot Trading Will Go Live Tonight at 23:30</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26852</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to an official announcement, Binance has initiated the 34th project within the Binance HODLer Airdrop: Mitosis (MITO).Binance is scheduled to list MITO on August 29, 2025, at 3:30 PM (UTC) and commence trading for the pairs USDT, USDC, BNB, FDUSD, and TRY. MITO will bear a Seed label. Users will be able to commence depositing MITO on August 29, 2025, at 11:30 AM (UTC).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26852</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcement: U.S. Core PCE Price Index YoY for July and U.S. University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment Index Final Value for August will be released tonight</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26850</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on the schedule, the US July Core PCE Price Index Annual Rate will be released at 20:30 Beijing time tonight. Meanwhile, the final value of the University of Michigan Consumer Confidence Index for August will be announced at 22:00.According to forecasts, the PCE Price Index is anticipated to rise by 0.3% in July, remaining the same as the previous month. If this forecast comes true, the year-on-year growth rate of PCE inflation will go up from 2.8% to 2.9%, reaching the highest level since February this year and also being the third consecutive month of increase.Economists state that high inflation may restrict the space for further rate cuts later this year. Some believe that only a significant increase in the August CPI inflation data, which will be released in two weeks, can prompt the Fed to reexamine its rate cut plans during the meeting on September 16th to 17th. (Jin10)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26850</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWE&apos;s second World Launch has officially kicked off, featuring the Trade Clash project.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26851</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per official channels, the decentralized AI project AWE has initiated its second World Launch on the World.fun platform, featuring the Trade Clash project, and officially launched at 9 a.m. (UTC+8) today.This issuance is based on the Base chain, with a targeted fundraising cap of 60,000 USDC, which corresponds to an estimated initial market capitalization of approximately $300,000. Once the cap is reached, the project team will promptly deploy a liquidity pool (LP) and simultaneously open token claiming.The event first enters the whitelist subscription period, which lasts for 24 hours. If the cap is not reached, the remaining allocation will be opened to the public. The whitelist comprises participants of the Trade Clash Alpha Tournament and some collaborating communities and KOLs, with a maximum individual wallet subscription of 1,000 USDC.The project team indicated that the World Launch will serve as a mechanism for continuous improvement, constantly enhancin</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26851</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bluemoon Interactive disclosed that it purchased a total of approximately $7.85 million worth of BTC, ETH, and SOL in the first half of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26849</link>
      <description>August 29th. According to an announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, Bluehole Interactive stated that by June 30, 2025, the main addition to intangible assets during the past six months was the acquisition of cryptocurrency.During the six months ending on June 30th, the Group purchased cryptocurrency, including 62.98 Bitcoins, 330.49 Ethereums, and 6991.7 Solanas, with a total cash outlay of $7.85 million (approximately RMB 56.36 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26849</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PetroChina: closely monitoring the Hong Kong stablecoin, will initiate cross-border settlement feasibility study</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26848</link>
      <description>On August 29th, PetroChina (00857.HK) disclosed at its semi-annual earnings conference that it is closely observing the licensing policy of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority for stablecoins and is planning to launch a feasibility study on using stablecoins for cross-border settlement and payments.As one of China&apos;s largest state-owned energy enterprises, PetroChina has become one of the first traditional energy giants to publicly respond to Hong Kong&apos;s &quot;Stablecoin Regulation.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump: China is &quot;an absolutely terrifying force&quot; in the cryptocurrency space</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26847</link>
      <description>August 29th, Eric Trump, the son of the former U.S. President, during the BITCOIN ASIA 2025 conference, declared: In the cryptocurrency field, although China has effectively prohibited digital token transactions since 2021, it is &quot;an extremely powerful country.&quot;On Friday, at the Bitcoin Asia conference in Hong Kong, when Eric Trump was having a Q&amp;A session with crypto investor David Bailey, he said: &quot;There is no doubt that China is an absolute power in this domain.&quot; He was responding to Bailey&apos;s comparison of China and the United States as the &quot;two superpowers of Bitcoin.&quot; (Bloomberg)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26847</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum Could Drop to Around $4270 to Find Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26846</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to crypto analyst Lennaert Snyder, the next key support level for Ethereum that requires attention is $4270. If Ethereum is able to hold above this level and &quot;confirm&quot; support, then it would be reasonable to consider taking a long position.[If $4,270 is breached, one can consider opening a short position. Deeper liquidity can be found around $3,950, and if a reversal signal occurs, that area is a key support level to watch for a potential long opportunity.]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26846</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Sell the HYPE and Long ETH Whale] Nearly half an hour stop loss resulted in a $1.26 billion liquidation of long positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26845</link>
      <description>August 29th: As per Infura, with the price of ETH getting close to the liquidation price of the [Sell the Hype, Long the ETH Whale] position. In an effort to avoid liquidation, the whale has already sold 28,959 ETH ($126 million) in the market within the past half an hour.After reducing the position, the whale still maintains a long position of 57,800 ETH ($251 million), and the liquidation price has decreased to $4,233.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will suspend Conflux Network (CFX) token deposits and withdrawals on September 1st to support its network upgrade and hard fork.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26844</link>
      <description>Update, August 29: As per an official communication, Binance is anticipated to halt token deposits and withdrawals for the Conflux Network (CFX) on September 1 at 08:03 (UTC+8) in order to support its network upgrade and hard fork. This measure is being taken to offer users a more enhanced experience.The project team is set to carry out the network upgrade and hard fork at block height 129,680,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26844</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoldTech Holdings has completed a HKD 2.65 billion new share placement financing, which will be used to explore Risk-Weighted Assets (RWA) applications and develop new blockchain businesses.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26843</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the Hong Kong-listed company Crystal International Group Limited (02228.HK) successfully completed a new share placement with a pricing of HKD 2.65 billion. The placement price was set at HKD 9.28 per share, which represents a premium of approximately 75.8% compared to the IPO price. According to the announcement, in addition to being used for company operations, product development, and mergers and acquisitions, the funds will also be utilized to explore innovative financial instruments such as Real World Assets (RWA) and Real Data Assets (RDA), and to conduct research and development on new blockchain businesses. (Securities Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 08:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>