<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 11:53:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 11:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Outlook: U.S. August PPI, CPI Data Incoming</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27969</link>
      <description>September 6th. During this week, the financial markets underwent significant changes. The surprise weakness in the U.S. nonfarm payroll data led to an increase in the expectation of a Fed rate cut. Despite the market&apos;s anticipation of further rate cuts by the Fed, the U.S. dollar surprisingly remained strong and did not experience a significant drop even after the disappointing nonfarm payroll data.Several Fed watchers have stated that this U.S. nonfarm payroll data has confirmed a rate cut this month. Investors hold the same view, which has boosted the probability of a rate cut at this month&apos;s meeting to 99%.Monday, 23:00: The 1-year inflation expectation of the U.S. New York Fed for August;Tuesday, 22:00: The nonfarm employment benchmark revision for 2025 in the U.S.;Wednesday, 20:30: U.S. August PPI data;Wednesday, 22:00: U.S. July Wholesale Sales month-on-month;Thursday, 20:30: U.S. August CPI data and U.S. Initial Jobless Claims up to September 6th;Friday, 22:00: The init</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27969</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital to Stake 387,000 HYPE Tokens, Worth Around $18.2 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27967</link>
      <description>On September 6th, Galaxy Digital staked 387,000 HYPE tokens through its private validator 17 hours ago, with an approximate value of $18.2 million. Before this, these 387,000 HYPE tokens had been held in Galaxy Digital&apos;s HyperEVM address but had not been staked.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27967</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has listed Starpower Network (STAR)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27968</link>
      <description>On September 6th, Binance Alpha officially launched the Starpower Network (STAR) at 18:00 today.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: US August Non-Farm Payrolls Data Disappointing, Bitcoin Weekly Chart Shows Weakness, Possible Support at $93,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27966</link>
      <description>September 6th: On the evening of September 5th, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics made an announcement. Only 22,000 non-farm jobs were added in August, which is much lower than the market&apos;s expectation of 75,000. The unemployment rate rose to 4.3%, reaching a new high since the end of 2021.This weak employment data has led to a decline in the U.S. dollar and a rise in gold prices, causing volatility in the short-term trend of Bitcoin. Looking at the latest Bitcoin candlestick chart, the weekly chart of BTC is showing a clear downward trend. It has been closing below key support levels for several consecutive weeks. The short-term moving averages are trending downward, and there is a clear bearish crossover in the MACD, indicating a weakening of the bullish momentum. From a technical perspective, if Bitcoin fails to hold above the $100,000 psychological level, the immediate support below may first test the range of $96,000 to $98,000. Further breakdown could extend to around $93,000</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27966</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale took a long position this morning with an average price of $47.175 for 440,000 HYPE tokens, with a liquidation price of $28.324.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27965</link>
      <description>On September 6th, Whale tummy (@tummyy1). This morning, it went long with a 3x leverage on 440,000 HYPE at an average price of $47.175, and the liquidation price is $28.324. Currently, it is facing an unrealized loss of $245,000.In addition, tummy also holds long positions with a 3x leverage in ENA, PUMP, and PENGU. The unrealized losses in them are $170,000, $1,569,000, and $169,000 respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27965</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XTTA Hits All-Time High, Reaching $0.475 Today with a Peak Gain of 37%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27964</link>
      <description>On September 6th, market data indicates that the price of XTTA witnessed a rapid upward surge. During the trading session, it reached a peak of $0.475, marking a 37% increase and hitting a new all-time high. Since its listing on Gate on January 26, 2025, XTTA has generally maintained a stable trend and shown a continuous upward trajectory.Market analysis holds that this round of increase is attributed to the TrendX Hashrate 2.0 upgrade, the rapid growth of the ecosystem surrounding XTTA, and the upcoming halving event related to XTTA. As the core token of the TrendX Hashrate ecosystem, the use cases of XTTA continue to expand, attracting the attention of an increasing number of miners and investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27964</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Exempts Metals Such as Gold, Tungsten, and Uranium from Global Tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27963</link>
      <description>September 6th: On Friday, President Trump of the US took measures to exempt graphite, tungsten, uranium, gold bars and other metals from the country&apos;s tariffs while imposing tariffs on silicone products. According to an executive order issued on Friday, these changes will come into effect on Monday.Trump&apos;s directive may also accelerate the implementation of customized trade agreements between the US and other countries, making it easier for Washington to lift tariffs on aircraft parts, generic drugs and certain products that cannot be grown, mined or naturally produced domestically (such as specific spices, coffee and some rare metals).The President&apos;s order states that these changes were made based on the recommendations of US officials. According to the measure, &quot;these modifications are necessary and appropriate to address the national emergency declared by Trump when he first implemented national-level tariffs in April.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27963</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraday will soon announce its Cryptocurrency Strategy Business Plan and Vehicle Ledger.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27962</link>
      <description>On September 6, the California-based electric vehicle company Faraday Future Intelligent Electric Inc. (NASDAQ: FFAI) announced today that it will hold the 919 Futurist Day and Shareholder Day at its global headquarters in Los Angeles on September 19, 2025, from 3:30 to 6:00 pm (Pacific Time). Highlights of the event on 9/19:· EAI Flywheel: An exclusive immersive experience of FX Super One product features. In-depth interpretation of the final release and delivery plan of FX Super One. Announcement of key milestones in the Octo-State Co-creation and sales activities, as well as new partners. The first anniversary of the FX brand: Strategic review and outlook.· Crypto Flywheel: Release of C10 and the crypto strategic business plan and capital value realization roadmap. Announcement of the product deployment strategy for the FF EAI Ecosystem Vehicle Chain.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 17, according to official sources, Faraday Future announced and launched the &quot;EAI+Cry</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27962</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALT5Sigma has disclosed that its WLFI token holding has increased to around 7.28 billion tokens.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27961</link>
      <description>On September 6th, the financial technology company ALT5 Sigma Corporation (with Nasdaq code: ALTS and Frankfurt Stock Exchange code: 5AR1) announced the latest update regarding its WLFI holdings on September 4th. As of this announcement, ALT5 holds approximately 7.28 billion WLFI tokens.Moreover, the company stressed that the WLFI token, which serves as the core foundational digital asset in its digital asset treasury strategy, is currently tradable on some established cryptocurrency exchanges, allowing the general crypto investing public to conveniently access the token. Within 24 hours after its launch on September 1, 2025, the spot trading volume of WLFI reached $4.7 billion, ranking it among the top ten assets in terms of volume on its first day.As of today, ALT5 holds a total of 7,283,585,650 $WLFI. Based on a market price of $0.181 per WLFI, the company&apos;s digital asset treasury is valued at approximately $1.31 billion.Currently, the company has 124,946,728 common shares and</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27961</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Justin Sun&apos;s Sale of Unlocked WLFI Is Unobjectionable, Responsibility Lies with WLFI Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27960</link>
      <description>September 6: The CEO of the data analytics platform CryptoQuant, Ki Young Ju, posted on social media, saying, &quot;I am in support of Justin on this matter. There is no problem with selling unlocked tokens.The liability should be with the WLFI Foundation as they &apos;debanked&apos; users, which goes against their original intentions.&quot;BlockBeats previously reported that on September 1, Justin Sun posted on social media, expressing his belief that WLFI would become one of the largest and most significant projects in the cryptocurrency space. He currently has no intention of quickly selling unlocked tokens. The long-term vision of the project is very strong, and he is fully in line with its mission.On September 5, World Liberty blacklisted Justin Sun&apos;s address and locked 540 million unlocked tokens and 2.4 billion staked tokens. They stated that they believe a certain exchange has been using user tokens for selling pressure to suppress the price. Justin Sun later mentioned that his WL</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>