<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:29:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company U Power has entered into a strategic partnership with IoTeX to explore the realm of Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21558</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U Power Limited (with Nasdaq stock code: UCAR; hereinafter referred to as &quot;U Power&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) - a provider concentrating on next-generation smart grid and intelligent transportation systems driven by AI solutions - announced today the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding and a Business Cooperation Agreement with IoTeX.IoTeX is a blockchain pioneer committed to transforming machine-generated data into AI collective intelligence. According to the terms of the strategic cooperation agreement:IoTeX will purchase Real World Assets (RWA) issued by U Power and backed by corporate bonds. This will enhance U Power&apos;s capital structure and support the continuous research and development of its UOTTA? electric vehicle battery swapping technology, facilitating U Power&apos;s expansion in Web 3.0 AI-driven energy and transportation system solutions.The two parties will also actively explore innovative solutions for tokenizing these RWA and integrate advanced AI technology</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperion launches the native staking mechanism RION StakingⅠ and announces the official unveiling of RION Utility</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21557</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Aptos, which is the largest decentralized exchange platform, announced the official launch of the RION Utility Prologue for Hyperion and took the lead in opening the native staking Staking Phase I. Users are now able to lock up RION to participate in the native staking mechanism and enter the first stage of network construction and value sharing.Staking Phase I will last for a total of 1 month and will end at 9 p.m. Beijing time on August 22nd. The user&apos;s staking time will be based on the actual participation time, and the rewards will come from a portion of the platform&apos;s transaction fee income. This mechanism is designed to identify and incentivize real contributors, lay the foundation for more RION application scenarios in the future, and reflect Hyperion&apos;s high regard for genuine interaction and ecosystem virtuous cycle.Hyperion stated that this phase is the first step in unlocking RION Utility, and more utility scenarios based on real income will be continuously</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Further Increases Holdings by 117.93 BTC, Bringing Total Holdings to 628.22 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21556</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Swedish-listed company announced another increase in its holdings by 117.93 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 628.22 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: U.S. to Lift Burdensome AI Development Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21555</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the White House made an announcement that President Trump will promote the swift construction of artificial intelligence data centers. The US will repeal onerous AI development regulations. (Forex)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21555</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaulta (formerly EOS) has secured a $6 million investment commitment from WLFI to advance the development of the Web3 banking sector in the United States.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21553</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to official channels, WLFI has entered into a strategic partnership with Vaulta (formerly EOS). WLFI has committed to investing $6 million to boost the development of the Web3 banking industry in the United States.As part of this cooperation:Vaulta&apos;s native assets will be integrated into WLFI&apos;s macro strategic reserves;WLFI&apos;s USD1 stablecoin will be directly incorporated into Vaulta&apos;s Web3 banking infrastructure.The aim is to allow users to utilize the speed, security, and freedom of the decentralized financial system to manage, grow, and safeguard their wealth.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21553</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s long position faces a new round of liquidation, resulting in a loss of over $300,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21554</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, James Wynn&apos;s long positions in Bitcoin and PEPE just underwent a new round of liquidation, resulting in a loss of more than $300,000. Even after depositing an additional $1.25 million into Hyperliquid, his balance has decreased to below $300,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21554</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Drops Below $3,600</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21552</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to HTX market data, Ethereum dropped below $3,600, with a 24-hour decline of 1.95%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institution: Tariff Uncertainty May Prompt the European Central Bank to Cut Interest Rates More Than Once</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21551</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Analyst Gabriele Foa from Algebris Investments stated in a report that due to tariff uncertainty, the interest rate cut of the European Central Bank may exceed the current expectations of the market. This portfolio manager said: &quot;Trade tensions and tariff developments may lead to the endpoint of the rate-cutting cycle being a bit lower than the current market expectations.&quot;Data from LSEG shows that the money market currently anticipates that the ECB will cut rates by another 25 basis points in December. Foa suggested that the spillover effects of tariffs on Europe may take a longer time to become apparent. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Threatens to &quot;Substantially Increase Tariffs&quot; Unless Countries Agree to Open Markets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21550</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. President Trump posted on his personal social media platform and said, &quot;I will only reduce tariffs if a country agrees to open its market. Otherwise, higher tariffs will be imposed! Japan&apos;s market is now open (for the first time in history)! U.S. businesses will achieve prosperity!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: SOL Drops Below $190</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21549</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on HTX market data, SOL dropped below $190, experiencing a 24-hour decrease of 6.10%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21549</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>