<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:18:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>This week, the US Ethereum Spot ETF saw a total net inflow of $1.543 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23001</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, based on Farside&apos;s monitoring data, this week the US Ethereum spot ETF witnessed a cumulative net inflow of $154.3 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23001</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week, the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF saw a cumulative net outflow of $6.429 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23000</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, based on Farside&apos;s monitoring data, this week in the US, the Bitcoin spot ETF witnessed a total net outflow of $6.429 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is actively scouting for the next Federal Reserve Chair with Bostic</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22999</link>
      <description>August 3rd: In an interview, the Director of the National Economic Council of the White House, Hassett, stated that President Trump is actively collaborating with Treasury Secretary Benet to look for candidates for the next Chairperson of the Federal Reserve. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22999</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBF Appeal Case Scheduled for Trial in November 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22998</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, the FTX creditor representative Sunil posted on social media that the appeal of FTX founder SBF is scheduled to be heard during the week of November 3, 2025, at the United States Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit. SBF was previously convicted of 7 charges in November 2023 and sentenced to 25 years in prison in March 2024.SBF officially filed for an appeal in September 2024, and all the relevant legal documents were submitted by January 2025. The outcome of this hearing will be a crucial milestone in his retrial and potential sentence modification.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22998</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Citi, JPMorgan, Goldman Sachs, and SBI Group Lead Traditional Financial Institutions in Blockchain Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22997</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, as per Cointelegraph, Ripple and CB Insights, in conjunction with the UK Blockchain Technology Center, jointly issued a recent report which indicates that Citigroup, JPMorgan Chase, Goldman Sachs, and Japan&apos;s SBI Group have emerged as the most active representatives among traditional financial institutions in supporting blockchain startups.The report highlights that from 2020 to 2024, global banks collectively participated in a total of 345 investments in blockchain companies, with a majority of these focused on early-stage financing. Specifically, Citigroup and Goldman Sachs each completed 18 transactions, taking the lead in the industry. JPMorgan Chase and MUFG closely followed, each making 15 investments.Among them, the &quot;mega financing round&quot; with $100 million or more constitutes a key area of focus for bank deployment. Over the past four years, banks have been involved in a total of 33 such financings, and the funds have mainly flowed to companies specializing in</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22997</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun&apos;s Space Reentry EVA Image Revealed, Smiling and in Good Health</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22996</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, based on Blue Origin&apos;s live broadcast, the founder of TRON Foundation, Justin Sun, has successfully exited the New Shepard spacecraft. He was smiling and in good health.Justin Sun has just completed a suborbital space flight lasting 10 minutes and 14 seconds and has become one of the few Chinese entrepreneurs to enter space.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 13:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22996</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun boards Blue Origin and returns to Earth, total spaceflight time 10 minutes and 14 seconds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22995</link>
      <description>August 3rd. Based on Blue Origin&apos;s official live streaming, Justin Sun, who is the founder of TRON, boarded the New Shepard and completed a space journey. The crew capsule landed successfully, lasting for 10 minutes and 14 seconds.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 13:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22995</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun boards Spaceship and Ignites Engines, Space Journey Officially Begins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22994</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, as per Blue Origin&apos;s official live stream, the Blue Origin spacecraft New Shepard, which was carrying TRON Founder Justin Sun, ignited and took off at 20:43. The spacecraft has successfully reached space.In 2021, Justin Sun successfully bid $28 million for the &quot;New Shepard&quot; first crewed flight seat. He donated all the bidding funds to Blue Origin&apos;s &quot;Club for the Future&quot; in order to support global youth STEM education.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 13:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22994</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale AguilaTrades&apos; 40x leverage Bitcoin long position is currently at a $12,000 unrealized loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22993</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, as monitored by Onchain Lens, whale AguilaTrades&apos; newly opened 40x leveraged long position in Bitcoin is currently facing a $12,000 unrealized loss. Previously, it had achieved an unrealized gain of more than $40 million but ultimately &quot;got liquidated to zero,&quot; with only $73,000 remaining in the wallet.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22993</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin Retests Key Support Level, Institutional Buying Pressure Key Variable</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22992</link>
      <description>On August 3rd, CryptoQuant analyst Axel Adler Jr. put forward that due to the non-farm payroll data coming in below expectations (73k versus the expected 110k), the Fed&apos;s decision to hold rates for the fifth consecutive time with internal differences, and the escalating trade tensions and other macro headwinds, the global market has shifted to a &quot;risk-off&quot; mode. The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq experienced their worst performance since April. U.S. bond yields dropped by nearly 20 basis points, and gold saw an inflow.Bitcoin also came under pressure and quickly retraced from a high of $119,800 to $112,000. The 30-day momentum decreased to +3%, and the ADX slid to 36, indicating a weakening short-term bullish momentum. On-chain activity decreased, but exchange outflows still showed ongoing accumulation in the market.Despite the intensified short-term volatility, the structural bullish thesis remains unchanged. Strategies and institutions added more than 30k BTC to their holdings in the past we</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>