<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:50:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The WLFI token is expected to be launched on the Solana blockchain, with a small-scale cross-chain test conducted today.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27000</link>
      <description>On August 31st, the crypto project WLFI of the Trump family was cross-chain routed to the Solana blockchain through Chainlink CCIP 4 hours ago. The cross-chain token transfer involved 10 WLFI tokens and was for a small-scale test. Dario Laverde, the developer of the WLFI project, responded to the community, stating that &quot;The WLFI token will be launched on the Solana blockchain.&quot;BlockBeats previously reported that the World Liberty Finance (WLFI) project of the Trump family is scheduled to launch on Ethereum on September 1st, enabling claiming and trading. Early supporters (in the 0.015 and 0.05 USD rounds) will unlock 20%, while the remaining 80% will be determined by community vote. Tokens held by the founding team, advisors, and partners will not be unlocked. Trading will start at 8:00 PM Beijing time on September 1st, and the 20% token allocation for claiming will begin.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Etherscan: 10th Anniversary Celebration Coming to a Close</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26999</link>
      <description>On August 31st, Etherscan officially declared that the tenth-anniversary celebration event is coming to a close. Users have the opportunity to claim OG rewards, obtain badges, and accumulate points by taking quizzes and finding Easter eggs before 8:00 on September 1st.On August 15th, the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan announced the launch of the Etherscan Points event, which allows for earning and redeeming rewards on Etherscan. Users can participate in daily check-ins, quizzes, share Etherscan moments, and other activities to earn OG points and redeem limited-edition tenth-anniversary badges. To participate in the event, one needs to hold an active Etherscan account created before August 12, 2025. The official statement indicates that this is not a token airdrop but merely a gesture of appreciation for the anniversary event.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26999</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Investment Commission: Stablecoin as a Cross-Border Remittance Tool Will Reduce Payment Costs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27001</link>
      <description>August 31st. According to a report from Hong Kong 01, Doo Gon Kun, the Chairman of the Hong Kong Investment and Financial Education Committee (Investment Committee), stated in a recent interview that the primary use of stablecoins is as a cross-border remittance tool. If they are widely accepted by society in the future, stablecoins will have the opportunity to lower the cost of cross-border payments. Stablecoins are associated with cryptocurrency and are issued by private institutions and backed by mainstream fiat assets such as the US dollar. However, stablecoins backed by cryptocurrency can exhibit high volatility. Therefore, investments should not be made without a sufficient understanding of the relevant products.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27001</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVC Health Signs Digital Asset Business Cooperation Framework Agreement with QuantumCTek and North China PharmaTech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26998</link>
      <description>On August 31, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Meinian Health Industry Co., Ltd., namely Meinian Health Industry Holding Co., Ltd., entered into a Digital Asset Business Cooperation Framework Agreement with Guofu Quantum Innovation Co., Ltd. and Beijing North Information Technology Co., Ltd. The three parties will leverage their respective resources to explore and cooperate in the field of digital asset RWA, seeking a new paradigm for the value realization of health and medical equipment and data assets and facilitating the upgrading and innovation of the health industry. (Soochow Securities)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26998</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The crypto market has significantly rebounded from fear, with some altcoins leading the way.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26997</link>
      <description>On August 31st, according to HTX market data, the crypto market experienced a notable rebound. Bitcoin rose above $109,000 and Ethereum rose above $4,450. The total cryptocurrency market capitalization rose to $3.877 trillion, with a 24-hour increase of 1%. The Greed Index went from 39 to 48, changing market sentiment from fear to neutrality. Some altcoins took the lead in the rebound, including:DOLO with a 24-hour increase of 36.2% and now trading at $0.293;AXS with a 24-hour increase of 15.98% and now trading at $2.62;JOE with a 24-hour increase of 15% and now trading at $0.176;DASH with a 24-hour increase of 9.3% and now trading at $24.8;CFX with a 24-hour increase of 8.8% and now trading at $0.2;1000Simon&apos;s Cat with a 24-hour increase of 6.2% and now trading at $0.008.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26997</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale is Hoarding 433,176 IP Tokens, Worth $3.7 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26996</link>
      <description>On August 31st, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, a whale address (0x8A1d) has just withdrawn 433,176 IP from Bybit, with a value of $3.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26996</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet received 230,420 SOL tokens and staked them.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26995</link>
      <description>On August 31st, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a newly established wallet received 230,420 SOL from FalconX, which was worth $46.36 million, and then staked the assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26995</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longling Capital once again increased its holdings by 7,000 ETH, worth $30.67 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26994</link>
      <description>August 31. As per the monitoring of EmberCN, Longling Capital once more enhanced its holdings by 7,000 ETH. During the past 5 days, it transferred 20 million USDT to Binance and withdrew 7,000 ETH from Binance 10 minutes ago, with a value of 30.67 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26994</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale 0x8A1d just withdrew 433,176 $IP($3.7M) from #Bybit.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26992</link>
      <description>Whale 0x8A1d just withdrew 433,176 $IP($3.7M) from #Bybit.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 00:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch and US Authorities Seize Online Fake ID Trading Platform VerifTools</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26993</link>
      <description>On August 31st, as reported by Decrypt, Dutch and U.S. law enforcement agencies have confiscated the online platform for trading fake IDs, VerifTools. This marketplace sold counterfeit documents for as little as $9 in cryptocurrency, generating a revenue of $6.4 million, making it one of the largest suppliers of fraudulent identity documents in the world. VerifTools required users to upload a passport photo and enter false data, which the website operators then used to create fake ID documents. These documents were almost indistinguishable from real ones, employing advanced techniques like holograms and UV ink. Users ultimately paid for the forged IDs using cryptocurrency. The operation seized 23 servers, two domain names used by the VerifTools marketplace, and a promotional blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 00:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26993</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>