<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:49:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Reserve Concept Stocks Mixed, BMNR Up 5.15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22674</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on Rockflow market data, the concept stocks related to US cryptocurrency reserves showed mixed trends. Specifically, among Ethereum reserve concept stocks:Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR) increased by 5.15%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) decreased by 2.61%;BTCS Inc (BTCS) rose by 0.9%;GameSquare (GAME) dropped by 0.03%;Bit Digital (BTBT) fell by 0.53%.For BNB reserve concept stocks:CEA Industries (VAPE) declined by 5.61%;Windtree (WINT) rose by 1.42%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22674</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trends Founder Mable: Minting Different Content Tokens is the Future, But Not All Content Should Be Tokenized</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22673</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Mable Jiang, the founder of Trends, served as a guest on BlockBeats&apos; &quot;Content Coin: Hype, Hope, or the Creator Economy&apos;s Second Spring?&quot; Space theme and expressed agreement with the overall view of Jesse Pollak, the founder of Base, on the direction of Content Coin. However, she did not agree with Jesse&apos;s idea of converting all content into tokens, believing that it would not be of much use. Tokens issued that do not have subsequent user transactions prove to be valueless, so she agreed with Toly, the co-founder of Solana, on this point. Nevertheless, she still agreed with Jesse&apos;s overall directional understanding that in the future, there may be millions of tokens minted every day representing various kinds of information, which is definitely the future.A recent intense debate surrounding &quot;Creator Tokens&quot; has ignited the crypto community. Rarely have the founders of Base and Solana personally intervened and engaged in a direct confrontation regarding the platforms ZORA</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Energy adopts Bitcoin as its primary treasury asset, with an initial investment of $5 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22672</link>
      <description>July 31st. The international shipping company Robin Energy listed in the US has made Bitcoin its main treasury asset. It initially invested 5 million dollars and plans to allocate up to 50% of its cash reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale Launches the Grayscale Story Trust</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22671</link>
      <description>On July 31, Grayscale launched the Grayscale Story Trust, which offers investors the chance to invest in the native token IP of the Story network.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Dollar Index (DXY) rose for the first time since May 29, hitting 100.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22670</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the US Dollar Index (DXY) reached 100, which was the first time since May 29th. It rose by 0.23% during the trading day. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22670</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Raises $28 Million in Seed Funding, Led by Bitfinex and Hack VC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22668</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per the report by CoinDesk, Stable, a novel blockchain project centered around Tether&apos;s USDT, announced the accomplishment of a $28 million seed round of funding. This round was spearheaded by Bitfinex and Hack VC, with the participation of investors such as Franklin Templeton, Castle Island Ventures, KuCoin Ventures, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino, and Braintree founder Bryan Johnson.The Stable blockchain intends to utilize USDT as the underlying gas token to construct a swift and low-cost stable payment network. Its roadmap is divided into three stages: in the first stage, it achieves USDT payment gas fees and sub-second block confirmations; in the second stage, it provides block space guarantees for enterprise payments; and in the third stage, it focuses on developer tools and performance enhancements.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22668</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed&apos;s Whisperer」: June Core PCE Inflation Begins to Deteriorate, Some Metrics Even Worse Than During Last Year&apos;s Rate Cut Phase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22669</link>
      <description>On July 31st, in a &quot;Federal Reserve megaphone&quot; communication, Nick Timiraos said, &quot;Core PCE inflation in June seems to be deteriorating and is no more favorable than when the Federal Reserve started cutting rates last year. In some aspects, it is even worse. The June core PCE price index has a 3-month annualized rate of 2.6% (compared to 2.3% a year ago). When calculated on a 6-month annualized basis, this figure is 3.2% (compared to 3.3% a year ago).&quot; (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22669</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willy Woo: Bitcoin Enters Consolidation Phase, Correction and Consolidation May Precede Next Breakout</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22667</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the cryptocurrency analyst Willy Woo tweeted, stating, &quot;July witnesses Bitcoin&apos;s shift from an uptrend to a consolidation stage. The intensified speculation and profit-taking behavior are suppressing the market&apos;s momentum, suggesting that Bitcoin may require a correction or a period of consolidation before attempting the next breakout.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22667</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of initial jobless claims in the United States was roughly flat last week, raising concerns among economists about potential underlying weakness.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22666</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the U.S. Department of Labor announced on Thursday that the number of initial unemployment claims in the United States last week remained stable, which is a source of reassurance. For the week ending July 26th, the number of initial claims for unemployment benefits was 218,000, compared to 217,000 in the previous week. The number of ongoing claims for unemployment benefits was 1.95 million, remaining unchanged from the previous week. Last night, the Fed maintained its interest rate for the fifth consecutive meeting. At a press conference, Fed Chairman Powell stated that the stable labor market suggests no haste to switch to a more accommodative monetary policy stance through rate cuts. However, some economists are concerned that the weakness in the labor market is concealed behind a strong appearance. Despite the still relatively low unemployment rate, many workers report long job search times and difficulties in finding opportunities. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22666</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The key inflation indicator in the United States is rising, while consumer spending is nearly stagnant.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22665</link>
      <description>July 31st: The Federal Reserve&apos;s favored core inflation indicator picked up pace in June and reached one of the swiftest rates this year. Meanwhile, consumer spending witnessed only a minimal growth, highlighting the factors that have led policymakers to differ in their interest rate stances. The data made public on Thursday indicated that the &quot;Core Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) Price Index,&quot; which excludes food and energy prices, rose by 0.3% from May. It also showed a 2.8% year-on-year increase, suggesting that there has been limited advancement in curbing inflation over the past year.The data revealed that inflation-adjusted consumer spending experienced a slight rise in June after a decline in May. These data imply that the economic tug-of-war has caused Fed officials to diverge in their monetary policy directions. On one side, the progress of inflation has essentially come to a standstill, and central bank officials are worried that President Trump&apos;s tariffs may exert</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22665</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>