<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21713</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Trump posted on Truth Social and said, &quot;Everyone is suggesting that I will annul Musk&apos;s substantial subsidies from the U.S. government, thereby ruining his company. This is completely untrue. I desire Musk, as well as all our nation&apos;s companies, to flourish. In fact, they are prospering like never before. The better they perform, the better America performs, and this is beneficial to all of us. We are setting records every day, and I hope this trend will continue.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21713</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opens, Dow Down 0.52%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21715</link>
      <description>On July 24th, when the U.S. stock market opened, the Dow dropped by 0.52%, the S&amp;P 500 increased by 0.14%, and the Nasdaq rose by 0.37%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21715</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Falls 8.9%, Marking Its Largest Decline Since June 5</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21714</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Tesla (TSLA.O) declined by 8.9%, which marked its largest drop since June 5th.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Digital Teams Up with Ethena Labs to Launch First GENIUS Act-Compliant and Federally Regulated Stablecoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21712</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Anchorage Digital, a federally chartered crypto bank in the US, announced a strategic partnership with Ethena Labs. This partnership aims to bring USDtb to the US, enabling it to become a stablecoin with a clear compliance path under the recently enacted &quot;GENIUS Act&quot;. The issuance will be the first to utilize Anchorage Digital&apos;s stablecoin issuance platform, which provides a turnkey solution for institutions to issue and manage fully regulated digital dollars. Anchorage Digital chose to partner with Ethena, which focuses on developing secure and compliance-driven rails and products, offering institutional investors a means to access the unique advantages of digital assets. Through this partnership, the USDtb stablecoin currently issued overseas will be issued in the US by Anchorage Digital. As a result, Anchorage Digital Bank becomes the leading stablecoin issuance institution in the US, serving institutions that seek compliance with the highest regulatory standards of th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle&apos;s interest-bearing stablecoin USYC will be natively issued on the BNB Chain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21711</link>
      <description>On July 24th, BNB Chain released a statement stating that the development of Real World Assets (RWA) on the BNB Chain is experiencing rapid growth. Circle is about to launch an interest-bearing stablecoin, USYC (backed by US Treasuries), on the BNB Chain, which will greatly enhance the capital efficiency of global users. Users can obtain yields, maintain liquidity, improve transaction speeds, and support on-chain operations. Through the BNB Chain native USYC, users can:· Continuously earn yields while using it as collateral.· Exchange for USDC at nearly instantaneous speeds.· Seamlessly access existing tokenized Real World Assets (RWA) within the ecosystem.Circle&apos;s USYC is about to be launched, bringing nearly instantaneous liquidity and continuous yields to the BNB Chain and driving an intelligent upgrade of the Decentralized Finance (DeFi) experience.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21711</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine Updates ETH Holdings: Holds 566,776 ETH, Valued at Over $2 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21710</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Bitmine updated its holdings of ETH. As of 11:59 PM EDT on July 23rd, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing Time on the same day), Bitmine held a total of 566,776 ETH, with a value of more than 2 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21710</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The initial jobless claims in the US unexpectedly decreased last week, keeping the labor market stable.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21709</link>
      <description>On July 24th, last week in the United States, the number of initial jobless claims unexpectedly dropped, suggesting a stable labor market situation. Nevertheless, the slowdown in hiring has made it harder for many laid-off workers to obtain new job opportunities. The data released by the U.S. Department of Labor on Thursday indicated that for the week ending July 19th, the seasonally adjusted initial unemployment claims decreased by 4,000 to 217,000, which was lower than expected. This data has shown a retreat since the initial claims reached an eight-month high in early June.The report also revealed that for the week ending July 12th, the seasonally adjusted continued claims increased by 4,000 to 1.955 million. Goldman Sachs economist Elsie Peng wrote in the report: &quot;Looking ahead, we anticipate that the &apos;stabilization threshold&apos; of employment growth—the monthly net job additions required to maintain a stable unemployment rate—will gradually decrease from the current estimated 90,00</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21709</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgravia Hartford has increased its holdings by 25 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 40.8 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21708</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the publicly-listed company Belgravia Hartford in Canada increased its holdings by 25 BTC, and its total holdings reached 40.8 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21708</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC and CCTP V2 have officially launched on the Sei Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21707</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the native USDC was officially launched on the Sei network with CCTP V2. Circle Mint provides full support for native USDC on Sei, enabling institutional users to access USDC liquidity through Sei&apos;s high-performance infrastructure. By leveraging Sei&apos;s high-performance architecture, over 13-chain cross-chain stablecoin transfers can be achieved without bridging and slippage.The old version Sei USDC.n can still be used, and its users will gradually migrate to the new version of Sei native USDC. Sei is accelerating its pace to become a core infrastructure for cross-chain finance. The native USDC has brought institutional-grade financial infrastructure to Sei. Unlike cross-chain bridged tokens with counterparty risks and usage friction, Sei&apos;s native USDC is directly issued by Circle on Sei, providing developers with the trust and capital efficiency they need.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21707</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satsuma Technology Raises $135 Million to Establish Bitcoin Treasury</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21706</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per Cointelegraph, the London-based artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology has secured ￡100 million (approximately $135 million) to establish a Bitcoin treasury, thereby setting a record for Bitcoin treasury fundraising in the UK.The company declared that it has achieved a higher amount than the targeted one, and all the committed funds are anticipated to be in place within the next two weeks. If all the funds are converted into Bitcoin, this acquisition will position Satsuma as the second-largest corporate Bitcoin holder in the UK, trailing only The Smarter Web Company, which holds 1600 BTC (valued at around $190 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21706</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>