<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:51:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Perplexity AI Makes $34.5 Billion Acquisition Offer to Google-Owned Chrome Browser</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24269</link>
      <description>August 12th. As per The Wall Street Journal, the artificial intelligence search platform Perplexity AI has presented a $34.5 billion acquisition offer to Google&apos;s Chrome browser, with the intention of challenging Google&apos;s search hegemony.Perplexity&apos;s offer is significantly higher than its own valuation (estimated to be $18 billion). Perplexity declared that several investors, comprising multiple large venture capital funds, have given their full support to this transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24269</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAGS&apos; Meme Token PEPE Surges to a Transient Market Cap Exceeding $20 Million, With a 2251% 24-Hour Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24268</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on the data from GMGN, the Meme token PEPE (Pepe By Matt Furie) of BAGS briefly rose above a market capitalization of $20 million and has now retraced to $12 million. The 24-hour trading volume is $16 million, with a 24-hour increase of 2251%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24268</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase has announced the launch of its second Stablecoin Initiative Fund, Bootstrap Fund.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24267</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Coinbase made an announcement regarding the impending launch of the second Stablecoin-Led Bootstrap Fund with the aim of bolstering the stablecoin liquidity in DeFi capital markets. This fund, which is managed by Coinbase Asset Management (CBAM), will initially be allocated to protocols such as Aave, Morpho, Kamino, and Jupiter.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24267</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Launches Kickstart Program, Integrates LaaS to Provide All-in-One Project Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24266</link>
      <description>August 12th. BNB Chain made an announcement regarding the upgrade of the Kickstart Plan. It has been fully integrated with the original LaaS Program. This provides developers and high-potential projects within the ecosystem with quicker and more precise one-stop support. It helps to accelerate the entire process from concept to realization and growth.After the upgrade, the service coverage of the Kickstart Plan has been expanded to 18 major categories and more than 50 top-tier service providers. These include CertiK (for security auditing), AWS and Google (for cloud services), NodeReal (for infrastructure), PancakeSwap (for token issuance), etc. It offers comprehensive resources from technical support, security auditing to fund management, user growth, and marketing promotion for projects at different stages.The plan is divided into two phases:- The dApp Development Phase is targeted at emerging developers and teams, providing foundational support such as development frameworks, s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24266</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morpho Officially Launches on the Arbitrum Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24265</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the lending protocol Morpho officially launched on the Arbitrum network.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24265</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Tariff Pass-Through Effect on CPI is Minimal, Fed Likely to Cut Rates in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24264</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Guy LeBas, the Chief Fixed Income Strategist at Janney Montgomery Scott, stated that July&apos;s CPI roughly met expectations and did not pass too much tariff impact onto consumer prices. This is certainly enough to solidify the possibility of a rate cut in September. There is still a long way to go before the next month&apos;s meeting, but at least in terms of inflation data, the current situation is not a cause for concern. As an independent and impartial economist, one can interpret this data from two perspectives. Firstly, since the tariff effect has not yet fully manifested, future inflation may rise. Secondly, corporate companies are absorbing the tariff impact, so it will not be passed through to consumer inflation. But in either case, it is enough to provide the Fed with a valid reason to cut interest rates in September, provided that next month&apos;s data does not show a significant acceleration. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale/Institution Once Again Increases Holdings by 35,237 ETH, Worth $155.06 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24262</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a &quot;mysterious&quot; whale or institution once more augmented its holdings by 35,237 ETH, which is valued at $1.5506 billion.Its overall holdings reached 328,421 ETH, with a value of $1.445 billion. These holdings are distributed across 10 distinct wallets, and the held ETH originated from FalconX, Galaxy Digital, and BitGo.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24262</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonbirds Floor Price Surges Past 3.2 ETH, Marking a 7-Day Increase of 42.22%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24263</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Blur Data, the floor price of Moonbirds has exceeded 3.2 ETH. It has witnessed a 24-hour price increase of 28.53% and a 24-hour trading volume of 692.09 ETH. The 7-day price increase is 42.22%, with a 7-day trading volume of 1375.3 ETH. Currently, the market capitalization of Moonbirds has entered the top ten of the Ethereum ecosystem NFT rankings.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24263</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader TheWhiteWhaleHL ranks first on the Hyperliquid 30-day Leaderboard, with a profit of $45.8 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24260</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, the top trader @TheWhiteWhaleHL ranked first on the 30-day leaderboard of Hyperliquid with a profit of $45.8 million. During the market crash a few weeks ago, he maintained a long position.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24260</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctum Community has submitted Proposal CLOUD-005, seeking investor support for immediate CLOUD vested release</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24261</link>
      <description>August 12th. In the Solana ecosystem&apos;s LST protocol, the Sanctum community has put forward Proposal CLOUD-005. The intention is to give the Sanctum team the authorization to provide an immediate unlock of their vested CLOUD to investors and allocate 30% of their CLOUD to the team reserve. Currently, 9% of the token supply for Sanctum investors will unlock on a monthly basis over the next 24 months.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24261</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>