<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:41:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit will list the 1000NEIROCTO perpetual contract trading pair.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22621</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bybit will commence the trading of 1000NEIROCTO futures.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22621</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Group has announced the establishment of a treasury worth over $1.5 billion in Bitcoin and SOL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22620</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the UAE-based cryptocurrency, blockchain, and digital asset infrastructure company Phoenix Group announced the formal establishment of a treasury with a value of over $150 million in Bitcoin and Solana. Currently, Phoenix Group holds 514 BTC and more than 630,000 SOL as part of its long-term reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22620</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Official: US to Impose 15% Tariffs on EU Wine and Spirits Starting August 1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22622</link>
      <description>July 31: EU officials declared that starting from August 1, the US will impose a 15% tariff on EU wine and spirits until an agreement on the industry is reached between the EU and the US. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22622</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vana will partner with H&amp;M to hold X Space on July 31st, focusing on the capital potential of cultural data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22619</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Vana is going to host an X Space on the same day with the theme &quot;From Emotion to Value: Unlocking the Capital Potential of Cultural Data on Vana&quot;. It will feature Spotify DataDAO (who recently sold user-owned streaming data to SoloAI), the former Chief Technology Officer Senior Advisor at H&amp;M, Noreen N. who is the founder of BeyondSDG, and Vana Foundation Managing Director Art Abal.This conversation will center around a core viewpoint: personal data is evolving into the most valuable cultural asset of our era. It can predict tastes, drive multi-billion-dollar business decisions, and transform social signals into actual revenue. Whether in the fashion industry or artificial intelligence, we are entering a new economic paradigm - where users not only possess data signals but also determine the ultimate outcome.“As the boundaries among ethics, identity, and income become blurred, we will explore in depth how data ownership is opening up new frontiers of power, value, and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22619</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentora: RLUSD Trading Volume on Aave Hits Approximately $54 Million All-Time High Yesterday</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22618</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to the data disclosed by Sentora, the trading volume of RLUSD on Aave reached a brand new daily peak of 54,521,729.51 RLUSD yesterday.The US dollar stablecoin RLUSD, launched by Ripple, has achieved a market capitalization of $500 million within 7 months since its listing. This product is issued on both the XRP Ledger and Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22618</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address deposited 6427 ETH to a CEX 5 hours ago, totaling $24.7 million in value</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22617</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the address 0x41A...F7277 deposited 6427 ETH into Bybit 5 hours ago, with a value of $24.7 million. This address has had interactions with Mirana Ventures in the past, but its ownership cannot be confirmed at present.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22617</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha and Futures Will List Naoris Protocol (NAORIS), Phase 1 Airdrop Threshold at 228 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22616</link>
      <description>July 31st. Binance Alpha and Futures will list Naoris Protocol (NAORIS). Binance Alpha trading will commence on July 31 at 8:00 PM (UTC+8), and Futures trading will start on July 31 at 8:30 PM (UTC+8). Eligible users can claim a 500 NAORIS token airdrop by using Alpha Points on the Alpha event page within 24 hours after the start of trading.The Binance Alpha airdrop will be carried out in two phases:Phase One (First 18 hours): Users with a minimum of 228 Binance Alpha Points can be eligible for the airdrop.Phase Two (Last 6 hours): Users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha Points can participate in the airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the rewards are not fully distributed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport has completed its second annual XAUm gold reserve audit, with the managed gold holdings increasing by over 500% in the past six months.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22615</link>
      <description>July 31st: Matrixport&apos;s real-world asset (RWA) tokenization platform, Matrixdock, announced the successful completion of the second half of 2025 XAUm gold reserve audit. This has achieved a leading level of asset reserve transparency in the industry. Matrixdock remains committed to secure storage and on-chain real-time accessible asset operation.This audit was carried out by Bureau Veritas, an international inspection group. The audit report issued by Bureau Veritas indicates that they have conducted a 100% audit of the gold inventory held by Matrixdock in multiple vaults. This includes weighing, testing, and sealing of all gold bars. The gold managed by Matrixdock is securely stored in well-protected offline vaults and has independent serial numbers. Currently, Matrixdock holds 421 gold bars, all 1 KG of 99.99% physical gold. Compared to the audit report publicly released in January 2025, the scale of gold managed by Matrixdock has increased by more than 500% in the past six months,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22615</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX Research has released its latest Stablecoin Research Report: Exploring the Far-reaching Impact of Stablecoins on the Global Payment System</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22614</link>
      <description>On July 31st, HTX Research released a significant report titled &quot;New Order of Stablecoins: Global Payment Restructuring, Institutional Empowerment, and Capital War (Part 1)&quot;. This report systematically analyzed how stablecoins have transformed from on-chain transaction tools into a global financial infrastructure, reshaping the landscape of cross-border payments, trade settlement, and capital flow.The report pointed out that by 2024, the total on-chain transaction volume of stablecoins had reached $15.6 trillion, gradually replacing traditional high-cost settlement systems like SWIFT and becoming a key channel for capital flow in developing countries. As the regulatory frameworks such as the U.S. GENIUS Act, EU MiCA regulation, and Hong Kong licensing system became clearer, stablecoins were entering a crucial window of comprehensive compliance and institutionalized development.The report proposed a &quot;two-stage rocket&quot; expansion path for stablecoin development. The first stage was le</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22614</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink has increased its holdings today by an additional 11,259 ETH, with a transaction amount of approximately $43.09 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22613</link>
      <description>On July 31, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, SharpLink Gaming once again increased its holdings by 11,259 ETH from Galaxy Digital today. The transaction amount is approximately $43.09 million, and the average purchase price is around $3,827. SharpLink transferred an equivalent amount of USDC to Galaxy Digital 10 hours ago and received ETH about 15 minutes ago.SharpLink Gaming has accumulated a total of 449,000 ETH. The current holding market value reaches $1.74 billion. The average acquisition cost is around $3,011, with an unrealized gain of approximately $386 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22613</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>