<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitfinex Analyst: Altseason Kickoff to Hinge on Altcoin ETF Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26276</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per the report by Cointelegraph, a Bitfinex analyst stated that unless an ETF is launched to enable investors to access higher-risk crypto assets, altcoins may not experience a widespread and exaggerated rebound.With Bitcoin (BTC) losing 6% of its market dominance in the past 30 days, crypto market participants have been looking forward to a rebound in the altcoin market, or the so-called &quot;alt season.&quot; However, in a market report released on Monday, the Bitfinex analyst expressed the expectation that an &quot;alt season&quot; is unlikely to occur before the latter part of this year, only when capital flows into Bitcoin products regain momentum and new investment tools for altcoins are introduced.The Bitfinex analyst stated that the current market shows a &quot;low risk appetite&quot; in this cycle. They added, &quot;Although the inflow of funds remains positive, the mild trend reflects a more cautious investor sentiment, in contrast to the aggressive demand witnessed during previous all-</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26276</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Protocol spent 1.4 million USDS to buy back 20.06 million SKY in the past week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26277</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Sky Protocol (formerly known as MakerDAO) tweeted that they had allocated 1.4 million USDS in the past week and used it to repurchase 20.06 million SKY.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26277</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the United States Ethereum spot ETF saw a net inflow of $4.439 billion, while the Bitcoin spot ETF saw a net inflow of $2.191 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26275</link>
      <description>August 26: As reported by Farside Investors, the net inflow into the US Ethereum spot ETF yesterday was $443.9 million.There was a net inflow of $219.1 million into the US Bitcoin spot ETF yesterday.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26275</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX Financial CEO: ETF Issuers Must Choose Carefully, Most Cryptocurrencies &apos;Quite Unreliable&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26274</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per Cointelegraph, Greg King, the CEO of REX Financial, stated that the issuers of cryptocurrency exchange-traded funds (ETFs) should give careful consideration to which cryptocurrencies to include in the exposure of their funds. This is because most cryptocurrencies are &quot;rather unreliable.&quot;Greg King said in an interview with Bloomberg&apos;s ETF IQ on Monday: &quot;Cryptocurrencies outside the top ten are quite unreliable, especially those outside the top twenty. Issuers need to make strict selections when choosing the underlying assets.&quot; He also expressed that he believes that ETF applications for various cryptocurrencies will not witness &quot;explosive growth,&quot; but rather anticipates &quot;many funds for each type of coin.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26274</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ETH Queued for Exiting the Ethereum PoS Network Rises to 914,000, While Over 620,000 ETH is Waiting to Join</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26273</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network has risen to 914,690 ETH, which is approximately worth $40.3 billion. The withdrawal delay has been extended to 15 days and 21 hours.At the same time, the ETH waiting to join the network is about 623,750 ETH, approximately worth $27.5 billion. It is also showing an upward trend, and the current waiting time in the admission queue is 10 days and 20 hours.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may choose to cash out significantly after the sharp rise of Ethereum since the April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have increased their ETH holdings and are</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26273</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale sold 886,000 HYPE tokens and 1,630,000 Fartcoin tokens, and went long on 51,691 ETH with 15x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26272</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as monitored by LookOnChain, in the past 12 hours, Whale 0xa523 sold 886,287 HYPE tokens ($39.66 million) and 1.63 million Fartcoin tokens ($1.27 million), resulting in a loss of $1.14 million and went long on ETH. He took a 15x leveraged long position on 51,691 ETH ($2.267 billion). Currently, he is facing an unrealized loss of more than $13 million, with a liquidation price of $4,075.7.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 4 years of silence, a whale withdrew 6,334 ETH from Kraken.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26271</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as monitored by LookOnChain, Whale 0x4097, which had been dormant for 4 years, withdrew 6,334 ETH (equivalent to 28.08 million USD) from Kraken 50 minutes ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26271</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve&apos;s September interest rate cut probability is 84.6%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26270</link>
      <description>August 26: Based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch Tool&quot;, there is a 15.4% probability that the Fed will maintain interest rates in September. Meanwhile, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 84.6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26270</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUI Treasury Management Company Mill City Ventures III has today officially rebranded as SUI Group Holdings (SUIG).</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26269</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the SUI Treasury Management Company Mill City Ventures III announced its rebranding to Sui Group Holdings. It will commence trading on Nasdaq under the new ticker symbol SUIG starting from August 26, 2025.SUI Group indicated that the renaming is aimed at strengthening its treasury strategy positioning within the Sui ecosystem and better aligning with SuiFoundation. As the sole publicly listed company with an official association with the Sui Foundation, the group will focus on promoting the development and adoption of the Sui Network while providing long-term value to shareholders.The company stressed that existing shareholders do not need to take any actions regarding this renaming and ticker symbol change. The stock will continue to be listed on the Nasdaq Capital Market and will remain eligible for options trading on Cboe Global Markets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26269</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins will be launching a Soulbound Token called Early to the Party</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26268</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the NFT series Pudgy Penguins is going to launch a Soulbound Token named Early to the Party. Users are required to pre-download Pudgy Party and go through the registration process. Once the game is launched, the tokens will be distributed to eligible wallets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26268</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>