<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:54:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has accumulated over 39,000 ETH through FalconX in the past two days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23238</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to Arkham Monitoring, Whale 0x86F purchased $1.416 billion worth of ETH from FalconX within the past two days. The total quantity purchased was 39,294 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23238</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Threatens to Increase Tariffs on India Significantly Amid Russian Oil Trade, India and Kremlin Respond</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23239</link>
      <description>August 5th: On August 4th, US President Trump gave a threat that he would increase tariffs on India significantly. According to media like Reuters and Sky News UK, India responded on the 5th, indicating that it would take all necessary actions to safeguard national interests and economic security.Sky News UK reported that a spokesperson for the Indian Ministry of External Affairs said that since the Russia-Ukraine conflict broke out, India has been &quot;targeted&quot; by the US and the EU because of importing oil from Russia. &quot;In fact, the reason why India began to import oil from Russia was that after the conflict occurred, traditional oil supplies shifted to Europe,&quot; the spokesperson stated. &quot;At that time, the US actively encouraged India and similar import activities to enhance the stability of the global energy market.&quot; According to the latest news from Agence France-Presse on the 5th, the Kremlin in Russia also criticized Trump&apos;s threat to increase tariffs on India, emphasizing that &quot;sov</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23239</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Robin Energy makes its first $3 million Bitcoin purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23237</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as monitored by @btcNLNico, the publicly listed company Robin Energy in the US made its first purchase of Bitcoin worth $3 million to implement its Bitcoin treasury strategy.Robin Energy is a publicly listed company in the US with its headquarters in Cyprus and specializes in international vessel ownership and providing global energy transportation services.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23237</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Bounces Back Above $115,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23236</link>
      <description>On August 5th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin rebounded and rose above $115,000. It is currently trading at $115,033.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23236</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Concept Stocks See Mixed Pre-market Trading, BNMR Up 1.35%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23235</link>
      <description>On August 5th, based on the market data from Rockflow, the pre-market trading of U.S. crypto stocks showed a mixed performance. This includes:The largest Ethereum hodler institution BNMR increased by 1.35%;SBET rose by 2.61%;CRCL decreased by 1.63%;COIN experienced a slight drop of 0.13%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23235</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance&apos;s new Alpha project INFINIT unveils Tokenomics: 5% of the total supply allocated for the initial airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23234</link>
      <description>August 5th. Binance&apos;s new Alpha project INFINIT made the tokenomics announcement. The team declared that 5% of the total supply is set aside for the initial airdrop. The purpose of this is to achieve two strategic goals:- Reward Past Contributions: Acknowledge early product users and community members for their feedback, concept validation, and idea dissemination regarding INFINIT.- Support Future Participation in Agentic DeFi Economy: Offer the community IN to enable them to directly participate in further shaping the Agentic DeFi economy, whether through governance participation, staking, or direct engagement in one-click agent execution.Consequently, holders of INFINIT Stones, INFINIT Yappers, community contributors, and ecosystem partners will be entitled to this airdrop. The airdrop portal will open for claiming starting from August 7, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23234</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Launch Composite Index Universal Perpetual Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23233</link>
      <description>August 5th. As per an official announcement, Binance Futures is set to launch the ALL 75x Composite Index U Perpetual Contract on August 6, 2025, at 5:00 PM (UTC+8).The Binance ALL Composite Index tracks all USDT-margined perpetual contracts on Binance Futures, with the following exclusions:The ETHBTC perpetual contract;U Perpetual Contracts quoted in USDC or other stablecoins;U-margined delivery contracts;Composite Index perpetual contracts;Perpetual pre-market trading;Coin-margined perpetual and delivery contracts.The Binance ALL Composite Index is calculated by using the weighted average price of all constituent real-time index prices.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23233</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockworks Team Discloses Asset Holdings, Including BTC, ETH, SUI, ENA, HYPE, etc.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23232</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Jason Yanowitz (Yano), the co-founder of Blockworks, released his personal asset disclosure for August. Yano&apos;s holdings this month comprise: BTC, ETH, SOL, HYPE, FARTCOIN, ENA, SUI, XRP, AVAX, TIA, as well as equities COIN, HOOD, GLXY, and certain NFTs.According to Blockworks&apos; policy, all employees who hold public-facing roles or create content are required to disclose holdings of a single asset exceeding $5000; holdings below this threshold are not disclosed.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonbirds: Holders of the relevant NFTs with Towns Wallets bound before the snapshot are eligible for the TOWNS airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23231</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to an announcement from the NFT project Moonbirds, holders of Moonbirds, Mythic, and Oddity who had bound their Towns Wallets before the snapshot are eligible to receive a TOWNS airdrop. It is crucial to note that the airdrop query address is not the user&apos;s NFT holding address but the Towns Wallets address bound to the holding address.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23231</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Trump will sign an executive order to protect cryptocurrency companies and individuals from the impact of &quot;debanking.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23230</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per The Wall Street Journal, President Trump is in the process of preparing to sign an executive order that focuses on financial institutions engaging in de-risking behavior towards businesses and individuals, including cryptocurrency companies.Based on a draft of the executive order that was accessed by the media, the decree intends to address the discrimination against cryptocurrency companies and conservative individuals. It poses a threat of fines against banks that cut off customer relationships for political reasons and imposes consent orders or other disciplinary actions. The executive order also directs regulatory agencies to conduct investigations into whether any financial institutions have violated the Equal Credit Opportunity Act, antitrust laws, or consumer financial protection laws. Nevertheless, the executive order does not name any specific companies. Sources with knowledge of the matter stated that the executive order could be signed as early</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23230</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>