<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:24:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「ETH-native Microstrategy」 SharpLink announces total holdings increased to approximately 438,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22304</link>
      <description>July 29th. The &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot;, SharpLink (SBET), officially declared that it currently holds approximately 438,190 ETH. From July 21st to 27th, SharpLink purchased about 77,210 ETH at a total cost of approximately $290 million, with an average price of around $3,756.The per-ETH share (&quot;ETH Concentration&quot;) is now about 3.4, which is higher than around 3.06 from last week. Since implementing the Ethereum Treasury strategy on June 2nd, the per-ETH share has increased by about 70%, and the cumulative staking reward has reached approximately 722 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「SOL Version of MicroStrategy」 DDC Increases Holdings by 181,300 SOL, Total Holding Reaches approximately 1.18 Million SOL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22303</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as reported by Business Insider, the &quot;SOL Version of MicroStrategy,&quot; DDC, augmented its holdings by 181,300 SOL. The total holding amounts to approximately 1.18 million SOL. Additionally, it will raise $20 million through a securities line of credit, with around $10 million of the proceeds still available for future accumulation of SOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22303</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has launched TREE and will list TREE spot trading at 22:00</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22302</link>
      <description>July 29th. Binance Alpha has initiated Treehouse (TREE). Additionally, Binance will commence TREE spot trading on July 29th, 2025, at 22:00 (UTC+8). Trading pairs will include USDT, USDC, BNB, FDUSD, and TRY. TREE will hold a Seed Label.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22302</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) Warns of Suspicious Investment Products Named &quot;FoFund,&quot; &quot;Fo Coin,&quot; and &quot;Peach Blossom Land NFT&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22301</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission issued a warning to the public, cautioning them to be on guard against suspicious investment products named &quot;FoFund Dodo No. 1&quot; and &quot;FoFund Dodo No. 2&quot;, &quot;Fo Coin&quot;, and &quot;Peach Blossom NFT&quot;. These products involve management strategies related to virtual asset investment, digital tokens, and related unique tokens of art, and have not received authorization from the Commission for offering to the Hong Kong public. It should be noted that the Hong Kong public can obtain information about these products through the respective websites, social media accounts, and associated mobile apps of the products.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22301</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance C2C Escrowed Trading Section Launches New Test Phase, Providing 50% Reimbursement Guarantee to Enhance Asset Trading Security</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22300</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement made by Binance, Binance C2C is set to launch a &quot;Curated&quot; section. This particular section will be occupied by platform-curated Trusted Advertisers or Bulk Advertisers. In the event that a user&apos;s sell transaction within the Curated section undergoes a funds freeze due to the Advertiser, the user will be entitled to a 50% compensation of the transaction amount. The maximum compensation limit per transaction is 20,000 USDT, thereby providing users with enhanced asset security.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22300</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company Bakkt has announced its intention to conduct an initial public offering to raise approximately $75 million for investing in Bitcoin and other digital assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22299</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Businesswire, the publicly traded company Bakkt Holdings (BKKT) in the US announced that it will issue Class A common stock and prepaid warrants to purchase up to 746,373 shares of Class A common stock. The total fundraising amount is estimated to be approximately $75 million. Bakkt intends to utilize the net proceeds from this offering to purchase Bitcoin and other digital assets in line with its investment policy, use them as working capital, and for general corporate purposes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22299</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Company ZOOZ Announces $180 Million Private Placement to Launch Bitcoin Treasury Reserve Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22298</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Globenewswire, the U.S. listed company ZOOZ Power Ltd. (ZOOZ) made an announcement regarding a private placement of $180 million and the initiation of a Bitcoin treasury reserve strategy. This private investment in public equity (PIPE) still requires approval from shareholders and is expected to sell 180 million shares of common stock along with pre-funded warrants at a price of $1 per share. The participants in this PIPE comprise strategic investors such as Pantera Capital, FalconX, Arrington Capital, UTXO Management, ATW Partners, and the renowned Israeli investor Alex Rabinovitch.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22298</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Listed Company ZOOZ&apos;s Pre-market Gain Widens to 22.54%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22297</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to the market data of RockFlow (with the URL https://rockflow.ai/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats and targeted at _blank), the U.S.-listed company ZOOZ Power Ltd. (ZOOZ) witnessed its pre-market gains expand to 22.54%, and the stock price currently stands at $4.21.ZOOZ Power Ltd. (ZOOZ) announced a $180 million private placement to implement a Bitcoin treasury reserve strategy. The participants include strategic investors such as Pantera Capital, FalconX, Arrington Capital, UTXO Management, ATW Partners, and the well-known Israeli investor Alex Rabinovitch.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22297</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company Marti Technologies has initiated a Cryptocurrency Treasury Strategy, planning to allocate 20% of its cash reserves to hold BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22296</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Businesswire, Marti Technologies (MRT), a New York Stock Exchange-listed Turkish app development company, announced the commencement of a crypto treasury strategy. Initially, it intends to allocate 20% of its cash reserves to hold BTC, and will subsequently raise this ratio to 50% and acquire other crypto assets like Ethereum and Solana.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana On-chain Market Update: New Coin MAU, CLUELESS Trading Volume Surges into Top Five; Blue Chip Sector SUNK, CMINI Goes Live and Sparks Frenzy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22295</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to data from GMGN, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume within the past 24 hours are TRUMP, Fartcoin, Bonk, MAU, and CLUELESS. Among them, both the MAU and CLUELESS tokens have been listed for less than 24 hours, presenting high risks. Investors, please pay attention to the security of your funds.Based on GMGN&apos;s recommendations in the &quot;Next Blue Chip&quot; section, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume within the past 24 hours are SUNK, CMINI, Falcon1, AutoTrader, and GOLDPEPE. It should be noted that tokens in the blue chip sector are often listed for less than 24 hours, with concentrated holdings, and pose high risks. Investors, please pay attention to the security of your funds.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins often lack practical use cases and have significant price volatility, and investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22295</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>