<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:29:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Long ETH Liquidation」 Whale Long Position Partially Liquidated, Unrealized Gain Drops to $1.13 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26131</link>
      <description>August 25th. According to ChainInfo, the long position of the &quot;Long ETH with $125k Leveraged Position&quot; whale in ETH was partially liquidated once more. The open long position profit has decreased from $5.5 million to $1.13 million.After the liquidation and reduction, the whale still maintains 14.6k ETH long positions, which are worth $67.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26131</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainOpera Ranks Top on the BSC Chain AI Project List, Driving the Development of the &quot;Collaborative Intelligence&quot; Ecosystem, with AI Users Surpassing 3 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26132</link>
      <description>On August 25th, ChainOpera AI achieved the top position on the daily list within the AI category of DApp Bay on the BNB Smart Chain (BSC), emerging as the AI DApp with the highest on-chain transaction volume.The official announcement on X conveyed that ChainOpera has ascended to &quot;the first among AI projects and the second in the overall ranking&quot; on the BNB Smart Chain and expressed gratitude to the community, users, and developers.Since proposing the concept of &quot;Collaborative Intelligence,&quot; ChainOpera has constructed a full-stack collaborative AI ecosystem, encompassing Agent social networks, the Intelligent Agent Marketplace, and decentralized AI infrastructure (models, computing power, data), attracting more than 3 million users and 100,000 developers. Super AI applications based on the Agent social network continuously release strong community vitality and user stickiness.This ranking at the top of DApp Bay indicates that ChainOpera has further consolidated its leading position i</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26132</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch MTP, and the airdrop claiming threshold is set at 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26130</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per official channels, Binance Alpha is set to launch Multiple Network (MTP), and Alpha trading will commence on August 25, 2025, at 22:00 (UTC+8).After the trading initiates, users possessing at least 200 Binance Alpha Points can obtain 750 MTP tokens through a first-served basis airdrop. In case the reward pool is not entirely distributed, the points threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points every hour.Claiming the airdrop will require 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must complete the confirmation on the Alpha Events page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the claim.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26130</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy, Jump, and Multicoin seek to raise $1 billion to purchase SOL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26129</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to Bloomberg, Galaxy, Jump, and Multicoin are aiming to raise $1 billion in order to purchase SOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26129</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin drops below $110,000, the cumulative long liquidation pressure on mainstream CEXs will reach 1.128 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26128</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to Coinglass data, in the event that Bitcoin drops below $110,000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.128 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin surges above $115,000, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.332 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not provide an exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows the extent to which the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that when the price reaches that point, a more intense reaction will occur due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has increased its holdings by 254.92 BTC, accumulating a total position of $249 million in BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26127</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale once more received 254.92 BTC from FalconX, which is valued at $28.57 million. Currently, within the past month, this whale has amassed a total of 2,219 BTC, and the total value is approximately $249 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26127</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $112,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26126</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $112,000 and is currently trading at $111,916, with a 24-hour decrease of 2.68%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26126</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XerpaAI makes its debut at WebX, unveiling the world&apos;s first AI Growth Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26125</link>
      <description>On August 25th, XerpaAI officially launched the world&apos;s first AI Growth Agent (AGA) and put forward the brand slogan &quot;Speed Up Your Growth.&quot; It is committed to providing an all-in-one intelligent growth solution for emerging projects.According to data, more than 70% of pre-listed Web3 projects lack dedicated growth personnel, and more than half of the budget is difficult to generate effective results. XerpaAI combines the Create-Distribute-Optimize growth model with an AI-driven system to help projects achieve real engagement. Through the Xerpa Index, complex influence metrics are quantified into standard scores to assist in data-driven decision-making.XerpaAI will also successively launch features such as Creative Labs 2.0 and Autonomous Agents to continuously expand the boundaries of AI-driven growth. The management team stated: &quot;Our goal is to be the &apos;Sherpa&apos; for emerging projects and guide them across the growth peak.&quot; The release of XerpaAI also marks the entry of Web3 growth</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26125</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Profited $1.72 Million from a LINK Swing Trade and Reopened a $16.85 Million LINK Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26123</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale that had made a profit of $1.72 million from scalping LINK two years ago has resurfaced. It recently purchased 663,580 LINK (with a value of $16.85 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Unveils New Brand Image at WebX Summit, Founder Dr. Han Delivers Keynote Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26124</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the WebX Summit commenced in Tokyo, Japan. The globally prominent cryptocurrency exchange Gate unveiled its novel brand image at this event, emphasizing its latest attainments in transaction security, compliance systems, and diversified ecosystem development. By means of interactive demonstrations, the event presented the platform&apos;s comprehensive strength in asset protection, innovative products, and global strategic planning to the participants. Additionally, Gate&apos;s founder and CEO, Dr. Han, delivered a keynote speech during the conference, sharing global cryptocurrency industry trends and platform strategic concepts.As the title sponsor of this conference, Gate will host an exclusive VIP Side Meeting in Tokyo on the evening of August 26th, serving as the official Side Meeting event of WebX. The event will invite project teams, capital institutions, and ecosystem partners from the Asia-Pacific region and around the world to have in-depth discussions on regional colla</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 06:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26124</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>