<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:34:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater Associates Founder Ray Dalio Sells Remaining Stake, to Step Down from Board of Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22752</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as reported by Reuters, in a letter addressed to investors, Ray Dalio, the founder of Bridgewater Associates, has sold his remaining stake in the fund. Dalio established the Bridgewater hedge fund 50 years ago, and this transaction signals the conclusion of a multi-year transition for the world&apos;s largest hedge fund with $92.1 billion in assets under management. Ray Dalio, who is 76 years old, stepped down as the CEO in 2017 and is scheduled to transfer the control of the Bridgewater hedge fund to a new generation of investors in 2022. A source disclosed that Ray Dalio will also resign from the board.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink: The per-mil &quot;ETH concentration&quot; has increased from around 2 to around 3.4, a 70% increase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22751</link>
      <description>August 1st, The &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink Gaming declared that our mission is to maximize shareholder value while holding as much Ethereum as possible. To ensure full transparency, we not only report the issued number of shares or the amount of ETH held but also monitor the ETH amount within every 1000 shares of ownership. We refer to it as &quot;ETH Concentration&quot;, which indicates how much Ethereum is supporting every 1,000 shares of SBET stock. Since the implementation of the ETH Treasury strategy, the &quot;ETH Concentration&quot; has risen from approximately 2.00 to about 3.40, representing a 70% increase.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22751</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot Blockchain&apos;s Net Revenue Reaches $219.5 Million in Q2, Mining Cost Doubles Year Over Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22750</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per TheBlock, the Bitcoin mining firm Riot Platforms attained a net revenue of $219.5 million during the second quarter of 2025. This reversed a net loss of nearly $300 million in the first quarter. As of this year, Riot Platforms has accumulated a net loss of $76.9 million. Owing to the global average network hash rate increase, the cost of mining one Bitcoin has gone up by 93% compared to the same period last year. In the second quarter, Riot Platforms mined 1,426 Bitcoins, raising their total holdings to 19,273 Bitcoins and ranking fourth among publicly traded global companies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22750</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In July, the U.S. Ethereum Spot ETF saw a precise net inflow of $54.309 billion, setting a new monthly record for inflows</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22749</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as monitored by Farside Investors, the precise data indicates that the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF in July reached $5.4309 billion, setting a record for the highest monthly inflow. Ethereum&apos;s monthly low began at $2485.47 and closed at $3698.39, representing a roughly 48.8% increase. This marks the highest monthly gain since August 2022. During this period, it reached a 2025-year-to-date high of $3941.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22749</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Ethereum Spot ETF has seen net inflows for 20 consecutive trading days, with yesterday&apos;s inflow reaching $17 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22748</link>
      <description>Update: On August 1st, based on the information from Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF was $17 million the previous day, indicating that it has seen net inflows for 20 consecutive days.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22748</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; has officially come into effect today, opening the first round of stablecoin issuer license applications.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22747</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; in Hong Kong officially came into effect today. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority has opened the application for stablecoin issuance licenses, marking a new stage in the development of stablecoins in the Hong Kong region. Over the past year, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority has promoted sandbox testing of stablecoin application scenarios, gradually clarifying regulatory guidelines and application processes. Now, participating institutions will transition from testing to the formal issuance and circulation under the regulatory framework. According to incomplete statistics, dozens of institutions have indicated that they will apply for a stablecoin license, including JD Coin Chain Technology (Hong Kong) Limited, RoundCoin Innovation Technology Limited, Standard Chartered Bank (Hong Kong) Limited, Onchain Group Limited, Hong Kong Telecommunications (HKT) Limited, and others. Meanwhile, more local banks, tech companies, and Web3 teams are making fu</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22747</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the U.S. Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net outflow of $114.8 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22745</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on the data from Farside Investors, yesterday the net outflow of the US Bitcoin spot ETF was $114.8 million. Specifically, Fidelity FBTC had a net outflow of $53.6 million, and ARK Invest&apos;s ARKB witnessed a net outflow of $89.9 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22745</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In July, the net inflow into the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF totaled $6.0126 billion, marking the third-highest monthly inflow in history.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22746</link>
      <description>August 1st. As reported by Farside Investors, the exact figure for the net inflows into the July US Bitcoin spot ETF was $6.0126 billion, which constitutes the third-highest monthly inflow in history. The Bitcoin monthly candle began at $107,146.51 and ended at $115,764.08, representing an approximately 8.04% increase. During this time, it reached a historical high of $123,218.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22746</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale in a Certain Circle Rebuys 20,000 ETH, Worth Around $74.06 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22744</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, a whale trader who has cumulatively made a profit of $73.96 million in ETH trades has begun to purchase ETH again. In the past 4 hours, this address transferred 173 million USDT to Wintermute and then received 20,000 ETH, which is approximately worth $74.06 million.The whale previously bought 132,000 ETH in June at an average price of $2540 and sold 113,600 ETH in July at an average price of $2923, realizing a profit of $43.5 million. Currently, this address holds 40,000 ETH with an average holding price of $3121.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum August Historical Returns: rose 3 times and fell 6 times since 2016, with an average return of 5.5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22743</link>
      <description>August 1st. According to Coinglass data, within Ethereum&apos;s history, among the 9 &quot;August&quot; price movements since 2016, there were 3 instances of increase and 6 instances of decrease. The most significant monthly increase took place in August 2017, with a gain of 92.86%; the most substantial monthly decrease occurred in August 2018, with a decline of 34.79%. From 2016 up to the present, Ethereum&apos;s average rate of return during &quot;August&quot; is 5.5%, and the median rate of return is -4.54%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22743</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>