<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The US stock EMPD has announced that it has increased its holdings by 110 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 3913 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23111</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per the report in businesswire, Empery Digital Inc. (NASDAQ: EMPD) declared today that since the previous update on July 31st, the company has made an additional purchase of 110.00 Bitcoins, with a total purchase value of 12.6 million dollars. As of the moment of this press release, the company possesses a total of 3913.23 Bitcoins, with a total purchase expenditure of approximately 460 million dollars, and an average purchase price of 117,629 dollars per Bitcoin.According to rockflow data, EMPD has witnessed a 6.97% increase in pre-market trading and is currently trading at 10.43 dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23111</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget will list SUP and TOWNS spot trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23110</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per official information, Bitget is set to list SUP and TOWNS in its Innovation Zone, and the deposit channels have already been opened. Trading for these assets will begin on August 5th at 19:00 and 22:30 (UTC+8) respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23110</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After a brief 3% increase, TON experienced a 5% decrease and is now trading at $3.45.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23109</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on HTX market data, the TON price experienced a brief surge of 3% and reached $3.648. This might have been influenced by the news that Verb Technology, a US-listed company, raised $558 million to establish the TON Treasury. Subsequently, the price dropped by approximately 5% and is currently trading at $3.455.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23109</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock DFDV Announces Increase in Holding of 110,000 SOL, Bringing Total Holdings to 1,293,000 SOL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23108</link>
      <description>August 4th. As per official channels, the US-listed company DeFi Dev Corp. (DFDV) announced that it has made an addition of 110,466 SOL, resulting in its total holdings reaching 1,293,562 SOL (approximately $209 million).The official statement showed that, based on an average purchase price of $166.61, its &quot;Per SOL Holding&quot; (SPS) has witnessed a surge of 47% within the past 30 days and has reached 0.0618 SOL.According to rockflow data, DFDV&apos;s stock price has increased by 4.63% in pre-market trading and is currently at $14.7.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23108</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verb Technology to Raise $558 Million in Private Funding for TON Reserve Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23106</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to market information, Verb Technology Co. (NASDAQ: VERB) announced a private placement of approximately $558 million with Kingsway Capital to establish the first publicly traded TON financial strategy company.Previously, BlockBeats reported that Manuel Stotz, the founder and CEO of Kingsway Capital, disclosed at the end of June that the institution&apos;s largest token holding to date is TON, and the venture capital firm started purchasing TON tokens two years ago (earlier than Pantera Capital).Bloomberg also reported on July 24th that the TON Foundation and Kingsway Capital plan to raise $400 million for the Toncoin treasury.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23106</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Pharma Company Artelo Announces Launch of Solana Reserve Asset Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23107</link>
      <description>On August 4th, the pharmaceutical company Artelo Biosciences (Nasdaq: ARTL) announced the accomplishment of a $9.475 million off-market private placement. This placement will be employed to initiate a Solana (SOL)-centered digital asset reserve strategy, thereby making it the first publicly traded pharmaceutical company to incorporate SOL as a reserve asset.This private placement involves the issuance of common stock (or pre-funded warrants) at a price of $10.45 per share. Additionally, there are two tranches of warrants with exercise prices of $10.20 and $50 respectively, and a three-year term. The transaction is anticipated to be completed on August 5, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23107</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ether Machine has announced an increase in holdings of 10,605 ETH, bringing the total holdings to 345,362 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23105</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as reported by globenewswire, The Ether Machine and Dynamix Corporation (Nasdaq code: DYNX) jointly announced today that the subsidiary, The Ether Reserve LLC, has increased its holdings by 10,605 ETH at an average price of $3,781. This action constitutes a crucial part of its long-term accumulation strategy. To date, the total amount of ETH purchased and locked up by the company since the start of this month has reached 345,362 ETH.The funds utilized for this purchase originate from the $97 million cash reserve that was raised in the company&apos;s previously announced private placement financing. After acquiring approximately 15,000 ETH last week to mark the tenth anniversary of Ethereum, this additional purchase indicates a continuous progression in its strategic layout.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23105</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin asset management company ProCap BTC has appointed Bitwise Alpha&apos;s Head of Strategy, Jeff Park, as Chief Investment Officer.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23104</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on market information, Anthony Pompliano&apos;s Bitcoin asset management firm ProCap BTC has appointed Jeff Park, the head of strategy at Bitwise Alpha, as the chief investment officer. ProCap BTC currently possesses 4,950 bitcoins but is awaiting the completion of the merger.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameSquare increased its position by buying an additional 2717 ETH, bringing the total holding to 15,630 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23103</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on market information, GameSquare has given approval to a stock buyback plan that is financed by Ethereum earnings. It has set aside $10 million to repurchase 2,717 ETH, thereby increasing its treasury holdings to 15,630.07 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23103</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy increased its position last week by purchasing an additional 21,021 BTC, spending $2.46 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23102</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to market information, from July 28th to August 3rd, Strategy made an investment of $2.46 billion to purchase an additional 21,021 BTC with an average cost of $117,256 per coin.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23102</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>