<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:37:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>White House Cryptocurrency Report Officially Released</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22539</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the White House Cryptocurrency Report was officially made public. From the construction of railways connecting the East and West coasts to the connection of the world through the internet, since its establishment, each generation of American entrepreneurs has led the construction of the next-generation technology. &quot;Crypto 3.0&quot; should be no exception.As the author of this report, the Working Group is of the opinion that digital assets and blockchain technology can not only completely innovate America&apos;s financial system but also innovate ownership structures and governance systems across the entire economic system. American entrepreneurs who pioneer emerging industries using these technologies should receive clear policy guidance and full recognition of their achievements. The core policy recommendations are as follows:· American citizens and businesses should have the right to legally hold digital assets and use blockchain technology without the fear of being held acco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve Interest Rate Decision saw two board members dissenting, marking the first time in nearly 30 years.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22538</link>
      <description>July 31st. On Wednesday, the Federal Reserve maintained the interest rates unchanged. There was a rare division in the decision-making process, and no definite indication was given regarding when a rate cut might take place. This decision encountered opposition from two of Trump&apos;s appointed governors, Waller and Bowman. Both of them think that the current monetary policy is too tight.This is the first time in more than 30 years that two governors dissented in a decision. The FOMC voted 9 to 2 to keep the target federal funds rate within the 4.25%-4.50% range and maintained the status quo for the fifth consecutive meeting.In its statement, the Federal Reserve stated that &quot;the unemployment rate remains low and the labor market remains strong. Inflation remains slightly above the target.&quot; The statement also pointed out that economic growth &quot;slowed&quot; in the first half of the year. If this trend continues, it could strengthen the case for a rate cut at a future meeting. However, the stat</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traders Still Fully Expect the Fed to Cut Rates at Least Once by 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22537</link>
      <description>July 31, Traders still firmly anticipate that the Fed will cut rates at least once by 2025. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump imposes an additional 40% tariff on Brazil, bringing the total tariff to 50%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22536</link>
      <description>July 31, in the White House, USA: Trump signs an executive order imposing an additional 40% tariff on Brazil, raising the total tariff to 50%. (GoldenFinance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve Keeps Interest Rates Unchanged for the Fifth Consecutive Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22535</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the Federal Reserve maintained the interest rate at the same level for the fifth consecutive time.The Federal Reserve maintained the benchmark interest rate at 4.25% - 4.50%, which was in line with market expectations. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOMC Statement: Fed Governors Waller, Bowman Dissent on Rate Decision</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22534</link>
      <description>On July 31, the Federal Reserve FOMC issued a statement. Federal Reserve Governors Waller and Bowman dissented from keeping interest rates unchanged. Economic growth showed a slowdown in the first half of this year. The uncertainty regarding the economic outlook remains at a high level. (Kryptonite)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22534</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fed Removes Language Indicating Reduced Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22533</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the Federal Reserve removed the language suggesting that the uncertainty has been reduced. (Kinjun)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22533</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Powell may not cut interest rates today, heard the Fed will cut rates in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22532</link>
      <description>On July 31st, U.S. President Trump said that Powell might not cut interest rates today. Keeping a high rate is harming the people.A high rate is hurting those who want to buy homes. Rates should be lowered. I heard that the Fed will cut rates in September. Powell is too slow.Powell always acts too late. Even if he &quot;takes action&quot; today. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22532</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Advisor: Data Indicates Fed Has Justification for Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22531</link>
      <description>On July 31st: Senior Advisor Hassett of the White House declared that the data indicates that the Fed has grounds to lower interest rates. A great many economists hold the view that the Fed has been overly slow in taking action. We respect the independence of the Fed.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22531</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institution: Any dovish suggestions for September could potentially boost Bitcoin&apos;s price</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22530</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Matthew Sigel, the Director of Digital Asset Research at VanEck, stated that &quot;Bitcoin serves as a hedge against currency depreciation. If the Federal Reserve hints at adopting a more dovish policy stance in the future, the cryptocurrency market is likely to interpret it as a green light.&quot;LMAX Group&apos;s Market Strategist, Joel Kruger, said that &quot;All eyes will be focused on the Federal Reserve and the upcoming cryptocurrency policy report from the White House. Any dovish tone from the Federal Reserve or hints from the White House regarding the strategic purchase of Bitcoin reserves could quickly reverse Bitcoin&apos;s recent weakness.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22530</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>