<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>TACEO Completes $5.5M Seed Round Funding, with a16z CSX Participation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22680</link>
      <description>July 31st. The cryptocurrency data company TACEO concluded a $5.5 million seed round of financing. The financing was led by Archetype VC and was participated in by a16z CSX, Cyber.Fund, a_capital, and Polymorphic Capital. This round of funding will expedite the launch of TACEO&apos;s innovative data infrastructure product, &quot;Private Shared State&quot;. This product enables collaborative computation, validation, and updating of encrypted data sets without the necessity of a trusted central authority or the exposure of data.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tako Founder Edison: The purpose of Content Coin bringing traffic is to build consensus, and consensus building is what brings Holder.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22679</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Edison, the founder of Tako Protocol, who was a guest on BlockBeats&apos; &quot;Content Coin: Hype, Hope, or Creator Economy Revival?&quot; themed Space, stated that content coin is the hope to drive traffic by means of content creation, and then tokenize the traffic through content. Traffic and attention are the sole values of content tokens. The ultimate goal of bringing traffic through content coins is to achieve consensus. Traffic is merely the foundation of consensus, and the consensus aggregation of users brings Holder.Ongoing Space: https://x.com/i/spaces/1vAxRDOWWqkGl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22679</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: 99% of CFOs Plan to Adopt Cryptocurrency in the Long Term, with 23% Expecting to Adopt Within Two Years</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22678</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per the report by Cointelegraph, based on Deloitte&apos;s Q2 2025 survey of Chief Financial Officers (CFOs), cryptocurrency is emerging as a priority in corporate financial planning. A whopping 99% of CFOs from billion-dollar-level enterprises anticipate incorporating it into their business scenarios in the long run.This survey encompassed 200 CFOs of enterprises with an annual revenue exceeding $1 billion, and 23% of them expect their finance departments to utilize cryptocurrency for investment or payment within the next two years. In enterprises with an annual revenue over $10 billion, this proportion is nearly 40%.Although there is a strong adoption trend, financial executives remain vigilant. Price volatility stands as the primary hurdle in adopting non-stablecoin, with 43% of the respondents citing it as a major concern. Other significant concerns include complex accounting treatment (42%) and regulatory uncertainty (40%), and the latter is particularly prominent d</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22678</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liu Feng: Pump.Fun is no longer just a Meme issuance platform; Meme creation is also a form of content creation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22677</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Liu Feng, a partner at BODL Ventures, as a guest on BlockBeats&apos; themed Space titled &quot;Content Coin: Hype, Hope, or the Second Spring of the Creator Economy?&quot;, stated that he did not clearly sense the distinct boundary between Meme coins and content coins. Today, Pump.Fun is no longer merely a Meme issuance platform. Many people have a fondness for it, and those who love Pump.Fun will bestow upon it countless different stories and interpretations. A more prevalent interpretation is that Pump.Fun is actually a live streaming platform, a news platform, and more significantly, a platform for creating socially trending content. This kind of meme token that motivates everyone to create is actually a type of content coin.Space in progress: https://x.com/i/spaces/1vAxRDOWWqkGl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22677</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernstein: Crypto Bull Market Cycle Still &apos;Early Stage&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22676</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as reported by The Block, Bernstein said that the current crypto bull market cycle is still in its nascent stage. Trading platforms like Robinhood and Coinbase are set to gain from the increased trading volume and the mainstream market&apos;s adoption. Bernstein reiterated its &quot;outperform&quot; rating for both companies and remained confident in their performance.The report indicates that Robinhood&apos;s second-quarter performance, which was announced on Wednesday, was remarkable and it continues to expand its cryptocurrency products. In July, its trading volume reached a six-month high, benefiting from the resurgence in market volatility and factors such as its listing on Circle. Investors&apos; interest in ETH, SOL, and DeFi tokens is on the rise, and it is expected that cryptocurrency trading volume will increase significantly in the second half of the year. Additionally, the report mentioned Coinbase&apos;s strategic partnership with JPMorgan Chase, which has significantly promoted the mai</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22676</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Appeals Court Overturns Fraud Conviction of OpenSea Former Product Manager Nathaniel Chastain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22675</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per Reuters, the U.S. Appeals Court reversed the fraud conviction of Nathaniel Chastain, the former product manager of OpenSea. This case was once regarded by prosecutors as the first one involving &quot;insider trading&quot; in digital assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22675</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Reserve Concept Stocks Mixed, BMNR Up 5.15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22674</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on Rockflow market data, the concept stocks related to US cryptocurrency reserves showed mixed trends. Specifically, among Ethereum reserve concept stocks:Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR) increased by 5.15%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) decreased by 2.61%;BTCS Inc (BTCS) rose by 0.9%;GameSquare (GAME) dropped by 0.03%;Bit Digital (BTBT) fell by 0.53%.For BNB reserve concept stocks:CEA Industries (VAPE) declined by 5.61%;Windtree (WINT) rose by 1.42%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22674</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trends Founder Mable: Minting Different Content Tokens is the Future, But Not All Content Should Be Tokenized</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22673</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Mable Jiang, the founder of Trends, served as a guest on BlockBeats&apos; &quot;Content Coin: Hype, Hope, or the Creator Economy&apos;s Second Spring?&quot; Space theme and expressed agreement with the overall view of Jesse Pollak, the founder of Base, on the direction of Content Coin. However, she did not agree with Jesse&apos;s idea of converting all content into tokens, believing that it would not be of much use. Tokens issued that do not have subsequent user transactions prove to be valueless, so she agreed with Toly, the co-founder of Solana, on this point. Nevertheless, she still agreed with Jesse&apos;s overall directional understanding that in the future, there may be millions of tokens minted every day representing various kinds of information, which is definitely the future.A recent intense debate surrounding &quot;Creator Tokens&quot; has ignited the crypto community. Rarely have the founders of Base and Solana personally intervened and engaged in a direct confrontation regarding the platforms ZORA</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Energy adopts Bitcoin as its primary treasury asset, with an initial investment of $5 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22672</link>
      <description>July 31st. The international shipping company Robin Energy listed in the US has made Bitcoin its main treasury asset. It initially invested 5 million dollars and plans to allocate up to 50% of its cash reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale Launches the Grayscale Story Trust</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22671</link>
      <description>On July 31, Grayscale launched the Grayscale Story Trust, which offers investors the chance to invest in the native token IP of the Story network.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>