<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:29:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Who Shorted BTC Four Times in a Row is Still &quot;Holding the Bag,&quot; with an Unrealized Loss of $12.81 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24541</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the whale that has been shorting BTC four times starting from March 2025 is still maintaining its position. Over the course of two months, its 20x leveraged BTC short position has transitioned from a floating profit of $5.74 million to a floating loss of $12.81 million. However, it has managed to earn $4.33 million through funding fees.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Surges Above $865 in Short Time, Hits All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24540</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on HTX market data, BNB briefly soared above $865 and is currently trading at $861.79. It hit a new all-time high with a 24-hour change of 3.19%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin Shows No Clear Signs of &quot;Overheating&quot; Yet, Current Main Risk is a Normal Pullback</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24539</link>
      <description>On August 14th, CryptoQuant analyst Axel Adler Jr. posted that although Bitcoin reached a new all-time high, the Bitcoin Price Temperature (BPT) still remained at a moderately high level of 2.56 (below the local peak of 3.57). This shows that the current cycle is in the &quot;warm&quot; range but has not yet shown significant signs of overheating. The price is maintaining above the four-year moving average and its +2σ, confirming a bullish trend.The main risk is a normal pullback in the uptrend, and the &quot;endgame&quot; signal will appear when BPT accelerates above 3.0.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin drops below $120,000, the mainstream CEX long liquidation volume will reach $1.569 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24538</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Bitcoin continued to decline in the afternoon. It is currently priced at $121,625, with a 1.44% drop occurring in nearly 4 hours.According to Coinglass data, if Bitcoin falls below $120,000, the cumulative long liquidation strength of mainstream CEXs will reach $1.569 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin rises above $123,000, the cumulative short liquidation strength of mainstream CEXs will reach $977 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of the liquidated contracts. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, strength.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows the extent to which the underlying price will be impacted when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will have a more intense reaction due to a surge in liquidity.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches USDC Lending with Limited-Time 4% APY Discount</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24537</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to official channels, Binance has made an announcement regarding a USDC Reward Program. From 16:00 on August 15, 2025 (in UTC time) until 15:59 on September 16 (in UTC+8), users who newly take out a loan or hold USDC loans through Binance Margin or Savings will be able to enjoy a fixed annual percentage yield (APY) of 4%. This event is available to regular users up to VIP 9 and encompasses products such as Savings, VIP Loans, Cross Collateral, Isolated Margin, and Institutional Lending.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Partner: October Market Cap or Peak, Ethereum sees $6900, SOL sees $420</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24536</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Chris Burniske, who was formerly the lead of Ark Invest&apos;s crypto and is now a partner at Placeholder VC, predicted the following peak prices for major cryptocurrencies in October: Bitcoin: $142,690; Ethereum: $6,900 - $8,000; SOL: $420. Chris Burniske also noted that the crazier the prices in August, September, and October are, the more convinced he is that October will be the top. If the market can experience a sharp correction soon and remain relatively calm, perhaps this bull run could last even longer.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: Overlay Protocol (OVL) Airdrop Threshold 200 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24535</link>
      <description>On August 14th, according to official channels, the trading of Binance Alpha&apos;s new project, Overlay Protocol (OVL), is set to commence on August 14, 2025, at 15:30 (UTC+8). After the trading begins, users who hold at least 200 Alpha points will be eligible to claim a 111 OVL token airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event has not ended, the point threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashKey Cloud partners with OneInfinity to launch Slashing Insurance, providing comprehensive protection for customer staked assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24534</link>
      <description>August 14th, HashKey Cloud officially declared a strategic partnership with OneInfinity by OneDegree, which is the first licensed digital asset insurance company in Asia. Together, they launched an on-chain staking* insurance solution. This partnership will offer professional Slashing insurance services to crypto investors, Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs), and crypto custodians. It enables users to participate in the DeFi and staking ecosystem with confidence and explore new opportunities for value growth safely and efficiently.HashKey Cloud is dedicated to providing users with secure and professional staking services. By integrating OneInfinity&apos;s innovative slashing insurance, we effectively address the slashing penalty risk caused by validator nodes. This comprehensively safeguards customer staked assets from accidental losses and provides solid protection to maximize customer returns.Customer asset security is the core commitment of HashKey Cloud. Recognizing the potential losses f</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24534</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbos DEX Cumulative Trading Volume Surpasses $7 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24533</link>
      <description>On August 14th, according to official channels, the flagship project within the Sui ecosystem, Turbos DEX, has officially exceeded a total trading volume of 7 billion USD. The official announcement noted that they will continue to cooperate with builders in the Sui ecosystem to promote DeFi innovation.Furthermore, at present, several liquidity pools on the platform offer attractive yields and provide multiple token incentives. These include an APY of 172.51% for SUI/USDC, an APY of 16.73% for USDT/USDC, and an APY of 24.26% for TURBOS/SUI.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24533</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK June GDP 3-Month Average Monthly Growth Rate 0.3%, Expected 0.1%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24532</link>
      <description>August 14th: In the UK, for the June 3-Month period, GDP MoM was 0.3%. The expected value was 0.1%, and the previous value was revised from 0.5% to 0.6%. In the UK, for June, Industrial Output MoM was 0.7%. The expected value was 0.2%, and the previous value was revised from -0.9% to -1.3%. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 06:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24532</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>