<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:49:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Cemtrex purchases $1 million worth of SOL, planning to establish a $10 million cryptocurrency reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22793</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the Nasdaq-listed company Cemtrex (stock code: CETX) announced that it had acquired $1 million worth of SOL as the initial step in its digital asset reserve strategy. The company purchased 5500 SOL at an average price of $181 per coin and intends to gradually expand the size of its cryptocurrency reserves to $10 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22793</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan: Lowers Coinbase Price Target from $405 to $375</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22792</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the financial institution Jefferies issued a report indicating that it had reduced Coinbase&apos;s target price from $405 to $375. (Securities Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>华兴资本: Applying to Expand Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission Type 1, 4, and 9 Licenses to Include Digital Asset Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22791</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per AASTOCKS, Zi Yuan Shi, the Head of Proprietary Investment at Huaxing Capital, stated that &quot;The company will continuously and actively embrace Web3.0 and the digital asset industry. By leveraging its professional capabilities and high-quality resources through investment banking services, strategic funds, and direct investments, etc., it aims to empower the Hong Kong digital industry ecosystem. The company has applied to expand its Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission Type 1, 4, 9 licenses to cover digital asset business. And it looks forward to collaborating with industry partners to enhance investment and construction efforts in digital asset financial infrastructure, on-chain ecosystems, and RWA assets, jointly promoting industry innovation, stable development, and assisting Hong Kong in becoming a global digital asset hub.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22791</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Non-Farm Payrolls Data will be released tonight, and the results will have a significant impact on the Fed&apos;s September interest rate decision.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22790</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the July employment report, which is scheduled to be released at 8:30 p.m. Beijing time on Friday, is anticipated to indicate an addition of 110,000 jobs, a notable decline from June&apos;s 147,000. The unemployment rate is expected to increase from 4.1% to 4.2%, and the average hourly earnings are predicted to rise by 0.3%, which is higher than June&apos;s 0.2%. If the forecast proves accurate, it will strengthen the perception of a decelerating job market, although it may not necessarily call for a response from the Fed.Earlier this week during the interest rate meeting, Powell did not offer guidance on the September rate decision, suggesting that there is a significant amount of data to be disclosed before then. Friday&apos;s July nonfarm payroll report will be a part of the puzzle that will assist in shaping expectations for a September Fed rate cut.Analysts note that if the nonfarm payroll data is below 100,000 and the unemployment rate rises, it may imply a weakening job mark</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22790</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: U.S. Fiscal Uncertainty Still Core Driver of Hard Asset Appreciation, but Short-Term Consolidation Possible</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22789</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Matrixport released its latest report indicating that the core catalyst for Bitcoin&apos;s new round of increase is gradually coming into view. Although there have been frequent positive developments in Ethereum (such as ETF inflows, increasing institutional allocations, and the SEC possibly approving staking mechanisms), the funding rate has only risen to 15%, suggesting that the market heat has not yet completely dissipated.The report mentioned that August and September have historically been relatively weak months for Bitcoin&apos;s performance throughout the year. With the latest FOMC meeting having concluded and the next meeting scheduled for September 17th, lacking short-term policy catalysts, the market may shift into a wait-and-see mode and enter a consolidation phase.Furthermore, U.S. fiscal uncertainty remains a core driver of the rise in hard assets. The recent proposal by Trump for a $5 trillion debt ceiling expansion plan has already led to a more than 10% increas</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22789</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum briefly dropped below $3,600, marking a 4.64% decrease in the last 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22788</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to HTX market data, Ethereum briefly fell below $3,600 and is currently trading at $3,611, with a 24-hour decrease of 4.64%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22788</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Reserve Concept Stock Pre-market Generally Down, BMNR Pre-market Down 6.9%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22787</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on the market data from Rockflow, the pre-market trading of US crypto stock reserve concept stocks generally declined. This includes:The largest holder of Ethereum, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), saw a 6.9% drop in the pre-market;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) experienced a 5.74% pre-market drop;MSTR saw a 3.03% pre-market drop;CRCL had a 3.71% pre-market drop;Coinbase witnessed a 11.07% pre-market drop.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22787</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions, a digital identity verification platform, has raised $30 million in funding, with participation from Polychain, Coinbase Ventures, and others.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22786</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to official channels, the digital identity verification platform Billions declared that it has successfully completed a financing round of $30 million. This round of financing was spearheaded by Polychain, Coinbase Ventures, Polygon, LibertyCityVentures, BITKRAFT Ventures, and others. The funds from this financing round will be employed to construct the first universal human-machine and artificial intelligence network.The Billions Network is a digital identity verification platform formulated to offer a future of mutual trust between humans and artificial intelligence. The platform makes use of zero-knowledge proof technology to provide a scalable and secure approach to verifying the identities of both humans and artificial intelligence.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22786</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Insider Trader」 @qwatio&apos;s short position opened this morning is now up over $3.3 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22785</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio&apos;s short positions in BTC (40x) and ETH (25x) opened this morning have now amassed a profit of over $3.3 million.This morning, the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio transferred 2.98 million USDC to Hyperliquid to initiate short positions in BTC and ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22785</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ark Invest bought 60,000 shares of Figma yesterday, worth approximately $6.93 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22784</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to Ark Invest Daily, Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest purchased 60,000 shares of Figma the previous day. Given the closing price of $115.5, the stake is valued at around $6.93 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>