<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 10:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 10:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched the U-based YZY perpetual contract, with leverage ranging from 1 to 20x.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25554</link>
      <description>On August 21, as per an official announcement, Bitget has declared the launch of the U-based YZY perpetual contract. The leverage offered ranges from 1 to 20x. Additionally, the contract trading BOT will be made available simultaneously.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25554</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Hedge Fund Short Position Increases to $4.19 Billion, Ethereum Price May Continue to Face Downward Pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25553</link>
      <description>On August 21st, a BiyaPay analyst pointed out that the recent Ethereum price failed to break through a crucial resistance level, resulting in another round of market downturn. The bearish pressure in this round of the market is mainly driven by large hedge funds. These funds have been increasing their Ethereum short positions and attempting to trigger stop-losses by pushing down the ETH price. According to The Block&apos;s &quot;CME Ether Futures Net Position&quot; data, the current number of Ethereum shorts has reached an unprecedented level, indicating a strong market expectation for a further decline in the Ethereum price.Especially in August, hedge funds&apos; Ethereum short positions nearly doubled, rising from $2.3 billion on August 5th to $4.19 billion. This change indicates that institutional investors continue to bet on the Ethereum price maintaining a downward trend. In the current market environment, the increase in short positions is one of the main factors putting pressure on the Ethereum p</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25553</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: Tron will adjust network transaction fees based on the market to stay competitive</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25552</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Justin Sun announced on social media that Tron super representatives are fully cognizant that as the price of TRX surges during a bull market, the network transaction fees are continuously on the rise. The Tron community will adjust the network fees in accordance with the actual situation to ensure the competitiveness of the Tron network.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese clothing retailer Mac House has officially established a crypto reserve, making its first purchase of 17.51 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25551</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as per @btcNLNico, the nationwide chain clothing retailer Mac House in Japan announced that it had made its first purchase of 17.51 BTC. This was part of a &quot;proof of concept&quot; operation, with a Bitcoin reserve target set at 1000 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale has reduced a $2.95 billion ETH long position, continuously selling BTC to exchange for ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25550</link>
      <description>August 21st. Based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, this morning, a Bitcoin ancient whale that sold 550 BTC of leveraged long positions on Ethereum is reducing its holdings of 68,130 ETH (approximately $295 million) of long positions and switching to purchasing ETH spot.In the past 6 hours, it has deposited 1000 BTC into Hyperliquid (approximately $113.95 million) to buy ETH. As of now, it has bought 19,794 ETH (approximately $85 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Market Cap Surpasses Rolls-Royce, Global Asset Market Cap Ranking Rises to 187th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25549</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on 8marketcap data, the market capitalization of BNB has exceeded $119 billion, surpassing Rolls-Royce and ranking 187th in the global asset market capitalization.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25549</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnicornX will host a new UniCall Countdown AMA today at 9:00 PM.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25548</link>
      <description>August 21st. UnicornX declared that it is going to hold a brand new UniCall countdown AMA at 21:00 (UTC+8) on August 21st. The keynote speakers comprise Anna Ann (the Founder of Unicorn Verse and an Investor in UnicornX), Wang Xin (a member of the Fair3 CTO Team), Crypto Charity (a well-known KOL and Trader), and Archer (the Research Director of Unicorn Verse).It is reported that UnicornX will make the latest UniCall project public during the AMA. Historical data indicates that previous projects have achieved an average growth of +507.3% after launching UniCall.In addition, to commemorate this AMA, UnicornX will randomly choose 3 lucky participants from the X (Twitter) interactions, and each of them will receive 100 X Points.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25548</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale is currently longing both BTC and YZY, with an unrealized loss of over $300,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25547</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale deposited 2.087 million USDC into Hyperliquid. It then went long on BTC with 40 times leverage, resulting in an unrealized loss of $36,000. At the same time, it went long on YZY with 3 times leverage, leading to an unrealized loss of $288,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25547</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: Bitcoin Traders on Edge Ahead of Powell&apos;s Jackson Hole Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25546</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as per Bloomberg, digital assets are experiencing a weakening trend as traders prepare themselves for the highly anticipated speech by Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Friday at the Jackson Hole Symposium.In the US, Bitcoin and Ethereum spot ETFs have witnessed outflows for four consecutive trading days, with investors&apos; net withdrawals amounting to $1.9 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25546</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs Announces U.S. Expansion Plan and Seeks Community Vote on Network Parameter Adjustment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25545</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Sonic Labs presented a community proposal indicating its aspiration to establish Sonic USA LLC in order to initiate its U.S. operations. The proposal encompasses the hiring of a Sonic USA CEO and a full U.S. team, the setup of a New York office, and the implementation of a performance-based employee incentive program. Furthermore, the company intends to enhance long-term deflation through a Gas Fee mechanism.Community members will engage in voting to determine the adjustments of network parameters: to approve the issuance of tokens for a $50 million ETF allocation, a $100 million Nasdaq PIPE deal, $150 million in S tokens for Sonic USA, or to reject all the aforementioned parameter adjustments.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 09:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25545</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>