<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:42:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market and Cryptocurrency Stocks opened with mixed results, SBET up by 1.77%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25778</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on market information, US stock cryptocurrency shares opened with a mixed performance:Coinbase (COIN) decreased by 0.4%;Circle (CRCL) increased by 0.54%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) fell by 1.14%;Bitmine (BMNR) dropped by 0.84%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET), which announced a $1.5 billion stock repurchase plan today, rose by 1.77%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25778</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The South Korean court has ordered Wemade to compensate a former employee approximately $7.14 million in arrears.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25777</link>
      <description>August 22nd. As per Nwes1, the Seoul Central District Court has issued a partial ruling in favor of the plaintiffs in a compensation lawsuit that current and former employees had brought against Wemade. The court has determined that Wemade is required to compensate them a combined total of 99.3928 billion Korean won (approximately $7.14 million).In July of the previous year, 27 current and former executives and employees of Wemade filed a lawsuit against the company, seeking 161.7648 billion Korean won in compensation. Those who had been working at Wemade&apos;s subsidiary, Wemade Tree, claimed that the company had promised to make payments but had failed to do so, thus leading to the filing of the lawsuit.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25777</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Collins: Current US Economic Inflation Faces Upside Risk, Labor Faces Downside Risk</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25776</link>
      <description>August 22: Federal Reserve official Collins noted that the current US economic inflation is exposed to upside risks, while the labor market is facing downside risks. We cannot afford to wait for all uncertainties to subside (in order to discuss interest rate adjustments).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trinity Dispute Resolution Plan (DvP) for Security Tokens Based on Stablecoins Launched to Facilitate Cross-Chain Settlement between Japanese Stablecoin and Security Token.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25775</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to an official announcement by Cosmos, Project Trinity, a DvP (Delivery versus Payment) settlement project driven by stablecoins and initiated by financial institutions such as Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation (SMBC), Progmat, Boostry, and Datachain, has officially begun. TOKI is participating in this project as a technical partner. The project intends to utilize the IBC protocol and LCP technology to achieve cross-chain atomic swaps between stablecoins and security tokens across blockchain platforms like Avalanche and Quorum.Currently, in Japan, the stablecoin market has been growing rapidly following the updates to the &quot;Payment Services Act,&quot; enabling the compliant issuance of stablecoins to facilitate more efficient and secure financial transaction settlements. The security token market continues to expand, with the issuance reaching over 193.8 billion yen (approximately 1.3 billion USD) by the end of July 2025. Project Trinity aims to eventually achieve</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25775</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huaxin Capital Partners with YZi Labs to Invest Approximately $100 Million in Strategic Allocation of BNB Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25774</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to an announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, Huaxing Capital has announced a strategic cooperation memorandum with YZi Labs. The purpose is to support applications in the BNB and BNB Chain ecosystems and establish a mutually beneficial partnership. The cooperation includes the following aspects:Huaxing Capital&apos;s leading strategic BNB special allocation: The company will invest approximately $100 million in a special allocation of BNB assets, aiming to become the first Hong Kong-listed company to include BNB in a special digital asset allocation.Promotion of Web3 ecosystem-related initiatives and facilitation of BNB&apos;s listing on compliant exchanges.Establishment of a Real World Asset (RWA) Fund and promotion of BNB Chain ecosystem projects.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25774</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: If Powell delivers a hawkish speech tonight, ETH may retest $4000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25773</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of BitMEX, expressed his views on the impact of Powell&apos;s interest rate policy on the crypto market during his appearance on the Crypto Banter podcast. The key points are as follows:1. He doesn&apos;t believe that Powell has to do anything. Personally, he won&apos;t trade based on the assumption that &quot;the Fed cuts rates by 50 basis points.&quot; If Powell insists on not cutting rates, the government will definitely find a way to &quot;squeeze out liquidity.&quot;2. The market is very likely to replay the 2022 scenario - anticipating a rate cut, but Powell suddenly delivers a &quot;hawkish blow,&quot; resulting in a market crash.3. If Powell delivers a hawkish speech at Jackson Hole, ETH may retest $4000 first.Regarding stablecoins, Arthur Hayes said that people&apos;s imagination about stablecoins is not big enough. Treasury Secretary Benson will use stablecoins to reverse the trend of &quot;de-dollarization&quot; - bringing back global offshore dollar flows to the United States whil</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25773</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Betting Powell to Stay Hawkish on Rate Cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25772</link>
      <description>August 22nd. The data of currency options indicates that the bullish sentiment towards the US dollar has reached the highest level in three weeks. Traders are betting that Powell will not adopt an overly dovish stance on interest rate cuts. &quot;The possibility of a 25-basis-point rate cut in September will be maintained,&quot; said Sonja Martens, the director of FX and currency policy research at Deutsche Bank. &quot;But I don&apos;t think he will be more aggressive than that.&quot;Martens suggested that Powell may resist the pressure from Trump for rate cuts and will &quot;very clearly show that he will not take a path that may lack fundamental support due to the pressure from the White House.&quot; Nick Rees, the head of macro research at Monex Europe, said that if the market &quot;overreacts&quot; to any hints from Powell about a possible rate cut in September, it may trigger the initial selling of the US dollar. However, this situation may be temporary. &quot;Overall, we expect a hawkish tone, which will further strengthen the</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25772</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Mixed Feelings Economic Data May Force Powell to Strike a Balance in Tonight&apos;s Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25771</link>
      <description>August 22: Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is scheduled to deliver a speech at the Jackson Hole Annual Economic Symposium at 10 p.m. Beijing time on Friday. Currently, the Fed is encountering unprecedented political pressure from the United States. However, the mixed economic data may compel Powell to adopt a moderate stance, leaving key issues unresolved.Regarding the interest rate policy, some analysts anticipate a middle-of-the-road approach. Powell may potentially leave the door open for a rate cut in September to recognize the necessity for further easing due to weak job growth. Nevertheless, he will not make more definite commitments until policymakers are more certain that the rising inflation is temporary. This stance may not satisfy Trump, who advocates for a significant cut in rates to around 1%, nor investors who are betting on multiple rate cuts this year. Although the market&apos;s confidence in a September rate cut has already shown signs of wavering. (Golde</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink&apos;s Board of Directors Approves $1.5 Billion Stock Repurchase Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25770</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per an official announcement, the Ethereum treasury firm SharpLink disclosed that its board of directors had given the green light to a stock buyback plan, with a maximum buyback amount of $1.5 billion for the company&apos;s common stock.SharpLink&apos;s Co-CEO Joseph Chalom stated, &quot;At SharpLink, we are consistently committed to a rigorous capital market strategy. In the event that our stock&apos;s trading price reaches or drops below the net asset value (&apos;NAV&apos;) of the ETH we hold, issuing new shares through financing would lead to a dilution of the per-share ETH equity. In such a situation, a value-enhancing approach could be to repurchase our common stock. This plan enables us to flexibly respond to these circumstances and take prompt and decisive action.&quot;The stock buyback plan is designed to enhance market support, optimize capital allocation, and strengthen SharpLink&apos;s long-term dedication to driving sustainable shareholder value. Repurchases under this plan may be carried</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25770</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messari has released the BNB Chain Q2 2025 Report: DEX Trading Volume, Stablecoin Transaction Count, and Active Users Lead the Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25769</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the most recent BNB Chain Q2 2025 report presented by Messari indicates that the BNB Chain has maintained its robust growth during the second quarter, with record-breaking user activity and on-chain transactions. Daily active addresses and transaction volume have witnessed significant surges, and the DeFi activity remains vigorous. The DEX trading volume, stablecoin transaction count, and active users all claim the top positions across the chain, thereby solidifying its leading status within the Web3 ecosystem.**Key Highlights:**Market Capitalization and Investor Confidence: The market capitalization of BNB increased by 7.5% during the quarter, reaching $92.6 billion.On-Chain Transactions and Activity: The average daily transaction volume rose by 101.9% to 9.9 million transactions, and the average daily active addresses grew by 33.2% to 1.6 million. In May, there were 17 million new addresses.DEX Performance: The DEX trading volume ranked first across the chain,</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25769</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>