<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:52:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Trading Volume Increases by 30% After Aerodrome Integrates with Coinbase DEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26436</link>
      <description>August 27th: Based on Aerodrome Finance data, since August 8th when it integrated with Coinbase DEX, the trading volume has witnessed a 30% increase. During the two weeks prior to the integration, Aerodrome&apos;s trading volume was $8.7 billion. However, in the two weeks following the integration, the trading volume rose to $11.3 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26436</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Surges Past $200, with a 24-hour Gain of 4.81%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26435</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to HTX market data, SOL has exceeded $200 and is currently trading at $200.1, with a 24-hour percentage change of 4.81%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26435</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock&apos;s Securitize CEO: RWA Tokenization Represents $20 Trillion Market Potential, Ethereum Leads the Space</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26434</link>
      <description>August 27th. The CEO of Securitize, Carlos Domingo, under the Belldex brand, made a post via the Ethereum official X account. He stated that Real World Assets (RWA) represent a market potential exceeding $20 trillion, yet only a small fraction of it is on-chain. In terms of market value, Ethereum is the leading blockchain in the RWA field, but we are still in the early stages. Even a 1% market share could bring an opportunity of over $200 billion.Domingo pointed out that Securitize mints on-chain native assets, with 68% (over $23 billion) on Ethereum. Many issuers believe that Ethereum provides the safest, most composable, and censorship-resistant foundation for tokenized financial products. Tokenized stocks are the next step in bringing real-world financial markets onto the blockchain. Since the global stock market is valued at approximately $100 trillion, it is difficult to overstate the long-term opportunity of anchoring these assets on Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaplanet extensively exercised stock options and redeemed a portion of the bonds early</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26433</link>
      <description>August 27th - Metaplanet Inc. made an announcement today. From August 14th to 26th, 2025, EVO FUND substantially exercised its Series 20 stock subscription rights, with a total of 27,500,000 shares, accounting for 14.86% of the total issued shares. Meanwhile, the company used the funds obtained from the exercise of subscription rights to partially redeem ￥5,250,000,000 of the Series 19 common bonds. After multiple redemptions in July and early August, the total redemption amount reached ￥21,000,000,000.After this stock issuance, the company&apos;s total issued shares increased to 739,714,340 shares, and the unexercised subscription rights decreased to 460,000 rights (equivalent to 46,000,000 shares).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26433</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 10 million USDC into Hyperliquid to buy HYPE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26432</link>
      <description>August 27th. Based on on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the address 0xFF0...24FbF withdrew 10 million USDC from Coinbase within the past hour. Subsequently, it was deposited into Hyperliquid to purchase $9 million worth of HYPE. Currently, there remains $1 million with a limit buy order at $49.306.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US-based cloud development platform company Vercel&apos;s AI-powered frontend development tool v0 now accepts USDC for purchasing credits.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26431</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to official information, the AI frontend development tool v0 of the U.S.-based cloud development platform company Vercel has announced that users are now able to purchase v0 points by using USDC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26431</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee Updates Ethereum Price Target Prediction: Surge to $5,500 in a Few Weeks, Year-End Target of $10,000 to $12,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26430</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Tom Lee, the chairman of BitMine, recently stated in a live interview with amit that he anticipates Ethereum to rise to $5500 within a few weeks, with a year-end target price ranging from $10,000 to $12,000. Generally, in the cryptocurrency market, significant movements often occur in the fourth quarter. &quot;So, if you have already achieved a 35% gain since the beginning of the year and need to end up with a 200% gain for the year, most of that gain is likely to happen in the next few months.&quot;However, Tom Lee also expressed worries about a potential seasonal market correction in September. Nevertheless, he still emphasized that &quot;a dip presents a buying opportunity.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX C2C has launched a new &quot;Freeze Compensation&quot; system: up to 100% compensation with a limit of 30,000 USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26429</link>
      <description>According to an official proclamation, on August 27th, 2025, OKX officially initiated a novel &quot;Frozen Compensation&quot; system. Users engaging in transactions with merchants marked with &quot;Frozen Compensation&quot; will be qualified for a compensation ratio of up to 100% and a maximum single claim limit of 30,000 USDT in the event that their receiving account is frozen due to the counterparty&apos;s payment. At the same time, they will also receive support from the platform&apos;s funds, enhancing security and protection.It is reported that only high-quality merchants that have passed strict audits can obtain the &quot;Frozen Compensation&quot; qualification. These include Bulk Compensation Merchants and Certified Compensation Merchants. Among them, Bulk Compensation Merchants have paid a substantial security deposit, ensuring safety, reliability, and strong compensation capabilities. Certified Compensation Merchants are certified by the platform and provide stable compensation in accordance with the rules. Users</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26429</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYPE records a 24-hour price increase of 11.77%, continuing to hit an all-time high</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26428</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on market data, HYPE reached a peak of $49.798. Currently, it is trading at $49.37, showing a 24-hour percentage increase of 11.84% and setting a new all-time high.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26428</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain user insider traded on the news of Taylor Swift&apos;s engagement, accurately purchasing relevant prediction shares on Polymarket</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26427</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to the crypto KOL @Domahhhh, a Polymarket user named &quot;romanticpaul&quot; has been vigorously betting on the prediction of Taylor Swift&apos;s engagement since approximately 3:00 PM local time the previous day.The user raised the probability of the event &quot;Taylor Swift will get engaged to Travis Kelce this year&quot; from 25% to 45%. Nevertheless, the total amount of funds involved in this prediction is not considerable (approximately $350,000).In today&apos;s news, the renowned singer Taylor Swift officially announced her engagement to the NFL star Travis Kelce on social media.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 03:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26427</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>