<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:02:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter: JLP Liquidity Pool TVL Surpasses $2 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28050</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Jupiter tweeted, &quot;The TVL of the JLP Liquidity Pool has exceeded 2 billion US dollars.&quot;According to the data on the official website, the current JLP APY is 17.58%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28050</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FutureCrest Acquisition, led by Tom Lee, has submitted an IPO application aiming to raise $250 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28049</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Tom Lee, the chairman of BitMine, led a blank check company (SPAC) named FutureCrest Acquisition. They submitted a filing to the U.S. SEC on Friday and planned to raise up to $250 million through an initial public offering (IPO).Tom Lee, who is known in the media for his optimistic views on cryptocurrency, also emphasized his previous Bitcoin price predictions in the IPO prospectus. FutureCrest Acquisition stated that when seeking acquisition targets, the company would leverage the management team&apos;s expertise and social capital in fields such as AI, digital assets, fintech, infrastructure, robotics, and communications. Additionally, the company is optimistic about opportunities in business intelligence, productivity software, and digital health.FutureCrest Acquisition plans to list on the Nasdaq under the stock symbol FCRSU. The company confidentially submitted its filings on August 5, 2025. Cantor Fitzgerald is the exclusive bookrunner for this transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28049</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessant: Job Data Shows Trump&apos;s Criticism of Fed&apos;s Slow Action Was Right</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28048</link>
      <description>On September 7th, US Treasury Secretary Yellen stated that the employment data indicates that Trump&apos;s criticism of the Fed&apos;s slow action was valid. The revised employment projections for 2024 may be reduced by 800,000 jobs. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor once again shares Bitcoin Tracker information, hinting at another BTC purchase.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28047</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Michael Saylor, the founder of Strategy, once again shared information related to the Bitcoin Tracker and stated, &quot;Require more orange.&quot; According to the previous pattern, Strategy always discloses additional Bitcoin purchase information on the second day after such news is released.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28047</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot will release important news tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28046</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the Polkadot team said, &quot;There will be a significant release the day after tomorrow.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28046</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Has Not Sold BTC, Will Continue to Invest Part of Profits in Bitcoin, Gold, Land, and Other Safe Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28045</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Paolo Ardoino, the CEO of Tether, responded to the statement &quot;Tether is selling Bitcoin in exchange for gold&quot; on the X platform. He said, &quot;Tether has not sold any Bitcoin. Instead, it has allocated a portion of its Bitcoin reserves to the XXI project. Tether will continue to invest a portion of its profits in secure assets like Bitcoin, gold, and land. Tether is a stable company.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28045</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The August market slowdown trend may continue in the short term, even as the market anticipates the Fed will cut interest rates in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28044</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Binance Research presented its September cryptocurrency trend report, indicating that in August, the cryptocurrency market witnessed a slight cooling with a total market capitalization decline of 1.7%. Both Bitcoin and Ethereum retraced from their peaks. As capital shifted towards alternative coins, Bitcoin&apos;s dominance further decreased to 57.3%, while Ethereum&apos;s dominance increased to 14.2%. Corporate funds started to flow into Ethereum. Furthermore, historically, September has been a month with relatively weak performance in the crypto market. Therefore, even though the market is closely monitoring the possibility of a Fed rate cut, the slowdown trend in the crypto market may persist in the short term.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28044</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin is in a consolidation phase, slightly biased towards a bullish outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28043</link>
      <description>On September 7th, CryptoQuant analyst Axel Adler Jr. put out a post stating, &quot;This week, the Bitcoin market entered a &apos;consolidation&apos; stage. The price consolidated within the range of $110,000 to $112,000, near the crucial support level. Derivative sellers lost their dominance, yet the upward momentum remains feeble. On-chain indicators indicate a decrease in activity, while exchanges witnessed positive net outflows. In the macro environment, yields are on the decline, and the US labor market is soft, providing support for risk assets. The market is in a consolidation phase, slightly inclined towards a cautious uptrend, but it remains highly sensitive to inflation data and options expiry.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28043</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARA mined 705 BTC in August, with a total holding of 52,477 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28042</link>
      <description>September 7th, the Bitcoin mining firm MARA Holdings presented its unaudited Bitcoin mining update for August 2025. During August, the company successfully mined 705 BTC. As of August 31, 2025, MARA Holdings possesses a cumulative total of 52,477 BTC, and it did not dispose of any Bitcoin in August.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28042</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela&apos;s annual inflation rate reaches 229%, USDT and other stablecoins become a daily payment tool for the public</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28041</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to Cointelegraph, with Venezuela&apos;s annual inflation rate skyrocketing to 229%, stablecoins like USDT have turned into the de facto currency for millions of Venezuelans.Mauricio Di Bartolomeo, the co-founder of Ledn, stated that USDT, which was once limited to users familiar with cryptocurrency and commonly known as the &quot;Binance USD&quot; locally, is now widely used in daily transactions in Venezuela, including buying groceries, paying condo fees, and making salary and supplier payments.Venezuela&apos;s national currency, the Bolivar, has almost no practical value in daily commerce. Rampant inflation, strict capital controls, and a fragmented exchange rate system have led an increasing number of people to prefer using stablecoins rather than cash or local bank transfers.Di Bartolomeo commented: &quot;People and companies prefer to price goods and services in dollars and receive dollars.&quot; He pointed out that USDT is now regarded as the &quot;better dollar.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28041</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>