<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:26:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Survey: WLFI Small Holders Sell-Off Target Price $0.47, Whale Holders Target Price $1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27128</link>
      <description>September 1st. In a Discord group survey among holders who own at least 1 million WLFI tokens, numerous small holders indicated that they would choose to sell if the price reaches $0.47. The group operator, Vincent Deriu, revealed that large holders are aiming for a price above $1. Many are planning to sell only a portion of their tokens, up to 20%. Holder Bruno Ver stated that he intends to sell approximately 10% of his holdings after trading begins. He predicted that the token&apos;s price could reach $0.35 to $0.5. &quot;It will definitely be used for family expenses,&quot; he disclosed. &quot;I&apos;ve already informed my wife that we are going on a cruise in September.&quot; (Jinse)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>0xSun: If Ethereum cannot sustain its lead in the market, we may consider ending the &quot;long ETH, short various altcoins&quot; strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27126</link>
      <description>On September 1st, Smart Money, the crypto KOL 0xsun.sol (@0xSunNFT) summarized the &quot;Long ETH, Short Shitcoins&quot; strategy on social media. They said, &quot;In general, this strategy has been very successful, especially when facing market volatility. In the last few days of August, due to SOL&apos;s sudden strength, which led the altcoins, the profits of the strategy suffered some drawdowns. We will continue to observe. If this situation persists for a while and ETH cannot lead the market, we can consider taking profits.&quot;Furthermore, regarding on-chain operations, 0xSun mentioned, &quot;Currently, because the listing channel cannot be opened, there is a limited ceiling. It is still a good choice for small funds, but the cost-effectiveness for large funds is too low. Liquidity injection is needed, or some iconic events to open up the ceiling to improve this situation.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27126</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list World Liberty Financial (WLFI) spot trading at 20:00 on September 1st.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27127</link>
      <description>September 1st. According to an official announcement, at the request of the World Liberty Financial (WLFI) project team, Gate will list World Liberty Financial (WLFI) spot trading at 20:00 on September 1st (coordinated universal time + 8).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 05:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27127</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: The WLFI total on-chain staking amount has reached $880 million, with a 47.58% increase in the last 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27125</link>
      <description>On September 1st, based on Coinglass data, the current total on-chain contract position of WLFI is $880 million. In terms of coins, the position is 2.563 billion WLFI, and it has increased by 47.58% in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27125</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb will list the USD/KRW trading pair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27124</link>
      <description>On September 1st, as per official information, Bithumb is set to list the USD1/KRW trading pair. The trading is scheduled to commence on Monday, September 1, 2025, at 4:00 PM in the local time.Previously, there were reports suggesting that Upbit announced it would list WLFI along with USD1/KRW, USDT, and Bitcoin trading pairs.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27124</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Laureate Warning: Insufficient Stablecoin Regulation Could Lead to Government Bailouts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27123</link>
      <description>On September 1st, as reported by the Financial Times, the Nobel Prize-winning economist Jean Tirole cautioned that the current regulation of stablecoins is &quot;inadequate.&quot; If these tokens were to fail during a future financial crisis, the government might be compelled to inject billions of dollars for a bailout. In an interview, the 2014 Nobel Prize-winning economist expressed that he is &quot;extremely, extremely concerned&quot; about the regulation of stablecoins and the potential for a bank run if there is doubt regarding the underlying reserve assets linked to these digital tokens.Tirole pointed out that although stablecoins may seem like &quot;absolutely safe deposits&quot; in the eyes of ordinary users, they could actually lead to losses and trigger calls for costly government bailouts. He also warned that using U.S. Treasury bonds as the backing asset for stablecoins might become unpopular due to the relatively low yields of these underlying assets. As a result, stablecoin issuers may be motivated</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit will list USD1 KRW, USDT, and Bitcoin trading pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27122</link>
      <description>September 1st. According to official information, Upbit will list trading pairs involving USD1 South Korean Won, USDT, and Bitcoin. The trading is scheduled to commence on September 1st at 4:00 PM in the local time zone.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the impact of the BONK.fun and WLFI partnership announcement, the Bonk ecosystem development protocol token GP surged 34% in just under 1 hour.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27121</link>
      <description>On September 1st, based on GMGN market information, the Bonk ecosystem development protocol token GP surged by 34% in the past hour, and its current market value is $1.168 billion.In earlier news, WLFI announced that USD1 has officially been launched on Solana and has integrated with Raydium, BONK.fun, and Kamino.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget is about to launch WLFI spot trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27120</link>
      <description>September 1st. As per an official proclamation, Bitget is going to list World Liberty Financial (WLFI) in its Innovation Zone and DeFi Zone. The deposit channel has been made accessible, and the trading channel will commence at 9:00 PM on September 1st (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haotian International Securities will apply to the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission for Virtual Asset Trading Service</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27119</link>
      <description>On September 1st, the Hong Kong Stock Exchange-listed company Haitong International Investment announced that its wholly-owned subsidiary, Haitong International Securities, intends to apply to the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission for offering virtual asset trading services through a comprehensive account arrangement. If approved by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission, the company will be able to provide virtual asset trading services to retail clients. (Sing Tao Daily)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 04:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>