<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:55:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CME FedWatch: 87.4% Probability of a 25 Basis Point Rate Cut in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23402</link>
      <description>Update: On August 6th, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut in September is 87.4%, and the probability of maintaining the rates at the current level is 12.6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23402</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ALL-in-One Index Perpetual Contract opened on Binance at 1.679 US dollars, reaching a high of 1.679 US dollars and is currently trading at 1.03 US dollars.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23401</link>
      <description>On August 6th, based on market data, the ALL-In-One Index Perpetual Contract opened on Binance at 1.679 US dollars and is currently trading at 1.03 US dollars.Previously, it was reported that the ALL-In-One Index tracks all USDT-denominated perpetual contracts on Binance Futures, excluding the following contracts: the ETHBTC Perpetual Contract, U-denominated perpetual contracts quoted in USDC or other stablecoins, U-denominated Futures contracts, the All-In-One Index Perpetual Contract, Perpetual Contract Pre-market Trading, and Coin-margined Perpetual and Futures contracts. The Binance ALL-In-One Index is calculated by using the weighted average price of all constituent real-time index prices.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23401</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Trump to Release &quot;A Statement&quot; Tomorrow at 4:30 AM</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23400</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the White House announced that President Trump of the US will give a &quot;statement&quot; in the Oval Office at 4:30 pm ET on Wednesday (4:30 am Beijing time the next day). (IG)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derivatives: Option data shows traders hedging against Bitcoin dropping below $100,000 and Ethereum dropping below $3,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23399</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per The Block, following a robust uptrend in Bitcoin, Ethereum, and other major cryptocurrencies last month, the recent cryptocurrency price movement has been rather unimpressive. This seemingly has led some market participants to adopt a bearish stance. The cryptocurrency options platform Derive has indicated that its options positions set to expire on August 29th have shown a significant preference for Bitcoin and Ethereum put options. This indicates that traders are hedging against a potential price decline by the end of the month.Sean Dawson, the Head of Research at Derive, has stated that the number of Ethereum put options expiring by August 29th exceeds the number of call options by more than 10%. The highest interest is concentrated at strike prices of $3,200, $3,000, and $2,200. The analyst pointed out that this positioning is in line with the expectation of &quot;any scenario ranging from a mild pullback to a more significant correction.&quot; The bearish sentiment i</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23399</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutional Ethereum Whale Holdings Change in the Last 30 Days: BMNR Holds 833.1K ETH, Ranking First</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23398</link>
      <description>On August 6th, based on the data from strategicethreserve, the following are the treasury companies and institutions with significant changes in Ethereum holdings in the past 30 days:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) takes the first place, currently holding 833,100 ETH, which is approximately worth $30.3 billion, and there has been a 410.68% increase in holdings in the past 30 days;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) ranks second, currently holding 521,900 ETH, approximately worth $19 billion, with a 163.38% increase in holdings in the past 30 days;The Ether Machine (DYNX) comes in third, currently holding 345,400 ETH, about $12.5 billion, and there is an 8.01% increase in holdings in the past 30 days;Ethereum Foundation ranks fourth, holding 232,600 ETH, approximately worth $8.445 billion, with a 5.25% decrease in holdings in the past 30 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23398</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Firefly to Land on Nasdaq, One of the Most Promising Commercial Space Companies Outside of SpaceX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23397</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the U.S. commercial aerospace company Firefly Aerospace Inc. (NYSE: FLY) is scheduled to officially be listed on NASDAQ on August 7th. It is hailed as the most anticipated tech unicorn IPO since Circle and Figma.BiyaPay analysts pointed out that since its establishment in 2017, Firefly has constructed a complete &quot;space logistics chain&quot; centered around small rocket launches, the Elytra orbital transfer vehicle, the Blue Ghost lunar lander, and the reusable rocket Eclipse. In March of this year, its self-developed Blue Ghost successfully completed a NASA lunar mission, making Firefly the first U.S. commercial company to achieve a commercial moon landing. Its customers include NASA, the Department of Defense, Lockheed Martin, and the existing orders total more than $1.1 billion.Although it is not currently profitable, Firefly&apos;s IPO valuation this time has reached as high as $5.6 billion due to its advantages in government orders, high-end delivery capabilities, and a co</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23397</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>spacex</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Bitcoin Whales and Retail Investors have increased their BTC holdings over the past 15 days, which may reflect accumulation during the pullback.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23394</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Glassnode put out a post saying, &quot;During the past 15 days, both whales (those holding more than 1,000 BTC) and retail investors (those holding less than 1 BTC) have been on average adding more to their holdings than they have been selling. This shows that they have been purchasing during the recent pullback. Nevertheless, this signal is lagging as it represents smoothed data over a 15-day period.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23394</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Lifts Retail Crypto ETN Ban, Indicating Efforts to Become Cryptocurrency Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23396</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to Cointelegraph&apos;s report, the UK financial regulator has removed the ban on exchange-traded notes (cETNs) for retail investors on cryptocurrency exchanges, enabling individual investors to independently assume risks and make choices on their own. This move has received industry support and is regarded as a step for the UK to align with the global crypto market and enhance its position as a hub for digital assets.Last Friday, the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) of the UK announced the lifting of the ban on retail investor trading of cETNs, and the regulatory changes will come into effect on October 8th. The ban was implemented in January 2021 due to extreme market volatility and &quot;a lack of legitimate investment need.&quot;The reversal of the cETN ban reflects a change in the regulatory agency&apos;s stance on crypto assets. A senior FCA executive stated in a release that this decision reflects the development of the market and an increased public understanding of c</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23396</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economist: U.S. Section 232 Investigation Results and Tariff Plan Will Not Be Implemented Immediately</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23395</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per foreign media reports, the U.S. government is on the verge of releasing the investigation results of Section 232 regarding specific industries such as global semiconductors, pharmaceutical raw materials, servers, key components, minerals, etc. Economists have pointed out that procedurally, after the investigation results are out, the U.S. President will take action within 90 days upon receiving the report. During this period, all countries have the opportunity to negotiate with the U.S. Therefore, similar to the tariff retaliation in early April, the investigation results and tariff plans of Section 232 are not anticipated to be implemented immediately. The U.S. may introduce an investment framework or structure to further negotiate U.S. investment with other countries, with conditions that might involve different durations and amounts, in exchange for a reduction in tariff rates. Regarding the semiconductor tariff rate, economists have speculated on levels rangin</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23395</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KakaoBank Plans to Enter the South Korean Stablecoin Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23393</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to The Block, Kwon Tae-hun, the CFO of KakaoBank, stated at the event for the release of the first half of 2025 performance that the bank is evaluating the issuance and custody services of digital assets and is collaborating with the stablecoin working group of the Kakao Group. KakaoBank has accumulated experience in areas such as the issuance of real-name accounts on cryptocurrency exchanges, anti-money laundering monitoring, and has participated in the pilot project of the central bank digital currency of the Bank of Korea.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23393</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>