<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:04:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Reborn Coffee Launches Cryptocurrency Payment Pilot</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25588</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the Nasdaq-listed U.S. coffee chain Reborn Coffee announced its intention to conduct pilot cryptocurrency payments at some of its Southern California stores in 2025 and integrate this feature into its existing Point of Sale (POS) platform. Previously, Reborn Coffee had announced the start of a strategic assessment to consider incorporating regulated digital assets into its financial management framework. The company plans to explore blockchain assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum in order to optimize fund management efficiency and achieve the diversification of non-operational capital reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25588</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. initial jobless claims saw the largest three-month increase in three months, while continued claims rose to a high for 2021.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25587</link>
      <description>August 21st. In the US last week, initial jobless claims witnessed the largest rise in nearly three months, suggesting a rising trend in layoffs and further intensifying signs of labor market weakness. The Labor Department stated on Thursday that for the week ending August 16th, seasonally adjusted initial jobless claims increased by 11,000 to 235,000, marking the largest jump since late May. As businesses were dealing with Trump&apos;s protectionist trade policies, the labor market was characterized by &quot;low layoffs and weak hiring.&quot;Earlier this month, the government reported that over the past three months, employment had been increasing by an average of 35,000 jobs per month. The second-quarter domestic demand growth rate had slowed down to the lowest level since the fourth quarter of 2022. The report showed that for the week ending August 9th, continuing jobless claims rose by 30,000 to 1.972 million, reaching the highest level since November 2021. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25587</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether and Circle Executives to Meet with CEO of Major South Korean Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25586</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as per Decrypt, representatives from Tether and Circle are slated to hold meetings with the CEOs of several leading financial groups in South Korea this week. These include CEO Jin Ok-dong of NewHan Financial Group and CEO Ham Young-joo of Hana Financial Group. The meetings will center around the potential distribution and utilization of the US dollar stablecoin within Korea, as well as the issuance of a stablecoin backed by the Korean won. This meeting takes place as South Korea is gearing up to launch a stablecoin regulatory framework in October of this year, with the ruling party and the opposition party holding divergent views on stablecoin regulation.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25586</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Enterprise increased its BTC holdings by 100 coins, bringing its total holdings to 688 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25585</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the NYSE-listed company DDC Enterprise announced that it has increased its holdings of 100 BTC and now its total Bitcoin holdings amount to 688 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25585</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Jobless Claims Rise, Treasuries Erase Losses</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25584</link>
      <description>August 21st: The number of US jobless claims has gone up, and US Treasuries have wiped out their losses. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale has deposited 22,344 ETH into Aave V3, equivalent to $95.6 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25583</link>
      <description>On August 21, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a certain Bitcoin ancient whale has transferred 22,344 ETH (approximately $95.6 million) into Aave V3. The whale still retains 8,023 ETH (about $34.49 million) in other wallets.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25583</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the United States, the initial jobless claims for the week ending August 16th were 235,000, compared to an expected 225,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25582</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the number of initial jobless claims in the United States during the week ending August 16 was 235,000. The expected value was 225,000 and the previous value was 224,000. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25582</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address has potentially accumulated 2004 ETH in the past 2 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25581</link>
      <description>August 21st. According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the address 0x7E4...00107 is reported to have accumulated 2004 ETH within the past 2 hours, which is worth 8.55 million US dollars. It withdrew 1802 ETH from Binance and repurchased 201.45 ETH on-chain using USDC with an average price of 4268.59 US dollars. Currently, 1000 ETH has been deposited into Aave.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25581</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chair Candidate Brad Calls for 100 Basis Point Rate Cut, Plans to Meet With U.S. Treasury Secretary After Labor Day</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25580</link>
      <description>August 21st - The former president of the St. Louis Fed and the front-runner for the next Federal Reserve Chair, Brad, advocated for a 100-basis-point rate cut this year and additional cuts in 2026. Brad stated in an interview on Thursday: &quot;Current interest rates are a bit on the high side. I believe we can reduce them by approximately 100 basis points by 2026. I think this will commence with a cut at the September meeting and may be followed by further actions later this year.&quot;Brad mentioned that he has been in communication with Treasury Secretary Benson regarding his candidacy for the Federal Reserve Chair and plans to &quot;possibly&quot; arrange a meeting after Labor Day on September 1st. Regarding further rate cuts next year, Brad stated that it will depend on the data performance. He also highlighted the significance of maintaining the status of the US dollar as a reserve currency. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25580</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chainlink Receives ISO 27001 and SOC 2 Compliance Certifications</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25579</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Chainlink announced that it had obtained ISO 27001 certification and SOC 2 Type 1 certification. The scope of this assessment encompasses:Chainlink Data Feeds—specifically, Price Feeds and Smart Data (including Proof of Reserve and Net Asset Value (NAV)), all based on Chainlink Data Standards;Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP)—Chainlink&apos;s interoperability standard.All reviews were carried out by the independent accounting firm Deloitte &amp; Touche LLP in accordance with the auditing standards established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25579</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>