<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:59:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi Leveraged Token Anniversary Celebration: Huobi Lending + Trading Dual Leaderboard Event, Join to Share a $30,000 Prize Pool</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24388</link>
      <description>August 13th. According to an official announcement from Huobi HTX, in celebration of the platform&apos;s 12th anniversary, Huobi Futures launched a Leveraged Loan + Trading Dual Leaderboard Special Event from 8:00 PM on August 12th to 8:00 PM on September 12th (UTC+8). The event encompasses seven popular coins: LTC, DOGE, ADA, PEPE, SAND, THETA, TON (all isolated margin), with a total prize pool of up to $30,000.During the event, users who complete registration and participate in leveraged loans for the event coins will share $20,000 in rewards according to the loan amount. Those who participate in leveraged trading for the event coins will share $10,000 in rewards based on the trading volume. Furthermore, users participating in LTC leveraged loans during the event can also enjoy a super low annual interest rate of 0.99%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24388</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list Cherry AI (AIBOT) spot trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24387</link>
      <description>August 13th. According to an official announcement, Gate is scheduled to list Cherry AI (AIBOT) for spot trading at 18:05 (UTC+8) on August 14th.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24387</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: ETH Surges to 4600 on Bullish HODLing, Nearing Historical Supply Zone; Watch Out for Resistance at 4650-4900, Risk Management Key for Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24386</link>
      <description>August 13th: Bitmine is formulating a new round of financing with the aim of increasing its holdings of Ethereum by up to 20 billion US dollars. It is targeting a 5% ownership of the circulating supply. The market sentiment continues to rise. ETH has risen to approximately 4600 and is currently testing the historical supply zone that overlaps with the high point in 2021, which is between 4650 and 4900. The previous high liquidity level at 4200 has been broken through and has now transformed into support, with structural support below at 3300.Bitunix Analyst Suggestion:Bitmine&apos;s additional holding plan belongs to &quot;long-term capital commitment,&quot; which has a positive influence on the supply-demand structure. However, this is a medium- to long-term factor and cannot change the short-term market reality of pressure within the historical supply zone. Furthermore, the increase in institutional holdings will lead to an increase in liquidity concentration, amplifying gains in a bull market b</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24386</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKB Burn and Upgrade Specific Timeline: Burn on August 15th, Smart Contract Upgrade on August 18th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24385</link>
      <description>On August 13th, according to an official announcement from OKX, the specific timetable (Beijing Time) for the completion of the X Layer&apos;s PP upgrade and the launch of the OKB Gas Token economic model optimization is as follows:At 2:10 PM on August 13th: OKT trading will be suspended on the OKX trading platform, while OKTChain will continue to generate blocks and handle on-chain transactions as usual.At 3:00 PM on August 13th: The OKX trading platform will stop OKB withdrawals to ETH L1.At 10:00 AM on August 15th: The platform will automatically convert users&apos; OKT holdings into OKB according to the rules.At 2:00 PM on August 15th: One-time destruction of OKB, followed by on-chain burning through a smart contract.At 2:00 PM on August 18th: Upgrade of the OKB Smart Contract to remove minting and burning functionalities.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24385</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullish Raises IPO Price Again to $37</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24384</link>
      <description>On August 13th, the cryptocurrency exchange Bullish announced that it has increased the IPO price to $37 per share, which was previously priced between $32 and $33 per share, and the initial price range was between $28 and $31 per share.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the FOMO sentiment of OKB&apos;s price surge, HK Stock EuroChain saw a 26.09% increase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24383</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on market data, perhaps influenced by the FOMO sentiment triggered by the significant increase of OKB, OK Group&apos;s OKLink rose by 26.09% in Hong Kong stocks and is currently trading at HKD 0.58.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24383</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEX Platform Coins Experience General Increase, BGB Surges Over 15%, GT Surges Over 30%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24382</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on market data, influenced by the FOMO sentiment triggered by the significant increase of OKB, the platform tokens of centralized cryptocurrency exchanges witnessed a general upward trend, including:OKX&apos;s platform token OKB surged by 200% and is now trading at $134.Bitget&apos;s platform token BGB surged by 15.5% and is now trading at $4.97.Gate&apos;s platform token GT surged by 31.1% and is now trading at $19.16.Binance&apos;s platform token rose by 2.5% and is now trading at $849.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24382</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by FOMO sentiment, Hong Kong Stock NewFire Technology rose by 37.20%, while Gate Platform&apos;s coin GT surged over 30%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24381</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on market data, due to the FOMO sentiment possibly triggered by the significant surge of OKB, the Hong Kong-listed Neufund Technology rose by 37.20% and is now trading at 6.86 Hong Kong dollars. GateToken (GT), the native token of the Gate.io platform, surged by more than 30% and is currently priced at $19.6.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24381</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKB Surges, Breaks Above $130 in Short Time, 1-Hour Gain Expands to 186%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24379</link>
      <description>August 13th. Based on market data, OKB saw a brief pullback and then continued to rise. It quickly surged and broke through $130. Currently, it is trading at $120, with a 1-hour price increase of 186%. (The rally began at 14:15.)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24379</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Large Burn + X Layer Upgrade Bring Multiple Benefits, OKB Skyrockets 112% in Half an Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24380</link>
      <description>August 13th. Based on market data, OKB began to rise at 14:15 Beijing time today and maintained an accelerating trend. Eventually, it reached a high of $99.27 at 14:40 and then pulled back, seeing a 112% increase within just 25 minutes.In terms of news, OKX officially announced that they have made a strategic decision to upgrade X Layer, positioning it as a leading public chain focusing on DeFi, payments, and RWA scenarios. The network&apos;s throughput has been enhanced to 5000 TPS, Gas costs have been reduced to nearly zero, and security and Ethereum mainnet compatibility have been significantly improved. OKB will continue to serve as the exclusive Gas and native token of X Layer. Furthermore, 65.25 million OKB from historical buybacks and reserves will be burned at one time, fixing the total supply at 21 million OKB.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24380</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>