<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Watch: Market Volatility, Multiple Whale Accounts Reducing Long Positions, Increasing Short Positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21730</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight accessible at https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, the cryptocurrency market witnessed a short-term volatility. There were changes in the Hyperliquid contract positions of whales. Some whales reduced their long positions and increased their short positions:The whale with the address beginning with 0x20c2d increased its ETH short position by approximately $970,000. The current unrealized loss is about $21.56 million, and the current liquidation price is around $4,899.The whale with the address starting with 0x469e9 reduced its ETH long position by 1,419 coins. The current unrealized gain is approximately $149,600, and the current liquidation price is $2,701.The whale with the address starting with 0x2ba55 reduced its ETH long position by 1,550 coins. The current unrealized gain is approximately $4.05 million, and the current liquidation price is $1,755.The whale with the address starting with 0x880ac increased its ETH short</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21730</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital Founder Jack Yi: ETH&apos;s Strength is Nearing the End of Its Rally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21729</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Jack Yi, the founder of LD Capital, posted on social media, saying, &quot;The strong upward momentum of ETH is approaching the end of consolidation. Originally, this was a major resistance level at which many OGs collectively exited their positions. In a bull market trend, regardless of any FUD, it is advisable to avoid shorting and try not to engage in short selling. Adhere to the trend and investment principles.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21729</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana has released the &quot;Internet Capital Markets&quot; roadmap, focusing on application-driven execution.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21728</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the Solana Foundation disclosed the &quot;Internet Capital Markets&quot; roadmap. This roadmap was jointly authored by team members from the Solana Foundation, Anza, Jito Labs, DoubleZero, Drift, and Multicoin Capital, with application control execution serving as its core. The roadmap outlined six key trade-offs: the balance between Privacy and Transparency, the contrast between Throttling and Unthrottled Transactions, the trade-offs among Inclusivity, Finality, and Latency, the choice between Hosted and Geographically Distributed, the difference between Maker-First and Taker-First Priority, and the trade-off between Flexibility and Opinionated Architecture.In the short term, the Jito Labs team announced on Monday its Blockchain Assembly Market (BAM). BAM is a &quot;transaction processing system&quot; that provides powerful new tools for Solana validators, traders, and applications to enhance performance. BAM is set to launch at the end of this month, aiming to bring privacy and transpare</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy intends to increase the fundraising amount from $500 million to $2 billion, to be used to purchase Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21727</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per Bloomberg, Strategy (formerly known as MicroStrategy) intends to expand the scale of its financing from $500 million to $2 billion with the aim of purchasing Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21727</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Concept Stocks Mixed, Sharplink Gaming Up 8.87%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21726</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to the market data of Rockflow, US stock cryptocurrency concept stocks witnessed mixed gains and losses. These include:· Sharplink Gaming increased by 8.87%;· Bitmine went up by 6.29%;· Bitdeer rose by 3.97%;· Strategy rose by 0.19%;· Circle dropped by 5.01%;· Coinbase fell by 0.42%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21726</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeFi Development has partnered with the cross-chain transaction protocol Mayan to support cross-chain functionality for DFDVx.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21725</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the financially strategic listed company DeFi Development announced a strategic partnership with Solana&apos;s cross-chain trading protocol Mayan. By means of this integration, Mayan now enables the support of DeFi Dev Corp&apos;s tokenized equity tool DFDVx for cross-chain and native exchanges, thereby offering seamless access for users across multiple blockchain networks.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21725</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Past $119,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21724</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin surged past $119,000 with a 24-hour fluctuation of 0.83%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21724</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Breaks $3,700</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21723</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum has exceeded $3700, and the 24-hour percentage change is 3.08%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21723</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun Makes Appearance at TRON.Inc Rebranding Bell-Ringing Ceremony, Initiating a New Chapter in the Integration of the Cryptocurrency Market and Traditional Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21722</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, was invited to participate in the opening bell ringing ceremony of the Nasdaq Stock Exchange as a strategic advisor of TRON.Inc to celebrate the official renaming of the Nasdaq-listed company TRON.Inc (stock code: TRON). In June of this year, the predecessor of TRON.Inc—Nasdaq-listed SRM Entertainment announced plans to launch a maximum $210 million TRON enterprise treasury strategy and rename it to Tron Inc. On July 16th, SRM Entertainment was officially renamed Tron Inc, and the stock ticker symbol on Nasdaq was changed from &quot;SRM&quot; to &quot;TRON&quot; effective July 17, 2025. This series of capital operations indicates that the integration of crypto assets with the traditional financial system is entering a new stage.Justin Sun stated: &quot;I am extremely proud to announce to everyone that TRON (TRX) has been strategically reserved by a Nasdaq-listed company. I believe that this is not only a significant milestone for TRON.Inc but also an important m</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21722</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Conner: The future price increase of ETH is expected to come from the global adoption of stablecoins, rather than corporate treasuries embracing it</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21721</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Eric Conner, a former Ethereum core developer, stated that &quot;in the next few years, the future price growth of Ethereum (ETH) actually does not depend on the adoption of &apos;treasury companies&apos;. The real bull market logic lies in the global adoption of stablecoins. People all over the world are eager to obtain USD exposure, and this demand will experience explosive growth. In this process, tens of billions of people may come into contact with and get to know Ethereum.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21721</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>