<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:02:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has abandoned the queuing process to withdraw their staked assets, opting to sell 4242.4 stETH in exchange for 4231 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24902</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale directly conducted a transaction where 4242.4 stETH was exchanged for 4231 ETH (valued at $18.74 million), and this ETH was deposited into Kraken for sale. During this direct exchange, a loss of 11.4 ETH (approximately $50,500) was incurred.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24902</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary CEO: Bitcoin Expected to Reach $150,000 This Year, Ethereum&apos;s Ability to Sustain Its Growth Trajectory Remains Uncertain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24901</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per Decrypt, Steven McClurg, the CEO of Canary Capital, stated that Bitcoin might rise to $150,000 by the end of this year; however, it will encounter a new bear market in 2026. Meanwhile, he is doubtful about whether the recent rise of Ethereum can be maintained.This Bitcoin prediction arrives as the cryptocurrency market is approaching its all-time high and institutional investors are pouring into Bitcoin ETFs.He attributes this current rise to the growth of ETF demand and the expansion of the institutional buyer base, which includes sovereign wealth funds, pension funds, and corporate treasuries.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 03:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24901</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Layer Token Definitive (EDGE) Market Cap Briefly Surpasses $150 Million, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24900</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on GMGN market data, the on-chain transaction execution platform Definitive&apos;s token EDGE briefly reached a market capitalization of over $1.5 billion. Currently, it stands at $1.46 billion and has hit a new all-time high with a 24-hour increase of 24.58%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24900</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Suspends Monero Deposits Due to 51% Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24899</link>
      <description>August 17th, according to an official communication, Kraken has declared that as a security measure, it has temporarily ceased Monero (XMR) deposits because it detected that a single mining pool was controlling more than 50% of the network&apos;s total hashrate. Such a concentration of hashrate may pose a potential threat to network integrity.Kraken is closely observing the situation and will resume deposits once security is verified. XMR trading and withdrawals are still operating normally.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 03:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24899</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 wallet addresses will collectively swap 4806 ETH for LINK, approximately $21.23 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24896</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, 5 wallet addresses that are likely to belong to the same entity carried out a swap. They exchanged 4806 ETH for 938,489 LINK, with an approximate value of $21.23 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand Introduces Cryptocurrency Exchange Program for Foreign Tourists to Boost the Tourism Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24898</link>
      <description>On August 17th, according to the report in &quot;crowdfund insider&quot;, Thailand is scheduled to launch a new measure on Monday. This measure enables foreign tourists to convert cryptocurrency into Thai Baht for making payments. The aim is to rejuvenate the tourism industry after a decrease in the number of tourists.This initiative, named &quot;TouristDigiPay&quot;, will be announced at a press conference presided over by the Thai Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Pichai Chunhavajira. Officials from the Ministry of Finance, the Securities and Exchange Commission, the Anti-Money Laundering Office, and the Ministry of Tourism and Sports will be in attendance.The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission has completed a public consultation on using digital assets to support economic and tourism growth. The feedback period ended on August 13th.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24898</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Reserve Holdings and Cumulative ETF Holdings Exceed 10 Million Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24893</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on the data from strategicethreserve.xyz, the current reserve holdings of Ethereum by the Ethereum Reserve Company and various ETH spot ETFs are 3.06% and 5.42% of the total supply respectively, with a total holding of 10.26 million ETH. The overall percentage has exceeded 8.4% of the total supply of Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24893</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump, Son of Former President Trump: Buy Bitcoin and Ethereum on Dips</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24897</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, responded on his social media platform to the news that &quot;a certain WLFI linked address spent $18.6 million to purchase 1911 ETH and 84.5 WBTC,&quot; and he said, &quot;Buy the dips.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24897</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitosis Foundation unveils MITO Tokenomics, with the Genesis Airdrop accounting for 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24895</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per official information, the Mitosis Foundation has made an announcement regarding the MITO tokenomics. The total supply of the token is 1 billion and is allocated as follows: 45.5% is allocated to the ecosystem; 15% is allocated to the team; 8.76% is allocated to investors; 10% is allocated to the foundation; 10% is allocated to the genesis airdrop; 2% is allocated to builder rewards; 3.5% is allocated to exchange platform marketing; 4% is allocated to initial liquidity; and 1.24% is allocated to research and development. The MITO token will be natively issued on the Mitosis mainnet and serves as the native token of the Mitosis Chain, which is fully EVM compatible.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24895</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caixin: Insiders Say HKMA Encourages RWA Cases in New Energy, Aviation, and Shipping Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24894</link>
      <description>August 17th. According to Caixin&apos;s report, overseas RWA issuance fundraising is in full swing. This is driven by uneven underlying asset quality, questionable transaction architecture and pricing, and opaque cross-border fund flows. The earliest domestic RWA cases in China originate from Ant Group and all follow the &quot;onshore asset - Hong Kong securitization - global circulation&quot; paradigm. In accordance with Hong Kong regulatory requirements, they have not been open to retail investors but only to institutions/professional investors, and there is no secondary market trading.Industry insiders have stated that regarding underlying assets, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority encourages RWA cases such as new energy and aviation trade financing but does not support real estate projects. Investors are mainly private equity firms, family offices, and wealth management institutions in Hong Kong. &quot;International capital is limited, and Chinese investors are more likely to understand these projects</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24894</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>