<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 22:56:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 22:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bullish IPO Soars Over 176% on First Trading Day, Reaching a Market Cap of Nearly $15 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24471</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on the market data from Rockflow, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Bullish (BLSH.US) witnessed a first-day IPO opening surge of more than 176%, reaching $102.44, and its total market value was nearly $15 billion.It has now pulled back to $90.12, with a market value of $13.158 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24471</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Will Appoint New Fed Chair Soon, Only Three to Four Candidates Left</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24469</link>
      <description>On August 14th, President Trump of the United States stated that he will appoint a new Chairman of the Federal Reserve as soon as possible, and there are only three to four candidates left. When the renovation of the Federal Reserve building is completed, Powell will have &quot;already left office.&quot; (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24469</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: If &quot;TrumPutin&quot; goes smoothly, a trilateral meeting among the US, Russia, and Ukraine will take place</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24470</link>
      <description>On Wednesday, August 14th, U.S. President Trump stated that if his meeting with Russian President Putin proceeds smoothly, he anticipates the possibility of promptly convening a second meeting involving both Putin and Ukrainian President Zelensky. He said, &quot;If the first one goes well, we&apos;ll have a second one shortly.&quot; Trump further expressed his desire to hold the second meeting immediately. If both Putin and Zelensky desire it, he indicated that a second meeting among Putin, Zelensky, and himself would be arranged very quickly. Trump did not specify a definite timeline for the second meeting. Additionally, Trump stated that if Putin refuses to agree to halt the war, Russia will face certain consequences. He did not elaborate on these consequences, but he had previously warned that in the absence of a breakthrough, strict economic sanctions would be imposed. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24470</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, a total of $545 million has been liquidated across the network, with the majority coming from liquidated short positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24468</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, a total of $545 million was liquidated across the entire network. There were $170 million in long liquidations and $375 million in short liquidations. A total of 114,878 people were liquidated globally. The largest single liquidation took place on Bybit - BTCUSD with a value of $10 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPPY Meme Coin Surges Over 34% in the Past Hour, Market Cap Reaches $22.4 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24467</link>
      <description>August 13th. According to GMGN data, the Solana-based Meme coin CLIPPY (Clippy PFP Cult) witnessed a surge of over 34% in the past hour. It has a market capitalization of $22.4 million and a 24-hour trading volume of $18.2 million.CLIPPY (Clippy PFP Cult) showcases the image of the classic Microsoft Office assistant Clippy. It represents a silent protest against modern tech companies that harm user interests through aggressive advertising, data collection, and complex subscription models. It conveys nostalgia for the pure software era of the past.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, caution should be exercised when investing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24467</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Deposits $3.36 Million into HyperLiquid to Short BTC, ETH, and SOL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24464</link>
      <description>On August 13th, as monitored by OnchainLens, a whale address deposited $3.36 million USDC into HyperLiquid and initiated short positions: BTC (with 40x leverage), ETH (with 10x leverage), and SOL (with 20x leverage).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveel Unveils REVA Tokenomics: 1 Billion Total Supply with 37% Allocated to the Community</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24466</link>
      <description>August 13th, Reveel made the tokenomics of the REVA token public. The total supply of REVA tokens is 1 billion. 37% is allocated to the community, 25% to investors, 22% to the company fund, and 16% to the team and advisors. The initial circulating supply is approximately 150 million. It follows a fixed supply model and plans to have deflation through buybacks supported by dynamic income.The buyback mechanism stipulates that initially 75% of net income will be used for token buybacks. In each subsequent period, there will be a 5% decrease, but the absolute amount must continue to increase, with a minimum buyback ratio of 25%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24466</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary TRUMP ETF has been registered in the state of Delaware</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24465</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on market information, the Canary TRUMP COIN ETF has been registered in Delaware, the United States.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24465</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zguangsi.eth associated address deposited 5,054.5 ETH to a CEX.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24463</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on the monitoring of OnchainLens, a wallet address linked to zguangsi.eth has transferred 5,054.5 ETH to Binance, with a value of $23.6 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24463</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offchain Labs Acquires Smart Contract Account Development Team ZeroDev</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24462</link>
      <description>On August 13th, Offchain Labs made an announcement stating that they have acquired the smart contract account development team, ZeroDev. Currently, ZeroDev supports more than 5 million smart contract accounts across over 30 chains and provides tools for various crypto projects such as ApeCoin, Conduit, Crossmint, and others.This acquisition is intended to meet the continuously growing on-chain infrastructure requirements and drive the on-chain transformation of large institutions and consumer applications. It will collaborate with the previously launched Universal Intent Engine to achieve fast cross-chain transactions and a seamless user experience.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24462</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>