<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Coinshares: Last week saw a net outflow of $1.43 billion from digital asset investment products, the highest on record since March.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26178</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to Coinshares&apos; data, digital asset investment products witnessed a record-breaking outflow of $1.43 billion during the last week. This is the highest outflow since March. Meanwhile, the trading volume of ETP surged to $38 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26178</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Achieves All-Time High with $3.4 Billion in 24-hour Trading Volume, Becoming the Second-Largest Bitcoin Spot Trading Platform on the Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26177</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to official information, the Hyperliquid platform achieved a new record high with a 24-hour spot trading volume of $3.4 billion. This growth was primarily led by the Unit&apos;s active effort to substantially increase BTC and ETH deposits and spot trading volume.Having a single-day $1.5 billion BTC trading volume, Hyperliquid has now become the second-largest spot Bitcoin trading platform among centralized and decentralized exchanges.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26177</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Exchange-listed company Mega Matrix has announced the establishment of a stablecoin governance token treasury reserve centered around the ENA token.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26176</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the report from prnewswire, Mega Matrix Inc., a company listed on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE code: MPU), announced today that it has formulated a Treasury Reserve strategy for a stablecoin governance token (DAT). It has selected $ENA, the governance token of Ethena, which is the issuer of the third-largest stablecoin USDe, as the core strategic reserve asset. This move is intended to strategically hold leading stablecoin governance tokens in order to actively engage in the governance of the stablecoin ecosystem, with the aim of propelling the company to the vanguard of stablecoin innovation.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONK Treasury Company Safety Shot has successfully completed a $30 million financing round, with $25 million paid by BONK founding members in token form.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26174</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to a report from &quot;businessinsider&quot;, the BONK Treasury company Safety Shot announced the completion of a $30 million financing round. The lead investor was FalconX and others. The transaction involved an approximately $5 million cash registration direct issuance and a $25 million simultaneous private placement. These funds were paid in BONK tokens by the BONK founding members.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26174</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empery Digital increased its holdings by 13 Bitcoins, bringing the total holdings to 4,065 coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26175</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to market information, the Nasdaq-listed company Empery Digital enhanced its holdings by 13 Bitcoins, resulting in its total Bitcoin holdings reaching 4,065 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26175</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock SOL Treasury Company DFDV Raises $125 Million to Increase SOL Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26172</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the U.S. Stock SOL Treasury Company DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) announced today that it has reached a definitive agreement to carry out a $125 million equity financing at a price of $12.50 per share. The transaction is anticipated to be completed on Thursday, August 28, 2025, provided that the customary closing conditions are met.According to the terms of the subscription agreement, the company will sell approximately 4.2 million shares of common stock (at a purchase price of $12.50 per share) and warrants that can be exercised for approximately 5.7 million shares of common stock (at a purchase price of $12.4999 per share with an exercise price of $0.0001 per share). The consideration for this issuance will be in the form of a combination of cash and locked SOL, which will further enhance DFDV&apos;s strategic goal of maximizing Solana Per Share (SPS) growth. The net proceeds raised will be utilized to increase the holdings of spot SOL and discounted locked SOL in order t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26172</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haassett: Powell Unlikely to Regain Trump&apos;s Favor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26173</link>
      <description>August 25th: On this August 25th, Brian Deese, who is the Director of the White House National Economic Council, expressed that it is unlikely for Powell to regain Trump&apos;s favor.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26173</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHZilla Approves $250 Million Stock Buyback Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26170</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the Board of Directors of ETHZilla Corporation (NASDAQ: ETHZ) has given approval to a stock buyback plan. The maximum buyback amount is $2.5 billion, and this plan comes into effect immediately. Additionally, the company has announced that it currently possesses 102,237 ETH. The average purchase price of these ETH is $3,948.72, and they are currently valued at approximately $4.89 billion. Apart from ETH, ETHZilla also holds around $2.15 billion in US dollar cash equivalents.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26170</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House National Economic Council Director: Fed Considering Rate Cut Is Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26171</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Hassett, who is the Director of the White House National Economic Council, referred to the Federal Reserve and expressed that it is suitable for the Fed to think about a rate cut. It is anticipated that it will take several months for the decision on the Fed Chair nominee to be made before President Trump makes a choice. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26171</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronin is launching the &quot;Developer Revenue Share Program&quot;.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26169</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per official information, the Ethereum Layer 2 project Ronin announced the commencement of the &quot;Developer Revenue Sharing Plan.&quot; Whether it is developing games, applications, or migrating projects to Ronin, developers can enhance their earnings through this plan. The &quot;Developer Revenue Sharing Plan&quot; will allocate a portion of Sky Mavis&apos;s total revenue back to developers. When a referred user engages in any of the following transactions, the referrer can receive a reward:路 Minting NFTs on the Ronin Launchpad.路 Participating in secondary market transactions on the Ronin Marketplace.路 Making purchases through the Ronin Store and in-game transactions.路 Paying Ronin Wallet conversion fees.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26169</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>