<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 22:33:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 22:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve&apos;s probability of a rate cut in September is 86.4%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26986</link>
      <description>On August 31st, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of the Fed keeping interest rates unchanged in September is 13.6%, and the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 86.4%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26986</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Total Market Cap Grew by 2.63% in the Last 7 Days, Surpassing $283.4 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26985</link>
      <description>On August 30th, based on the data from DefiLlama, the current total market capitalization of stablecoins across the entire network is reported to be $283.93 billion, showing a 2.63% increase in the past 7 days. Among them, USDT accounts for 59.12% of the market share.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 15:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26985</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Co-founder: ETH Price Could Surge 100x in the Future, or Even More</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26984</link>
      <description>On August 30th, Joseph Lubin, the co-founder of Ethereum and the CEO of ConsenSys, stated that Wall Street will participate in staking because they are currently incurring costs for their infrastructure. Ethereum will replace many of the independent systems they operate (for example, JPMorgan Chase may operate multiple independent systems from banks it has acquired and absorbed).Wall Street firms will need to transform into traditional financial companies operating on a decentralized track, which means engaging in staking, running validation nodes, operating L2/L3, participating in decentralized finance (DeFi), and writing smart contracts for protocols, processes, and financial tools. The perception that L2 will cannibalize L1 will soon be disproven, as demonstrated in projects like Linea and Proof of Burn.The price of ETH may increase by 100 times or even more in the future. ETH will surpass BTC as the monetary base. Tom Lee and I have a good relationship, and the only difference</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 15:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rate displays a continued market divergence, with both bearish and neutral sentiments coexisting.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26983</link>
      <description>On August 30th, based on Coinglass data, the current funding rates of mainstream CEX and DEX are showing a continuous divergence in the market, with a combination of bearish and neutral sentiments. The specific funding rates for mainstream coins are as shown in the attached image.BlockBeats Note: The funding rate is a fee set by cryptocurrency exchanges to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price. It is usually applicable to perpetual contracts and is a fund exchange mechanism between long and short traders. The trading platform does not charge this fee. It is used to adjust the cost or profit of traders holding contracts to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the funding rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the funding rate is greater than 0.01%, it indicates a generally bullish market. When the funding rate is less than 0.005%, it indicates a generally bearish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 15:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26983</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X Layer&apos;s on-chain transaction volume in the last 24 hours reached $10.58 million, representing a 12.81% decrease compared to the previous period.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26981</link>
      <description>On August 30th, based on geckoterminal data, X Layer showed a 24-hour on-chain transaction volume of $10.58 million, which was a 12.81% decrease compared to the previous period and had a total of 94.6K transactions.The market capitalization of the meme coin XDOG reached $8.31 million, with a 4.8% decrease in the 24-hour price.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coin prices are highly volatile. Please be cautious about asset protection and avoid the fear of missing out (FOMO).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26981</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Financial Leasing Group has disclosed its investment in BlackRock and a Hong Kong-listed Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26982</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per an announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, the Hong Kong-listed company China Financial Leasing Group presented its interim performance report dated June 30, 2025. The report revealed that the continuous weakness of the US dollar has led to the strengthening of Bitcoin. The company has started to pay attention to the cryptocurrency market and has begun to make investments in the cryptocurrency industry. Specifically, it is holding physical cryptocurrency instead of synthetic products on relevant exchanges and trading platforms. The current main investments comprise: South East England Hong Kong Dollar Money Market ETF, BlackRock iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF, Huaxia Bitcoin ETF, iShares Ethereum Trust ETF.Previously reported, Cai Wensheng acquired shares of China Financial Leasing at a premium and will focus on AI, Web3, and Hong Kong technology incubation.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26982</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willy Woo: Bitcoin Network Sees First Inflow of Funds in Weeks, Signaling Structural Support Buildup</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26980</link>
      <description>On August 30th, Crypto analyst Willy Woo put out a post indicating that following several weeks of declining inflows, the Bitcoin network witnessed its first day of inflow growth, which signaled the first indication of Bitcoin&apos;s structural bottoming. Bitcoin is currently in a state of stabilization. For a bullish structure to form, investors need to continuously buy the dips. This process has already commenced.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26980</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue reduced to around 1.024M ETH, while Entry Queue increased to around 0.808M ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26979</link>
      <description>August 30th. According to the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, it is reported that the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is 1,024,545 ETH. Based on the current price, approximately $4.45 billion worth of ETH is leaving the PoS network, and the withdrawal delay is currently 17 days and 19 hours.At the same time, there has been a growth in staking demand from new validators. The staking queue for today has increased to 808,910 ETH, with a value of around $3.51 billion. The current queuing time for admission is 14 days and 1 hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26979</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Wong: Hong Kong is actively building an international hub for digital assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26978</link>
      <description>August 30th. A member of the Hong Kong Legislative Council, Wu Jiezhuang, posted on social media, stating that Hong Kong is actively establishing an international digital asset center. He emphasized that enterprises should focus on both innovation and compliance. He also believed that the integration of the capital market and the digital asset industry would bring new impetus to the market. DePIN, which combines blockchain with the real economy, is expected to transform traditional industries such as the Internet of Things, energy, and transportation, and is an important direction for the implementation of Web3.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26978</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Official: Trump in Good Health, About to Go Play Golf</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26977</link>
      <description>On August 30th, Barak Ravid, a reporter from Axios Global Affairs, wrote that a U.S. official stated that President Trump is in a good physical state and will go play golf this morning in the local time. At the moment when this news was released, widespread speculation about Trump&apos;s health was still circulating on social media.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26977</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>