<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:55:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale has submitted an S-1 registration application to the U.S. SEC for DOT and ADA Spot ETFs.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26931</link>
      <description>On August 30th, based on official information, Grayscale has submitted a Polkadot (DOT) and Cardano (ADA) spot ETF S-1 registration application to the U.S. SEC.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26931</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address withdrew 7260 ETH from OKX in the past 14 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26930</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, within the past 14 hours, a whale address withdrew 7,260 ETH from OKX. The value of this withdrawal is $31.64 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26930</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address has deposited 11.68 million U into HyperLiquid to place a continuous buy order for SOL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26929</link>
      <description>August 30th: As per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, within the past 8 hours, a whale address has deposited 11.68 million USDC into HyperLiquid for the purpose of purchasing SOL. Up to now, the address has acquired 28,390 SOL and still has a TWAP order outstanding.In addition, the address also holds 346,598 HYPE tokens, which are worth $15.28 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26929</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Retirement Fund increased its MSTR holdings by $6 million in Q2, bringing its total MSTR holdings to $80 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26928</link>
      <description>On August 30th, based on BitcoinTreasuries&apos; data, the $20.5 billion Florida retirement fund augmented its holdings of MicroStrategy (MSTR) stock by $6 million during the second quarter. Currently, it holds a total of 240,026 shares of MSTR, which are valued at $80 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source: InsiderInsider: Musk&apos;s Private Lawyer Set to Become Chairman of New DOGE Treasury Company, Which Aims to Raise $200 Million to Establish DOGE Treasury</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26927</link>
      <description>August 30th. As per Fortune, six anonymous sources disclosed that investors in the market are currently receiving a fundraising proposal from a DOGE Treasury company that will focus on investing in DOGE. Three of the sources were directly engaged in the project briefing, while the other three learned about the plan from parties involved in the transaction.According to two sources, the company intends to raise at least $2 billion. Details regarding the specific structure of the listing entity and the launch date have not been made public.Three sources indicated that the official DOGE entity, the &apos;House of Doge,&apos; has signed an agreement approving the proposal to become the &apos;official&apos; treasury operation platform for DOGE. The company was founded by the DOGE Foundation in early 2025 and is headquartered in Miami, mainly responsible for promoting and developing the DOGE token.According to the fundraising documents sent to potential investors and revealed by five knowledgeable s</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26927</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-profile ETH to BTC Whale has sold 2000 BTC and purchased 49,850 ETH in the past 12 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26926</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a highly prominent BTC whale focused on ETH has sold 2,000 BTC (valued at $221 million) and purchased 49,850 ETH (valued at $219 million) within the past 12 hours. This address has now amassed a total of 691,358 ETH (valued at $3 billion).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26926</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrum Foundation performed a regular transfer 9 hours ago, moving 10 million ARB to Coinbase Prime. In the past 2 years, they have sold 350 million ARB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26925</link>
      <description>On August 30th, according to on-chain data analyst Yujin Monitoring, a multi-signature wallet of the Arbitrum Foundation transferred 10 million ARB tokens (approximately $4.99 million) to Coinbase Prime 9 hours ago.It is reported that this wallet unlocks and claims around 15 million ARB tokens each month from the unlocking vesting contract of the Arbitrum Foundation. Out of these, 10 million are transferred to Coinbase Prime. The wallet has been unlocking ARB tokens since July 2023 and has thus far unlocked a total of 414 million ARB tokens. Out of the claimed tokens, 350 million have been transferred to Coinbase Prime. Based on the price at the time of transfer to the trading platform, the value is $318 million, with an average price of $0.91.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26925</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renowned ETH/BTC exchange rate bull James Fickel transferred 39,800 ETH to Coinbase Prime 4 hours ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26924</link>
      <description>August 30th. According to the monitoring of on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, the former largest ETH/BTC exchange rate bull, James Fickel, transferred 39,800 ETH (approximately $172 million) to Coinbase Prime four hours ago.Throughout last year, he lost 20,600 ETH due to longing the ETH/BTC exchange rate. Based on the current ETH price, this amounts to approximately $90 million. At present, his Coinbase Prime custody wallet still holds 57,000 ETH (approximately $249 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26924</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Index Dips, BLSH Down by 8.38%, ALTS Down by 5.63%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26923</link>
      <description>August 30: On Friday, the U.S. stock market closed at a lower level, with all three major indexes showing a downward trend. The Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJIA) declined by 0.2%, the S&amp;P 500 Index dropped by 0.64%, and the Nasdaq Composite decreased by 1.15%. Crypto stocks also witnessed a general decline, which included:Coinbase (COIN) dropped by 1.27%, with a trading volume of $20.14 billion.Circle (CRCL) rose by 0.79%, and the trading volume was $10.79 billion.MicroStrategy (MSTR) fell by 1.31%, with a trading volume of $34.12 billion.Bullish (BLSH) decreased by 8.38%, and the trading volume was $2.19 billion.Bitmine (BMNR) fell by 4.28%, with a trading volume of $15.33 billion.BTCS (BTCS) dropped by 3.91%, and the trading volume was $13.878 million.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) fell by 3.47%, with a trading volume of $3.75 billion.BNB Network Company (BNC) fell by 1.31%, with a trading volume of $6.6002 million.ALT5 Sigma (ALTS) decreased by 5.63%, with a trading vol</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26923</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Market Downturn, BIGTIME and LPT Fall Over 15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26922</link>
      <description>On August 30th, according to HTX market data, when Bitcoin dropped below $108,000 earlier today, the crypto market witnessed a general decline, including:ETH saw a 24-hour decrease of 3.45% and is currently priced at $4,337.SOL had a 24-hour decrease of 5.48% and is currently priced at $203.5.BIGTIME experienced a 24-hour decrease of 15.56% and is currently priced at $0.0569.LPT saw a 24-hour decrease of 15% and is currently priced at $6.83.SHELL had a 24-hour decrease of 9.84% and is currently priced at $0.1237.PYTH had a 24-hour decrease of 9% and is currently priced at $0.203.RAY had a 24-hour decrease of 8.71% and is currently priced at $3.48.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26922</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>