<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:38:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Token GEN Market Cap Surpasses $45 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate 35%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23843</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on GMGN data, the ecological AI concept token GEN of Solana briefly surged to $0.045. It currently has a market value of $45 million and a 24-hour increase of 35%.It is reported that GEN is the native token of the General Impressions (GI) project. GI is building the core infrastructure of the Agentic AI era. It is a Rust-driven intelligent agent network that provides underlying support for the trusted execution of autonomous AI, low-cost reusability, and multi-agent collaboration. As a key driver of the emergence of the Agentic Paradigm, GI is gradually becoming a key algorithm protocol for decentralized intelligent systems.BlockBeats reminds users that token prices are highly volatile, so investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 5000 ETH into Binance after hibernating for five years, bringing its total Ethereum earnings to $45.38 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23842</link>
      <description>On September 8th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale that had been inactive for five years deposited 5,000 ETH ($21.14 million) into Binance. The total profit it has now made on ETH amounts to $45.38 million.This whale had accumulated 55,001 ETH seven years ago, which was valued at $6.73 million at that time. It still holds 5,001 ETH with a value of $21.07 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23842</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Token Ecosystem Experiences Overall Price Increase, CLANKER Surges Above $60</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23841</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to HTX market data, the Base ecosystem tokens witnessed a general upward trend. These include:The price of CLANKER experienced a short-term spike and broke through $60, with a 24-hour increase of 24.8% and a current value of $60 million.ZORA saw a 4.66% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $8.88 billion, approaching its all-time high.TOSHI had a 13.39% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $3 billion.KTA saw an 11.51% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $1.4 billion.DRB had a 5.3% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $23 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23841</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes &quot;Sells Low, Buys High&quot; ETH, Chases Price Up to Reacquire $10.5M Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23840</link>
      <description>September 8th. As per the monitoring by LookOnChain, Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of BitMEX, sold 2,373 ETH a week ago when the price of ETH was approximately $3,507, amounting to $8.32 million.4 hours ago, he once more withdrew 10.5 million USDC to repurchase ETH at a higher price.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale/Institutional Address Once Again Increases Its Holdings, Adding $34 Million Worth of ETH at an Average Price of $4,193</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23839</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, a Whale/Institutional address once again increased its holdings 1 hour ago by purchasing 34 million USD worth of ETH. Now it holds a total of 8,109 coins with an average purchase price of 4,193 USD.This Whale/Institutional address has spent a total of 84 million USD in the past 20 days to acquire 21,571 ETH, with an average purchase price of 3,894 USD. Currently, it has an unrealized gain of 7.12 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23839</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X.me has announced that its withdrawal feature will be officially launched in late September.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23838</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the Web2 and Web3 dual-engine AI social media platform X.me announced today that it will officially launch the &quot;Withdrawal&quot; function in late September.X.me stated that it is fully aware of users&apos; close attention to token value and asset security. Recently, X.me has been committed to a major upgrade of the platform&apos;s security protection system. By means of intelligent interception of abnormal operations + facial recognition to verify the user&apos;s identity + defense against bulk fake accounts and other cutting-edge technical iterations, X.me will safeguard users&apos; &quot;Withdrawal&quot; security from multiple dimensions.The &quot;Withdrawal function&quot; is currently in its final testing phase, and users will soon be able to withdraw XME tokens and Dogecoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23838</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cool Cats Floor Price Surpasses 0.74 ETH, Marking a 48% Increase in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23837</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to Blur data, the floor price of Cool Cats has exceeded 0.74 ETH. It has witnessed a 48% increase in the past 24 hours, with a 24-hour trading volume of 112.51 ETH and a 7-day growth of 61%.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 8th, Animoca Brands and its affiliated entities (collectively &quot;Animoca Brands&quot;) announced the completion of a strategic investment in the NFT brand Cool Cats Group. After the investment, Animoca Brands and Coin Operated Group will hold a majority stake in Cool Cats Group.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23837</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoins Surge Across the Board, Ethereum Ecosystem Tokens Lead the Way</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23836</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to HTX market data, as Ethereum continues to surge, altcoins are generally on the rise, and Ethereum ecosystem tokens are leading the market. Among them:COW is currently trading at $0.4853, with a 24-hour increase of 30.75%;ENA is currently trading at $0.739, with a 24-hour increase of 20.1%;RESOLV is currently trading at $0.1969, with a 24-hour increase of 16.66%;TURBO is currently trading at $0.0051, with a 24-hour increase of 15.7%;EIGEN is currently trading at $1.44, with a 24-hour increase of 14.29%;SHELL is currently trading at $0.1815, with a 24-hour increase of 14.2%;SSV is currently trading at $10.19, with a 24-hour increase of 12.85%;COMP is currently trading at $53.94, with a 24-hour increase of 11.72%;ETHFI is currently trading at $1.237, with a 24-hour increase of 11.71%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23836</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overall Ethereum Futures Open Interest Hits New All-Time High, Surging Over 11.12% in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23835</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to Coinglass data, market participants are continuously increasing their wagers on the Ethereum trend. The total open interest of Ethereum futures contracts across all exchanges has once again exceeded $58 billion, reaching a historical high of $58.54 billion. On July 9th, the total open interest of Ethereum futures contracts was $35.58 billion. There has been an increase of over 64.5% in the past 30 days and over 11.12% in the past 24 hours.In addition, the total open interest of Bitcoin futures contracts across all exchanges is currently at $78.93 billion, with a decrease of over 2.04% in the last 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23835</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: US Stock Listed Company BitMine Continues to Rise, Tom Lee States Ethereum at a Key Moment, Target Price $15,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23834</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Tom Lee, the newly appointed chairman of the US-listed company BitMine, recently made a statement. He pointed out that Ethereum (ETH) is currently at a crucial juncture similar to that of Bitcoin in 2017. With Wall Street&apos;s growing focus on cryptocurrency, Lee believes that Ethereum is emerging as a core platform in the &quot;tokenization&quot; process of the financial market, and he anticipates that this will be one of the largest macro trading events in the next decade.Lee specifically emphasized that Ethereum should not be simply compared to Bitcoin but rather to the traditional financial market. If forced to choose between Bitcoin and Ethereum, he is more inclined towards ETH. On August 2nd, BitMine&apos;s chairman Lee pointed out that traditional financial institutions are steadily and quietly increasing their holdings of cryptocurrency, especially Ethereum. This is because of its legal clarity and technical reliability. Moreover, Ethereum has never experienced a crash, which is</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23834</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>