<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:19:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Q2 Earnings Report: Raises Nearly $2.4 Billion for Bitcoin Treasury Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22912</link>
      <description>August 2nd - Lately, the Trump Media &amp; Technology Group declared its Q2 financial report. The financial assets reached approximately $3.1 billion, consisting of cash, cash equivalents, restricted cash, trading securities, and short-term investments, witnessing a year-on-year growth of nearly 800%.The company successfully raised nearly $2.4 billion for its Bitcoin treasury strategy, enabling it to accumulate around $2 billion in Bitcoin and Bitcoin-related securities by July 2025, thereby becoming one of the publicly traded companies with the largest Bitcoin reserves.In Q2, the company achieved positive operating cash flow for the first time, with a cash flow from operating activities of $2.3 million. Additionally, the company continued to make progress in its Separately Managed Account (SMA) and Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) plans, submitting multiple ETF registration statements in the second quarter and subsequent periods, such as the Truth Social Crypto Blue Chip ETF, Truth Social Bit</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Son: Buying the Dip in BTC and ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22911</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Eric Trump, the son of former U.S. President Donald Trump, made a post on social media and stated, &quot;I&apos;ll repeat it once more: Purchase during market dips!!! BTC, ETH.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22911</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The address has accumulated 331 million PI tokens in the past three months, worth approximately 148.5 million US dollars.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22908</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, as reported by Cointelegraph, in the past three months, a mysterious wallet address named GAS...ODM has amassed a total of 331 million PI coins, which is approximately worth $148.5 million.The address has repeatedly withdrawn large amounts of PI from major exchanges such as OKX, Gate.io, and MEXC. Currently, it is the sixth largest holder in the Pi Network ecosystem, surpassing exchange platform wallets like Bitget and MEXC.During this accumulation period, the price of PI witnessed a maximum decline of 70% from its high in early May to fluctuate around $0.44 to $0.48 in mid-July. As of the time of writing, it is priced at $0.3496, with a 24-hour decrease of 13.32%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22908</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Trading Volume Continues to Shrink: XRP, ETH, BTC Remain Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22910</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit was only 2.134 billion US dollars. The XRP/KRW trading pair took the lead with a 20.39% share. ETH and BTC ranked second and third respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22910</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Daily Active Addresses Surpass 840,000, Hitting a One-Year High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22909</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, as per the monitoring of @ali_charts, the number of daily active addresses on Ethereum witnessed a significant surge and reached 841,100, which is the highest level in a year. This sharp increase in data took place prior to the ETH price falling below $3,500.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22909</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address withdrew 10,245 ETH from a CEX in the last 8 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22905</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, Whale 0xF436 once more withdrew 10,245 ETH (approximately $36 million) from the exchange within the past 8 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22905</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the last 24 hours, CEX net outflow of 705.12 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22907</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, based on Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, CEX has experienced a net outflow of 705.12 BTC. The top three exchanges with outflows are as follows:路 Bitstamp, with an outflow of 2,016.02 BTC;路 Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 1,310.78 BTC;路 Kraken, with an outflow of 487.69 BTC.In addition, Binance saw an inflow of 1,798.70 BTC and ranked first on the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22907</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEET48 today held the &quot;1st Annual WEB3.0 Global Idol Popularity Final Selection&quot; at the Hong Kong路AsiaWorld-Expo Arena, with many celebrity guests such as Jacky Wu, Super Junior-D&amp;E, Sandara Park, ...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22906</link>
      <description>August 2nd. According to official channels, the world&apos;s first AIUGC dedicated to the entertainment industry and fan economy ecosystem, MEET48, is set to hold the first annual WEB3.0 Global Idol Popularity Finals at the AsiaWorld-Expo Arena in Hong Kong, China today (the 1st Web3.0 All-Community Annual Idol Popularity Audition &amp; Ceremony, abbreviated as WIPA). This event, in cooperation with China&apos;s large-scale youth girl group SNH48 GROUP, will introduce blockchain mechanisms into the idol selection system and offer exclusive singles, overseas stages, and game endorsements as prestigious rewards for the top-ranked real idols and AI-Agent virtual idols.It is reported that the exclusive title sponsor of WIPA is the AIUGC virtual idol sound and dance development ecosystem simulation game &quot;AuditionsGO,&quot; developed by the original operating marketing team behind the globally popular &quot;Audition&quot; game. Jacky Wu is scheduled to appear as a special guest presenter, with performances by Super Ju</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22906</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: I have once again gone long on ETH, not advisable to quickly switch to a short position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22904</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio posted on his personal channel, indicating that he has once again taken a long position on ETH. The bullish sentiment in August was hyped prematurely by the market. However, $113,000 for BTC and $3,500 for ETH are still reasonable entry points, with stop-loss set below $112,000 and $3,400 respectively.Although the hype about Data Availability Technology (DAT) may gradually wane, there is still significant structural buying interest in the current market. Therefore, it is not advisable to switch to a bearish outlook too hastily. Many people have been constantly jumping back and forth between &quot;bull market return&quot; and &quot;total collapse,&quot; yet they fail to realize that the market does not follow a simple binary path.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Alpha Users with at least 200 Points Can Receive a 750 AIO Airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22903</link>
      <description>August 2nd. As per official channels, the trading of OLAXBT (AIO) on Binance Alpha is set to commence on August 2, 2025, at 18:00 (UTC+8).After the commencement of trading, users who hold at least 200 Alpha Points will be eligible to claim a 750 AIO token airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is still ongoing, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.It is important to note that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, the airdrop will be deemed forfeited.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22903</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>