<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:12:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Aave to Receive 7% of WLFI Total Token Supply」 Sparks Ongoing Dispute, Both Sides Stick to Their Guns with No Resolution</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25978</link>
      <description>August 24th witnessed a disagreement between the Aave official and the WLFI team regarding &quot;Aave will receive 7% of the WLFI total token supply,&quot; which triggered a significant price fluctuation of the AAVE token. The timeline of this event is as follows:On December 6th, 2024, the WLFI team proposed &quot;Launching Aave V3 Instance on the Ethereum Mainnet,&quot; and it was passed on December 13th. According to the proposal, as a lending ecosystem partner of WLFI, Aave will adopt the same reserve factor mechanism in this Aave v3 instance as the main Aave instance. AaveDAO will receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by the WLFI Aave v3 instance and will receive approximately 7% of the total WLFI token supply for participating in future WLFI governance processes, liquidity mining, and driving the decentralization of the WLFI platform.Last evening at 8:30 PM, Aave founder Stani.eth responded to doubts about &quot;Is the WLFI partnership with AAVE still valid? Are they really building on Aave? Ther</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25978</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Bought 24,959 ETH 9 Years Ago, Has Earned a Whopping $102 Million Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25977</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as monitored by Onchainlens, a whale deposited 1,400 ETH ($6.63 million) into Kraken. This led to them earning a substantial profit of $102 million on their ETH holdings.Nine years ago, this whale spent a total of $258,000 to purchase 24,959 ETH from Kraken and ShapeShift. Currently, they still hold 13,477 ETH, which is worth $64.52 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25977</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROMPT Surges Above $0.31, Marking a 114% Increase in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25976</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to HTX market data, PROMPT (Wayfinder) witnessed a significant surge and broke through $0.31. It is currently priced at $0.311, with a 24-hour increase of 114% and a market capitalization of $290 million.Yesterday, Wayfinder released its Open Alpha, enabling users to access its encrypted AI agent and engage in cross-chain transactions, deployment, and exploration.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Surges Past $210, 24-hour Gain Expands to 6.62%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25975</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on HTX market data, SOL rose above $210, and the 24-hour price increase expanded to 6.62%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25975</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Long ETH Liquidation」 Whale has realized a profit of $4.78 million, with a position value of approximately $120 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25974</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as per on-chain analyst Ai (@ai_9684xtpa), the 125k USD liquidated long ETH whale&apos;s 15x long position in ETH is currently showing a profit of 4.78 million USD. At present, their position is in a liquidation state, holding 25,108.32 ETH, which is approximately 120 million USD. The entry price is 4,590 USD and the liquidation price is 4,670.3 USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25974</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movachain has secured a $100 million valuation strategic investment, with leading investors including the Aqua1 Foundation and UAE&apos;s GeoNova Capital.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25972</link>
      <description>August 23rd. MovaChain, a modular blockchain platform tailored for the global payment arena, announced today that it has successfully completed a strategic financing round, resulting in a post-investment valuation of $1 billion. This round was jointly led by the Aqua1 Foundation and GeoNova Capital based in the UAE. Other top financial institutions in Abu Dhabi also participated.The Aqua1 Foundation is a prominent Web3 investment fund in the UAE, concentrating on blockchain infrastructure, financial protocols, and the tokenization of real assets. It drew attention for investing $100 million in the crypto platform World Liberty Financial, which has connections with the Trump family. GeoNova Capital, on the other hand, is a fund established by Standard Chartered Bank, multiple UAE institutions, and family offices. It specializes in active investments in high-growth sectors, collaborates closely with sovereign wealth funds, family offices, and private capital, and is dedicated to creati</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25972</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of cryptocurrency millionaires in South Korea with holdings of over 1 billion KRW has reached approximately 18,000, with an average holding value per user on the top five platforms of 10...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25971</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to Yonhap News Agency, the number of South Korean &quot;crypto whales&quot; holding more than 1 billion KRW has reached approximately 18,000. The average holdings of this group of users have reached 2.228 billion KRW, which is more than 200 times the average holdings per user (10.27 million KRW) of the top five exchanges in South Korea.When looking at the distribution across age groups, those holding more than 1 billion KRW in cryptocurrency are mostly in their 50s (3,994 people), followed by those in their 40s (3,086 people), those over 60 years old (2,426 people), and those in their 30s (1,167 people). Among them, there are 137 &quot;young whales&quot; in their 20s. About 76% of the &quot;whales&quot; (8,242 people) are Upbit users, far exceeding Upbit&apos;s 52% share among the top five exchanges.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25971</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain newly created address withdrew 2883 ETH from Kraken 9 hours ago, totaling $13.69 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25970</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), 9 hours ago, the new address 0xD30...1Bc82 withdrew 2883 ETH from Kraken, with a value of $13.69 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25970</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI has dropped over 25% in the last 12 hours, now trading at $0.293.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25973</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on HTX market data, the pre-market trading price of WLFI (World Liberty Financial) has fallen below $0.3 and once reached $0.258. It is currently trading at $0.293, with a continuous drop of more than 25% in the past 12 hours.BlockBeats previously reported that the Trump family&apos;s project, World Liberty Finance (WLFI), is scheduled to be launched on Ethereum on September 1 with open claiming and trading. Early supporters (in the $0.015 and $0.05 rounds) will unlock 20%, and the remaining 80% will be determined by community vote. Tokens for the founding team, advisors, and partners will not unlock. Trading will begin at 8 p.m. on September 1 (Beijing time), and the 20% token allocation will be available for claiming.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25973</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fosun Wealth Holdings Becomes a DBS Bank Tokenization Structured Note Distributor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25969</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Fosun Wealth Management has emerged as one of the distributors of DBS Bank&apos;s tokenized structured notes. The tokenized structured notes product being distributed this time is a participation note linked to cryptocurrency. It provides cash payouts when the prices of digital assets rise and limits downside risk. (ChainDD)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 01:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25969</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>