<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:31:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market Crypto Stocks in US Market Show Mixed Performance, with Bullish Up by 2.44%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24746</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the market data from RockFlow, the pre-market cryptocurrency stocks in the US showed mixed trends. These included:- The mining firm TeraWulf (WULF) decreased by 0.11%.- The cryptocurrency exchange platform Bullish (BLSH) increased by 2.44%.- Circle (CRCL) decreased by 0.77%.- Coinbase (COIN) increased by 0.55%.- MicroStrategy (MSTR) increased by 0.25%.- SharpLink Gaming (SBET) increased by 0.3%.- Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) increased by 2.06%.- The &quot;IP Treasury Strategy&quot; company Heritage Distilling (CASK) increased by 9.98%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24746</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow Futures Up 0.7%, Intel Continues Pre-market rally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24745</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the market data from RockFlow, the S&amp;P 500 Index Futures increased by 0.2%, the Nasdaq 100 Index Futures rose by 0.04%, and the Dow Jones Index Futures went up by 0.7%. Intel maintained its pre-market rally, rising by more than 4%. It closed up by 7.38% yesterday, with a market value of $104.4 billion.Earlier, according to informed sources, the Trump administration is in negotiations with Intel (INTC.O) with the aim of seeking a U.S. government stake.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24745</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midgame and OSL Group Reach Strategic Partnership to Jointly Promote Stablecoin Payment Collaboration New Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24744</link>
      <description>August 15th, the global IP game operator Century Huatong and the compliant digital financial infrastructure platform OSL Group (0863.HK) have entered into a strategic cooperation. They will deeply integrate OSL Group&apos;s compliant virtual asset financial infrastructure capabilities with Century Huatong&apos;s rich global IP game application ecosystem in order to jointly promote the application scenarios of compliant stablecoin ecosystem cooperation.This strategic cooperation between the two parties is based on the complementarity of their businesses and aims to bridge the value loop of Web3 technology from the underlying infrastructure to the upper-layer compliant applications within a multi-jurisdictional license network. By leveraging Century Huatong&apos;s own technological capabilities and industry influence, and based on OSL&apos;s provision of compliant digital asset custody and a unified settlement layer tool supporting multiple chains and currencies, they will provide 24/7 global cross-border</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Reveals Justin Sun&apos;s &quot;$24.6 Billion&quot; Asset List, the Latter Sues Alleging Privacy Breach</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24743</link>
      <description>August 15th. According to the data disclosed in the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, as of August 15, 2025, the assets of Justin Sun were nominally valued at approximately $24.6 billion. After discounting based on liquidity, it was around $12.4 billion. The majority of his net worth comes from his cryptocurrency holdings, which include:· 600 billion TRX, accounting for 63.3% of the total TRX supply, with a nominal value of $21.6 billion. Due to concerns about illiquidity, Bloomberg discounted this part of assets by 75%;· Approximately 17,000 Bitcoins (worth about $20.4 billion), 224,000 Ethereums (worth about $10.52 billion), and 700,000 USDT. The analysis only covers on-chain tokens; tokens held by Justin Sun on exchanges such as HTX and Binance are not included in the analysis as their holdings could not be verified;In response to this information, Justin Sun has filed a lawsuit against Bloomberg, claiming that the latter &quot;recklessly and inappropriately disclosed his highly co</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24743</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list TCOM Global (TCOM) with a minimum airdrop threshold of 200 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24742</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Binance Alpha will list TCOM Global (TCOM), and trading will commence on August 15, 2025, at 20:00 (UTC+8). Users who have at least 200 Binance Alpha points can receive an airdrop of 600 TCOM tokens on a first-come, first-served basis.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24742</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juventus Fan Token JUV Surges Over 35.5% in 24 Hours, with Tether as Its Club&apos;s Second-Largest Shareholder</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24741</link>
      <description>August 15th. Based on HTX market information, the fan token sector witnessed a general upward trend. This includes:The Juventus Fan Token JUV is currently trading at $1.79, with a 24-hour increase of 35.5%.The Manchester City Fan Token CITY is currently trading at $1.28, with a 24-hour increase of 13.98%.The Porto Fan Token PORTO is currently trading at $1.09, with a 24-hour increase of 9.17%.The AC Milan Fan Token ACM is currently trading at $1.17, with a 24-hour increase of 7.49%.The surge of the Juventus Fan Token JUV may be related to its connection with Tether. Currently, Tether is the second-largest shareholder of Juventus, second only to Exor NV, the largest shareholder. Exor is the investment company of the Italian billionaire Agnelli family, which has been in charge of the football club for over a century. According to a statement from Tether, they are also seeking a seat on Juventus&apos; board of directors. Until 2025, no major European football club had ever listed a crypto</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 08:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24741</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renowned YouTuber MrBeast&apos;s Charity Livestream Triggers Meme Coin Rug Pull, Fair3 Community Initiates Fund Airdrop Compensation Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24740</link>
      <description>August 15th. The highly renowned overseas KOL MrBeast, who has millions of fans on YouTube, conducted a charity live stream on a streaming platform today. The purpose of this live stream is to provide clean drinking water to remote communities in developing countries. In response to this event, the Bags platform released a meme coin with the same name and stated that the royalties of the token would be directly donated to this charity event. However, within two hours after the token was released, its market capitalization surged past $7 million, but due to a rug pull by the involved parties, the token price plummeted to zero.In response to this situation, Fair3 announced the launch of the &quot;Technical Fairness Foundation&quot; plan:- A snapshot will be taken of users who hold both Fair3 tokens and MrBeast Meme tokens before 6:45 AM on August 15, 2025 (UTC+8).- Eligible wallet addresses will receive compensation airdropped by the Fair3 Foundation.- The details of the airdrop will be annou</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24740</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Etherscan has announced the launch of the OG Points Event, where participants can redeem a limited-edition Tenth Anniversary commemorative badge.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24739</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan announced the commencement of the Etherscan Points reward event, enabling users to earn and redeem rewards on Etherscan. Users can participate in daily check-ins, quizzes, sharing Etherscan moments, and other activities to obtain OG points and redeem limited-edition tenth-anniversary badges.To participate in the event, one needs to hold an active Etherscan account created prior to August 12, 2025. The official announcement indicated that this is not a token airdrop but a reward for a commemorative event.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24739</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The address bought 1778.7 WETH today, with an average cost of $4646.4</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24738</link>
      <description>August 15th. According to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), an address spent 8.264 million USDC this morning and purchased 1778.7 WETH at an average price of $4646.4. This address has carried out two swing trades since August, with a total profit of $930,000. Currently, their record shows one win and one loss.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24738</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the United States Ethereum spot ETF saw a net inflow of $639.6 million, while the Bitcoin spot ETF saw a net inflow of $230.8 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24737</link>
      <description>August 15th. As reported by Farside Investors, yesterday, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF reached $639.6 million, indicating the 8th consecutive day of net inflows. Specifically, the BlackRock ETHA witnessed a net inflow of $519.7 million.Yesterday, the net inflow of the US Bitcoin spot ETF was $230.8 million, maintaining its streak of 7 consecutive days of net inflows. Among them, BlackRock&apos;s IBIT had a net inflow of $523.7 million, while ARK&apos;s ARKB experienced a net outflow of $149.9 million, and Fidelity&apos;s FBTC had a net outflow of $113.5 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24737</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>