<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>TRM Labs Partners with Binance and Coinbase to Launch the First Network for Real-Time Response to Crypto Crime</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25507</link>
      <description>On August 21st, TRM Labs, in conjunction with Coinbase, Binance, Kraken, PayPal, and other entities, launched the Beacon Network, establishing the world&apos;s first real-time cryptocurrency crime response network. The network aims to collaboratively track and freeze illegal crypto funds in real time through the cooperation of CEXs, payment institutions, law enforcement agencies, and security researchers.TRM Labs characterized this as the first &quot;end-to-end anti-money laundering chain&quot; for illicit crypto assets, with the process from detection to action taking only minutes. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Becomes the Silver Sponsor of Taipei Blockchain Week 2025, Promoting the Convergence of Web3 and AI</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25506</link>
      <description>August 21st. As per an announcement by WEEX, WEEX will take part as a silver sponsor in the 2025 Taipei Blockchain Week (TBW2025). This event will be held grandly from September 4th to 6th at the Songshan Cultural and Creative Park in Taipei.Being the largest immersive Web3 and AI event in Asia, the 2025 Taipei Blockchain Week will gather blockchain and cryptocurrency experts and enthusiasts from around the world. For the first time, it will introduce the theme of AI to explore the future possibilities of the integration of blockchain and artificial intelligence technologies. The event aims to drive industry innovation and development through multi-dimensional workshops, exhibitions, and interactive experiences. The WEEX trading platform has sponsored the Taipei Blockchain Week for two consecutive years, which shows its deep involvement in the Web3 field and brand influence.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: YZY Falls Below $1.2</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25505</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to GMGN market data, YZY fell below $1.2 and is currently trading at $1.15. The total trading volume since its launch is $3.972 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25505</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain trader is 3x short on YZY, currently with an unrealized gain of $168,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25504</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a trader initiated a short position in YZY with a 3x leverage. Currently, they are holding a floating profit of $168,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyStonks Risk Management Incident Participant Caroline: Previously published information regarding MyStonks was inaccurate and has now been removed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25503</link>
      <description>On August 21st, User X Caroline (@thcaroline2233) declared that the information previously provided by this account about the MyStonks platform was false and has now been removed.In a previous communication, Caroline mentioned that she was unable to withdraw $6.2 million from the on-chain security platform MyStocks due to a risk control activation. MyStonks responded in a post, indicating that they had received a regulatory enforcement request regarding a particular user. MyStonks emphasized that the security of user assets and the stable operation of the business are of the utmost importance. The platform will continuously optimize compliance measures to protect the legitimate rights and interests of all users and their funds. As a compliant platform, MyStonks will actively cooperate with any regulatory actions requested by sovereign countries.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Network Achieves a Real TPS of 2300 During YZY Token Launch, Setting a New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25502</link>
      <description>On August 21st, during the YZY token launch, the actual TPS (non-voting transactions) of the Solana Network reached 2300, hitting a new all-time high. (Solana Floor)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn: Bought YZY, Retail FOMO Rally on the Horizon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25501</link>
      <description>On August 21st, James Wynn made a post stating that he had purchased YZY and said, &quot;This might actually set off a bull market in the retail sector. Let&apos;s wait and observe.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A trader goes long on YZY with 3x leverage for the third time, having lost nearly $1.6 million in the previous two attempts.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25500</link>
      <description>August 21th. Based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, trader 0x68c0 has once again initiated a 3x long position on YZY. In the past hour, he has carried out 2 long trades on $YZY. Both trades ended in losses, with a total loss of $1.596 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25500</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the release of the Federal Reserve&apos;s July meeting minutes, the market reduced its expectations of a rate cut in September.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25499</link>
      <description>August 21: This morning, the Federal Reserve made public the minutes of its July meeting. It was noted that trade tensions have introduced significant uncertainties. Moreover, the downward revision of non-farm payroll numbers has aggravated concerns regarding economic slowdown.According to Polymarket data, at present, the market anticipates that the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut in September will decrease to 68%, and the probability of a 50-basis-point rate cut will drop to 2%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25499</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa is hiring a Blockchain Data Analyst, with an annual salary of up to $166,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25498</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on the job posting on SmartRecruiters, global payment technology giant Visa is in the process of recruiting a On-chain Data Analyst to become a part of Visa&apos;s cryptocurrency product team. This position demands that applicants possess knowledge in both the blockchain and payment domains. They should be proficient in SQL/Python and data visualization tools. Additionally, having experience in using on-chain data analysis tools such as Dune, Allium, Artemis, etc. is required.The job location is in Foster City, California, and it follows a hybrid office model. The annual salary range for this position is between $117,600 and $166,150. In addition to the base salary, there are bonuses and equity incentives available. The main responsibility of this role is to analyze VisaNet and public blockchain data and provide the team with blockchain-related analysis reports and research briefs.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25498</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>