<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:47:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Reserve Entity and Spot ETF Holdings Exceed 9% of Current Ethereum Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26624</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on strategicethreserve data, the holdings of the Ethereum Reserve Entity and ETH Spot ETF have exceeded the current Ethereum supply by 9% and now stand at 9.2%. The details are as follows:There are a total of 70 Ethereum Reserve Entities that hold 3.6% of the total ETH supply, which is approximately equivalent to $19.96 billion.The Ethereum Spot ETF holds 5.6% of the total ETH supply, which is approximately equivalent to $30.99 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: At the current price, Bitmine would need to invest approximately $19 billion more to reach the &quot;5% Ethereum supply&quot; goal.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26623</link>
      <description>On August 28th, according to CryptoISO, Bitmine is currently reported to be holding more than 1.7 million ETH. In order to reach a reserve target of 5% of Ethereum&apos;s supply, approximately an additional 4.3 million ETH would need to be purchased.At the current price ($4534), this transaction would demand an investment of around $19.5 billion. When the ETH price is close to $4200, this cost will be reduced to approximately $18.2 billion. The estimated daily trading volume of ETH is between $30 billion and $50 billion.An analysis indicates that compared to Michael Saylor, who often makes large purchases of $500 million to $1 billion, each time causing the Bitcoin price to immediately rise by more than 2%, Tom Lee is evidently more experienced. Nevertheless, this also means that after the low point of $4060, ETH is most likely to have an &quot;invisible floor&quot; within the range of $4200 to $4400.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26623</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the Upbit listing news, TREE experienced a brief spike of over 70%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26622</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on HTX market information, due to the Upbit listing announcement, TREE witnessed a short-term surge of more than 70% and is currently trading at $0.5466.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26622</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit has added TREE/KRW, TREE/BTC, and TREE/USDT trading pairs.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26621</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to official information, Upbit has included TREE Korean Won, Bitcoin, and USDT trading pairs. Trading is scheduled to commence at 4:00 pm local time on August 28th.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26621</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has added to their Ethereum long position, with the position now worth nearly $400 million. The liquidation price is $4342.8.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26620</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Whale 0xa523 kept increasing its 15x long position in ETH. Currently, the total position has reached 86,845 ETH ($3.977 billion), and the liquidation price is $4342.8.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 05:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26620</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Breaks $113,000, Surging 0.94% in Nearly 1 Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26619</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin has surged past $113,000, and the current price stands at $113,030, indicating a nearly 0.94% increase in the past hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26619</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun: Bought around $10.65 million worth of PUMP tokens in the past week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26617</link>
      <description>Update: On August 28th, pump.fun declared in a post that they had acquired approximately $10.65 million worth of PUMP tokens in the past week. This amount is equivalent to 99.32% of their total earnings during the period from August 20th to August 26th.As of the present moment, pump.fun has made a total purchase of more than $58.13 million worth of PUMP tokens, which accounts for 4.261% of the circulating supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26617</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Investment Advisor」 Emerges as the Largest Purchasing Group for Crypto Spot ETF, Signaling a Shift in Funds Flow from Speculation to Long-term, Portfolio-driven Allocation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26618</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to the data disclosed by Bloomberg analyst James Seyffart, the investment advisor &quot;which is known for dominating the Ethereum ETF&quot; made an investment of over $1.3 billion in the second quarter. This is equivalent to 539,000 Ether, representing a 68% increase compared to the previous quarter. A similar situation was observed with the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF. &quot;Now, advisors are the largest holders,&quot; holding 161,000 Bitcoin with a value of over $17 billion.In response to this, Vincent Liu, the Chief Investment Officer of Kronos Research, stated that this data indicates a shift in fund flows from being speculative to being long-term and portfolio-driven allocations. &quot;As the largest holders, their strategic positioning has provided deeper liquidity and a more stable foundation for the integration of cryptocurrency into the global markets.&quot; Furthermore, as more advisors adopt Bitcoin and Ether ETFs, cryptocurrency will be recommended and recognized as a long-term diver</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 04:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26618</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>glassnode: Bitcoin&apos;s recent support is located in the $107k range, and if broken, it will test the $93k to $95k range.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26616</link>
      <description>August 28th: Glassnode presented a report indicating that the crucial support range for Bitcoin is between $107,000 and $108,900. In case this range is broken through, there is additional downside potential within the range of $93,000 to $95,000, where a cluster of on-chain support levels is located. Due to the selling pressure from short-term holders, $113,600 may serve as a resistance level for any rebound.Presently, the spot market demand for Bitcoin is neutral, while the perpetual futures market sentiment is bearish yet fragile. The funding rate remains at approximately 0.01%, suggesting that market sentiment remains uncertain. When compared to previous cycles, the current correction is not substantial, but confidence is declining, and the market is likely to reach a balance between a rebound and further downside.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Senator Proposes On-chain National Budget to Enhance Fiscal Transparency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26615</link>
      <description>August 28th, Philippine Senator Bam Aquino proposed at the Manila Tech Summit that national budget transactions should be documented on the blockchain in order for citizens to monitor every fund flow. He stated, &quot;No one would be inclined to place transactions on a chain that can be traced by everyone, but we are willing to give it a try.&quot;There has not been a formal bill submitted yet. Once implemented, the plan will rely on the blockchain platform already launched by the Philippine Department of Budget and Management (DBM), which has become the first in Asia to place certain financial documents on the chain.The platform is supported by the local blockchain infrastructure company BayaniChain. Its CEO Paul Soliman pointed out that although blockchain is not a &quot;panacea&quot; against corruption, it can enhance accountability through an unalterable record. The existing DBM system utilizes the Polygon PoS network as a transparency and consensus layer, where budget-related documents such as Sp</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26615</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>