<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:53:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SkyBridge Founder: Maintaining Bitcoin End-of-Year Target Price of $180,000 to $200,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25214</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Anthony Scaramucci, the founder of SkyBridge Capital, stated in an interview with CNBC that he maintains his year-end price target for Bitcoin to be between $180,000 and $200,000. He also touched upon this week&apos;s Wyoming Blockchain Summit, the potential next Fed chair, the current status of Bitcoin, and his perspectives on stablecoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25214</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monex USA: Federal Reserve May Speed Up Interest Rate Cuts After Powell&apos;s Term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25213</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Monex USA indicated that after Powell&apos;s term concludes, the Federal Reserve may expedite interest rate cuts; there is a high likelihood that U.S. companies will pass on the cost of tariffs to consumers. (FX Street)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25213</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMask will natively integrate the TRON network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25212</link>
      <description>August 19th - As per The Block, a strategic partnership agreement has been reached between TRON DAO and MetaMask. MetaMask will incorporate TRON natively within its self-hosted encrypted wallet that is developed by Consensys. This integration will enable MetaMask users to interact directly with the TRON ecosystem via the wallet interface.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25212</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle has announced that Circle Gateway has officially launched on the mainnet</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25211</link>
      <description>August 19th. According to official channels, Circle has declared that a novel infrastructure, Circle Gateway, which is intended to achieve a unified cross-chain balance for USDC, has officially gone live on the mainnet. This enables users to access USDC across chains in seconds and will keep expanding to more blockchains. The key features are as follows:1. Cross-chain Access within &lt;500ms: Instantly gain access to a unified USDC balance without the requirement of a cross-chain bridge or pre-positioned assets;2. Efficient Liquidity Management: Meet multi-chain liquidity demands through a single integration, minimizing capital utilization;3. Non-custodial Design: Users have full ownership and control of USDC, and funds can only be moved with signed authorization. Withdrawals do not require trust in a third party.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25211</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCI Global Announces $2 Billion Partnership Through Sovereign-Grade Encryption Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25210</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per globenewswire, VCI Global Limited (with a Nasdaq code of VCIG) declared today that it has formed a partnership with a digital asset holder. Together, they have established a sovereign-level infrastructure joint venture (JV). This JV is backed by 18,000 bitcoins, which are valued at more than $21.6 billion at the current market price.Under the terms of the JV agreement, VCI Global will own 70% of the equity and take the lead in commercialization and infrastructure management. Meanwhile, its digital asset partner will maintain full custody and control over the Bitcoin reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25210</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Son to Speak at Bitcoin Asia on August 29th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25209</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to official information, Eric Trump, the son of former US President Donald Trump, is scheduled to give a speech at Bitcoin Asia on August 29th.It is reported that the Bitcoin Asia conference organized by the Bitcoin Conference will take place at the Hong Kong Convention and Exhibition Centre from August 28th to 29th.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25209</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Trader The White Whale&apos;s long position is currently showing a paper profit of nearly $20 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25206</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the six addresses of top trader The White Whale still hold a combined value of $300 million. This includes 530,925.04 SOL long positions and 55,358.87 ETH long positions, with a total unrealized gain of $19.895 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25206</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullish has received $1.15 billion in proceeds from its IPO in the form of a stablecoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25208</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per an official declaration, the crypto exchange Bullish has made an announcement. It has arranged to obtain the proceeds from its recently completed initial public offering (IPO) in the form of stablecoins amounting to $1.15 billion. This marks a historic milestone in the utilization of stablecoins in a U.S. IPO.The vast majority of the stablecoins were created on the Solana network for Bullish. Bullish has received the following stablecoins with denominations in USD and EUR: funds from the IPO, mainly settled in USDC, with some settled in EURC. All these stablecoins are held in exclusive custody by Coinbase, along with USDCV, EURCV, USDG, PYUSD, RLUSD, USD1, AUSD, and EURAU.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Latest Interview Recap: Solely Interested in Ending Russia-Ukraine Conflict, Putin and Zelensky Must Make a Decision</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25207</link>
      <description>August 19th. At 8:00 PM this evening, President Trump of the United States was interviewed on the FOX&amp;FRIENDS program. The interview has come to an end, and the recap is as follows:路 Europeans have the hope to bring an end to the war between Ukraine and Russia. (Regarding the meeting between Putin and Zelensky) We will first allow them to meet. U.S.-Russia relations only make sense when we can make progress. I hope that President Putin of Russia behaves well; otherwise, the situation will be very serious.路 Zelensky must also show flexibility. Putin and Zelensky got along better than was expected. Arrangements are being made for Putin and Zelensky to meet. Putin and Zelensky must make decisions.路 Ukraine will not become a NATO member. France, Germany, and the UK hope to deploy ground troops in Ukraine. Putin may not want to reach an agreement. We will understand Putin&apos;s intentions in the coming weeks.路 (When asked about the United States not sending ground troops during the Russ</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25207</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investment Company Cardone Capital Announces Acquisition of 130 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25205</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to official channels, the CEO of the real estate investment firm Cardone Capital, Grant Cardone, declared that he has once more augmented his holdings by 130 BTC (approximately $15 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25205</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>