<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:47:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>An Ethereum ICO address has deposited 2,000 ETH into a CEX and still holds 58,000 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24041</link>
      <description>On August 11th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, an Ethereum ICO participant transferred 2,000 ETH to Kraken, with an approximate value of $8.55 million.This whale had acquired 100,000 ETH during the ICO at a price of $31,100. Currently, the whale holds 58,000 ETH distributed across multiple wallets, which is worth around $2.4786 billion.Deposit Address: 0x815C53bF36a3BC8B066715Da459B365e6ce6c3eDICO Address: 0x2c06Dd922b61514aAFEDd84488c0c28e6dCF0E99</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24041</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Trader Profited Nearly $500,000 from SPARK Trade, While Also Increasing Their AVA Holdings by 2.79 Million Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24040</link>
      <description>On August 11th, as monitored by lookonchain, the whale &quot;8dduty&quot; recently achieved a profit of $489,700 on SPARK, with a growth rate of 906.7%. In the past 16 hours, they have purchased 2.79 million AVA tokens, which are approximately worth $118,000.This whale also holds 509.33 million PUMP tokens, with a value of about $1.83 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citigroup: Raises Year-End Target for S&amp;P 500 Index, Expects Tax Cut Measures to Offset Tariff Headwinds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24039</link>
      <description>On August 11th, the strategist of Citigroup raised the target for the S&amp;P 500 index and claimed that tax cuts should offset the negative influence of tariffs on U.S. companies. The team led by Scott Chronert increased the year-end target for the index from 6300 points to 6600 points, suggesting a roughly 3% growth compared to the close of last Friday.This quarter&apos;s earnings reports were stronger than expected, with little indication of the impact of tariffs on performance, which has driven the stock market to new highs this month. Institutional data shows that more than 81% of S&amp;P 500 index component companies have exceeded expectations, which is the highest level in seven quarters. The Citigroup team stated that companies not only performed well but also mostly maintained their expectations for the second half of the year.Therefore, market consensus earnings per share expectations are being elevated. They have raised the earnings per share forecast for S&amp;P 500 index component comp</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24039</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Ivy League Universities Hold Bitcoin Worth Nearly $130 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24038</link>
      <description>On August 11th, as per a 13F filing made public by the U.S. SEC, two out of the eight Ivy League schools, namely Harvard University and Brown University, have taken positions in Bitcoin assets. Specifically:Harvard University holds $116.6 million worth of the Valkyrie Bitcoin ETF (IBIT), and it ranks fifth on its asset list.Brown University holds $13 million worth of the Valkyrie Bitcoin ETF (IBIT), and it ranks third on its asset list.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24038</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale &quot;8dduty,&quot; who recently profited $489.7K(+906.7%) on $SPARK, bought 2.79M $AVA($118K) in the past 16 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24037</link>
      <description>Whale &quot;8dduty,&quot; who recently profited $489.7K(+906.7%) on $SPARK, bought 2.79M $AVA($118K) in the past 16 hours. The whale also holds 509.33M $PUMP($1.83M).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24037</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Bitcoin and Ethereum Approach Yearly Highs, Boosting US Stock Market &quot;BitStock&quot; Concept Stocks in Overnight Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24036</link>
      <description>August 11th. According to BiyaPay analysts, during the after-hours trading of the US stock market on August 11th, the &quot;Coin Stock&quot; concept stocks witnessed a continuous surge. Multiple cryptocurrency-related concept stocks exhibited strong performance. Ethereum-related stocks: SharpLink Gaming increased by more than 15%, BitMine rose by more than 20%, BTCS went up by more than 10%, and GameSquare rose by more than 12%; BNB-related stocks: Nano Labs rose by more than 20%, and BNC rose by more than 4%; XRP-related stocks: VivoPower rose by more than 16%; DOGE-related stocks: Bit Origin rose by nearly 15%.BiyaPay analysts pointed out that this series of gains was attributed to the continuous bullish factors in the cryptocurrency market. Especially, the performance of Bitcoin and Ethereum approaching yearly highs attracted a large number of investors&apos; attention and further boosted the prices of cryptocurrency-related stocks.In such a market environment, the BiyaPay platform offers user</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24036</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, the digital asset sector saw a net inflow of $572 million, with Ethereum ETP leading the market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24035</link>
      <description>On August 11th, as per the latest weekly report from CoinShares, digital asset investment products witnessed inflows during the previous week, reaching a total of $572 million. Earlier this week, there were outflows of $1 billion, which might have been driven by growth concerns following the soft US employment data.However, in the latter part of the week, inflows reached $1.57 billion, possibly due to the US government&apos;s announcement permitting the use of digital assets in 401(k) retirement plans. The trading volume for digital asset ETPs decreased by 23% compared to the previous week, probably because of the subdued summer trading activity. Regionally, inflows in the US and Canada were $608 million and $16.5 million respectively, while Europe continued to experience outflows, with Germany, Sweden, and Switzerland having a total of $54.3 million in outflows.Ethereum ETP took the lead in the market, attracting $268 million in inflows and becoming the highest among all assets. This l</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24035</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, the Bitcoin financial company collectively increased its holdings by approximately 5,000 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24034</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to NLNico, from August 4th to 10th, the Bitcoin Treasury company issued a total of 53 announcements. These announcements involved approximately 5,000 BTC. Here are the details:- 6 new Bitcoin Treasuries were added, with a total of 1,039.79 BTC.- There were 8 upcoming Treasury announcements, with a value of around $145 million.- 24 companies added holdings of 3,923 BTC.- 7 companies planned to increase their Bitcoin holdings, with amounts in the millions of dollars.- In addition, there were 8 other disclosures related to the Treasury.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24034</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WCR: Weekend Crypto Market Sees Strong Rebound, Market Focused on This Week&apos;s CPI Data and Institutional Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24033</link>
      <description>August 11th. QCP issued its daily market observation, stating that during the low-liquidity weekend period, the crypto market witnessed a strong rebound. Bitcoin broke through $122,000 and approached its all-time high, completely recovering from last week&apos;s decline. Ethereum performed outstandingly, rising by 21% in the past seven days and breaking through $4,300 for the first time, hitting a new high since 2021.Since mid-July, the correlation between Bitcoin and the stock market has increased significantly. Therefore, today&apos;s outperformance in the crypto market is in line with the overall trend of rising risk appetite. The U.S. stock market rebounded close to its historical high after a brief pullback following the release of last week&apos;s job data, almost ignoring the impact of new tariffs and macro uncertainty.Under the strong bullish momentum, the market&apos;s short-term focus is now on the U.S. Consumer Price Index (CPI) to be released on Tuesday. The market generally expects the ye</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24033</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TST developers sold $30,000 worth of tokens this morning, following CZ&apos;s statement that the private key to create TST has been deleted.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24032</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to GMGN data, the TST developer address sold tokens worth more than $30,000 11 hours ago. As of the time of writing, the TST market capitalization is temporarily reported at $23.51 million, with a 24-hour decrease of 3.95%. Previously, Binance founder CZ stated that the private key for the TST address had been deleted. The original text review is as follows:CZ wrote on February 6th of this year: &quot;A somewhat awkward situation. A member of the BNB Chain team just informed me: &apos;We created a step-by-step operation video tutorial for listing the MEME coin on the four.meme platform. In this video, we took a token called TST as an example. When we released this tutorial video yesterday, at the 1:18 mark, a frame showed the token&apos;s name. Some KOLs from the Chinese community began trading and promoting this token, and now the token&apos;s market capitalization has reached $494,560.&apos;This team member deleted the video upon becoming aware of the situation. But the internet</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>