<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:34:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin SPARK&apos;s Market Cap Briefly Surpasses $40 Million, With a 24-hour Gain of 80.2%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23987</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to GMGN data, the on-chain AI virtual creature concept Meme token SPARK on Solana momentarily exceeded a market cap of $40 million and reached a historical high. It had a 24-hour price increase of 80.2% and a 24-hour trading volume of $24.4 million.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins usually lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23987</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital Founder Andy Li: To launch the unified Liquid Capital brand series name, heralding the dawn of a new era in global on-chain finance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23986</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Li Xiaohua, the founder of LD Capital, stated in a post that when looking back at the past few months, being bullish on ETH and the resulting bull market, the market performed as expected or even more quickly. He is looking forward to the next major opportunity. With the deep involvement of Wall Street in the crypto market, it is expected that there may not be a major bottoming opportunity. The new financial era with 6 billion people worldwide going on-chain is approaching.LD Capital will use a new brand name - the full name of LD Capital is Liquid Capital, as well as Liquid Ventures (financial information first-level investment) and Liquid Digital, Liquid Group, Liquid Crypto, Liquid Labs, and other unified brand businesses. They will hold on to spot positions and set off again, not disappointing in this brand new era.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23986</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crypto Market Remains in a &quot;Greed&quot; State, with Sentiment Shifting from &quot;Neutral&quot; to Strongly Positive Since the Beginning of the Month</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23985</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to alternative data, the current Crypto Fear and Greed Index is 70. This compares to 69 from yesterday (with last week&apos;s average being 64), suggesting that the market sentiment is in a &quot;Greed&quot; state.The crypto market sentiment had previously dropped to 53 at the beginning of the month and entered &quot;Neutral&quot; territory for the first time since July. It has now fully recovered.Note: The Fear Index threshold ranges from 0 to 100 and incorporates the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Sentiment (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance in the Market (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23985</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stock Exchange plans to list a cryptocurrency perpetual futures contract by the end of the year, catering to institutional demand.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23984</link>
      <description>August 11th, the President of the Singapore Exchange stated that the Singapore Exchange might list cryptocurrency perpetual futures contracts by the end of the year. Cryptocurrency trading is not appropriate for retail investors, and cryptocurrency products will be launched to meet the demands of institutions. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT project Nakamigos saw its floor price reach a peak of 0.34 ETH yesterday, with a growth of over 25% in the past 7 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23983</link>
      <description>On August 11th, based on Blur market data, the floor price of the NFT project Nakamigos once exceeded 0.34 ETH, representing a more than 88% increase. Currently, it is trading at 0.19 ETH and has increased by more than 25% in the past 7 days, with a 7-day trading volume of 998.44 ETH.NFT project Crypto Fish&apos;s floor price once exceeded 0.4 ETH and is currently trading at 0.3 ETH. Its 7-day trading volume is 998.44 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23983</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This year’s cryptocurrency project funding has reached $20.6 billion, surpassing the total for the entire previous year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23982</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to CryptoRank data, by July 31, 2025, the fundraising of cryptocurrency projects this year has reached $20.6 billion, exceeding the full year of the previous year and breaking the previous funding records.Coinbase Ventures completed 44 transactions and ranked first among investment institutions. Animoca Brands and Amber Group ranked second and third respectively, with 31 and 25 transactions. Selini Capital and a16z CSX each completed 22 transactions and tied for fourth place.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23982</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institution has once again increased its holdings by 8745 ETH, accumulating a total of 68000 ETH since June 22nd.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23981</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the whale/institutional address &quot;0x395...45500&quot; has been accumulating a total of 68,000 ETH since June 22nd. The average price during this period was $2,597, resulting in an unrealized gain of $115 million. This address has been steadily accumulating ETH from $2,284 all the way up to the current $4,302. Additionally, it just withdrew 8,745 ETH from Binance in the past 5 minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23981</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: All markets have hit new highs, even higher than ever before</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23980</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Trump made a post on Truth Social saying that all markets have reached new highs and are now even higher than ever before. Paul Krugman of The New York Times had been predicting that the stock market would decline, and he had been wrong consistently for years, which led people to stay away from the &quot;greatest market in history.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23980</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins Teams Up with Suplay for a Comprehensive Upgrade of Global Distribution Channels</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23979</link>
      <description>August 11th: The prominent NFT project, Pudgy Penguins, declared a strategic partnership with China&apos;s premier toy and lifestyle enterprise, Suplay. This marks another significant milestone in the amalgamation of digital and physical collectibles markets. This collaboration will utilize Suplay&apos;s prowess in manufacturing and distribution to extend Pudgy Penguins&apos; beloved characters, which are already present in an extensive retail network, into a diverse range of physical products such as collectible cards, blind boxes, and licensed merchandise.Pudgy Penguins has already constructed a robust global retail distribution system, encompassing over 10,000 stores and forming profound partnerships with retail behemoths like Walmart, Target, and Amazon. The project has garnered over 500 billion GIPHY views, 5 billion+ TikTok video views, and achieved $10 million in retail sales. On the other hand, Suplay is a leading entity in China&apos;s toy culture sector, backed by Mihayo Capital, and has raise</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23979</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI L1 network Nesa has announced the launch of an on-chain reputation system driven by deep reinforcement learning.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23978</link>
      <description>On August 11th, the AI L1 network Nesa announced the commencement of an on-chain reputation system that is driven by deep reinforcement learning. Nesa has introduced a system composed of three control loops - request-based routing, hot-swapping and capacity rebalancing, as well as miner-level evolution.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23978</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>