<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:59:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will support Pundi AI (PUNDIAI) Contract Swap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21803</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as per official channels, Binance Alpha will provide support for the Pundi AI (PUNDIAI) contract swap. Binance will commence the suspension of PUNDIAI trading starting from 03:35 UTC on July 25th and will cancel all outstanding orders.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21803</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blueport Interactive Founder Wang Feng: The institutionalization of Bitcoin and Ethereum is a trend, and stablecoins will penetrate all industries.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21802</link>
      <description>July 25th - Wang Feng, the founder of Blue Harbor Interactive (@wangfeng_0128), elucidated the impetus for establishing LK Crypto. Wang Feng pointed out that the institutionalization of Bitcoin and Ethereum is a prevailing trend. Stablecoins will inevitably enter all enterprises or specific industries sooner or later. Stock tokenization will not merely merge coins and stocks but ultimately treat stocks as coins.Furthermore, Wang Feng predicted that the subsequent step will be that every enterprise, not limited to public companies, will form a crypto business team. Market and technical talents in the cryptocurrency field will be fiercely competed for with high salaries similar to those of AI talents.On July 16th, Blue Harbor Interactive established the LK Crypto division to supervise the company&apos;s mainstream crypto assets and expedite its Web3 and RWA layout.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21802</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital has withdrawn 200 million USDT from a CEX in the last 15 minutes, potentially indicating a partial completion of a Bitcoin sell-off.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21801</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to on-chain data, Galaxy Digital withdrew 200 million USDT from a CEX within approximately 15 minutes, which may suggest a partial sell-off of Bitcoin.Previously, Galaxy Digital had transferred more than 10,000 BTC to CEXs in less than 8 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21801</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Market Platform CoinWings has now launched the WLFI-exclusive airdrop event.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21800</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to the official news from CoinWings, the cryptocurrency market platform CoinWings has officially initiated a 1-million WLFI exclusive airdrop event for Pro users. The event has now commenced, and users who subscribe to the annual membership can obtain up to 720 WLFI airdrop rewards. This airdrop will conclude on December 31, 2025, and the rewards will be distributed uniformly after WLFI begins trading.CoinWings is an AI-driven cryptocurrency market and intelligence platform that offers on-chain AI signals, whale/whale tracking, technical analysis, listing monitoring, and a variety of practical trading tools. With the aid of large-scale model capabilities, it provides users with more professional, timely, and comprehensive market information support.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Watch: In the last 1 hour, multiple whale accounts have deleveraged. Over the past 24 hours, 2 whale accounts have collectively withdrawn $99 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21799</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight accessible at https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, changes in the holdings of multiple whale accounts came to light. Several whale short positions witnessed a reduction, and two whale accounts withdrew a combined total of 99 million USD within the past 24 hours. The details are as follows:The whale account beginning with 0x162cc decreased its SOL long position by 24,056.29 tokens, with the liquidation price shifting from 85.582 to 17.435;The whale account starting with 0x20c2d trimmed its ETH short position by 817,411 USD. The current profit and loss (P&amp;L) stands at -18,967,311.82, and the current liquidation price is 4,899.785 USD;The whale account beginning with 0x880ac reduced its ETH short position by 1,153,741 USD. The current P&amp;L is -12,912,367.65, and the current liquidation price is 4,791.017 USD;The whale account starting with 0x5d2f4 decreased its BTC short position by 1,617,326 USD. The current P&amp;L is -7,891,790</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21799</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades&apos; 20x Bitcoin Long Position Partially Liquidated, Resulting in $2.1 Million Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21797</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a portion of AguilaTrades&apos; long position in BTC (20x) was liquidated. A 720 BTC position was closed, and in this transaction, a loss of $2.1 million was incurred.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21797</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistics: Over the past 8 hours, Galaxy Digital has cumulatively transferred over 10,000 bitcoins to a CEX and still holds 27,127 bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21798</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as per the monitoring of LookIntoBitcoin, Galaxy Digital has transferred more than 10,000 BTC to a CEX within less than 8 hours. These bitcoins belong to a Bitcoin whale from the Satoshi era.As of the moment of writing, the sending address from Galaxy Digital still retains 27,127 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21798</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX has launched ASP perpetual contracts and kicked off a Contract Trading Party.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21796</link>
      <description>July 25th. According to an official announcement, Huobi HTX launched the ASP/USDT perpetual contract on July 25th, with a maximum leverage of 20 times. Meanwhile, Huobi HTX initiated the ASP Contract Trading Party from 12:00 on July 25th to 12:00 on August 1st (UTC+8), with a total prize pool of up to $10,000.During this event, users who sign up and participate in ASP/USDT contract trading and have a cumulative valid trading volume ≥$10,000 USDT will be eligible to share the prize pool according to their trading volume ranking. New contract users trading ASP/USDT will also receive exclusive benefits.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21796</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Ride or Die」 Huang Licheng suffered the second highest loss in a single-asset investment on PUMP, just behind FRIEND, making it his second biggest losing project</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21795</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to on-chain data, the 5x PUMP long position of &quot;Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng has already resulted in a paper loss of $8.66 million.This has made PUMP his second-largest single coin loss project. The top-ranked one is FRIEND.From May 3rd to June 8th of last year, Huang Licheng spent a total of 4,975 ETH (approximately $15.6 million) to purchase 8.6 million FRIEND tokens at an average price of $1.81. This FRIEND holding is currently only worth $310,000, already incurring a paper loss of at least $15 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21795</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy CEO: Ethereum Will Break $4,000, Outperform Bitcoin in the Next Six Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21794</link>
      <description>On July 25th, Michael Novogratz, the CEO of Galaxy Digital, told CNBC that institutional interest in Ethereum is growing rapidly. This could lead to a supply shock and potentially cause Ether to outperform Bitcoin in the next six months. &quot;ETH has a limited supply, so I think ETH may have the opportunity to outperform Bitcoin in the next three to six months.&quot;Furthermore, Michael Novogratz believes that Bitcoin will rise to $150,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21794</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>