<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:41:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Powell May Avoid Signaling Ease This Friday, Inflation Rebound Gives Him Reason to Remain Cautious</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25053</link>
      <description>August 18th. The market generally anticipates that the Fed will reduce interest rates by 25 basis points in September. Nevertheless, analysts from HSBC and Bank of America pointed out that although there are weak employment data and they are facing political pressure, Powell may refrain from sending a dovish signal during his speech at the Jackson Hole Symposium this Friday. Worries about stagflation risks and the inflation rebound might be the reasons for him to remain cautious. (Bloomberg)BlockBeats Note: At 10:00 PM on this Friday, Fed Chair Powell will give a speech at the Jackson Hole Economic Policy Symposium.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25053</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Ethereum ICO participation address transferred 9803 ETH to Kraken in the last 7 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25052</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a particular Ethereum ICO participant address once more transferred 4,460 ETH to Kraken, with a value of $19.85 million.During the past 7 days, this address has cumulatively sent 9,803 ETH to Kraken, amounting to a total of $43.88 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25052</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock BTCS: Will Distribute a One-Time Blockchain Dividend to Shareholders in ETH Form, with a Maximum Reward of $0.4 per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25051</link>
      <description>On August 18th, BTCS Inc. made an official announcement on social media that the company will distribute a one-time blockchain dividend to shareholders in the form of Ethereum (ETH), with a rate of $0.05 per share. Furthermore, for shareholders who convert their holdings into book-entry form by January 26, 2026 and continue to hold, an additional $0.35 per share Ethereum loyalty reward will be distributed.In total, eligible shareholders can receive a $0.40 per share ETH dividend (including the dividend and loyalty reward).The official statement pointed out that this innovative dividend is designed to reward long-term shareholders, reduce the risk of stock lending to malicious short sellers, and enable shareholders to truly have control over their investments. This is not only a dividend but also BTCS&apos;s response to shareholder trust, a testament to mutual loyalty, and a demonstration of the shared belief in BTCS&apos;s future development.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25051</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet will launch the Mitosis (MITO) Booster Event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25050</link>
      <description>August 18th. According to official information, Binance Wallet is set to launch the Mitosis (MITO) Booster event. The first season of this Booster event will commence on August 19th, 2025, at 8:00 Beijing time. A total of 15 million MITO tokens will be awarded.By depositing BNB or USDT into the Simple Yield Mitosis Treasury via Binance Wallet, one can partake in sharing the MITO rewards.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25050</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Bitcoin Dips Below $11,500, On-Chain Data Alert, Potential Sell-Off Pressure in the Next 1-2 Weeks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25049</link>
      <description>August 18th: The analyst of BiyaPay stated that according to the fund flow analysis of Binance, Bitcoin may face selling pressure in the next 1 to 2 weeks. The data indicates that the net flow of Bitcoin on Binance has turned positive, the outflow has decreased, and the exchange reserves are continuing to grow, suggesting that investors are sending Bitcoin to exchanges for profit-taking. Binance&apos;s large trading volume has a significant impact on the market, and whale selling may increase the volatility of Bitcoin prices.Today, Bitcoin has fallen below $115,000, with significant market fluctuations. Looking at the medium to long term, Bitcoin still leans towards being bearish and needs to fall below the $100,000 support area to confirm the top. After being under pressure following a short-term rally, it may continue to fall back. The bullish performance in the new week is weak, and investors should pay attention to risk control.BiyaPay provides convenient digital asset trading servi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25049</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kingdom of Bhutan has transferred 799.69 BTC to two new addresses, approximately $92.06 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25048</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the government of the Kingdom of Bhutan has transferred 799.69 Bitcoins (valued at approximately $92.06 million) to two new wallets. This transfer may be intended for depositing into a centralized exchange.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs expects the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates three times this year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25047</link>
      <description>August 18th: Goldman Sachs anticipates that the Fed will implement three interest rate cuts this year. These cuts are expected to take place in September, October, and December. The reason for this expectation is the weak growth in US jobs. Analysts pointed out that the addition of jobs has slowed to approximately 30,000 per month. This is significantly lower than the approximately 80,000 needed for full employment. Moreover, future revisions to the data may be more negative. They believe that the risks do not only stem from trade and immigration. &quot;Compensatory hiring&quot; is on the wane, and the growth in most industries is close to zero. Goldman Sachs cautioned that although the unemployment rate remains stable, even a mild slowdown in the labor market is a cause for concern. If the unemployment rate shows a more pronounced increase, it could lead to a larger 50-basis-point rate cut.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25047</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Analysis: Powell&apos;s Jackson Hole Summit May Face Noise from Trump and Bezent</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25046</link>
      <description>On August 18th, Patrick Munnelly, the market strategist of the Tickmill Group, stated in a report that the upcoming Jackson Hole Symposium, which is scheduled to open on Friday, is anticipated to be a crucial moment for the market. At that time, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will outline the near-term policy direction of the Fed.However, he pointed out that, as usual, the different views from Trump and Bostic could bring noise. Munnelly said that the noise could stem from the ongoing discussions regarding the Fed appointment, potential legal challenges, and changes in the labor market report.He further added, &quot;Prior to this, the July FOMC meeting minutes released on Wednesday may offer valuable clues to narrowing the gap in interest rate prospects.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25046</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoRich standalone version officially launched on the BIT App</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25045</link>
      <description>On August 18th, the on-chain transaction tool GoRich officially launched its standalone version and established an exclusive operation interface within the BIT App. This upgrade indicates that GoRich has shifted from a functional module to a standalone version, further solidifying its differentiated positioning in the on-chain transaction track and providing users with a clearer and more efficient one-stop on-chain transaction experience.In the standalone version of GoRich, users can conveniently utilize core functions such as Smart Wallet Signal, on-chain transactions, asset management, etc. Users can directly use the account on the BIT trading platform to complete cross-chain asset transactions. In this case, USDT can be used not only to purchase assets but also to pay on-chain Gas, without the need to prepare an additional wallet or native tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25045</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXC Lists LINEA (LINEA) for Pre-market Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25044</link>
      <description>August 18th. As per official information, MEXC commenced the pre-trading of LINEA (LINEA) at 18:00 (UTC+8) on August 18, 2025. Users are able to trade in advance prior to the opening of the spot trading for LINEA.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25044</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>