<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:33:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Will Drastically Increase Tariffs on India in the Next 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23253</link>
      <description>On August 5th, during a live interview on CNBC&apos;s &quot;Squawk Box&quot;, President Trump of the United States stated that India is the country with the highest tariffs and that he will significantly increase tariffs on India within the next 24 hours. India is not a good trading partner, and the disagreement with India lies in its high tariffs. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23253</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Will Announce Drug, Chip Tariffs Within Next Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23252</link>
      <description>On August 5th, during a live interview on CNBC&apos;s &quot;Squawk Box&quot;, President Trump of the United States stated that Switzerland made a significant amount of money through the pharmaceutical industry. He announced that drug tariffs would be imposed within the next week and chip tariffs would also be announced.We will initially impose relatively small tariffs on the pharmaceutical industry, but eventually, these tariffs will reach 250%. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23252</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Will Impose 35% Tariff on EU if Obligations Are Not Met</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23251</link>
      <description>On August 5th, during a live interview on CNBC&apos;s &quot;Squawk Box&quot;, President Trump of the United States stated that if the EU fails to fulfill its obligations, a 35% tariff will be imposed on the EU. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23251</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Might Soon Announce New Fed Chair, Powell Lowered Rates Too Late</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23250</link>
      <description>August 5th. During a live interview on CNBC&apos;s &quot;Squawk Box&quot;, President Trump of the United States stated that the position of the Fed Chair is a political one and that Powell cut rates too late. There are numerous excellent candidates for the Fed Chair, such as Warsh and Hassett, as well as two other candidates who may soon be announced as the next Fed Chair. He likes [Kevin] Warsh, but Warsh desires to remain at the Treasury. Perhaps the vacancy left by Powell could be utilized to select the future Fed Chair. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23250</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Labor statistics data is highly politicized and reiterates that the data is manipulated</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23249</link>
      <description>On August 5th, during a live interview on CNBC&apos;s &quot;Squawk Box&quot;, President Trump of the United States stated that U.S. labor statistics are highly politicized and reiterated that the data is manipulated. (Xinhua News)BlockBeats previously reported that on August 2nd, President Trump of the United States directly tweeted with accusations, &quot;This is a scam against him&quot;: &quot;In my opinion, today&apos;s job data is manipulated to embarrass Republicans and me—just as before and after the 2024 presidential election, they first presented three days of beautiful data, and then on November 15, 2024, shortly after the election, these data were significantly revised downward—this is entirely a scam.&quot; Trump then ordered the dismissal of Commissioner Erika McEntarfer of the Bureau of Labor Statistics, and her deputy William Wiatrowski will serve as the acting commissioner.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23249</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink increased its ETH holdings last week at an average price of $3,634 for a total of 83,561 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23248</link>
      <description>On August 5th, SharpLink announced in a post that from July 28th to August 3rd, SharpLink purchased 83,561 ETH with an average price of $3,634 per coin, totaling $265 million.The amount of ETH per share (that is, &quot;ETH holding concentration&quot;) is currently 3.66 ETH, which is higher than last week&apos;s 3.40 ETH, representing a 83% increase since the launch of this strategy on June 2nd.At present, 100% of the company&apos;s ETH is staked, and the accumulated staking rewards have reached 929 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kingdom of Bhutan&apos;s government transferred 517 bitcoins to a new address</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23247</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as monitored by OnchainLens, the government address of the Kingdom of Bhutan transferred 517 bitcoins (valued at approximately $59.23 million) to a new wallet (most likely to Binance).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23247</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYX is about to face a large unlocking tomorrow, with the coin&apos;s price surging nearly 5x in a single day</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23246</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst AI Auntie @ai_9684xtpa, MYX will experience a 3.9% monthly unlock tomorrow. The one-day increase of MYX is nearly 5 times, and it has surged 16 times in 7 days. Before this 38.99 million unlock of MYX, it was only valued at $3.9 million, but now it is valued as high as $59.42 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23246</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Bitcoin Premium Reverts to Positive, Analysts Bullish on Year-End Target of $130,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23245</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Coinbase&apos;s Bitcoin Premium Index has turned positive again, suggesting that the domestic U.S. demand is picking up, which further boosts analysts&apos; bullish views on Bitcoin&apos;s long-term price outlook. An analyst from the Bitcoin yield protocol TeraHash stated in an interview: &quot;If ETFs continue to receive inflows and the macro environment remains stable, Bitcoin may likely trade between $130,000 and $150,000 by the end of the year. However, everything still depends on the Federal Reserve&apos;s next decisions, especially the highly anticipated rate cut in September.&quot;It is widely held in the market that a Fed rate cut will act as a &quot;booster rocket&quot; for Bitcoin. A lower interest rate environment is more conducive to risk assets like cryptocurrencies and stocks. James Butterfill, the Research Director at CoinShares, stated that he expects the Fed to &quot;quickly shift to a dovish stance.&quot; This policy shift means a greater emphasis on economic growth rather than inflation control, usu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23245</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital reports Q2 Net Income of $30.7 Million, Reversing Previous Quarter Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23244</link>
      <description>On August 5th, the key highlights of Galaxy Digital&apos;s Q2 2025 financial report are as follows:Net income amounted to $30.7 million (with diluted earnings per share of $0.08), reversing the loss from the previous quarter.Adjusted EBITDA was $211 million.Total shareholder equity stood at $2.6 billion, and cash and stablecoin reserves reached $1.2 billion.The adjusted gross profit of the digital asset business increased by 10% quarter over quarter and reached $71.4 million.The adjusted gross profit of the global markets business increased by 28% quarter over quarter and reached $55.4 million.Total assets under management (AUM) increased by 27% quarter over quarter and reached $9 billion.The average loan book size increased by 27% and reached $1.1 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23244</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>