<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:44:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Yi Lihua: The future decade of the crypto industry is still the greatest opportunity for the average person. Long-term bullishness is the key to growth and success.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24728</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the founder of Liquid Capital (formerly LD Capital), Li Huayi, posted on the X Platform, stating: &quot;In the past decade, the crypto industry has been the greatest opportunity for ordinary people, and it will continue to be so in the next decade. Do not let short-term thinking mislead the long-term trend. I come from a rural area, and both of my parents are illiterate. After earning my first bucket of gold through entrepreneurship, I invested in tech companies while going all-in on the crypto industry. Looking back at 2015, none of these decisions seemed reliable at that time, but now it has been proved that they were all correct (although a substantial tuition fee was paid during the investment/trading/management process). Only by having a long-term bullish view can one achieve exponential growth and harvest.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Advisor Ogle: USD1 has been minted on Solana, but liquidity is not yet available</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24727</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the advisor of WLFI, Ogle, stated in a post that USD1 has just begun minting on Solana. However, this does not imply that it will immediately obtain liquidity.Based on the information on the WLFI official website, USD1 is already in circulation on the Ethereum mainnet, BSC, Tron, and Plume Network.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24727</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Treasury Capital to Conduct a Targeted Issue of Approximately 4 Million Swedish Krona Shares to Increase Bitcoin Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24725</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the board of directors of the Swedish-listed company Bitcoin Treasury Capital carried out a private placement of 13,803 Class B shares, which was approximately equivalent to 4 million Swedish Krona. The subscription price for this private placement was determined through fair negotiations and was set at 287 Swedish Krona per B share. All the B shares issued through the private placement have been subscribed and allocated. The funds will be exclusively used to acquire additional Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24725</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of cryptocurrency wallets holding over 10,000 SOL has reached 5,224, hitting a new all-time high.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24726</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as per on-chain analyst @ali_charts, the quantity of crypto wallets possessing more than 10,000 SOL (valued at approximately $2 million) has reached 5,224, reaching a brand-new record high.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24726</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Aims to Achieve 150ms Block Finality Confirmation with Major Consensus Upgrade, Related Proposal Launched Governance Process</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24724</link>
      <description>August 15th. The community governance process for Solana&apos;s SIMD 326 – Alpenglow proposal has begun. This proposal brings a major consensus upgrade with the goal of achieving 150ms block finality. The proposal voting is anticipated to last for about 16 days. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24724</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: PublicAI (PUBLIC) Phase 1 Airdrop Threshold 240 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24723</link>
      <description>August 15th. As per an official declaration, PublicAI (PUBLIC) is set to commence trading on Binance Alpha on August 15, 2025, at 15:00 (UTC+8).The Binance Alpha airdrop will be dispensed in two stages:Stage One (the initial 18 hours): Users who hold at least 240 Alpha points are eligible to claim.Stage Two (the subsequent 6 hours): Users possessing at least 200 Alpha points can participate in the second-stage airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the event is not completed, the points threshold will automatically reduce by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24723</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Bridge Surpasses $5.2 Billion in Total Value Locked, Sets New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24722</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to the data from @sealaunch Dune Dashboard, as of August 14th, the bridged funds of Hyperliquid exceeded $5.2 billion, reaching a new historical high.Yesterday, Hyperliquid&apos;s fees and revenues were $7.48 million and $6.96 million respectively, both hitting new record highs.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24722</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: PPI Surges Above Expectations; BTC Sees Short-Term Decline and Holds Firm at $117,900, Caution Required Against Pullback Risk</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24721</link>
      <description>August 15th: On August 15th, the US July PPI increased by 0.9% month-on-month and 3.3% year-on-year. Service and trade profits drove up prices, and there is a mixed interpretation regarding the high probability of a significant rate cut in September. Treasury Secretary Besent gave a speech on the &quot;neutral interest rate,&quot; which intensified policy uncertainty. The risk appetite of cryptocurrencies remains weak, and the trend is shifting towards a range-bound market.Bitunix Analyst Recommendation:The daily chart of BTC previously broke through a downtrend line and surged to 124.5k and then pulled back. The current price is above 119k, with 116,300 serving as the daily bullish/bearish watershed. The heat map shows 119,625, exhibiting a &quot;magnetic&quot; effect, with supply concentrated in the range of 124,600–126,800. It is advisable to engage in a range-bound game in the midst of policy noise. In the short term, focus on whether the market accepts 119,625. There is a possibility of testing t</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24721</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate is launching a brand new service, Gate Travel, offering a one-stop experience for booking flights and hotels with cryptocurrency payments.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24720</link>
      <description>August 15th, Gate, a prominent global cryptocurrency platform, declared that its brand-new one-stop travel booking platform, Gate Travel, has officially gone live. This platform enables bookings in more than 190 countries, encompassing over 1 million hotels and routes of 150 airlines. It supports one-click flight and hotel booking, and offers Gate users with end-to-end travel services.Gate Travel supports over 50 mainstream cryptocurrencies, travel reward points, credit cards, and buy-now-pay-later and other payment methods. With each booking, users earn travel reward points that can be directly redeemed for cash. All Gate users are entitled to a 5% exclusive discount.Users can access the Gate Travel by scrolling down on the homepage of the Gate App and navigating to the Gate Life page. Then, by clicking on &quot;Travel&quot;, they can choose the hotel or flight module, enter destination, date, and other information to search and filter results. After selecting the room type or flight and pr</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump family-linked mining firm American Bitcoin is seeking to acquire a publicly listed company in Hong Kong or Japan to fund the implementation of a Bitcoin Treasury strategy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24719</link>
      <description>August 15th - As reported by the Financial Times, the cryptocurrency mining company American Bitcoin, which is supported by Donald Trump&apos;s sons Donald Trump Jr. and Eric Trump, is set to acquire a publicly traded company in either Hong Kong or Japan.The company intends to follow the precedent set by the US company Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) founded by Michael Saylor and hold cryptocurrency on its balance sheet.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 06:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24719</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>