<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:55:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades closed an ETH long position with a profit of $1.67 million, and opened a 40x leveraged long position on BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22287</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, trader AguilaTrades liquidated his 25x leverage long position in ETH and achieved a profit of $1.67 million. Subsequently, he reopened a 40x leverage long position in BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22287</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURBOS, as the preferred DEX for the Sui Ecosystem&apos;s Ika TGE, initiates a multi-reward mechanism and early LP activity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22286</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to official information, the secure multiparty computation (MPC) network Ika of the Sui ecosystem announced the official launch of the IKA TGE today. At the same time, IKA-SUI was launched on TURBOS, a leading project in the Sui ecosystem. Both liquidity pools will simultaneously enjoy a dual reward mechanism: rewards of IKA tokens and USDC, with an initial Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of up to 5000%.At the same time, TURBOS has launched the TURBOS x IKA LP Incentive Activity. The first 100 users who provide at least $1000 of liquidity in this pool will have the opportunity to receive exclusive rewards and share a TURBOS token reward pool worth more than $5000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22286</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD1 on Binance experienced a mild depegging issue, briefly dipping to 0.9934 USDT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22285</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to market data, the price of USD1 on Binance deviated. It briefly dropped to 0.9934 USDT and has now rebounded to 0.9968 USDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22285</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Open Interest Reaches New High Since April 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22284</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Glassnode put out a post indicating that the market share of Ethereum&apos;s open interest contracts has risen to nearly 40%, reaching its highest level since April 2023. In history, only 5% of trading days have had a higher share. This alteration indicates a notable shift in speculative focus, with funds gradually transferring from Bitcoin to Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22284</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered Bank: Ethereum Poised to Break Above $4,000 in Treasury Purchase Trend</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22283</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Geoff Kendrick, the Head of Digital Asset Research at Standard Chartered Bank, stated that as cryptocurrency treasury companies continue to purchase Ethereum, Ethereum is anticipated to experience further growth. Cryptocurrency treasury companies, which are publicly listed companies holding digital assets on their balance sheets, have begun to integrate Ethereum into their asset allocations, and the institutional buying of Ethereum has even exceeded that of Bitcoin.He mentioned that due to the continuous restrictions on cryptocurrency asset investments in many jurisdictions, investors are increasingly turning to alternative channels such as public companies for allocation. &quot;If the inflow of funds can be sustained, Ethereum is expected to break through the key level of $4000 (our current end-of-2025 price prediction).&quot; (Kryptonian)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22283</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Quintenz&apos;s nomination vote to become chairman of the U.S. CFTC has been postponed again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22282</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Bitcoin.com, the progress of Trump&apos;s nomination of Brian Quintenz to serve as the new chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) might once more come to a standstill. His name has been wiped off the meeting agenda of the Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry.Quintenz, a former CFTC commissioner, is currently the policy head of the prominent venture capital firm a16z&apos;s crypto division. During another meeting of the same committee last week, his name was also unexpectedly removed from the voting list. Although the officials did not provide an explanation for the removal, there is widespread speculation that his nomination may be encountering difficulties.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22282</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spheron unveils the SPON Tokenomics, with an Airdrop and Incentive allocation of 9.01%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22281</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to official channels, the decentralized computing protocol Spheron has made the tokenomics of the SPON token public. Once the TGE (Token Generation Event) is completed, the internal accounting token uSPON will be gradually phased out, and SPON will be fully adopted as the primary economic token in the network. Users who hold uSPON will receive a 100% unlocked allocation of SPON at the TGE. Users without uSPON but with points will have to endure a 2-month lock-up period, followed by a 6-month linear release.In the distribution of the total token supply of SPON: Liquidity makes up 5.00%; the Pre-Seed Round accounts for 12.66%; the Seed Round accounts for 8.60%; the Strategic Round accounts for 1.33%; Network Rewards accounts for 24.00%; Ecosystem Projects accounts for 8.00%; Airdrops and Incentives account for 9.01%; the Foundation accounts for 10.00%; the Team and Advisors account for 21.40%.After the TGE, 41.75% of the airdrop rewards will be released immediate</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22281</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: Bitmain Plans to Establish First Factory in the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22280</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as reported by Bloomberg, Bitmain Technologies Ltd., which is the world&apos;s largest manufacturer of cryptocurrency mining rigs, intends to open its first factory in the United States within the next few months. This action is part of its strategic shift towards embracing the &quot;Made in America&quot; trend in digital assets.According to Irene Gao, the head of Bitmain&apos;s global business, the company plans to set up its new headquarters and assembly line in either Texas or Florida by the end of the third quarter of 2025. The first batch of production is anticipated to commence in early 2026, and then it will gradually increase to full-scale production within that year.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures and Alpha Finance will list PlaysOut (PLAY)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22279</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will list and commence trading for PlaysOut (PLAY) on July 31st, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). Furthermore, the Binance Futures platform will initiate the PLAYUSDT perpetual contract on July 31st, 2025, at 17:30 (UTC+8), with a maximum leverage of up to 50 times.All eligible Binance users will be entitled to a Binance exclusive token airdrop. Eligible users are required to claim the airdrop through the BinanceAlpha event page by using Binance Alpha points from July 31st, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8) to August 1st, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22279</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater&apos;s Ray Dalio: Advises Investors to Allocate 15% of Assets to Bitcoin or Gold</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22278</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the report by CoinDesk, Ray Dalio, the founder of Bridgewater Associates, recently advised investors to allocate 15% of their portfolios to Bitcoin or gold. He did this by citing the growing debt burden in the United States and the risks associated with long-term currency devaluation.Dalio stated on the &quot;Master Investor&quot; podcast, &quot;If you aim to optimize the risk-return ratio of your portfolio, then approximately 15% of your funds should be allocated to gold or Bitcoin.&quot;This perspective represents a notable shift from his 2022 recommendation of only a 1–2% Bitcoin allocation, which reflects his increasing worry about the so-called &quot;debt crisis loop.&quot; He pointed out that the United States is projected to issue an additional $12 trillion in new national debt within the next year in order to address the current $36.7 trillion national debt.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22278</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>