<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:38:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Security Alert: Hackers Launch Large-Scale Attack on TikTok Shop Users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23228</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to the latest report by the security research firm CTM360, a hacker operation named &quot;ClickTok&quot; is conducting attacks globally and targeting TikTok Shop users. The attackers have set up more than 10,000 spoofed websites and 5,000 malicious applications. They use hybrid fraud methods to steal user account credentials and spread the SparkKitty spyware with the intention of hijacking users&apos; cryptocurrency wallets.This activity has expanded beyond the 17 countries officially included in TikTok Shop. The attackers mainly take advantage of low-cost domains (such as.top and.shop) to establish phishing websites and spread malicious programs through malicious QR codes and download links.Security experts recommend that users access TikTok Shop through the official application, carefully verify the authenticity of websites, and avoid downloading software from unknown sources.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23228</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Perpetual Contract DEX Superp Launches Content Incentive Campaign, Earned Points Correspond to Subsequent Airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23227</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to official channels, the Meme Coin perpetual contract DEX Superp has now initiated a content incentive campaign. This event will run from August 4th at 6 pm (UTC+8) to August 11th at 6 pm (UTC+8). Users are able to post articles or videos on X discussing Superp and mention the Superp official account (@Superp_xyz). Then, they can submit the tweet link and email on the Superp official website.The team indicated that users can reflect on their Superp product experiences and suggestions in the content, analyze the product&apos;s innovative mechanisms, discuss the future development of Superp, Superp&apos;s TGE, and price performance.The points obtained from participating in the event will be evaluated manually based on the quality of user tweets, engagement, and influence. The points will be directly proportional to the ratio of the subsequent airdrop. The points will be distributed within 3 days after submitting the tweet.Previously, Binance Alpha was the first platfor</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23227</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Core Developer: In the coming months, the focus of development will be on the DeFi ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23226</link>
      <description>August 5, The core developer of Abstract, @0xCygaar, recently stated that in the months to come, the development of the Abstract DeFi ecosystem will be a key focus. The development team will make efforts to assist DeFi developers in achieving success within the Abstract ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23226</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum&apos;s Largest Whale Address BMNR&apos;s Position Reaches Unrealized Gains of $1.18 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23225</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to the most recent announcement, by August 3rd at 6:30 PM Eastern Time, the institution that holds the largest amount of ETH on Ethereum, BitMine (BMNR), holds 833,137 ETH. The price per ETH is $3,491.86.Based on the current Ethereum market price of $3,634, BMNR&apos;s current unrealized gain ratio is 4.07%, and the unrealized gain is $118.4 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 09:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23225</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KyberSwap Introduces FairFlow, MEV Revenue Selectively Returned to LP</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23224</link>
      <description>On August 5th, KyberSwap declared that it is set to launch a novel LP reward mechanism named FairFlow on August 6th. FairFlow is a Swap Hook based on Uniswap V4, aiming to return the arbitrage profits that were originally grabbed by external MEV arbitrageurs back to the liquidity providers (LPs). LPs can obtain rewards without staking LP tokens.The core mechanism is the Equilibrium Gain (EG) sharing plan: KyberSwap&apos;s aggregator integrates with the FairFlow pool. When a trade presents an arbitrage opportunity, the FairFlow Hook seizes a portion of the profit and distributes 70% proportionally to LPs, with 30% allocated to the platform&apos;s ecosystem. EG rewards are distributed weekly in a dual token format, and LP tokens can be used in other DeFi protocols simultaneously to earn additional yield.According to the official experimental data, the APR of the FairFlow pool is higher than that of traditional pools. For instance, in the ETH-cbBTC pair on the Base network, within 189 hours, th</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Over 70% of Linea LXP holders hold no more than 2250 tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23223</link>
      <description>On August 5th, based on Dune Data, the distribution of Linea LXP holders is as follows:? 1 - 1500 LXP: 40.0%;? 1501 - 2250 LXP: 30.4%;? 2251 - 2800 LXP: 10.2%;? 2801 - 3500 LXP: 8.1%;? 3501 - 5000 LXP: 7.2%;? 5000+ LXP: 4.0%;According to previous public information, 9% (6.48 billion LINEA) of the total supply of LINEA tokens is directly allocated to LXP holders.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23223</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Crypto Bank AMINA is launching the SUI token trading and custody service, with plans to offer SUI staking service.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23222</link>
      <description>August 5th: The Swiss crypto bank AMINA Bank has emerged as the world&apos;s first regulated bank to provide SUI token trading and custody services.It is reported that SUI is the native asset of the Sui blockchain, aiming to replace traditional Web2 infrastructure and support enterprise-grade low-latency applications and efficient transaction processing. AMINA plans to offer SUI staking services in the future and has opened buy and sell functions for customers with unrestricted trading volume. At the same time, governance tools have been incorporated to support compliance and auditing processes.In previous news, the Swiss bank AMINA supported the custody and trading of Ripple&apos;s stablecoin RLUSD.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23222</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Official: US 15% Tariff on EU is an All-In Tariff</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23221</link>
      <description>On Tuesday, EU officials stated that the 15% tariff imposed on EU goods entering the United States is comprehensive and covers the most favored nation rate. This is different from some other countries that have agreements with the US. The official pointed out that the 15% tariff applies to all goods except steel and aluminum. Currently, drugs and semiconductors have a zero tariff, but if these goods are subject to an increase due to the US 232 investigation, the tariff will also not exceed 15%. This 15% maximum also extends to cars and automotive parts. There are no quotas or restrictions on cars and automotive parts. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23221</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches Limited-Time Zero Fee Promotion for USDC Trading Pairs for VIP 2-9 and Spot Market Makers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23220</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to an official announcement, Binance will initiate a time-limited zero-fee trading activity for the trading pairs of BNB/USDC, ADA/USDC, TRX/USDC, and XRP/USDC from August 12th, 2025 to October 11th, 2025 (UTC). This activity is applicable to VIP 2 to VIP 9 users as well as Spot Liquidity Providers. During the event, both buyers and sellers will be able to avail of zero Maker/Taker fees.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23220</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: TOWNS Phase 1 Airdrop Threshold is 230 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23219</link>
      <description>August 5th. As per an official announcement, Binance Alpha TOWNS trading is set to commence on August 5, 2025, at 20:30 (UTC).The airdrop will be dispensed in two stages:Stage One (first 18 hours): Users who hold at least 230 Binance Alpha Points are eligible to claim the airdrop.Stage Two (last 6 hours): Users possessing at least 200 Alpha Points can participate in the airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the rewards are not completely distributed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points per hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23219</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>