<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:58:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>From August 1st, Indonesia will increase the cryptocurrency trading tax rate and cryptocurrency mining value-added tax (VAT) rate.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22425</link>
      <description>July 30th: The Ministry of Finance of Indonesia has issued a new regulation which will raise the tax rates associated with cryptocurrency transactions starting from August 1st. The transaction tax for sellers on local exchanges will be increased from 0.1% to 0.21%, and for sellers on foreign exchanges, it will go up from 0.2% to 1%. Buyers will no longer be required to pay value-added tax, with the original tax rate being 0.11% - 0.22%.Moreover, the value-added tax rate for cryptocurrency mining will be enhanced from 1.1% to 2.2%, and the previously applicable 0.1% special income tax will be abolished in 2026 and will be shifted to individual or corporate income tax. (Reuters)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22425</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: After the sale by the &quot;Ancient Whale&quot; of 80,000 BTC, 97% of the circulating supply is still in a profitable position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22423</link>
      <description>On July 30th, glassnode released an analysis article about the &quot;80,000 BTC Ancient Whale&quot; sell-off that took place last weekend. It was pointed out that although the sell-side volume reached as high as $9.6 billion, the market effectively absorbed the selling pressure. As a result, the price dropped to $115,000 and then stabilized briefly at $119,000, which is slightly below the all-time high.The analysis stated that even after this large-scale distribution event, the unrealized profit held by market participants is still substantial. Currently, the accrued on-chain profit exceeds $1.4 trillion, and 97% of the circulating supply is still in profit.According to multiple on-chain valuation models, the Bitcoin price is still fluctuating between $105,000 and $125,000. If it decisively breaks out of this range, it may trigger a rally to $141,000. Considering the high expected unrealized profit at this price level, the selling pressure may further intensify in this area.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22423</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Aggressive Rate Cut Could Damage Fed&apos;s Credibility, This Meeting Expected to Reaffirm Patience</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22424</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Benoit Anne, the Managing Director of MFS Investment Management, stated that the Federal Reserve is currently in a lagging position. &quot;We all hold the view that there will be more rate cuts in the future, but it is still uncertain when exactly they will commence,&quot; he said. He pointed out that the ongoing dispute regarding political intervention and the Fed&apos;s independence has caused significant disruptions to the decision-making environment. He cautioned that &quot;if the Fed were to suddenly adopt aggressive rate-cutting measures in the coming months, it could pose a certain reputational risk.&quot; In view of this, it is anticipated that the Fed will emphasize its &quot;patience&quot; stance at the FOMC meeting and reaffirm its cautious decision-making approach. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>某Hyperliquid made a profit of over $34 million. Smart Money flipped ETH long positions to short positions at an average entry price of $3,803.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22421</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per on-chain data, a shrewd whale has converted its long position in ETH into a short position today. It is currently holding a 25x short on Ethereum worth $1.9 million, with an entry price of $3,803.Moreover, this address also holds a $15.73 million 40x short on Bitcoin and a $11.05 million 20x short on SOL. The address has accumulated a profit of over $34 million on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22421</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: The development of stablecoins in Hong Kong should be anchored to real-world use cases such as cross-border trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22422</link>
      <description>July 30th: The &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; in Hong Kong is set to come into effect officially on August 1, 2025. Song Min, the Dean of the China-Central Institute for Regional Economic Development at Wuhan University, pointed out that the emergence of stablecoins is an inevitable outcome of technological progress. However, technology cannot replace regulation. China should seize the opportunity to establish a regulatory framework and follow a path of &quot;institution-led, scenario-based implementation, and gradual progress.&quot;Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin will be applicable in areas such as cross-border trade settlement and the integration of on-chain Real World Asset (RWA), which will boost the real economy. Hong Kong plays an irreplaceable strategic role in the internationalization of the RMB, with the most significant breakthrough in cross-border trade settlement. More RMB-denominated financial products need to be introduced. (NBD News)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22422</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Token Supply on Base has been higher than Solana for the past 3 days, with Zora as the main driver.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22420</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to the sealaunch data dashboard, the token issuance on Base has exceeded that on Solana for 3 consecutive days starting from the 26th, which marks the first time in history.It is worth noting that in terms of the coin issuance market share on the Base and Solana networks, Zora has been in the top position since July 23rd. As of July 28th, the coin issuance on the Zora platform reached 51,575, with a market share of 62.69%, surpassing the combined total daily coin issuance of Letsbonk (22,554) and pump.fun (4173).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22420</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Infrastructure Company Circle Tech Completes $40 Million Series A2 Funding Round, Led by Zhongan International</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22419</link>
      <description>On July 30th, RD Technologies announced the accomplishment of approximately $40 million in Series A2 financing. This was led by Zhongan International, Zhongwan International, Radiant Venture Capital, and Hivemind Capital. Sequoia China, Immutable Capital, Matrixport, and Guotai Junan International Private Equity Fund also participated.RD Technologies stated that it will expedite the development of enterprise-grade stablecoin infrastructure, thereby further strengthening its leadership position in establishing compliant stablecoin infrastructure in Hong Kong. Meanwhile, Zhongan Bank has signed a strategic cooperation memorandum to explore the application of stablecoins in compliant financial services. RD Technologies had previously participated in the Hong Kong Monetary Authority&apos;s stablecoin sandbox pilot and launched the HKDR stablecoin pegged at a 1:1 ratio to the Hong Kong Dollar.In September of the previous year, RD Technologies completed a $7.8 million Series A1 financing roun</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22419</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The police in You County, Hunan Province, China, have busted a USDT fraud scheme, where suspects lured foreign men to purchase USDT and illegally transfer assets through a trojan horse.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22418</link>
      <description>July 30th: According to the Yuxian Police, in the early morning of July 24th, under the command of the Criminal Investigation Detachment and the Party Committee of the Yuxian Public Security Bureau, a fraudulent &quot;USDT&quot; scheme in Yuxian County, Hunan Province, China was successfully raided. Three suspects, Tang, Zhang, and Xu, were arrested on the spot, and more than 30 mobile phones, more than 10 computers, and more than 30 overseas SIM cards were seized.Through investigation, it was discovered that since April 2025, the suspects Tang, Zhang, and Xu have been using multiple overseas SIM cards to register accounts on international versions of &quot;TanTan,&quot; Telegram, WhatsApp, Twitter and other social media platforms. They used edited and beautified photos of Zhang to create fake personas such as single wealthy women, solo residents overseas, and cryptocurrency players. They targeted males over 26 years old overseas, added them as friends, and followed pre-prepared scripts to engage in con</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22418</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: The overall NFT trading volume in the last 24 hours has decreased by 35.7%, reaching $16.03 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22417</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the overall trading volume of the NFT market witnessed a 35.7% decrease and reached $16.03 million. Regarding the top three NFTs in terms of trading volume, all of them are Ethereum-based projects, namely CryptoPunks, Fat Penguins, and Moonbirds.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22417</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSea Team Member: Token Airdrop Will Be Evaluated Based on User Profile</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22416</link>
      <description>On July 30th, an OpenSea team member named Adam Hollander responded in the Discord community regarding the impact of historical usage records on token airdrops. He stated that OpenSea will take into consideration users&apos; &quot;profiles&quot;.For instance, there are some people who visited here during the bull market and never returned. Others have only recently shown up, with the intention of &quot;rug pulling&quot;. Meanwhile, there are also senior figures who have never left, withstood the test of the bear market, and still remain strong here. This information is being evaluated by the foundation.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>