<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:49:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Burned 220M $BGB($1.09B) and Locked 220M $BGB($1.09B).</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27676</link>
      <description>In a major update for $BGB, 220M $BGB($1.09B) has been burned, and another 220M $BGB($1.09B) has been transferred to a new wallet for locking. This comes as Bitget (@bitgetglobal) and Morph(@MorphLayer) announce an exclusive strategic partnership.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27676</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeline: Powell Signals Rate Cut, Trump Seeks Fed Control</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27675</link>
      <description>September 4th: Following Powell&apos;s interest rate cut signal on August 22nd, Trump aimed to exert control over the Fed with the following chronological sequence:Powell&apos;s Attitude Shift:On August 22nd, at the Jackson Hole Symposium, Powell released a &quot;rate cut signal&quot; by citing a &quot;shift in the risk balance&quot;, which led to the probability of a rate cut in September rising from 75% to approximately 90%.Fed Governor Cunliffe Dismissed:On August 22nd, the same day as Powell&apos;s speech, Trump once again issued a threat to fire Fed Governor Cunliffe.On August 26th, Trump dismissed Fed Governor Cunliffe with immediate effect. A few hours later, Cunliffe responded, stating that there was no reason for his dismissal and he would not resign.On August 27th, a Fed spokesperson stated that Cunliffe still remained a Fed governor and could participate in the rate decision until a ruling was made.On August 28th, Cunliffe sued Trump over his dismissal from the Fed b</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27675</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institution has accumulated 191,000 AAVE over the past 3 weeks, worth $61.03 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27673</link>
      <description>September 4th. Based on EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, an institution has accumulated as many as 191,000 AAVE tokens, which are worth $61.03 million, through multiple CEXs in the past 3 weeks. In just the past 4 days, a total of 128,905 AAVE tokens with a value of $40.83 million have been withdrawn from exchanges like Binance and OKX. The most recent withdrawal took place just 30 minutes ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s current Union (U) airdrop single address yield is approximately $31</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27674</link>
      <description>On September 4th, based on market data, Binance Alpha has launched Union (U), and currently, U has a market capitalization of $22 million.Each eligible user can receive an airdrop of 2700 U tokens. According to the current price, the estimated airdrop value per user is around $31.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27674</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin Encounters Short-Term Cost Line Resistance, Increased Inflow of Funds Suggests Intensified Long vs Short Battle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27672</link>
      <description>On September 4th, on-chain data analyst Murphy elaborated on the potential for a post-balanced game on Binance following the accelerated growth of stablecoin balances. This morning, BTC peaked at $112,575 before encountering resistance, demonstrating the suppression of the short-term chip&apos;s average cost line at $112,700 and validating the rationality of analyzing the market from the viewpoints of short-term holder sentiment and holding mentality. The failure to break through the resistance level this time does not signify the end of the uptrend; there remains room for game theory. It was observed that since BTC entered a pullback on August 13th, Binance&apos;s mainstream stablecoin balance (USDT + USDC) has witnessed rapid and substantial growth.From August 13th to September 3rd, there was a net increase of $4.9 billion, which far exceeded the stablecoin balance growth during the same time period after BTC entered a pullback in August 2024 ($3.4 billion) and March 2025 ($2.8 billion). Cal</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEET48 has completed the burning of 23.47 million IDOL tokens and the buyback of 169.92 million IDOL tokens, further strengthening community empowerment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27671</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the world&apos;s first AIUGC centered around the entertainment sector and the fan economy ecosystem community, MEET48, announced the completion of the burning of 23,472,000 IDOL tokens. This accounts for approximately 0.489% of the total IDOL token supply and 30% of the total votes in the first Web3.0 All-Community Annual Idol Popularity Audition &amp; Ceremony (WIPA). The hash of the transaction sent to the black hole address was disclosed: 0x048070c7a8b36150ce33b75ade00af8d00c0d2335ef6b402bc72a722d83c833e.At the same time, MEET48 also completed the buyback of 169,920,000 IDOL tokens, which is approximately 3.54% of the total IDOL token supply. The buyback addresses were disclosed: 0x23787C1ca6fe2db73740f70b13c6dEF80c1c8521 and 0x5A1d78Bb15E074A085379FBcBAF959CfA7660E50.Previously, MEET48 was nominated for the BNB Chain 2025 Annual Award Rising Star and was among the Top 10 Rise Tokens in Binance Wallet&apos;s Alpha Focus in the past week. The IDOL burning and buyback plan is</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD.AI will increase the deposit limit to $160 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27670</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the AI Credit Stablecoin Protocol USD.AI declared that it will raise the deposit cap from $110 million to $160 million at 20:00 this evening. Additionally, the next increase in the deposit cap will be synchronized with the launch of the Plasma mainnet.Previously reported by BlockBeats, on August 28th, USD.AI announced a partnership with Plasma to deploy on the first day of the Plasma mainnet&apos;s launch, enabling users to deposit USDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27670</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINEA&apos;s price continued to drop after the launch of the pre-market contract, briefly touching $0.025.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27669</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to HTX market data, LINEA continued to decline after the opening of pre-market contracts. It briefly reached $0.025 and is now trading at $0.0263, with a 24-hour decrease of 14.78%. The 4-hour funding rate is currently 0.005%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 08:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27669</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US and Japan are close to reaching an agreement to reduce car tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27668</link>
      <description>September 4th - A source from the Japanese government disclosed on Thursday that Japan and the United States have reached the final stages of negotiations and are scheduled to implement measures to lower Japan&apos;s automobile import tariffs within 10 to 14 days after the U.S. President issues an executive order. The source indicated that this implies that the import tariff on Japanese automobiles will be reduced from the present 27.5% to 15%, and the new rate is anticipated to come into effect by the end of this month. The specific effective date in the executive order is still under deliberation, and the final decision will be made by President Trump. The U.S. Embassy in Tokyo has not provided a response to this matter yet. (Kin10)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 08:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27668</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Wealth: Subsidiary Registered to Establish RWA-Related Fund</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27667</link>
      <description>On September 4th, GF Quantum (00290.HK), which was listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, has set up a new fund under its subsidiary GF Strong Equity Investment Management. This new fund is called the &quot;GF Quantum Tokenized Digital Asset Limited Partnership Fund&quot; (RWA8 Fund), adding a new element to the Hong Kong RWA track. (Sohu Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 08:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27667</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>