<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:18:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Caixin: Beijing&apos;s Largest Shadow Margin Trading Operator, Song Shijie, Involved in Money Laundering and Crypto Scam, Settles with the US and UK for ￥200 Million, Assets Seized Worth ￥161 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27824</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as per Caixin, Song Shijie, the leading figure in off-exchange margin trading in Beijing, China, who owed 22 million yuan in treasury fines, surrendered nearly 200 million yuan in assets forfeiture and settlement funds to the UK and the US. The National Crime Agency in the UK seized his mansion, apartments, and bank accounts in London, which were worth approximately 161 million yuan, and determined that the funds originated from illegal securities trading in China and money laundering in the UK.The report indicated that Song Shijie was also involved in a cryptocurrency &quot;rug pull,&quot; and his 3 Binance accounts were frozen, containing about $10 million in cryptocurrency assets. According to a document from a court in Orlando, Florida at the end of March, he gave up his claim to avoid criminal charges.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The decentralized AI project Awe (AWE) has been listed on Coinbase.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27825</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the decentralized AI project Awe (AWE) was listed on Coinbase and is now accessible for purchase on the Coinbase iOS and Android apps.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27825</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the U.S. Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net outflow of $2.229 billion, while the Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net outflow of $1.673 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27823</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as monitored by Farside Investors, yesterday there was a net outflow of $2.229 billion from the US Bitcoin spot ETF. There was a net inflow of $1.348 billion into BlackRock&apos;s BIT. There was a net outflow of $1.174 billion from Fidelity. There was a net outflow of $1.255 billion from ARKB.For the Ethereum spot ETF, there was a net outflow of $1.673 billion, marking the fourth consecutive day of outflows. There was a net inflow of $1.488 billion into BlackRock&apos;s ETHA. There was a net outflow of $2.167 billion from Fidelity.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27823</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. SEC: Former Chairman Gary Gensler&apos;s Text Messages Permanently Lost Over &apos;Avoidable&apos; Technical Glitch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27822</link>
      <description>September 5th. According to a recent SEC report, owing to a series of &quot;preventable&quot; technical glitches in the agency&apos;s Information Technology Office, the one-year worth of text messages of former Chair Gary Gensler have been lost permanently.Cryptocurrency journalist Eleanor Terrett pointed out that these text messages encompassed those sent and received by the former chair through the government phone from October 18, 2022, to September 6, 2023.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27822</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Ethereum to Consolidate for Weeks, Could Peak Before Fed Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27821</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the crypto analyst @IamCryptoWolf shared an analysis of Ethereum, stating: Just as expected, aside from the usual fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD), there is nothing notable on the chart for ETH. &quot;ETH is still in a rather uneventful stage, and this situation is anticipated to persist for several weeks. The main scenario is that Ethereum will reach a high point two weeks prior to the FOMC meeting, then there will be a sell-off following the news, and ultimately reach a low point.&quot;@IamCryptoWolf published his analysis on the Tradingview platform in 2014 and has 111,000 followers on Platform X.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27821</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: WLFI Token Unjustly Frozen, Calls for Unlock</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27820</link>
      <description>September 5th, Justin Sun made a post on the X platform, saying: &quot;As one of the early significant investors in WLFI, I have not only provided funds but also placed my trust and support in the future development of this project. My aim has always been to grow together with the team and community and jointly build a robust and healthy WLFI ecosystem.&quot;However, during the operation process, my tokens were frozen unreasonably. As an early investor, I joined along with others. We made purchases in the same way, and we should all have the same rights.I appeal to the team to respect these principles, unlock my tokens, and let us move forward together towards the success of WLFI.I believe that a truly excellent financial brand must be established on the basis of fairness, transparency, and trust, rather than through one-sided actions to freeze investor assets. Such measures not only violate the legitimate rights of investors but may also undermine people&apos;s overall confidence in World Libe</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27820</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun retweeted a tweet from Nansen CEO supporting himself, with the comment &quot;I am innocent.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27819</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Justin Sun retweeted a tweet by Nansen CEO Alex Svanevik regarding the &quot;Justin Sun WLFI Token Address Activity Analysis&quot; and claimed, &quot;I am innocent.&quot;In the tweet, Alex Svanevik said, &quot;After verifying with the agent: Justin Sun did not lead to the WLFI price decline.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27819</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of Non-Farm Payrolls Data, the probability of a Fed rate cut on the CME has risen to 99.3%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27818</link>
      <description>September 5th: The US August non-farm payroll data is set to be released this evening. Prior to that, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September stands at 99.3%, with the probability of keeping rates unchanged at 0.7%.On Polymarket, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is relatively more cautious and currently stands at 88%.Moreover, derivative contracts employed to wager on the Fed&apos;s policy direction indicate that by the end of next year, the Fed will have implemented five rate cuts (each of 25 basis points), reducing the federal funds rate from the current range of 4.25%-4.5% to approximately 3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27818</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI TOP1 Holder Starts Transferring Distributed Value of $14.69M WLFI, May Sell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27817</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the top 1 WLFI holder has begun to transfer decentralized WLFI.In the past 18 hours, he has dispersed 79.54 million WLFI to 9 addresses (approximately $14.69 million). One address, moonmanifestphilanthropy.eth, had a small sell-off operation 3 days ago. Currently, the receiving addresses have no sell-off activities.The TOP1 holder, moonmanifest.eth, owns a total of 1% of WLFI tokens. With 2 billion tokens unlocked at TGE, this address is suspected to belong to TechnoRevenant, a key participant in the XPL sniper rug pull incident.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27817</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the Bithumb listing announcement, Euler experienced a short-term surge of over 30% before retracting.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27816</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on HTX market data, Euler (EUL) saw a brief surge of more than 30% and then pulled back. It is now trading at $11.4.Earlier news had reported that Bithumb added Euler (EUL) to its Korean won trading market.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>