<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:21:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Whale &quot;8dduty,&quot; who recently profited $489.7K(+906.7%) on $SPARK, bought 2.79M $AVA($118K) in the past 16 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24037</link>
      <description>Whale &quot;8dduty,&quot; who recently profited $489.7K(+906.7%) on $SPARK, bought 2.79M $AVA($118K) in the past 16 hours. The whale also holds 509.33M $PUMP($1.83M).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24037</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Bitcoin and Ethereum Approach Yearly Highs, Boosting US Stock Market &quot;BitStock&quot; Concept Stocks in Overnight Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24036</link>
      <description>August 11th. According to BiyaPay analysts, during the after-hours trading of the US stock market on August 11th, the &quot;Coin Stock&quot; concept stocks witnessed a continuous surge. Multiple cryptocurrency-related concept stocks exhibited strong performance. Ethereum-related stocks: SharpLink Gaming increased by more than 15%, BitMine rose by more than 20%, BTCS went up by more than 10%, and GameSquare rose by more than 12%; BNB-related stocks: Nano Labs rose by more than 20%, and BNC rose by more than 4%; XRP-related stocks: VivoPower rose by more than 16%; DOGE-related stocks: Bit Origin rose by nearly 15%.BiyaPay analysts pointed out that this series of gains was attributed to the continuous bullish factors in the cryptocurrency market. Especially, the performance of Bitcoin and Ethereum approaching yearly highs attracted a large number of investors&apos; attention and further boosted the prices of cryptocurrency-related stocks.In such a market environment, the BiyaPay platform offers user</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24036</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, the digital asset sector saw a net inflow of $572 million, with Ethereum ETP leading the market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24035</link>
      <description>On August 11th, as per the latest weekly report from CoinShares, digital asset investment products witnessed inflows during the previous week, reaching a total of $572 million. Earlier this week, there were outflows of $1 billion, which might have been driven by growth concerns following the soft US employment data.However, in the latter part of the week, inflows reached $1.57 billion, possibly due to the US government&apos;s announcement permitting the use of digital assets in 401(k) retirement plans. The trading volume for digital asset ETPs decreased by 23% compared to the previous week, probably because of the subdued summer trading activity. Regionally, inflows in the US and Canada were $608 million and $16.5 million respectively, while Europe continued to experience outflows, with Germany, Sweden, and Switzerland having a total of $54.3 million in outflows.Ethereum ETP took the lead in the market, attracting $268 million in inflows and becoming the highest among all assets. This l</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24035</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, the Bitcoin financial company collectively increased its holdings by approximately 5,000 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24034</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to NLNico, from August 4th to 10th, the Bitcoin Treasury company issued a total of 53 announcements. These announcements involved approximately 5,000 BTC. Here are the details:- 6 new Bitcoin Treasuries were added, with a total of 1,039.79 BTC.- There were 8 upcoming Treasury announcements, with a value of around $145 million.- 24 companies added holdings of 3,923 BTC.- 7 companies planned to increase their Bitcoin holdings, with amounts in the millions of dollars.- In addition, there were 8 other disclosures related to the Treasury.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24034</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WCR: Weekend Crypto Market Sees Strong Rebound, Market Focused on This Week&apos;s CPI Data and Institutional Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24033</link>
      <description>August 11th. QCP issued its daily market observation, stating that during the low-liquidity weekend period, the crypto market witnessed a strong rebound. Bitcoin broke through $122,000 and approached its all-time high, completely recovering from last week&apos;s decline. Ethereum performed outstandingly, rising by 21% in the past seven days and breaking through $4,300 for the first time, hitting a new high since 2021.Since mid-July, the correlation between Bitcoin and the stock market has increased significantly. Therefore, today&apos;s outperformance in the crypto market is in line with the overall trend of rising risk appetite. The U.S. stock market rebounded close to its historical high after a brief pullback following the release of last week&apos;s job data, almost ignoring the impact of new tariffs and macro uncertainty.Under the strong bullish momentum, the market&apos;s short-term focus is now on the U.S. Consumer Price Index (CPI) to be released on Tuesday. The market generally expects the ye</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24033</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TST developers sold $30,000 worth of tokens this morning, following CZ&apos;s statement that the private key to create TST has been deleted.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24032</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to GMGN data, the TST developer address sold tokens worth more than $30,000 11 hours ago. As of the time of writing, the TST market capitalization is temporarily reported at $23.51 million, with a 24-hour decrease of 3.95%. Previously, Binance founder CZ stated that the private key for the TST address had been deleted. The original text review is as follows:CZ wrote on February 6th of this year: &quot;A somewhat awkward situation. A member of the BNB Chain team just informed me: &apos;We created a step-by-step operation video tutorial for listing the MEME coin on the four.meme platform. In this video, we took a token called TST as an example. When we released this tutorial video yesterday, at the 1:18 mark, a frame showed the token&apos;s name. Some KOLs from the Chinese community began trading and promoting this token, and now the token&apos;s market capitalization has reached $494,560.&apos;This team member deleted the video upon becoming aware of the situation. But the internet</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ListaDao Proposal LIP 021: One-time 20% Token Burn, Optimizing Tokenomics</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24031</link>
      <description>August 11th. ListaDao recently put forward LIP 021. It plans to permanently burn 20% of the maximum token supply of the LISTA token (approximately 200 million tokens), reducing the maximum supply from 1 billion to 800 million to achieve a more powerful deflationary effect and enhance the stability of token value.At the same time, the proposal suggests canceling the current fixed mechanism that uses 40% of the protocol&apos;s weekly revenue for token buyback and burning, and replacing it with flexible allocation of this part of the revenue to both reward users holding veLISTA and support DAO operations and ecosystem development. The allocation of the remaining 60% of revenue will remain unchanged.The ListaDao team stated that this action will effectively control inflation risks, release more funds to drive ecosystem development, and enhance market and community confidence in the protocol&apos;s long-term value. Once approved, the proposal will be immediately executed, and the relevant tokenom</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24031</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Bitcoin is Certainty</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24030</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Paolo Ardoino, the CEO of Tether, stated that Bitcoin is all about determinism.According to Arkham data, Tether currently holds a total of 77,901 bitcoins, which are worth approximately $9.47 billion.Earlier on July 31st, Tether&apos;s financial report showed that the total holding of US Treasury bonds amounted to $127 billion. There were $105.5 billion held directly and $21.3 billion held indirectly. This was an increase of about $8 billion from the first quarter. The company achieved a net profit of $4.9 billion in the second quarter. In the first half of 2025, the total profit was $5.7 billion, including $3.1 billion in recurring profits.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24030</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance C2C launches $2000 T0 Withdrawal Limit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24029</link>
      <description>August 11th, Binance C2C declared that it will set a $2000 T0 (Instant) withdrawal limit for all users starting immediately. In order to further improve user experience, users who purchase less than $2000 worth of cryptocurrencies on the platform can avail themselves of instant withdrawals, which makes fund transfers more efficient and secure.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24029</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Hype Edition MicroStrategy」 HYPD Soars Over 17% in Pre-market Trading, Market Cap Rises to $41.8 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24028</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to data from Rockflow, the US stock &quot;HYPE Version MicroStrategy&quot; HYPD saw a surge of over 17% in pre-market trading, and its market value rose to $41.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24028</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>