<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:53:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>NFT project Rektguy&apos;s floor price surged over 47% in the past 24 hours, reaching 1.062 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21945</link>
      <description>On July 26th, the floor price of the NFT project Rektguy has seen a 47.59% surge in the past 24 hours and reached 1.062 ETH. It has witnessed a 108.24% increase in 7 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21945</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale doubled down on a long position on XRP, SOL, and BONK, with a principal exceeding 10 million US dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21944</link>
      <description>On July 26th, based on the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale deposited 11.37 million USDC into HyperLiquid and established a 2x leveraged long position for XRP and SOL. Additionally, they also initiated a small 2x leveraged long position for BONK.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Macro Outlook: Fed Rate Decision, Non-Farm Payrolls, PCE Data Release, and US-China Trade Talks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21943</link>
      <description>On July 26th, the significant macroeconomic data to be disclosed next week is as follows:Wednesday 20:15, the US July ADP Employment Change (k), with an expected value of 7.5 and a previous value of -3.5;Wednesday 00:00, a member of the Politburo of the Communist Party of China and the vice premier of the State Council, He Lifeng, will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to conduct economic and trade negotiations with the US side;Thursday 02:00, the FOMC announcement of the Federal Funds Rate;Thursday 02:30, Fed Chair Powell holds a Monetary Policy Press Conference;Thursday 20:30, the US Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending on July 26th (k), with a previous value of 21.7;Thursday 20:30, the US June Core PCE Price Index y/y, with an expected value of 2.70% and a previous value of 2.70%;Friday, Hong Kong&apos;s &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; comes into effect;Friday 20:30, the US July Nonfarm Payrolls (k), with an expected value of 10.2 and a previous value of 14.7;Friday 22:00, t</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21943</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched the U-based MDT perpetual contract, with leverage ranging from 1 to 20x.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21942</link>
      <description>On July 26th, as per the official announcement, Bitget has declared the launch of the U-based MDT perpetual contract. The leverage offered ranges from 1 to 20. Additionally, the contract trading BOT will be activated simultaneously.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21942</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP, CKB, and ENA Temporarily Rank Top Three in Upbit&apos;s 24-hour Trading Volume Leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21941</link>
      <description>On July 26th, according to CoinGecko data, in the past 24 hours, Upbit&apos;s trading volume reached $3.196 billion. The XRP/KRW trading pair accounted for 14.04% of the volume and ranked first in the Korean won market. The remaining top five are: CKB, ENA, STRIKE, ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21941</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Tron addresses holding over 10 million USDT each have been frozen by Tether</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21938</link>
      <description>On July 26th, as per the monitoring of Whale Alert, two Tron addresses that were holding more than 10 million USDT were frozen by Tether. One address was holding 12,756,824 USDT, and the other was holding 11,308,430 USDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21938</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethena team&apos;s associated address recently deposited 150 million ENA to a CEX, worth $77.35 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21936</link>
      <description>July 26th. Based on the monitoring of @EmberCN, on July 21st, following Ethena&apos;s announcement that StablecoinX would have ENA as a reserve, an address linked to an Ethena team member began to transfer out ENA.A total of 150 million ENA (equivalent to 77.35 million USD) has entered Binance and Bybit within the 5 days since the announcement. The most recent transfer to a trading platform took place 2 hours ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Co-founder Accuses JPMorgan of Blocking Gemini Due to Its Public Criticism</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21940</link>
      <description>On July 26th, Tyler Winklevoss, a co-founder of Gemini, accused JPMorgan of suspending the reconnection process to its cryptocurrency exchange Gemini because of his public criticism of the bank&apos;s latest data access policy. Winklevoss posted on X on Friday and stated that JPMorgan took retaliatory action after he pointed out that the bank&apos;s new policy showed anti-competitive behavior and could harm the fintech and crypto industry.“My tweet last week hit them where it matters. This week, JPMorgan informed us that due to that tweet, they have decided to suspend the reconnection process to Gemini. Previously, they had removed us in &apos;Operation ChokePoint 2.0&apos;,” Winklevoss wrote. The controversy arose from a recent Bloomberg report which revealed JPMorgan&apos;s decision to charge fintech firms for accessing customer bank data. Winklevoss believes this move will “bankrupt fintech firms supporting crypto purchases.”Winklevoss accused JPMorgan of trying to restrict consumers&apos; free access to the</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21940</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIBRA Project Advisor Acknowledges LIBRA as a Speculative Meme Coin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21939</link>
      <description>On July 26th, as per Argentine media Clarín, Hayden Davis, an advisor to the LIBRA project, recently submitted a document to a U.S. court. For the first time, he acknowledged that LIBRA is a Meme token and denied that it is an investment project with a business plan. This contradicts the claim made by President Javier Milei that it &quot;supports the Argentine economy.&quot;Davis&apos;s defense attorney admitted that the Meme token &quot;is not an investment, has no intrinsic value, but is an unsecured and uncollateralized asset with speculative and collectible characteristics, and its market volatility is extremely high.&quot; Meanwhile, another fund transaction came to light. On January 30th of this year, during a meeting at the presidential palace with Milei, the wallet associated with Davis transferred nearly 500,000 USDC to the centralized exchange Kraken, suspected to be related to project fund flows. Records also show that the purpose of the meeting held at the presidential palace on January 30th was</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21939</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoS Validation Protocol Blockscape Stakes Additional 140 ETH, Bringing Total Stake to 627 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21937</link>
      <description>On July 26th, based on the data of Strategic ETH Reserve, the Ethereum PoS validation protocol Blockscape has increased its reserves by approximately 140 ETH, which is worth about $510,000. As a result, the total Ethereum holdings have reached 627 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21937</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>