<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:41:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opening: Crypto Stocks Experience a Downtrend, WLFI Finance Company&apos;s ALTS Plunge 20%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27380</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the US stock market ushered in the opening of the first trading day of the week. The Dow declined by 0.9%, the S&amp;P 500 dropped by 1.2%, and the Nasdaq fell by 1.7%. Cryptocurrency stocks witnessed a general decline, encompassing:WLFI Treasury&apos;s ALT5 Sigma (ALTS) plunged by 20%. On August 11th, it announced the launch of a $1.5 billion private placement WLFI Treasury Strategic Initiative, with Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, joining the board;Bitmine (BMNR) decreased by 1.72%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) fell by 2.6%;Coinbase (COIN) dropped by 2.29%;Circle (CRCL) went down by 3.88%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) fell by 0.13%;BTCS (BTCS) declined by 4.67%;ETHZilla (ETHZ) fell by 0.75%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27380</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoshiharu Global will be renamed to Vestand and pursue a Crypto Treasury Strategy, acquiring Bitcoin and other digital assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27379</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, Yoshiharu Global Co., a Japanese restaurant operator (listed on NASDAQ: YOSH), announced that starting from September 3rd, 2025, the company will change its name to Vestand Inc (VSTD) and will adopt a crypto treasury strategy, making investments in Bitcoin and other major digital assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27379</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Avalon Labs has collected a total of $5.48 million in fees since June.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27378</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per DefiLlama data, since June, the cumulative transaction fee revenue of the Bitcoin financial services platform Avalon Labs has reached $5.48 million, and the average monthly transaction fee revenue is approximately $1.88 million. The platform&apos;s current TVL has reached $752 million.In May of this year, the Bitcoin stablecoin issuer Avalon Labs announced the completion of a strategic financing round, with YZi Labs taking the lead and participation from Mirana, CE Innovation Capital, and GSR.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27378</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company Empery Digital has announced an additional purchase of 16.51 BTC, increasing its total holdings to 4,081.39 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27377</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the US-listed company Empery Digital announced that it had increased its holdings by 16.51 BTC, raising its total Bitcoin holdings to 4,081.39 BTC. The total acquisition cost was approximately 480 million US dollars, with an average purchase price of around 117,517 US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27377</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propanc Biopharma Plans to Purchase $100 Million Worth of Ethereum in the Next 12 Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27375</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the US-listed biopharmaceutical company Propanc Biopharma (PPCB) declared its intention to purchase $100 million worth of Ethereum within the next 12 months. Propanc Biopharma pointed out that this action would reinforce its overall corporate strategy in aspects such as cryptocurrency investment, drug development, and asset acquisition.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27375</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRX Treasury Company Tron Inc Receives $110 Million New Investment, Holding TRX Worth Over $220 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27374</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the U.S.-listed TRX Treasury company Tron Inc. (TRON) obtained a new investment of $110 million from its largest shareholder to expand the TRX Treasury. Its largest shareholder, Bravemorning Limited, exercised warrants worth $110 million, which increased its holdings by 312,500,100 TRX tokens. As a result, the company&apos;s total TRX token holdings exceeded $220 million. After this transaction, Bravemorning&apos;s stake in Tron Inc. reached 86.6%, further strengthening its controlling position.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27374</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflux Foundation is exploring CFX Treasury collaboration with publicly traded companies, with a proposed lock-up period of not less than 4 years.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27376</link>
      <description>September 2nd: The Conflux Tree Graph officially launched the &quot;Conflux Ecosystem Fund Authorization Announcement,&quot; indicating that the Conflux Foundation proposed to authorize the Ecosystem Fund to engage in cooperation with public companies (including those listed on capital markets in Hong Kong or the United States) to explore the potential for strategic cooperation in the fields of Digital Asset Treasury (DAT) and ecosystem development (POS node operation, on-chain liquidity, RWA asset management). The CFX tokens injected into the digital asset Treasury of public companies will have a lock-up period of no less than 4 years.The Foundation intends to initiate a community governance vote on this matter shortly and will subsequently release a voting announcement.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Ethereum ICO Whale with 1 Million Coins」 Reaccumulates, Buys 2000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27373</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Sister (@ai_9684xtpa), following a month-long absence, the &quot;ETH ICO 1 Million Whale&quot; seems to have accumulated 2,000 ETH again, which is worth $8.79 million.From July 14th to August 4th, the whale had previously withdrawn 13,600 ETH from Kraken at an average price of $3,457 per ETH (approximately $47.01 million). This was the first time in nearly two years that the address had withdrawn ETH from an exchange instead of selling. Subsequently, from August 18th to 28th, the whale sold 5,300 ETH on-chain at an average price of $4,152, realizing a profit of $3.68 million through swing trading.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27373</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Alert: Bitcoin Hashpower Platform Bitroo Has Been Offline for Over a Year and a Half, and Users Are Still Unable to Withdraw Funds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27372</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the Bitcoin hashrate leasing and resale platform Bitroo has been experiencing abnormal withdrawal operations since April 2024. Users still cannot withdraw funds normally, resulting in a large amount of user funds being frozen. Crypto influencer EncryptedWarrior stated that he had recharged 50,000 USDT and has not received an official response yet. It is understood that the founder of Bitroo is former Golden Finance CEO An Xinxin.According to community sources, Bitroo issued an official email statement in March 2025, stating that due to an accident at an upstream cooperative mine, hashrate leasing and mining machine hosting services have been temporarily suspended. The platform stated that it will conduct an account settlement according to the agreement and fully refund user investments.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27372</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s 25x leveraged ETH long position has been partially liquidated, with a liquidation price of $4,258.75</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27371</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as monitored by OnchainLens, James Wynn&apos;s 25x leveraged long position in ETH was partially liquidated once again. Presently, he still maintains a long position in ETH with a nominal value of $300,000. The opening price is $4,317.85 and the liquidation price is $4,258.75.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27371</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>