<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:02:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The WEEX Official Community Group will host a WXT Two-Year Anniversary AMA on August 1st.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22628</link>
      <description>July 31st. An announcement was made in the official Chinese community group of WEEX, indicating that at 20:00 on August 1st (UTC+8), there will be a &quot;WXT Listing Anniversary&quot; AMA event. WEEX&apos;s global ambassadors L and Fredhsu are invited to share the ecosystem development, growth, and the upcoming deployment of WXT over the past 2 years. Users are motivated to join the group before the event starts to ask questions about WXT. Participants will have the chance to share 5,656 WXT + 50 USDT trial funds. During the event, there will also be live airdrops and merchandise giveaways as well as other benefits.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22628</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Department of Justice: The significance of the &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; lies in supporting the orderly and healthy development of the Hong Kong stablecoin market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22627</link>
      <description>July 31st. According to the &quot;Hong Kong Commercial Daily&quot;, Kenneth Zhang, Hong Kong&apos;s Deputy Solicitor General, stated that the upcoming &quot;Stablecoin Regulations&quot; which will come into effect on August 1st are based on three main aspects: a &quot;licensing system&quot;, &quot;asset reserve management&quot;, and &quot;technology and behavior regulation&quot;. The purpose is to establish a trusted market environment. He emphasized that the importance of these regulations lies in establishing a clear and transparent legal framework to ensure the orderly and healthy development of Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin market, and at the same time maintain the international market&apos;s confidence in Hong Kong as a leading global financial center. In the future, continuous efforts will be made to deepen cooperation with the mainland and international markets in various fields, and use international legal and other professional services to support mainland and overseas companies in expanding their businesses through Hong Kong&apos;s international</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22627</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Meme Coin MicroStrategy Stock Surges in Pre-market Trading, SharpLink Up by 6.44%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22626</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on the market data from RockFlow, US Stock Crypto Mimicry Stocks witnessed a general increase in the pre-market. These included:ETH Mimicry Stocks:Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) increased by 5.23%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) rose by 6.44%;Bit Digital (BTBT) went up by 3.87%;BTCS Inc (BTCS) rose by 2.28%.BNB Mimicry Stocks:CEA Industries (VAPE) increased by 4.06%;Windtree Therapeutics (WINT) went up by 0.65%.SOL Mimicry Stocks:DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) rose by 3.38%.LTC Mimicry Stocks:MEI Pharma (MEIP) increased by 8.12%.TRX Mimicry Stocks:TRON. Inc (TRON) went up by 3.98%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22626</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An whale who accumulated around 40,000 ETH at an average price of $906.5 over the past two weeks has reportedly started selling off 11,185 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22623</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the smart money that began to accumulate ETH in September 2020 is reported to have sold 11,185 ETH in the past two weeks at a price as low as $906.5. If sold, it may realize a profit of $31.35 million.Address 0x306...6Ab84 deposited 5000 ETH into Binance 6 hours ago, with a value of $19.21 million. At the same time, it initiated a redemption request of 6383.53 ETH to Lido. This is the second large deposit on a trading platform by this address this month. The previous deposit was 6185 ETH two weeks ago, approximately $22.28 million. From September 2020 to February 2025, this address and its funding sources accumulated 39,546.52 ETH at an average price of $906.5. Currently, it holds 10,513.14 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22623</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Past 6 Hours Solana On-chain Trading: Short-term Frenzy, 5 New Tokens Listed Less Than 24 Hours Ago Achieve Top Five Trading Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22625</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to GMGN data, in the past 6 hours within the hot sector, the top five tokens with the highest trading volume are all new meme tokens that have been listed for less than 24 hours. These tokens are Grepe, BONKPUTER, GENES, URANUS, and Immortal.BlockBeats reminds users that most meme coins lack practical use cases and experience high price volatility. Therefore, when investing, one should be cautious.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22625</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polygon Foundation: All RPC Services are Now Fully Restored</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22624</link>
      <description>July 31st, Polygon Foundation: All RPC services have been restored in their entirety at present, and user-facing services have also returned to normal. Fixes have been carried out for the root cause to prevent such an issue from recurring. A comprehensive post-incident analysis report will be released shortly.Yesterday evening, the Polygon network encountered a downtime.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Official: US to Impose 15% Tariffs on EU Wine and Spirits Starting August 1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22622</link>
      <description>July 31: EU officials declared that starting from August 1, the US will impose a 15% tariff on EU wine and spirits until an agreement on the industry is reached between the EU and the US. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22622</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit will list the 1000NEIROCTO perpetual contract trading pair.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22621</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bybit will commence the trading of 1000NEIROCTO futures.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22621</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Group has announced the establishment of a treasury worth over $1.5 billion in Bitcoin and SOL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22620</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the UAE-based cryptocurrency, blockchain, and digital asset infrastructure company Phoenix Group announced the formal establishment of a treasury with a value of over $150 million in Bitcoin and Solana. Currently, Phoenix Group holds 514 BTC and more than 630,000 SOL as part of its long-term reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22620</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vana will partner with H&amp;M to hold X Space on July 31st, focusing on the capital potential of cultural data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22619</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Vana is going to host an X Space on the same day with the theme &quot;From Emotion to Value: Unlocking the Capital Potential of Cultural Data on Vana&quot;. It will feature Spotify DataDAO (who recently sold user-owned streaming data to SoloAI), the former Chief Technology Officer Senior Advisor at H&amp;M, Noreen N. who is the founder of BeyondSDG, and Vana Foundation Managing Director Art Abal.This conversation will center around a core viewpoint: personal data is evolving into the most valuable cultural asset of our era. It can predict tastes, drive multi-billion-dollar business decisions, and transform social signals into actual revenue. Whether in the fashion industry or artificial intelligence, we are entering a new economic paradigm - where users not only possess data signals but also determine the ultimate outcome.“As the boundaries among ethics, identity, and income become blurred, we will explore in depth how data ownership is opening up new frontiers of power, value, and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22619</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>