<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:13:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: The Fed is considering a rate cut, but it needs to see a slowdown in employment data to &quot;give the green light.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22528</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the market almost unanimously held the view that the Federal Reserve would maintain the benchmark interest rate at 4.25% to 4.5% today. However, there is a divergence in the market&apos;s perspective on the subsequent policy path.Jefferies Chief Economist Mohit Kumar stated: &quot;In our opinion, the Fed intends to reduce rates from the current level. Nevertheless, it still needs to &apos;give the green light&apos; based on indications of a slowdown in employment data. Once the employment data shows weakness, they will initiate rate cuts.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Coinbase to List BIO, RSC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22527</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per an official announcement, Coinbase is going to introduce support for the Bio Protocol (BIO) (an ERC-20 token) on the Ethereum network. Provided that liquidity conditions are fulfilled, trading will commence on July 31, 2025, at 9 a.m. Pacific Time or subsequent to that. Once an adequate quantity of the asset becomes available, the trading for the BIO-USD pair will be introduced in phases.Coinbase will also add support for ResearchCoin (RSC) on the Base network. In case liquidity conditions are met, trading will start on July 31, 2025, at 9 a.m. Pacific Time or later. Once an appropriate supply of the asset is available, the trading for the RSC-USD pair will be phased in.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22527</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Silent for Over 14 Years Holding 3963 BTC」 Whale Recently Sold 150 Bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22526</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, the &quot;Dormant Whale&quot; which had been holding 3963 BTC for more than 14 years woke up in the past few days and has been gradually selling through a market maker. The address, after emerging from dormancy, moved 450 BTC (approximately $53.42 million). Within the past 5 days, 150 BTC entered Coinbase and the associated addresses of market makers B2C2 and Wintermute. Currently, the address still holds 3678 BTC (approximately $434 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22526</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libre Capital Rebrands to KAIO, Launches $100 Million Tokenized Revenue Fund</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22524</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the RWA platform, Libre Capital, announced today that it is rebranding as KAIO. This marks a significant step for the company in linking traditional finance with the decentralized ecosystem by means of compliant institutional-grade tokenization.In conjunction with the rebranding, KAIO has launched the tokenized Laser Digital Bitcoin Diversified Yield Fund. This is a cryptocurrency-native solution designed to offer BTC holders an attractive, enhanced, and compliant yield.The fund, managed by Laser Digital Middle East, has received more than $100 million in capital commitments. This demonstrates the trust of institutional investors in the KAIO infrastructure, which seamlessly combines cryptocurrency-native yield with the strictness of traditional asset management.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22524</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Department of Justice: Canadian Cybercriminal Sentenced to One Year in Jail for NFT Fraud</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22525</link>
      <description>July 30: The U.S. Department of Justice made an announcement that a Canadian individual received a one-year prison sentence the previous day due to conspiracy to commit telecommunications fraud, telecommunications fraud, and conspiracy to commit aggravated identity theft.Based on court documents, 22-year-old Cameron Albert Redman devised a plan to steal non-fungible tokens (NFTs). He achieved this by illegally accessing the X accounts of multiple digital artists. Redman and his accomplices employed these artists&apos; online identities to redirect their fans to a fraudulent website. On this website, the victims thought they were authorizing a transaction to have the NFTs transferred to their digital wallets, but in fact, they were unknowingly enabling the conspirators to steal cryptocurrency and NFTs from their wallets. It is reported that Cameron Albert Redman and his associates defrauded more than 200 victims and made a profit of over $794,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22525</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary: Fed Expected to Hold Rates Today, Fed Made Mistake on Inflation from Tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22523</link>
      <description>On July 30th, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen expressed that she desires to witness the Federal Reserve possessing &quot;a bit of imagination.&quot; She once again emphasized that the Fed made an error in evaluating the impact of tariffs on inflation. It is anticipated that the Fed will not reduce interest rates today. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22523</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Blockmate Ventures acquires an additional 1 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22522</link>
      <description>On July 30, the publicly traded company Blockmate Ventures announced the acquisition of 1 Bitcoin. The funds for this acquisition originated from Blockmate&apos;s existing cash reserves, and the current holdings have reached 2 Bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22522</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: Trade Negotiations Can Continue After August 1 If No Trade Agreement Is Reached</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22521</link>
      <description>July 30th: Treasury Secretary Yellen of the U.S. said, &quot;In the absence of an agreement, trade negotiations can proceed after August 1. I expect August to be quite busy as trade agreements still need to be reached.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22521</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Surges Above $3800</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22520</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum saw a rebound and managed to break through $3800. It witnessed a 0.03% decrease in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22519</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin saw a rebound and surpassed $11,800. The 24-hour decline narrowed to 0.12%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22519</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>