<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:43:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The ETH balance in the Ethereum PoS network&apos;s Exit Queue has dropped to 878,000 ETH, while over 200,000 ETH are waiting to join.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25516</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 878,966 ETH, which is approximately worth $37.7 billion. This shows some relief compared to the previous all-time high.At the same time, the amount of ETH queued to join the network is about 203,206, and it is also showing a downward trend.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may choose to cash out after Ethereum&apos;s significant rise since the April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also boosting the entry queue. For example, listed companies like SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion are increasing their ETH holdings and staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25516</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insight: The LP set by YZY developers can result in traders facing an implicit fee rate of 4-5%, due to excessive slippage</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25515</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to the crypto Key Opinion Leader @0xBiZzy, the YZY developer-set LP managed to earn nearly $10 million in transaction fees within just a few hours. What is even more remarkable is that the Bin Step (price range) of the LP was set too high (100 instead of the usual 50), which led to traders facing an implied fee rate of 4-5%. This indicates that the total cost for traders to enter and exit the transaction amounted to approximately 10%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View: Fed&apos;s Powell May Stay Neutral at Jackson Hole Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25514</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Blerina Uruci, the Chief U.S. Economist of T. Rowe Price, stated that during the Jackson Hole meeting, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell&apos;s speech may lay emphasis on maintaining maximum flexibility for the upcoming FOMC meetings and suggest that the policy path will be contingent upon inflation and labor market data.She pointed out that prior to the Fed meeting on September 17th, there will also be a jobs report and a CPI report. In the event that inflation rises significantly or the labor market exhibits strong improvement, the likelihood of keeping rates unchanged at the next meeting is higher; if August job growth drops to below 50,000 per month and the unemployment rate rises, there may be a dovish rate cut of 50 basis points. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25514</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale entered YZY at $1.56, exited at $1.06, and incurred a $500,000 loss in 2 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25513</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, the Whale address 6ZFnRH spent 1.55 million USDC to purchase 996,453 YZY tokens at a price of $1.56. Subsequently, it sold them off at a price of $1.06. Within less than 2 hours, the whale suffered a loss of $500,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25513</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boya Interactive has signed a Stock Placement Agreement for a maximum financing of 441 million Hong Kong dollars, to be used for business development in the Web3 space.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25512</link>
      <description>August 21st. According to an official announcement, Boyaa Interactive International Limited declared that it has reached a placing agreement with the placing agent. The intention is to place up to 63,510,000 new shares at a placing price of HK$6.95 per share. These placing shares account for 8.93% of the total issued shares or approximately 8.20% of the total issued shares after the enlargement.The maximum total amount of funds raised through the placing is HK$441 million, and the estimated net amount is approximately HK$436 million. The funds will be utilized for business development in the Web3 field, such as Web3 game R&amp;D and promotion, infrastructure construction, project investment and strategic partnerships, as well as for the group&apos;s operational funds and general corporate purposes.Boyaa Interactive has resumed trading. As of the writing time, Boyaa Interactive (HK:00434) is trading at HK$8, with an intraday increase of 5.68%.In March of this year, Boyaa Interactive (0434.HK)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West simultaneously posted a video releasing his own cryptocurrency on the domestic social platform Xiaohongshu, following a total of three previous posts.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25511</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Kanye West simultaneously posted a video about coin issuance on the domestic social platform Xiaohongshu (Red) Book. The video was posted at 11:24 AM, which was about 1 hour later than the YZY coin issuance.According to statistics, his account had previously published a total of 3 posts.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cactus Custody Empowers OnChain to Bring the CMBC International Currency Fund RWA On Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25510</link>
      <description>August 21st. OnChain joined forces with Cactus Custody to tokenize the CCB International USD Money Market Fund as a Real World Asset (RWA) within an on-chain operation. This offers investors an auditable on-chain investment option. The fund was established on February 2nd, 2024, and as of July 31st, 2025, it ranked first in the Bloomberg Asia-Pacific category. It leads the market with characteristics like transparency, low volatility, and a verifiable net asset value. This collaboration directly addresses four major pain points in on-chain wealth management:路 The lack of on-chain auditable custodial cash equivalents;路 The low efficiency in bank-to-on-chain fund transfers;路 The difficulty in unifying risk control audits across multiple legal jurisdictions;路 The liquidity fragmentation across multiple chains.OnChain provides RWA on-chain technology services. The net asset value is calculated off-chain and regularly brought onto the chain. Shareholding and transfer are subject to whi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers&apos; Daily: Abnormal Transaction of Cryptocurrency May Involve Criminal Activities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25509</link>
      <description>August 21st. Recently, the Second Intermediate People&apos;s Court of Beijing Municipality has heard a case related to the use of cryptocurrency transactions for concealing and disguising criminal proceeds. The defendant, being aware that it was criminal proceeds, still assisted in the transfer and was sentenced to 3 years and 6 months in prison. In August 2024, Mr. Liu sold USDT (commonly known as U Coin) to Mr. He. He knew that the cash held by Mr. He was the proceeds of crime and received 200,000 yuan in cash. The whereabouts of the involved funds are currently untraceable. After investigation, the 200,000 yuan transferred by Mr. Liu was the money defrauded from others.The final judgment of the court held that Mr. Liu, knowing that it was criminal proceeds, still assisted in the transfer. His behavior constituted the crime of concealing and disguising criminal proceeds. The court sentenced Mr. Liu to the crime of concealing and disguising criminal proceeds, sentenced him to 3 years and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: YZY briefly dropped below $1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25508</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on GMGN market data, YZY briefly fell below $1 and is currently trading at $1.0032.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRM Labs Partners with Binance and Coinbase to Launch the First Network for Real-Time Response to Crypto Crime</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25507</link>
      <description>On August 21st, TRM Labs, in conjunction with Coinbase, Binance, Kraken, PayPal, and other entities, launched the Beacon Network, establishing the world&apos;s first real-time cryptocurrency crime response network. The network aims to collaboratively track and freeze illegal crypto funds in real time through the cooperation of CEXs, payment institutions, law enforcement agencies, and security researchers.TRM Labs characterized this as the first &quot;end-to-end anti-money laundering chain&quot; for illicit crypto assets, with the process from detection to action taking only minutes. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>