<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:48:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>British publicly traded company Hamak Gold makes first-time purchase of 20 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22431</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the UK-listed company Hamak Gold announced that it had made its first purchase of 20 BTC, spending approximately ￡1.7714 million. This was part of its capital allocation and balance sheet optimization strategy. At the same time, the company entered into a strategic partnership with the FCA-regulated digital asset platform Archax in order to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22431</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: The first stage airdrop threshold for GAIA (GAIA) is 233 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22430</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per official information, Binance is set to list Gaia (GAIA). Trading will commence on July 30, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). Eligible users can utilize Alpha Points to claim a 500 GAIA token airdrop within 24 hours after the start of trading on the Alpha event page. In the first phase (the first 18 hours), users who hold at least 233 Alpha Points are eligible to claim. In the second phase (the last 6 hours), users holding at least 200 Alpha Points can participate in the second-phase airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is still in progress, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $25.16 billion worth of ETH is currently queued to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $8.92 billion worth of ETH is waiting to join.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22429</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 659,673 ETH, which is approximately worth $25.16 billion. The recent peak was 744,000 ETH. The exit waiting time is approximately 11 days and 11 hours.Meanwhile, the amount of ETH queuing to join the network is approximately 233,936 ETH, worth about $8.92 billion. The expected activation delay is about 4 days and 1 hour.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may have decided to cash out after Ethereum rebounded by more than 160% from its April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also increasing the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have increased their ETH holdings and staked the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22429</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smarter Web Company announced that it has increased its holdings by 225 Bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 2050 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22428</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the UK-listed company The Smarter Web Company announced that it has increased its holdings to 225 bitcoins, with a total holding of 2050 bitcoins. The average price for this increase is $118,080.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22428</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolut to Establish Tech Hub in Manila, Philippines</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22427</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Philippine Department of Finance announced today that the UK fintech company Revolut will set up a tech hub in Manila. (Sina Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22427</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Ethereum Faces Key Resistance at $4500, a Level Last Seen in March 2024 and During the Previous Cycle Peak</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22426</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on glassnode data, the +1σ Realized Price Range of ETH (currently at $4500) serves as a crucial upside threshold for the current rebound. This level has acted as resistance in March 2024 and during the 2020-21 cycle. A breakthrough at this level typically indicates a bullish market environment and an increased risk of structural instability.The &quot; +1σ Realized Price Range &quot; combines the Realized Price concept with the standard deviation (σ, sigma) from statistics to assess the average cost basis and price volatility of market participants.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22426</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From August 1st, Indonesia will increase the cryptocurrency trading tax rate and cryptocurrency mining value-added tax (VAT) rate.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22425</link>
      <description>July 30th: The Ministry of Finance of Indonesia has issued a new regulation which will raise the tax rates associated with cryptocurrency transactions starting from August 1st. The transaction tax for sellers on local exchanges will be increased from 0.1% to 0.21%, and for sellers on foreign exchanges, it will go up from 0.2% to 1%. Buyers will no longer be required to pay value-added tax, with the original tax rate being 0.11% - 0.22%.Moreover, the value-added tax rate for cryptocurrency mining will be enhanced from 1.1% to 2.2%, and the previously applicable 0.1% special income tax will be abolished in 2026 and will be shifted to individual or corporate income tax. (Reuters)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22425</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: After the sale by the &quot;Ancient Whale&quot; of 80,000 BTC, 97% of the circulating supply is still in a profitable position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22423</link>
      <description>On July 30th, glassnode released an analysis article about the &quot;80,000 BTC Ancient Whale&quot; sell-off that took place last weekend. It was pointed out that although the sell-side volume reached as high as $9.6 billion, the market effectively absorbed the selling pressure. As a result, the price dropped to $115,000 and then stabilized briefly at $119,000, which is slightly below the all-time high.The analysis stated that even after this large-scale distribution event, the unrealized profit held by market participants is still substantial. Currently, the accrued on-chain profit exceeds $1.4 trillion, and 97% of the circulating supply is still in profit.According to multiple on-chain valuation models, the Bitcoin price is still fluctuating between $105,000 and $125,000. If it decisively breaks out of this range, it may trigger a rally to $141,000. Considering the high expected unrealized profit at this price level, the selling pressure may further intensify in this area.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22423</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Aggressive Rate Cut Could Damage Fed&apos;s Credibility, This Meeting Expected to Reaffirm Patience</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22424</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Benoit Anne, the Managing Director of MFS Investment Management, stated that the Federal Reserve is currently in a lagging position. &quot;We all hold the view that there will be more rate cuts in the future, but it is still uncertain when exactly they will commence,&quot; he said. He pointed out that the ongoing dispute regarding political intervention and the Fed&apos;s independence has caused significant disruptions to the decision-making environment. He cautioned that &quot;if the Fed were to suddenly adopt aggressive rate-cutting measures in the coming months, it could pose a certain reputational risk.&quot; In view of this, it is anticipated that the Fed will emphasize its &quot;patience&quot; stance at the FOMC meeting and reaffirm its cautious decision-making approach. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: The development of stablecoins in Hong Kong should be anchored to real-world use cases such as cross-border trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22422</link>
      <description>July 30th: The &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; in Hong Kong is set to come into effect officially on August 1, 2025. Song Min, the Dean of the China-Central Institute for Regional Economic Development at Wuhan University, pointed out that the emergence of stablecoins is an inevitable outcome of technological progress. However, technology cannot replace regulation. China should seize the opportunity to establish a regulatory framework and follow a path of &quot;institution-led, scenario-based implementation, and gradual progress.&quot;Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin will be applicable in areas such as cross-border trade settlement and the integration of on-chain Real World Asset (RWA), which will boost the real economy. Hong Kong plays an irreplaceable strategic role in the internationalization of the RMB, with the most significant breakthrough in cross-border trade settlement. More RMB-denominated financial products need to be introduced. (NBD News)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 05:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22422</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>