<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:50:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Treasury Mints 1 Billion USDT on the Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25368</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as monitored by Whale Alert, Tether Treasury minted an extra 1 billion USDT on the Ethereum blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto mining firm BIT Mining is set to rebrand as SOLAI, aiming to expand its impact within the Solana ecosystem.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25367</link>
      <description>August 20th. According to the Associated Press, the crypto mining firm BIT Mining Limited listed on the New York Stock Exchange announced that it will rename itself as SOLAI to facilitate Solana&apos;s strategic transformation. The stock trading symbol of the company will also be changed to &quot;SLAI&quot;. In the future, the company will also explore next-generation blockchain infrastructure, decentralized finance, and smart contract innovations.BIT Mining Limited is continuously increasing its presence in the Solana ecosystem. Recently, it launched a validation node on Solana and started staking the SOL it purchased as part of its $300 million ecosystem strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25367</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes Allegedly Long 7.66M BIO Tokens, Worth $1.1M</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25366</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), it is reported that Arthur Hayes opened a position half an hour ago and purchased 7.66 million BIO tokens worth $1.1 million.Since August 10th, Arthur Hayes has already spent $14.37 million to acquire six Ethereum ecosystem tokens. Only PENDLE was partially sold (the destination of the sale could not be confirmed through the use of AMM trades), while the rest of the tokens are still in his holdings.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25366</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, Letsbonk has only minted 1 graduate token, causing its market share to shrink to 1%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25365</link>
      <description>On August 20th, BONK&apos;s Meme launchpad Letsbonk witnessed a notable decrease in token issuance and graduation tokens within the past 24 hours. It dropped from recent peaks and had once exceeded Pump.fun. In the past 24 hours, Letsbonk only had 1 graduation token, while Pump.fun had 166.According to Dune Analytics data, in the past 24 hours, the token issuance of Pump.fun was approximately 20,096, LetsBONK was 338, and BAGS was 920. It is noteworthy that the Launchpad platform Heaven has recently experienced a significant increase in market share, with a token issuance of 6,967 in the last 24 hours.In the past 24 hours, in the Solana token launch platform market share ranking, Pump.fun holds 63.6%, Heaven holds 28%, and Letsbonk&apos;s market share has contracted to 1%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25365</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Pre-market: Most Cryptocurrency Stocks Up, Bitmine Up 2.73%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25364</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on market data, pre-market cryptocurrency stocks in the US generally rose. These included:Circle (CRCL), which rose by 1.05%;Coinbase (COIN), with a rise of 0.8%;MicroStrategy (MSTR), increasing by 1%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET), rising by 2.01%;Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), up by 2.73%;BTCS Inc (BTCS), which saw a rise of 3.07%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25364</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Crown has been appointed as the President and CEO of the TON Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25363</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the TON Foundation announced today that Max Crown has been appointed as the President and CEO of the TON Foundation. Meanwhile, Manuel Stotz is stepping down in order to focus on his new role as the Executive Chairman of Verb Tech Company (which is soon to be renamed TON Strategy Co.).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25363</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A trader entered a long position with 25x leverage on ETH at $4,087.9, with a current unrealized profit of approximately $283,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25362</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as monitored by TheDataNerd, a trader initiated a 25x long position on ETH at $4,087.9 today. Currently, there is a floating profit of approximately $283,000.Since 2024, the address has been continuously taking long positions. There have been realized profits of about $8.5 million from taking long positions on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25362</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Smart Money trader has made over $48 million in profit over the past 4 months.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25361</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, a Smart Money trader whose address begins with 0x15b3 has achieved a profit of more than 48 million USD within the past 4 months.It is reported that since April, this address has taken long positions in 15 different tokens on Hyperliquid, including ETH, XRP, SOL, and LINK, with a total profit exceeding 38 million USD.In April, the trader also purchased 309 WBTC at an average price of 79,778 USD (approximately 24.68 million USD). Since June 16th, 199 WBTC have been sold at an average price of 110,687 USD (approximately 22.06 million USD). Currently, 110 WBTC (approximately 12.5 million USD) are held, with a profit of nearly 10 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25361</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashKey Capital has transferred 5,412,000 MNT to Bybit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25360</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, HashKey Capital transferred 5.412 million MNT to Bybit 15 minutes ago, with an approximate value of $7.42 million.It is reported that HashKey Capital withdrew these MNT from Bybit to an on-chain address 8 months ago. And now, within the past 15 minutes, it has been transferred back to Bybit. When withdrawn 8 months ago, the value of the MNT was $6.33 million, and now it is worth $7.42 million, indicating an increase in value of $1.09 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Stock Trading Platform StableStock Completes Seed Round Funding with Investment from YZi Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25359</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, the on-chain stock trading platform StableStock announced the completion of its seed round of financing. Participating in this round were YZi Labs, MPCi, and Vertex Ventures.StableStock is a trading-focused decentralized finance (TraDeFi) platform that is constructed around the on-chain stock ecosystem. Currently, StableStock is open to users for public testing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25359</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>