<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Chonky Penguin」 CEO Reveals Team Has Engaged in US Cryptocurrency Legislation, PENGU ETF to Cover Both Tokens and NFTs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22635</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Luca Netz, the CEO of &quot;Chubby Penguin&quot; Pudgy Penguins, stated in an interview that &quot;Pudgy Penguins has officially collaborated with the Abstract team as a government advisor to participate in U.S. cryptocurrency legislation and offer suggestions. Team members have made several visits to Washington, D.C. in the past three months and have submitted a PENGU ETF application, which will encompass not only the PENGU token but also NFTs.&quot;It was previously reported by BlockBeats that on June 26th, the Cboe BZX Exchange submitted a 19b-4 application to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for the Canary PENGU ETF.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22635</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Mercantile Exchange proposed simplifying the listing process for cryptocurrency ETFs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22634</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE) put forward a new proposal. It suggests that a crypto ETF meeting standardization requirements can bypass the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&apos;s case-by-case approval process and achieve automatic listing. The proposal indicates that if a crypto asset has been trading on a regulated market for futures for more than 6 months, the relevant ETF can be eligible for listing. Additionally, the proposal sets requirements for physically-backed ETFs. It states that a liquidity risk management plan must be established when more than 15% of ETF assets cannot be redeemed immediately.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22634</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong Stock Exchange-listed company Best Wealth Holdings is planning to change its name to &quot;Z Fin Limited&quot;, with a focus on RWA, Stablecoins, and other areas.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22633</link>
      <description>July 31. According to an official announcement, the Hong Kong-listed company Sinolink Worldwide Holdings Limited has declared its intention to modify its company name to &quot;Z Fin Limited&quot;. This change reflects the company&apos;s strategic emphasis on expanding into the fintech sector. Sinolink Worldwide Holdings has already established a foothold in the fintech sector by making investments in ZhongAn Online P&amp;C Insurance (06060.HK) and the joint venture ZhongAn Technology (International) Group (ZA Global).Sinolink Worldwide Holdings stated that it will continuously explore development opportunities in the fintech sector, with a particular focus on areas such as crypto assets, RWA, Web3, and stablecoins. This aligns with Hong Kong&apos;s policy direction of establishing itself as a hub for Asian cryptocurrency and digital asset activities.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22633</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Financial Services Commission of South Korea has led the establishment of a &quot;Virtual Asset Loan Service&quot; working group, and is expected to announce related guidelines next month.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22632</link>
      <description>July 31st. As per Yonhap News Agency, the Korea Financial Services Commission and the Financial Supervisory Service held the inaugural meeting of the &quot;Virtual Asset Loan Service&quot; Task Force in conjunction with the Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) and five major cryptocurrency exchanges today. They are planning to formulate relevant regulatory guidelines. This guidance will draw on overseas and domestic regulatory experiences and is intended to cover aspects such as leverage ratios, service targets, permissible lending assets, user education and risk warnings. At the same time, it will also examine the internal control standards of exchanges and high-risk services. The relevant guidelines are expected to be released next month and will be incorporated into the second phase of the virtual asset legislation process.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Transaction Alert: Hyperliquid Receives Around 10M USDC Deposit in the Last 4 Hours, Some Addresses See Large Withdrawals</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22631</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight at HyperInsight, within the past 4 hours, the rebalancing and opening orders of multiple whale accounts have shown a decrease. Some whales have made withdrawals or recharges.Recharge Dynamics:The whale with the address starting with 0x1597E4 recharged approximately 1 million USDC to Hyperliquid in the last hour.The whale with the address starting with 0x7E4E76 recharged around 7.66 million USDC to Hyperliquid in the last hour.The whale with the address starting with 0x8d0E34 recharged about 2 million USDC to Hyperliquid in the past 4 hours (this address had withdrawn about 5 million USDC this morning).Withdrawal Dynamics:The whale with the address starting with 0x4707d0 withdrew about 1 million USDC in the last hour.The whale with the address starting with 0x477296 withdrew approximately 9.27 million USDC in the past 24 hours.The whale with the address starting with 0</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22631</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese fashion brand ANAP increases its BTC holdings by 16.98 coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22630</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to NLNico&apos;s monitoring, the Japanese fashion brand ANAP increased its holdings by 16.98 BTC, with a total holding of 831.12 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22630</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US June Core PCE Price Index will be released tonight at 20:30 Beijing time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22629</link>
      <description>July 31st: The US June Core PCE Price Index is scheduled to be released at 20:30 Beijing time tonight. The annualized quarterly rate of the Core PCE Price Index for the second quarter, which was released yesterday, was higher than anticipated, suggesting a possible rebound in inflation in June. If the data fails to meet expectations, it will boost the speculation of a rate cut in September and cause significant market volatility at that time.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22629</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The WEEX Official Community Group will host a WXT Two-Year Anniversary AMA on August 1st.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22628</link>
      <description>July 31st. An announcement was made in the official Chinese community group of WEEX, indicating that at 20:00 on August 1st (UTC+8), there will be a &quot;WXT Listing Anniversary&quot; AMA event. WEEX&apos;s global ambassadors L and Fredhsu are invited to share the ecosystem development, growth, and the upcoming deployment of WXT over the past 2 years. Users are motivated to join the group before the event starts to ask questions about WXT. Participants will have the chance to share 5,656 WXT + 50 USDT trial funds. During the event, there will also be live airdrops and merchandise giveaways as well as other benefits.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22628</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Department of Justice: The significance of the &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; lies in supporting the orderly and healthy development of the Hong Kong stablecoin market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22627</link>
      <description>July 31st. According to the &quot;Hong Kong Commercial Daily&quot;, Kenneth Zhang, Hong Kong&apos;s Deputy Solicitor General, stated that the upcoming &quot;Stablecoin Regulations&quot; which will come into effect on August 1st are based on three main aspects: a &quot;licensing system&quot;, &quot;asset reserve management&quot;, and &quot;technology and behavior regulation&quot;. The purpose is to establish a trusted market environment. He emphasized that the importance of these regulations lies in establishing a clear and transparent legal framework to ensure the orderly and healthy development of Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin market, and at the same time maintain the international market&apos;s confidence in Hong Kong as a leading global financial center. In the future, continuous efforts will be made to deepen cooperation with the mainland and international markets in various fields, and use international legal and other professional services to support mainland and overseas companies in expanding their businesses through Hong Kong&apos;s international</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22627</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Meme Coin MicroStrategy Stock Surges in Pre-market Trading, SharpLink Up by 6.44%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22626</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on the market data from RockFlow, US Stock Crypto Mimicry Stocks witnessed a general increase in the pre-market. These included:ETH Mimicry Stocks:Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) increased by 5.23%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) rose by 6.44%;Bit Digital (BTBT) went up by 3.87%;BTCS Inc (BTCS) rose by 2.28%.BNB Mimicry Stocks:CEA Industries (VAPE) increased by 4.06%;Windtree Therapeutics (WINT) went up by 0.65%.SOL Mimicry Stocks:DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) rose by 3.38%.LTC Mimicry Stocks:MEI Pharma (MEIP) increased by 8.12%.TRX Mimicry Stocks:TRON. Inc (TRON) went up by 3.98%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22626</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>