<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:47:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Global has increased its holding of 1111 ETH, bringing its total position to 48,545 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26198</link>
      <description>August 25th. According to official channels, by August 25, 2025, Fundamental Global&apos;s current holdings of Ethereum (ETH) have risen to 48,545 coins. It recently purchased 1,111 ETH at an average price of $4,341. Based on Bloomberg data at 5:00 PM on August 24, 2025, Fundamental Global Inc.&apos;s total ETH holdings are valued at around $230 million (assuming an ETH price of $4,737). The company intends to rapidly increase its ETH holdings with the aim of becoming a 10% shareholder of the Ethereum network.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26198</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: Helen did not participate in YZi Labs&apos; strategic support for Project B.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26197</link>
      <description>On August 25th, CZ stated on social media that the cryptocurrency media TheBlock made some unfounded statements in its report on &quot;B Strategy&quot;. It was specifically added that &quot;B Strategy will receive strategic support from YZi Labs led by Binance co-founder CZ and Yi He&quot;, which was considered as &quot;over-interpretation&quot; as Ms. Yi He was not involved in this matter.Previously reported by BlockBeats, B Strategy, an investment company focusing on digital assets, announced plans to launch the BNB Treasury Company for listing on Nasdaq, aiming to raise $1 billion. The unnamed BNB Treasury Company of B Strategy will receive strategic support from YZi Labs. A representative stated that in addition to providing financial support, YZi Labs will also provide ecosystem support by connecting ecosystem partners.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26197</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol&apos;s first BioAgent Launch project, Aubrai, has been oversubscribed by 6 times.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26196</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Bio Protocol officially made an announcement on social media that the first BioAgent Launch project of Bio Protocol, Aubrai, has received 6 times more subscriptions than expected.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26196</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto-Friendly Bank Xapo Bank Hires Former FalconX Executive as Chief Customer Relationship Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26195</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to the report of CoinDesk, Xapo Bank, which is known for its crypto-friendly attitude, has appointed Tommy Doyle as its head of relationship management based in London.It is recorded that Doyle used to serve as the head of Europe for the crypto prime broker FalconX and also worked in hedge fund sales at the crypto exchange Coinbase. Before focusing on the crypto field, he had a successful career in traditional finance and worked at Wall Street banks such as Goldman Sachs, Citigroup, and Bank of America (BAC). Xapo Bank, with its headquarters in Gibraltar, is regulated by the Gibraltar Financial Services Commission (GFSC). Earlier this year, the bank started to offer bitcoin-backed loans.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26195</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Unicorn Anchorage Digital Establishes Venture Capital Arm to Support Early-Stage On-Chain Protocols</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26194</link>
      <description>August 25th. According to The Block, the cryptocurrency custody unicorn company Anchorage Digital was valued at more than $30 billion during its 2021 Series D fundraising round. Given the ongoing decline in the broader cryptocurrency funding market, the company has set up a venture capital department to offer support to early-stage protocol teams.The department is called Anchorage Digital Ventures and will provide funding and strategic assistance to founding teams that are building on-chain infrastructure. Anchorage indicated that the plan aims to assist protocols in being institution-ready from the very beginning and provide support beyond just financial investment.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26194</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boya Interactive recently spent approximately 257 million Hong Kong dollars to purchase a total of around 290 Bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26193</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Boyaa Interactive (00434) announced that from August 5th to August 25th, 2025, the Group carried out a series of transactions on the open market and purchased a total of about 290 Bitcoins for a total consideration of about 257 million Hong Kong dollars (equivalent to about 32.91 million US dollars). This purchase was made using the company&apos;s internal funds. After this purchase, as of the date of this announcement, the Group holds a total of about 3,670 Bitcoins, with an average purchase cost of 62,878 US dollars per Bitcoin. (Soochow Securities)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26193</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock-Listed IP Finance Company CASK Completes $223 Million Private Placement Financing</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26192</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as reported by stocktitan, the U.S. stock-listed IP treasury company Heritage Distilling Holding Company, Inc. (Nasdaq: CASK) announced today the successful completion of a private placement worth $223.8 million. This includes $95 million in cash and an additional $128 million in the form of IP tokens. The transaction was supported by the Story Foundation and other leading investors, such as a16z crypto, Amber Group, Arrington Capital, dao5, Hashed, Mirana Ventures, Neoclassic Capital, Open World, Polychain Capital, Selini Capital, Stix, and Syncracy Capital. The aim is to launch an innovative IP token digital asset treasury strategy. The transaction was officially completed on August 15, 2025.With this, Heritage has over 53.2 million IP tokens on its balance sheet. Based on a closing price of $6.0668 per token on August 22, 2025, these tokens are valued at over $320 million. This includes the acquisition of 23,529,411.76 IP tokens at a price of $3.40 per token using</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches Mitosis (MITO) Booster Program Season 2</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26191</link>
      <description>August 25th. As per official channels, Binance made an announcement regarding the launch of the Mitosis (MITO) Booster Event Season 2, providing $1.4 million worth of MITO token rewards.Season 2 Event Period: From 2025-08-26 00:00:00 to 2025-09-08 23:59:59.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26191</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected &quot;Sleeping Beauty Seven Years Loudly Swapped ETH for BTC Ancient Whale&quot; staked 269,400 ETH in the past 1 hour</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26189</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a suspected &quot;BTC Ancient Whale that has been dormant for seven years and recently made a high-profile switch to ETH&quot; staked 269,485 ETH on the ETH2 Beacon Chain within the past 1 hour. The value of this stake is $1.25 billion.This stake exceeds the holdings of the ETH entity in the TOP4, the Ethereum Foundation (231k ETH). This staking action has directly reduced the difference between Ethereum PoS network exits and entries to the queue to 260k ETH. By comparison, the difference yesterday was 727k ETH, accounting for 66.7% of today&apos;s queue entry increment.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26189</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $112,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26190</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin has seen a rebound and exceeded $112,000. It is currently trading at $112,148.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26190</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>