<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:14:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sui Ecosystem MPC Network Token IKA Market Cap Surpasses $400 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate 35.15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22646</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on GMGN data, the token Ika (IKA) of the Secure Multiparty Computation (MPC) network in the Sui ecosystem has exceeded a market capitalization of $400 million. It has a 24-hour price increase of 35.15%, with a current price of $0.0402 and a 24-hour trading volume of $6.7 million.BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of related tokens are highly volatile and that investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22646</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House Reiterates Support for Trump&apos;s Nomination of Brian Quintenz as CFTC Chairman</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22645</link>
      <description>July 31st: According to Bloomberg, the White House has once again expressed its support for Trump&apos;s nominee, Brian Quintenz, to serve as the chairman of the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). Previously, the confirmation of Brian Quintenz as CFTC chairman was postponed. On Monday, the Senate Agriculture Committee abruptly called off the vote on Quintenz&apos;s nomination. However, the White House made it clear on Wednesday that Quintenz still remains the top candidate for the position and they anticipate his prompt confirmation.Quintenz, a former CFTC commissioner, is currently serving as the policy head of the renowned venture capital firm a16z&apos;s crypto department. Last week, his name was also unexpectedly removed from the voting list during another meeting of the same committee. Although the official reasons for his removal were not disclosed, it is widely speculated in the public that there may be problems with his nomination.Yesterday, crypto journalist Eleanor Terret</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22645</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Tech Stocks See Significant Pre-market Gains, NVIDIA Hits New All-time High Market Cap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22644</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to the market data from RockFlow, after the solid financial reports of Microsoft and Meta, the major U.S. tech stocks witnessed significant pre-market gains. The pre-market gain of Nvidia reached 2.48% and is currently up by 1.68%, setting a new all-time high in market value. For other tech stocks: Microsoft (MSFT) increased by 8.3%; Meta Platforms (META) rose by 12%; Apple (AAPL) went up by 0.24%; Amazon (AMZN) advanced by 3.39%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22644</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank&apos;s DWS Teams Up with Galaxy to Launch Germany&apos;s First Regulated Euro-Backed Stablecoin - EURAU</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22643</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to Bloomberg, Deutsche Bank&apos;s DWS, in partnership with Galaxy, has launched Germany&apos;s first regulated Euro stablecoin, EURAU. Deutsche Bank&apos;s asset management subsidiary DWS, Flow Traders, and Galaxy&apos;s joint venture AllUnity obtained an Electronic Money Institution (EMI) license from the German Financial Supervisory Authority (BaFin) at the beginning of the month and announced the issuance of Germany&apos;s first regulated Euro stablecoin, EURAU. EURAU will fully adhere to the European Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) framework, be 100% backed, and provide institutional-grade transparency through reserve proof and regulatory reports. This stablecoin can be used for 24/7 instantaneous cross-border settlements, enabling seamless integration for regulated financial institutions, fintech companies, and corporate clients in Europe and other regions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22643</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Layer Token Ecosystem Experiences Price Surge, CLANKER Up by 31.96% in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22642</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on GMGN market data, the Base ecosystem tokens generally witnessed a rise. These include:CLANKER saw a 31.96% increase within the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $58 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $5.3 million.BNKR saw a 40.99% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $84 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $15.65 million.DRB saw a 35.91% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $22.48 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $2.24 million.noice saw a 5.13% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $29.5 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $2.06 million.KTA saw a 4.9% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $1.2 billion, and the 24-hour trading volume is $17.5 million.MAMO saw a 12.13% increase in the last 24 hours. Its current market value is $120 million, and the 24-hour trading volume is $1.27 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22642</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guotai Junan International Completes First Public Offering of Digital Native Bond Issued by a Chinese Securities Firm</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22641</link>
      <description>July 31st. The Hong Kong-listed company Guotai Junan International (1788.HK) announced the completion of the first public offering of a digital native bond by a Chinese securities firm. The issuance size does not exceed 300 million US dollars and the maturity is 3 years. This issuance adopts a direct issuance structure priced in US dollars and depends on the HSBC digital asset platform for issuance and settlement. As the lead global coordinator and settlement agent of the project, Guotai Junan International has taken the lead in enabling Chinese institutions to enter the blockchain bond market.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22641</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought 3,322 ETH after making a $13.6 million profit on Hyperliquid.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22639</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Whale 0x720A ceased perpetual contract trading on Hyperliquid after realizing a profit of $13.6 million and then purchased 3,322 ETH in the spot market, which was worth $12.84 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22639</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet: Treehouse (TREE) Booster Phase 1 Reward Distribution Has Ended</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22640</link>
      <description>July 31, Binance Wallet Announcement: The reward distribution for the first stage of the Treehouse (TREE) Booster event has come to an end. Since the total accumulated reward value has reached $750,000, there will be no more distributions. The remaining tokens will be allocated to the second stage of the event.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea Issues Warning on Cryptocurrency Loan and Margin Trading Services by Upbit and Bithumb</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22638</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per Decrypt&apos;s report, the Financial Services Commission (FSC) and the Financial Supervisory Service (FSS) of South Korea expressed their concerns last Friday regarding Upbit and Bithumb&apos;s launch of leverage up to 4 times on lending products, enabling short selling through borrowed funds. Upbit has already ceased its USDT lending service. Meanwhile, Bithumb adjusted its structure on Tuesday but still maintained the controversial 4x leverage ratio. South Korean crypto experts caution that stricter regulations may lead users to offshore platforms with weaker compliance standards, thereby weakening South Korea&apos;s investor protection and its capacity to shape its cryptocurrency market.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22638</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created address withdrew 4.2 million USD worth of tokens from Binance, including LINK, SHIB, MATIC, and ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22637</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a newly established wallet address withdrew tokens amounting to $4.2 million from Binance. Specifically, it withdrew 80,126 LINK with a value of $1.46 million; 110.34 billion SHIB with a value of $1.45 million; 3.44 million MATIC with a value of $762,000; and 142.62 ETH with a value of $552,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22637</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>