<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:46:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance HODLer Airdrop Launches Treehouse (TREE), to Be Listed for Spot Trading on July 29th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22176</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to official information, the Binance HODLer Airdrop is set to launch its 29th project, Treehouse (TREE).During the time period from 00:00 (UTC) on July 10, 2025, to 23:59 (UTC) on July 13, 2025, users who subscribed to BNB in Simple Yield (Flexible Yield and/or Locked Yield) and/or On-Chain Yield products will be eligible for the airdrop. The details of the HODLer airdrop are expected to be announced within 24 hours, and the new token will be distributed to users&apos; spot accounts at least 1 hour before trading begins.In addition, Binance will list TREE on July 29, 2025, at 14:00 (UTC) and open trading for USDT, USDC, BNB, FDUSD, and TRY pairs. TREE will receive a Seed Label. Users can start depositing TREE on July 28, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: I believe the Fed must cut rates this week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22175</link>
      <description>July 28th: When asked whether the Federal Reserve should cut interest rates this week, U.S. President Trump expressed his belief that it is necessary to do so. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22175</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company Volcon has announced an additional purchase of 316.9 bitcoins, bringing their total holdings to over 3,500 bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22174</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to official information, the U.S. listed company Volcon Inc. (VLCN) has increased its holdings by 316.8 bitcoins since its previous disclosure on July 25th, which amounts to $37.3 million. As of the date of the announcement, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings have reached 3,500.18 bitcoins, with a total investment of approximately $412 million and an average acquisition cost of $117,683 per bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22174</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Or Possibly Pumped by 108K HYPE Messages, Stock HYPD Surges 6.75% in Pre-market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22173</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on Rockflow data, the pre-market trading of the US stock HYPD may be affected by the announcement of holding an additional 108,594 HYPE tokens. The stock shows a 6.75% increase and is currently trading at $8.22.BlockBeats previously reported that Hyperion DeFi (Nasdaq stock code: HYPD) announced the acquisition of an additional 108,594 HYPE tokens, bringing its total HYPE holdings to 1,535,772 tokens, with an average purchase cost of $36.14 per token.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22173</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit Protocol Grove Expands to Avalanche Network, Plans to Invest $250 Million in Tokenized Credit Products</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22172</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per Coindesk, the credit protocol Grove within the Sky ecosystem (formerly of the MakerDAO ecosystem) announced on Monday that it is set to expand to the Avalanche blockchain network and intends to allocate up to $250 million in funding to tokenized credit products.According to the announcement, Grove will make an investment in the Anemoy AAA-rated CLO fund (JAAA) issued by Janus Henderson via the blockchain tokenization platform Centrifuge. Janus Henderson, a globally prominent asset management company with $373.0 billion in assets under management, has become one of the largest-scale endeavors by traditional financial institutions to enter the Avalanche Real World Asset (RWA) ecosystem. Centrifuge will also launch the Janus Henderson Anemoy Treasury fund backed by US Treasury bonds (JTRSY).It is reported that the Grove team comprises former members from Deloitte, Citi, and BlockTower who previously assisted MakerDAO in expanding the tokenized national debt market</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22172</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRON, Inc. Submits Mixed Shelf Offering Application to SEC, with Fundraising Scale of Up to $1 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22171</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to Reuters, TRON. Inc submitted a hybrid shelf offering to the SEC with a fundraising ceiling of up to $1 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22171</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal&apos;s New Feature Allows US Merchants to Accept Payment in Over 100 Cryptocurrencies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22170</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the report in Fortune, the fintech behemoth PayPal announced on Monday the initiation of a novel payment option. This enables U.S. small and medium-sized merchants to accept various mainstream cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum, along with more than 100 digital assets such as TrumpCoin and even FARTCOIN. A spokesperson from the company stated that all U.S. merchants utilizing the PayPal online payment processing platform are qualified for this feature. PayPal intends to extend its cryptocurrency payment service to U.S. and global large corporate clients but has declined to disclose a specific time schedule.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22170</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economic and trade teams of China and the United States have held the China-US Economic and Trade Talks in Stockholm.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22169</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the economic and trade teams of China and the United States held a China-US economic and trade dialogue in Stockholm, Sweden. (Golden Ten) 可以改写为：July 28th witnessed the holding of a China-US economic and trade dialogue in Stockholm, Sweden by the economic and trade teams of both countries. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22169</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Metavesco announced the purchase of 28 ETH at an average price of $3,595.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22168</link>
      <description>July 28th. As per the report in businessinsider, the diversified holding public company Metavesco, Inc. made an announcement today. In a tactical expansion of its digital asset strategy, the company purchased 28 Ethereum (ETH) with an average price of $3,595. While Bitcoin remains the company&apos;s long-term core reserve asset, this additional purchase of Ethereum is part of a strategic move considering the increased institutional adoption and a favorable macro environment.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered&apos;s Zodia Markets Completes $18.25M Series A Funding Round, with Participation from Circle Ventures</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22167</link>
      <description>July 28th. According to official channels, Zodia Markets, a cryptocurrency trading firm that is part of Standard Chartered (STAN), declared the accomplishment of a $18.25 million Series A funding round. This round was spearheaded by Pharsalus Capital, and it saw the participation of Circle Ventures, The Operating Group, XVC Tech, Token Bay Capital, Human Capital, and other strategic investors.As per a press release issued on Monday, the Series A funding will be employed to facilitate Zodia&apos;s international expansion endeavors and to continuously develop its stablecoin payment services.CEO Usman Ahmad stated in the announcement that Zodia is targeting financial institutions and is offering them a combination of wholesale financing and continuous digital asset trading in order to &quot;reimagine traditional forex capital flows through cross-border real-time stablecoin settlements.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22167</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>