<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:27:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cool Cats Floor Price Surpasses 0.74 ETH, Marking a 48% Increase in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23837</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to Blur data, the floor price of Cool Cats has exceeded 0.74 ETH. It has witnessed a 48% increase in the past 24 hours, with a 24-hour trading volume of 112.51 ETH and a 7-day growth of 61%.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 8th, Animoca Brands and its affiliated entities (collectively &quot;Animoca Brands&quot;) announced the completion of a strategic investment in the NFT brand Cool Cats Group. After the investment, Animoca Brands and Coin Operated Group will hold a majority stake in Cool Cats Group.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23837</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoins Surge Across the Board, Ethereum Ecosystem Tokens Lead the Way</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23836</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to HTX market data, as Ethereum continues to surge, altcoins are generally on the rise, and Ethereum ecosystem tokens are leading the market. Among them:COW is currently trading at $0.4853, with a 24-hour increase of 30.75%;ENA is currently trading at $0.739, with a 24-hour increase of 20.1%;RESOLV is currently trading at $0.1969, with a 24-hour increase of 16.66%;TURBO is currently trading at $0.0051, with a 24-hour increase of 15.7%;EIGEN is currently trading at $1.44, with a 24-hour increase of 14.29%;SHELL is currently trading at $0.1815, with a 24-hour increase of 14.2%;SSV is currently trading at $10.19, with a 24-hour increase of 12.85%;COMP is currently trading at $53.94, with a 24-hour increase of 11.72%;ETHFI is currently trading at $1.237, with a 24-hour increase of 11.71%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23836</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overall Ethereum Futures Open Interest Hits New All-Time High, Surging Over 11.12% in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23835</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to Coinglass data, market participants are continuously increasing their wagers on the Ethereum trend. The total open interest of Ethereum futures contracts across all exchanges has once again exceeded $58 billion, reaching a historical high of $58.54 billion. On July 9th, the total open interest of Ethereum futures contracts was $35.58 billion. There has been an increase of over 64.5% in the past 30 days and over 11.12% in the past 24 hours.In addition, the total open interest of Bitcoin futures contracts across all exchanges is currently at $78.93 billion, with a decrease of over 2.04% in the last 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23835</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: US Stock Listed Company BitMine Continues to Rise, Tom Lee States Ethereum at a Key Moment, Target Price $15,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23834</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Tom Lee, the newly appointed chairman of the US-listed company BitMine, recently made a statement. He pointed out that Ethereum (ETH) is currently at a crucial juncture similar to that of Bitcoin in 2017. With Wall Street&apos;s growing focus on cryptocurrency, Lee believes that Ethereum is emerging as a core platform in the &quot;tokenization&quot; process of the financial market, and he anticipates that this will be one of the largest macro trading events in the next decade.Lee specifically emphasized that Ethereum should not be simply compared to Bitcoin but rather to the traditional financial market. If forced to choose between Bitcoin and Ethereum, he is more inclined towards ETH. On August 2nd, BitMine&apos;s chairman Lee pointed out that traditional financial institutions are steadily and quietly increasing their holdings of cryptocurrency, especially Ethereum. This is because of its legal clarity and technical reliability. Moreover, Ethereum has never experienced a crash, which is</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23834</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum&apos;s 24-hour Gain Widens to Over 8%, Brief Spike Reaches $4,240</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23833</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum witnessed a short-term surge that reached $4,240. Currently, it is trading at $4,214, and the 24-hour price increase has expanded to 8.06%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23833</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Immersive Translation」 Plugin Might Have Caused Information Leakage, Official Announcement on Temporary Suspension of Bilingual Webpage Sharing Feature</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23832</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the &quot;Immersive Translation&quot; plugin officially announced the suspension of the bilingual webpage sharing feature. It stated, &quot;Recently, we have received feedback from the community that a few users inadvertently shared pages that may contain personal information while using this feature and did not promptly delete them from their personal center. In order to avoid potential privacy risks, we have decided to temporarily take down this feature and will not relaunch it until a robust privacy protection mechanism is established.&quot; The &quot;Immersive Translation&quot; team emphasized that this pause does not involve any leakage of translation content or backend user data because only when users actively use the bilingual webpage sharing feature will a publicly accessible link be generated.In addition, according to community reports, some users have provided feedback that the &quot;Immersive Translation&quot; plugin leaked user privacy due to improper permission controls. Some users reported lea</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-Chain Data: Whales Acquired Over 50 Million XRP in the Last 48 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23828</link>
      <description>On August 9th, cryptocurrency analyst @ali_charts presented on-chain data indicating that within the past 48 hours, whales collectively enhanced their XRP holdings by more than 50 million coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23828</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The average effective tariff rate in the United States has reached 18.6%, the highest level since 1933.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23831</link>
      <description>September 8th. The tariff tracking tool jointly established by the World Trade Organization and the International Monetary Fund indicates that by the 7th, the United States&apos; trade-weighted average tariff rate on all global products has risen to 20.11%, which is notably higher than the 2.44% at the beginning of the year. The data reveals that the United States&apos; simple average tariff rate on all global products has increased from 2.08% at the start of the year to 17.39% on the 7th. The global trade volume affected has soared from $2.8846 trillion at the beginning of the year to the current $27.47 trillion. A report issued by the Yale University Budget Lab on the 7th, which has been monitoring the long-term impact of US tariff policies, shows that with the continuous adjustment of US tariff policies, its current average effective tariff rate has reached 18.6%, the highest level since 1933. (Jinshi)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23831</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Market Capitalization Surges Above $4 Trillion, 24-hour Increase Reaches 1.7%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23830</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on CoinGecko data, the market capitalization of cryptocurrencies has witnessed a 24-hour increase of 1.7%, exceeding $4 trillion and currently standing at $4.021 trillion. The 24-hour trading volume of the cryptocurrency market is $1377.554 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23830</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simon Yuen: Hong Kong Insurance Companies Actively Embrace Advanced Technologies such as AI, Big Data, Blockchain, etc. AXA Hong Kong has Successfully Redomiciled</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23829</link>
      <description>September 8th. Paul Chan, the Financial Secretary of Hong Kong, declared that Hong Kong insurance companies are earnestly embracing advanced technologies like AI, big data, and blockchain to prompt the transformation of the industry. They are currently capable of enhancing customer experience and operational efficiency by means of digitalized claims, personalized insurance products, and intelligent risk assessment. As one of the initial insurance companies to relocate back to Hong Kong, AXA Hong Kong has manifested a firm confidence in Hong Kong&apos;s status as an international financial center.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23829</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>