<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Prior to the Non-Farm Payrolls data release, the probability of a Fed rate cut in September decreased slightly to 97.6%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27876</link>
      <description>At 20:30 Beijing time on September 5th, the United States will release the August unemployment rate and seasonally adjusted non-farm employment data.According to CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September has slightly decreased to 97.6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27876</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid will issue the stablecoin USDH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27875</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to market rumors, Hyperliquid is going to issue the USDH stablecoin. (A link to the relevant join page might be provided if applicable, such as https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, but it is not necessary to repeat the link in the rewritten text if the main focus is on the event of the stablecoin issuance.)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27875</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s latest SHARDS Airdrop generated approximately $158 in rewards per eligible user.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27874</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on market data, Binance Alpha has launched WORLDSHARDS (SHARDS), and the current price of SHARDS is $0.0395.During the first phase, each eligible user can receive an airdrop of 4000 SHARDS tokens. At the current price, the estimated single airdrop reward for this event is approximately $158.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27874</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullish Europe Subsidiary Secures MiCA License in Germany</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27873</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as per CoinDesk, the European subsidiary of the cryptocurrency exchange platform Bullish has secured a license in Germany within the framework of the Market in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation.Bullish Europe has obtained the license from the Federal Financial Supervisory Authority of Germany (BaFin), and the company had previously acquired a cryptocurrency brokerage and custody license issued by the regulatory body.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27873</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 12 hours, there has been a total of $92.41 million in liquidations across the network, with the largest single liquidation being a short position.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27872</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on Coinglass data, the entire network saw a liquidation of $92.41 million in the past 12 hours. There were $25.89 million in long liquidations and $66.52 million in short liquidations.Over the past 24 hours, a total of 95,028 people were liquidated globally, with a liquidation total of $266 million. The largest single liquidation took place on Binance - ETHUSDT, amounting to $2.3426 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk&apos;s Latest Compensation Plan Revealed, $1 Trillion &quot;Bet&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27871</link>
      <description>September 5th: On Friday, the board of directors of Tesla proposed a new compensation plan. Under this plan, if Musk achieves a series of extremely challenging goals within the next ten years, he will be awarded a reward worth approximately $1 trillion. In this plan, Musk will not receive any salary or bonus; his compensation will be in the form of gradually vested stocks. The unlocking conditions include a significant increase in Tesla&apos;s market value, a substantial improvement in profitability, the sale of millions of cars, and other key milestones.Board Chair Robyn Denholm stated in a letter to investors: &quot;Retaining and motivating Musk is of great significance for Tesla to become the most valuable company in history. This compensation plan is designed to align extraordinary long-term shareholder value with incentives to drive our visionary leader to achieve the best performance.&quot;The board emphasized that Musk&apos;s incentives are highly consistent with investor interests. If Tesla&apos;s</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27871</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit EU Group has applied for a MiFID II license, paving its way to the European derivatives market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27870</link>
      <description>September 5th, the cryptocurrency exchange Bybit is speeding up its expansion in Europe. The Bybit EU Group recently officially submitted an application to the Austrian Financial Market Authority (FMA), aiming to obtain an investment firm license for its subsidiary, Bybit X GmbH, in accordance with the MiFID II Austria Implementation Act.If approved, Bybit X will be capable of offering regulated derivative products across the entire European Economic Area (EEA), including futures and options. This will enlarge the business scope of the bybit.eu platform from the current MiCAR-authorized cryptocurrency spot services to the derivative market. Following the successful acquisition of the MiCAR license in May 2025, this is another crucial milestone in Bybit&apos;s European expansion strategy.The Bybit EU Group is headquartered in Vienna and officially launched the MiCAR-compliant platform bybit.eu in July 2025. Since its launch, Bybit EU has been continuously gaining strength, introducing fe</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27870</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sora Ventures Launches $1 Billion Fund to Support Asia&apos;s Bitcoin Reserve Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27869</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the Crypto VC firm Sora Ventures declared its intention to set up a $1 billion fund for investing in Asian Bitcoin reserve companies. In a press release issued on Friday, Sora Ventures mentioned that the company aims to raise $1 billion within the next 6 months and has already received an initial commitment of $200 million from regional partners and investors. This fund will be allocated to companies located in Asia that have Bitcoin on their balance sheets. This approach has attracted attention in recent years among publicly traded companies in Japan, Hong Kong, Thailand, and South Korea.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27869</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin surpasses $114,000, the total short liquidation volume on major CEXs will reach $847 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27868</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to Coinglass data, if Bitcoin manages to break through $114,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $847 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin drops below $111,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.416 billion.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of contracts that have been liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent reaching a particular price level will have an impact. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that once the price reaches that level, a more intense reaction will occur due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 09:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27868</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni Network has announced a rebrand to Nomina, with a 1:75 OMNI to new coin NOM ratio.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27867</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the Ethereum interoperability protocol Omni Network made an announcement about its rebranding to Nomina. It presented a new name, logo, visual identity, and a brand-new product narrative to showcase its future direction.As part of this rebranding process, the Omni team is currently engaged in developing an application for token migration. Currently, existing OMNI holders and stakers do not need to take any actions. It should also be noted that the new ticker symbol for Nomina&apos;s token will be NOM. After the rebranding, NOM will become the primary token on the network (Smart Contract: 0x6e6F6d696e61decd6605bD4a57836c5DB6923340), replacing OMNI.The ratio between OMNI and NOM is 1:75. This implies that at the time of launch, the circulating supply will be 2.9 billion NOM. Based on the tokenomics plan from the previous $OMNI TGE, the total supply will be 7.5 billion NOM. Since we aim to provide all community members with the opportunity to migrate to NOM at their own c</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 09:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27867</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>