<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>DeSci Ecosystem AI Agent yesnoerror Announces Entry into Public Beta</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26803</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the DeSci ecosystem AI agent yesnoerror declared its entry into the public testing stage. The team is leveraging the latest AI model powered by the YNE token to review and analyze each new paper related to AI and computer science (more than 500 papers per day). yesnoerror intends to cross-chain the YNE token to Base (to be announced shortly, with technical development already completed), expand the audit scope beyond arXiv journals, and develop a personalized research AI agent in the future.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26803</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin&apos;s relative strength index (RSI) continues to decline, showing a similar bearish divergence to the 2021 bull market top.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26802</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the cryptocurrency analyst @ali_charts put out a chart analysis indicating that the Bitcoin price has been maintaining its position within a new high range. Meanwhile, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has been on a downward trend, showing a divergence similar to that before the 2021 cycle peak.The RSI (Relative Strength Index) is a widely employed technical analysis indicator. It measures the speed and magnitude of price changes to determine whether the market is in an overbought or oversold state. The RSI ranges from 0 to 100. Values above 70 are generally regarded as overbought, suggesting that the price may be too high and at the risk of a pullback. Values below 30 are usually considered oversold, indicating that the price may be too low and is likely to rebound.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26802</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Cook Faces New Mortgage Fraud Allegations Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26801</link>
      <description>August 29th: On this day, Mark Pullen, who is the Director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency, once more submitted another criminal charge regarding the third property of Federal Reserve Board Governor Cook in Massachusetts to the Department of Justice. The charge asserts that Cook obtained a mortgage of $361,000 for an apartment in Massachusetts and claimed it as a second home. Eight months later, Cook claimed to have received rental income ranging from $15,000 to $50,000 and classified it as an investment property.Cook may be engaged in Reverse Occupancy Fraud. In this type of fraud, a borrower purchases a property as an investment but initially falsely represents it as a primary or secondary residence in order to obtain a lower mortgage rate or more favorable loan terms. Subsequently, the borrower may change the property&apos;s use by declaring rental income to conform to the definition of an investment property.BlockBeats had previously reported that a judge in charge of the case</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26801</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the US Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $1.789 billion, while the Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $39.1 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26800</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as monitored by Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Bitcoin spot ETF yesterday was $178.9 million, and BlackRock IBIT received a net inflow of $63.7 million.Yesterday, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF was $39.1 million, marking the 6th consecutive day of net inflow. Among them, BlackRock ETHA witnessed a net inflow of $67.6 million, while Fidelity FETH saw a net outflow of $33.5 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport appeared at Bitcoin Asia2025 to discuss how Asian institutions are leading the way in seizing new opportunities in Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26799</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Matrixport was extended an invitation to attend the Bitcoin Asia Summit and took part in a panel discussion entitled &quot;Asian Institutions Leading the Commencement of a New Bitcoin Era.&quot;During the event, Matrixport&apos;s COO, Cynthia Wu, pointed out that the digital asset investment is undergoing a substantial transformation. An increasing number of investors and corporate treasuries are regarding Bitcoin as a long-term asset allocation. They are continuously accumulating rather than engaging in short-term speculation. ETFs and stock tokens have made it more accessible for the general public to invest in digital assets, significantly reducing the learning curve. In just two years, the combined market value of these two has exceeded $260 billion and is approaching the current market capitalization of stablecoins. It can be anticipated that with the proliferation of stablecoins, the market capitalization of Bitcoin still has the potential to grow tenfold in the coming years.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26799</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL on Hyperliquid Continues to Surge, Breaking $1.1 Mark with a 36% Premium Over Binance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26798</link>
      <description>On August 29th, on Hyperliquid (accessible via https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD), XPL continued to experience a surge and broke through $1.1. The current annualized funding rate stands at an extremely high 254%, with a 36% positive premium compared to $0.808 on Binance.Early yesterday morning, Hyperliquid implemented a new mark price calculation method for pre-market perpetual contracts. The mark price of the contract will utilize the standard mark price formula and be combined with the price of external pre-market perpetual contracts (if available).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26798</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address withdrew 9.32 million WLD from Binance, worth $8.85 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26797</link>
      <description>August 29th. Based on the monitoring of OnchainLens, a newly established address withdrew 9.32 million WLD from Binance 11 hours ago, with a value of $8.85 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26797</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian company Luxxfolio plans to raise $73 million to expand its Litecoin treasury strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26795</link>
      <description>August 29th. As per Decrypt, the Canadian firm Luxxfolio intends to raise $73 million for the expansion of its Litecoin (LTC) treasury strategy. Charlie Lee, the founder of Litecoin, joined its advisory board by the end of June.It is worthy of note that the company reported zero revenue during the second quarter. It had a net loss of $197,000, cash reserves of merely $112,000, and accumulated losses approaching $19 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26795</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 219th Ethereum All Core Developers&apos; Meeting Fusaka Development Net Devnet3 is expected to be finalized today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26796</link>
      <description>August 29th, Tim Beiko provided a summary of the 219th Ethereum All Core Developers Meeting (ACDE). The key points of this meeting are as follows:The Fusaka development network Devnet 3 is anticipated to be completed by today. The consensus layer team is actively working on resolving synchronization issues. Provided that everything proceeds smoothly, Devnet 5 will be launched.There are arrangements to deprecate Holesky a few weeks after Fusaka becomes active. A public post will be issued to explain the timetable and migration guide.The Gas Limit target is to reach 60 million prior to the Fusaka upgrade.Glamsterdam Update (in future meetings, the discussion on the PFI matter requested by clients will take precedence) and other matters.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26796</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Indonesian Web3 platform Hypr has launched a Food &amp; Beverage Investment Exposure based on NFT technology.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26794</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per Techinasia, the Indonesian investment platform Hypr is presenting global investors with the chance to get involved in Indonesia&apos;s local F&amp;B (food and beverage) businesses via profit-sharing investments. Its initial portfolio company is DORé by LeTAO, a Japanese dessert brand renowned for its cheesecakes and having stores in Indonesia. Hypr employs NFT-based smart contracts to safeguard investors&apos; profit-sharing rights. It validates through the ordering system data and distributes profits on a monthly basis. Hypr operates under the supervision of the Indonesian Financial Services Authority (OJK) and holds ISO 27001 and ISO 9001 certifications. By facilitating profit-sharing and smart contracts, Hypr lowers the investment threshold, enabling retail investors to participate in Indonesia&apos;s F&amp;B market, which is projected to surpass $51.5 billion by 2024.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26794</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>