<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:54:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>White Star Capital&apos;s Fund Closes $25M, Aims to Raise $50M</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27694</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the venture capital firm White Star Capital declared that its fund had recently concluded a $25 million Series A financing round. Fonds de solidarité FTQ served as the lead investor, aiming for a total fund size of $50 million.Presently, White Star Capital possesses early growth funds as well as a digital asset fund that focuses on crypto and blockchain startups. In February of this year, it took part in the Series A financing of the AI blockchain risk management platform Lockchain.ai. Previously, it has made investments in the crypto lending platform Ledn, the crypto lending platform Trident Digital Group, the crypto payment solution provider BoomFi, the decentralized finance company Thala Labs, and the cryptocurrency index protocol Index Coop.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27694</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Solana Launchpad Market Share in the Last 24 Hours: pump.fun, Letsbonk, Believe ranked top three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27692</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, in the past 24 hours, in the Solana launchpad market share ranking, pump.fun took the first place with 77.2%, Letsbonk came in second with 9.73%, and Believe ranked third with 3.58%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27692</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun has transferred 50 million WLFI to a new wallet, or may transfer it to HTX.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27693</link>
      <description>On September 4th. Based on the monitoring of Onchain Lens, Justin Sun transferred 50 million WLFI tokens (approximately $9.12 million) to a new wallet. This transfer may be for HTX.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27693</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEIROETH has dropped over 25% in the last 24 hours, currently trading at $0.0586.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27691</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to HTX market data, the value of NEIROETH has decreased by more than 25% in the past 24 hours and is currently trading at $0.0586.Previously, it was reported that at 10:00 on September 4th, Trend Research under LD Capital deposited a total of 129 million NEIROETH into Bybit, with a value of $9.85 million. Trend Research is currently the largest holder of NEIROETH, having once held more than 67% of the tokens. At 19:00 on September 4th, Bybit announced the delisting of the NEIROETH U perpetual contract.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27691</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit will delist the NEIROETH Composite Perpetual Contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27690</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to official channels, Bybit has declared that it will remove the NEIROETH U perpetual contract on September 10th at 19:00 (UTC). Users are obligated to close their NEIROETH contracts and cancel any outstanding orders without delay.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27690</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Financial Regulator Proposes to Include Cryptocurrency in Securities Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27689</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as per Cointelegraph, on Tuesday, the Financial Services Agency (FSA) of Japan issued a report suggesting that the regulation of cryptocurrencies should be transferred from the &quot;Payment Services Act&quot; to the more rigorous &quot;Financial Instruments and Exchange Act&quot; (FIEA) framework. This action is intended to enhance investor protection, address issues such as unclear information disclosure, unregistered operations, and security vulnerabilities within the industry, and bring cryptocurrency regulation in line with securities regulation.The report shows that in Japan, there are already over 12 million cryptocurrency accounts, with total user deposits reaching 5 trillion yen (approximately 33.7 billion US dollars). If the new regulations come into effect, cryptocurrency issuers will be subject to stricter disclosure requirements, and intermediary services will also be under more intense oversight. The proposal is currently in the form of an internal briefing document await</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27689</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: Fed Could Cut Rates in September, Stock Market Expected to Rally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27688</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Tom Lee, the Chairman of BitMine&apos;s Board of Directors, stated in a Macro Minute video that although the market is widely concerned that September will witness a decline due to seasonal factors and the risk of a potential increase in VIX, he thinks the most appropriate approach is for the Federal Reserve to maintain its stance of inaction this year and start cutting rates in September. This will be beneficial to the stock market.The Federal Reserve has maintained a pause on rate hikes for the most part of this year. It is anticipated that the Federal Reserve will begin cutting rates in September, similar to what occurred in 1998 and 2024. In both these historical contexts, the market subsequently experienced a significant rebound, especially in the performance approaching the end of the year. Hence, Tom Lee has offered a &quot;contrarian&quot; assessment that goes against the general sentiment of the market: September 2025 may bring about a bullish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s Gata (GATA) Airdrop Single Ticket Revenue is approximately $25</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27687</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to market intelligence, Binance Alpha has listed Gata (GATA), and the current market value of GATA is $8 million. Each eligible user can obtain an airdrop of 500 GATA tokens. The estimated value of this airdrop based on current prices is approximately $25.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27687</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union Announces Mainnet Launch, Opens Airdrop Registration</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27686</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the interoperability protocol Union declared the launch of the mainnet. The U Drop airdrop is now available for claiming and will remain open until September 18th.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27686</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Jack Ma&apos;s affiliated company Yunfeng Financial acquires Ethereum, stock price surges 6% today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27685</link>
      <description>September 4th: In the past, an affiliate of Alibaba, Yunfeng Financial, purchased 10,000 ETH at an average price of $4,400. Today, Yunfeng Financial&apos;s Hong Kong stock [Stock Code: 00376] surged by more than 6%, which has attracted widespread attention in the market. Industry insiders stated that with the cryptocurrency market rebounding and institutional investors continuously entering, Yunfeng Financial&apos;s large position in ETH has a significant impact on market sentiment and price trends.It is worth noting that Yunfeng Financial not only focuses on the spot market but also actively makes arrangements in digital asset derivatives and blockchain payment applications, shaping a long-term strategy in the digital finance field. Investors can gain insights into institutional operations in the crypto market and risk management strategies, which can provide references for their investment decisions.BiyaPay, a multi-asset trading wallet, will continue to provide you with one-stop services</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27685</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>