<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:56:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley: The Fed is expected to cut rates by 25 basis points in both September and October, compared to the previous expectation of cuts in September and December</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28112</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Morgan Stanley anticipates that the Federal Reserve will reduce interest rates by 25 basis points in both September and October. Previously, it was expected to be in September and December. (Financial Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Monetary Easing Expectations Fully Priced In, Interest Rate Cut Unable to Propel Bitcoin Rebound Above $120,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28111</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Rachael Lucas, a cryptocurrency analyst at BTC Markets, stated: &quot;The soft US jobs report did give rise to expectations for a more dovish stance from the Federal Reserve. Generally speaking, this kind of situation supports risk assets like Bitcoin. However, the market has already incorporated a certain degree of policy easing. At the same time, we observe that institutional investors are taking profits, while ETF fund flows remain relatively stable. The resistance level of Bitcoin is at $113,400. There is further resistance at $115,400 and $117,100. Breaking through these resistance levels indicates that the market has absorbed the recent selling pressure and is ready to retest the highs.&quot;Kronos Research&apos;s Chief Information Officer Vincent Liu also said that even if the Federal Reserve decides to lower interest rates, the Bitcoin price may still remain relatively weak. &quot;Interest rate cuts may indicate a weak economy. Meanwhile, persistent high inflation and cautious</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28111</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays: Expects the Fed to Cut Interest Rates Three Times This Year, by 25 Basis Points Each Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28110</link>
      <description>On September 8th, from Barclays: It is expected that the Federal Reserve will reduce interest rates three times in 2025, with each reduction being 25 basis points. These cuts are anticipated to occur in September, October, and December, surpassing the previous forecast of two 25-basis-point cuts in September and December. (FX678)Previously, Standard Chartered Bank projected a 50-basis-point rate cut by the Federal Reserve in September.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28110</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jia Yueting: To Announce Three Major Growth Engines of Crypto Treasury and EAI Vehicle Chain Strategy, C10 Treasury Adds $2 Million in Digital Asset Allocation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28109</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Jia Yueting posted that &quot;The scale of C10 Treasury is expanding. The three major growth engines and the EAI Vehicle Chain strategy will be announced soon. At the same time, C10 Treasury is increasing the allocation of digital assets by $2 million.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28109</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected ConsenSys-Linked Address Buys $1.2M Worth of REX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28108</link>
      <description>On September 8th, according to @Andrey_10gwei, an address suspected to be affiliated with ConsenSys purchased $1.2 million worth of REX tokens of the Linea ecosystem DEX protocol Etherex in the past two weeks.On August 16th, address 0x0521b received 1.25 million USDC from the MetaMask multisig address and then bought REX. Subsequently, the tokens from this address were transferred to a new multisig address and REX was staked.ConsenSys, a software company founded by Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin, has cryptographic projects including the crypto wallet MetaMask and the Ethereum L2 solution Linea.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28108</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain savvy investor has increased their holdings to go long on BTC, ETH, HYPE, and other major tokens, with a total position value exceeding $17 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28103</link>
      <description>On September 8th, according to on-chain data, a smart money whale increased its position this morning. It took long positions in mainstream tokens such as BTC, ETH, and HYPE, with a total position value exceeding 17 million US dollars.As of the time of this writing, the address holds a 40x long position in Bitcoin worth 8.33 million US dollars, a 20x long position in Ethereum worth 6.45 million US dollars, and a 5x long position in HYPE worth 836,000 US dollars.This address has achieved a total profit of over 15.61 million US dollars on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28103</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venus Protocol: Assets of Phishing Incident Victims Have Been Restored in Equivalent Value Based on Today&apos;s Token Price</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28107</link>
      <description>On September 8th, the decentralized lending protocol Venus Protocol tweeted that after conducting due diligence, the team has officially returned the $11.4 million position to the victim Kuan Sun (@KuanSun1990) at the current token price.Previously, Venus Protocol released an analysis of a phishing attack stating that on September 2nd, user Kuan Sun suffered a loss of approximately $13 million. Within 13 hours, the Venus team took measures such as pausing the protocol and forcefully liquidating the attacker&apos;s wallet, successfully recovering all funds and restoring the normal operation of the protocol. A security audit confirmed that the protocol itself was not compromised.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28107</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered Bank: Expects the Federal Reserve to Cut Interest Rates by 50 Basis Points in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28106</link>
      <description>September 8th, Standard Chartered Bank: It is anticipated that the Federal Reserve will reduce interest rates by 50 basis points in September, which is greater than the previously estimated 25 basis points. (Caixin)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28106</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump Clarifies: Metaplanet is currently its sole partner in the Asian market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28105</link>
      <description>September 8th: In light of the circulating community rumors regarding a photo showing Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, with a CEO of an Asian company, which might give rise to a purchase deal, Eric Trump took to the X platform to provide a clarification. He asserted that he had no knowledge of the person he was photographed with. He specifically made it clear that he was not affiliated with the relevant company. The photo in question was captured during a local event. The only company with which he is currently collaborating in the Asian region is Metaplanet.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28105</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain user lost approximately $180,000 in assets due to signing a phishing transaction.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28104</link>
      <description>On September 8th, according to the monitoring of Scam Sniffer, a user lost approximately 180,000 USDT as a result of signing a phishing transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 03:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>