<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Mira Network establishes a foundation, hinting at or nearing TGE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26516</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to the decentralized AI infrastructure Mira, it declared the establishment of a foundation. This foundation will act as the long-term custodian of the Mira Network, concentrating on decentralized network and protocol governance and providing tooling support for developers, researchers, and the community.BlockBeats Note: The establishment of a cryptocurrency project foundation typically indicates that the Total Global Economic (TGE) is drawing near.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26516</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury Mints an Additional 250 Million USDC on the Solana Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26517</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per the monitoring of Whale Alert, the USDC Treasury has just minted an extra 2.5 billion USDC on the Solana blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26517</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonk Ecosystem Development Protocol Token GP Market Cap Surpasses $85 Million, Surging Over 40% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26515</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on the GMGN market information from GMGN, the Bonk ecosystem development protocol token GP reached the bottom and then rebounded. It broke through $1.45, with a price increase of more than 40% within 24 hours. The 24-hour trading volume was $2.7 million, and the market capitalization exceeded $85 million.BlockBeats reminds users that the token price is highly volatile and that investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Responds to XPL Surge: Contract Mark Price to Follow Standard Mark Price Formula</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26514</link>
      <description>On August 27th, officials from Hyperliquid once more responded to the surge in the XPL price. They stated that, based on user feedback, the mark price of the Hyperliquid contract will use the regular mark price formula and be combined with the price of perpetual contracts traded externally before listing (if any). This has no substantial impact on the vast majority of users and situations but can enhance the robustness of the system. It is crucial to note that this will not affect the funding rate or realized profit and loss (PnL). Thanks to those users who provided constructive feedback based on their interactions with the Hyperliquid contract market.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26514</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Bank: Fed Independence Risk, Rising U.S. Debt Hinder Dollar Structure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26513</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the German Bank analyst Antje Praefcke pointed out that the structural pressure factors facing the US dollar encompass the threat to the independence of the Federal Reserve and the continuous worsening of the US budget deficit. She said that the dismissal of Federal Reserve Board member Lisa Cook by US President Trump has given rise to new concerns regarding the Fed&apos;s independence. This independence is &quot;crucial for maintaining the value of the currency.&quot; Praefcke stated that the central bank must make painful decisions to address economic imbalances. Additionally, the US dollar is facing a setback due to concerns about the sustainability of US debt. Trump&apos;s tax and spending bill may ultimately end up being more costly than currently projected. She stated that although some tax cuts should be temporary, past experience shows that it is difficult to reverse these cuts once they are approaching expiration. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26513</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willy Woo: The current daily inflow of funds into ETH is around $9 billion, nearing BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26512</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the cryptocurrency analyst Willy Woo published an article indicating that funds have been moving from BTC to ETH. The daily inflow of ETH reached $9 billion (silver), approaching the inflow level of BTC (orange). Since Tom Lee&apos;s Ethereum fund management company, BitMine, began to accumulate ETH, the fund flow of Ethereum has been on the rise.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme People&apos;s Court and the Supreme People&apos;s Procuratorate Release Landmark Case of &quot;Concealment and Disguise of Criminal Proceeds through Virtual Currency and Other Means&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26511</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the Supreme People&apos;s Court of China and the Supreme People&apos;s Procuratorate jointly released typical cases of crimes related to the concealment and disguised proceeds of crime and the gains from crime in accordance with the law. This includes the case of &quot;An and others using virtual currency to conceal and disguise criminal proceeds.&quot;From September to October 2020, defendants An, Chen, and Guo conspired to transfer funds for others to make a profit through an online platform. An contacted criminals from a telecom fraud group (handled in a separate case) online and provided multiple bank accounts belonging to Guo to receive funds as instructed by the criminals. After Guo provided the bank account, he registered and logged into a cryptocurrency exchange platform in his own name. Meanwhile, Chen operated the trading platform to transfer the funds received from others into Guo&apos;s bank account to purchase virtual currency. The virtual currency was then transferred to an acco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Federal Prosecutor Appeals to Increase Sentence of HashFlare Mining Fraud Case Mastermind</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26510</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per the report in Decrypt, the U.S. federal prosecutors have appealed to the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals in an attempt to secure an increase in the &quot;time served&quot; sentence for Estonian citizens Sergei Potapenko and Ivan Tur?gin in the $577 million HashFlare cryptocurrency Ponzi scheme case. The federal prosecutors have characterized the original sentence as &quot;unusually lenient.&quot;These two individuals had previously pleaded guilty to conspiracy. They defrauded 440,000 global victims between 2015 and 2019 by means of false mining contracts, presenting a fabricated &quot;dashboard&quot; of returns, and using the funds to purchase luxury goods and pay early withdrawers. Previously, the judge sentenced them to three years of supervised release and a $25,000 fine each. The judge rejected the prosecutor&apos;s request for a 10-year prison term, citing concerns regarding the treatment of foreign defendants in the U.S., including the possibility of &quot;indefinite detention.&quot; Legal exp</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valour Launches Cryptocurrency ETP Products for SHIB, ONDO on Sweden&apos;s Spotlight Stock Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26509</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per MarketWatch, the subsidiary Valour of the US-listed company DeFi Technologies announced the launch of cryptocurrency ETP products priced in Swedish Krona on the Swedish Spotlight stock market. These products include: Shiba Inu (SHIB), Pi (PI), Ondo (ONDO), Cronos (CRO), Mantle (MNT), VeChain (VET), Ethena (ENA), and Celestia (TIA).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: Will &quot;Definitely&quot; Know Trump&apos;s Fed Chair Pick in the Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26508</link>
      <description>On August 27, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen stated: We will present 3 to 4 candidates for the position of Federal Reserve Chair to U.S. President Trump. President Trump holds great respect for the Federal Reserve and is currently considering candidates for the Fed Chair, and he will have conversations with them. According to President Trump, the selection of the Fed Chair will &quot;definitely&quot; be made known in the autumn. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>