<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sui has integrated with the Fireblocks platform and will support native custody and staking services</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21473</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Sui officially announced that the Sui Network has been integrated into the enterprise-grade digital asset infrastructure platform Fireblocks. The aim is to provide services to institutional users who pursue high performance and security.Currently, Fireblocks has supported the native custody of SUI and Sui ecosystem tokens, as well as MPC wallet policy control. Subsequently, it will support DeFi access through WalletConnect and integrate Fireblocks Trust&apos;s staking service. Sui stated that its high throughput and scalability are becoming the preferred path for financial institutions and game studios to access the next-generation digital asset world.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21473</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain smart money closed a long position on SOL on Hyperliquid and instead opened a $17.9 million ETH long position.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21472</link>
      <description>On July 23rd. Based on on-chain data, a particular smart money closed a long position on SOL through Hyperliquid 5 hours ago and simultaneously opened a 3x long position worth $17.9 million on ETH. The entry price for this long position was $3,743, and the liquidation price was $2,547.6. This address has amassed a profit of $3.36 million on Hyperliquid, with a weekly profit of $2.362 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insiders and SpaceX Filing Suggest Musk May Return to US Politics</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21471</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per Bloomberg which cited SpaceX documents and sources with knowledge of the matter, Elon Musk, who recently held the position of a senior advisor to former President Trump, is likely to re-enter the U.S. political arena.The report indicates that SpaceX incorporated wording related to such &quot;risk factors&quot; (Musk&apos;s return to the U.S. political arena) in the documents sent to investors regarding a tender offer, and this is the first time such wording has appeared in these tender offers.SpaceX has not yet made any comments on this matter.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21471</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>spacex</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPK Surges Above $0.12, Up Nearly 300% in the Past 2 Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21470</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to HTX market data, SPK has exceeded $0.12. The current price is $0.12008, indicating a nearly 300% increase in the past 2 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21470</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal will partner with Venmo to launch the PayPal World platform, connecting the world&apos;s largest payment system and digital wallet, with Tencent&apos;s WeChat Pay among the partner candidates.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21469</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per official information, PayPal is set to collaborate with Venmo to launch the PayPal World platform, linking the world&apos;s largest payment system with a digital wallet. The initial batch of partners encompasses Mercado Pago, NPCI International Payments Limited (UPI), and Tenpay Global as well.It is anticipated that PayPal World will become operational this fall, and all partners will be capable of interworking with PayPal and Venmo. The platform is intended to facilitate the future interoperability of partner wallets in order to further augment cross-border coverage and acceptance. PayPal World makes use of open commerce APIs and addresses the intricacies of cross-border commerce through a cloud-native, multi-region deployment architecture to guarantee low latency and high availability globally. The platform provides robust security features, establishing an environment for all partners that is free from constraints related to devices and technologies.Venmo is a U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21469</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 2.35 million SPX into Bybit, worth $4.53 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21468</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale has deposited an additional 2.35 million SPX into Bybit, which is worth $4.53 million.The whale had previously deposited 2.53 million SPX into Bybit on the 20th, with a value of $4.55 million, and has made a profit of $4.46 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq-Listed Company SEALSQ Plans to Establish $30 Million Cryptocurrency Investment Fund</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21466</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Nasdaq-listed public key infrastructure development company SEALSQ Corp announced that it is establishing a cryptocurrency investment fund with a scale of around $30 million. It plans to utilize this fund to purchase digital assets such as BTC, ETH, and HBAR.Moreover, the company also stated that its cryptocurrency investment fund will serve as a strategic fund tool, which is responsible for formulating a strategy to buy and hold cryptocurrencies, similar to how a company invests in traditional assets like bonds or stocks.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21466</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: Altseason Index Rising, FOMO Season Approaching</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21467</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, CZ stated in a post that although the accuracy of the Shitcoin Season Index on CoinMarketCap is in doubt, it is indeed on the rise. &quot;FOMO Season is Coming.&quot; As of the time of writing, the Shitcoin Season Index is reported to be at 55, indicating a significant increase from its low of 12 in April of this year.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21467</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean Regulator Requires Investment Firms to Control Exposure to Crypto-Related Companies such as Coinbase and Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21465</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per The Korea Economic Daily, the Financial Supervisory Service (FSS) of South Korea has recently given instructions to local asset management companies to adjust their Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs) in order to restrict their exposure to cryptocurrency-related companies like Coinbase and Strategy. The regulatory agency pointed out that asset management companies need to comply with the administrative guidelines issued by the Financial Services Commission (FSC) of Korea in 2017, which prohibit regulated financial institutions from holding, acquiring, or investing in virtual assets.This directive from the local regulatory agency has led to complaints from domestic financial participants who think it has created an unfair competitive environment because retail investors can purchase U.S. ETFs by investing in cryptocurrency companies. An official from the Financial Supervisory Service stated that even if the regulatory requirements in the U.S. and South Korea cha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21465</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Mining Firm DMG Blockchain Solutions Plans to Establish a Multi-Currency Digital Asset Treasury Including BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21464</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the publicly traded Bitcoin mining company DMG Blockchain Solutions announced that it is assessing the institutional-grade fund management strategy of its subsidiary, Systemic Trust Company. The aim is to establish a diversified digital asset treasury. Currently, the company&apos;s digital asset investment portfolio only includes Bitcoin. It has now started to evaluate the use of existing mining rewards and additional funds raised to acquire other digital assets in addition to Bitcoin.According to BitcoinTreasuries data, DMG Blockchain Solutions currently holds approximately 341 Bitcoins and ranks 54th among publicly traded Bitcoin treasury companies. (Globenewswire)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>