<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:26:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CRO Surges Another 37.6% in the Last 24 Hours, Hits Near 3-Year High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26586</link>
      <description>August 28th. Based on market data, CRO witnessed another 37.6% surge in the past 24 hours, reaching a high of $0.2869, which marked a new near-three-year high.CRO once initiated a one-sided upward trend in November 2021. From November 2nd to November 24th, it rose from $0.214 to $0.965, representing a 350% increase. Then, by the end of 2022, it dropped to $0.057, a 94% decline from the peak.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 26th, Yorkville Acquisition Corp, Trump Media &amp; Technology Group, and Crypto.com announced that the three parties had signed a definitive agreement to merge and establish Trump Media Group CRO Strategy, Inc., a digital asset treasury company focused on acquiring Cronos ecosystem-native cryptocurrency (CRO). The expected composition of the digital asset treasury includes: $1 billion in CRO, $200 million in cash, $220 million in cash-settled mandatory convertible bonds, and a $5 billion equity line of credit provided by Yorkville-affiliated com</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26586</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Enterprise Makes Fifth Bitcoin Purchase in August, Surpasses 1,000 Coins in Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26585</link>
      <description>On August 28th, DDC Enterprise Limited (&quot;DDC&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) announced today that it had completed its fifth Bitcoin purchase in August and had further acquired 120 BTC. With this acquisition, the company&apos;s total holdings had reached 1008 BTC, more than doubling from the 368 BTC it held at the beginning of the month.Norma Chu, the Founder, Chairman, and CEO of DDC, stated: &quot;This month&apos;s purchase not only demonstrates our execution ability and speed but also reflects our discipline and conviction. Against the backdrop of Bitcoin market volatility, achieving a doubling of our holdings in just a few weeks fully demonstrates our firm determination to become a leading Bitcoin reserve company.&quot;About DDC Enterprise Limited: DDC Enterprise Limited (NYSE: DDC) is not only continuously deepening its Asian food business but also leading the corporate trend of Bitcoin treasuryization. The company has strategically positioned Bitcoin as its core reserve asset and is implementing an active an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26585</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 ETH Long Liquidation」 Whale Long Position Loses Another $72,000, Remaining Balance Drops to $58,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26584</link>
      <description>On August 28th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the whale that opened a $125,000 long position in ETH has once again suffered a loss of $72,000, with only $58,000 remaining in the account.ETH rose to $4,664 last night and fell back this morning. The whale was forced to partially close the position to avoid liquidation. They still hold a 25x leveraged long position in ETH worth $1.79 million. Due to the limited available margin, the whale can only roll over the position if they want to make a comeback, which makes their liquidation risk extremely high.It is reported that the address initially started with a $125,000 investment in a leveraged long position in ETH and reached a peak where they once had a floating profit of $43 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn opened a 10x long position on DOGE with his last $9,000, liquidation price $0.209</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26583</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, James Wynn made a comeback. He opened a 10x leveraged long position on DOGE with a final investment of $9,000. The entry price was $0.21298 and the liquidation price was $0.20989.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26583</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new prediction platform, The Clearing, founded by former Polymarket and Kalshi employees, has raised $15 million in funding, with USV leading the investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26582</link>
      <description>August 28th. As per The Block, The Clearing Company, a prediction market platform established by former employees of Polymarket and Kalshi, declared the completion of a $15 million seed funding round. This funding round was spearheaded by Union Square Ventures and witnessed the participation of Haun Ventures, Variant, Coinbase Ventures, Compound, and others.The Clearing Company is set to vie with the market leaders Polymarket and Kalshi. According to the company&apos;s website, Toni Gemayel, who formerly held the position of growth lead at Polymarket and Kalshi, will serve as the CEO of The Clearing Company. Other staff members of this startup also comprise individuals who have previously worked at Polymarket.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26582</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Partners with Mastercard and Finastra to Expand Stablecoin Payments Business in Europe and Africa</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26581</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Circle made an announcement regarding a partnership with Mastercard and Finastra. The purpose of this partnership is to integrate stablecoin settlement functionality into mainstream finance, thereby facilitating the incorporation of USDC into the global payment sector.Mastercard stated on Wednesday that it will enable acquirers and merchants in the Eastern Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EEMEA) region to settle transactions using USDC and EURC. Arab Financial Services and Eazy Financial Services will be the first to avail of this service, marking Mastercard&apos;s initial provision of stablecoin settlement services in the region.The London-based financial software provider Finastra also announced on Wednesday the integration of USDC into its Global PAYplus platform. This platform processes more than $50 trillion in cross-border transactions on a daily basis.Circle indicated that this integration will empower banks in 50 countries to utilize USDC for international paym</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26581</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hemi: Opened HEMI Genesis Airdrop Check</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26580</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the Modular Blockchain Network Hemi announced on social media that its HEMI Genesis Airdrop Checker is now operational, enabling users to independently verify the specific amount of their airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26580</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Sell the HYPE and Long ETH] Whale&apos;s long position reaches $392 million after selling the HYPE, with an unrealized loss of $8 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26579</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as monitored by on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, the whale address that [sold HYPE and then opened a long ETH position] has been continuously increasing its position over the past 2 days. The current value of the ETH long position is $3.92 billion (86,800 ETH), with an entry price of $4,608, a liquidation price of $4,342, and it is currently at a floating loss of $8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26579</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia&apos;s Q2 Revenue Beats Expectations, Drops 5% in After-Hours Trading; Bitcoin Slides 1.25%, briefly dipping below $111,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26578</link>
      <description>On August 28th, NVIDIA (NVDA.O) announced a revenue of $46.7 billion for the second quarter of its 2026 fiscal year, surpassing market expectations of $46 billion. Furthermore, the company authorized an additional $60 billion for stock repurchase. NVIDIA provided a flat outlook for the third-quarter revenue at $54 billion, with a fluctuation range of up or down by 2%, in contrast to market expectations of $53.46 billion. This has sparked concerns in the market regarding the slowdown in the high spending growth rate in the field of artificial intelligence.After the release of the financial report, NVIDIA&apos;s stock initially dropped by 5% in after-hours trading and is now down by 3.14%. This phenomenon is common during &quot;NVIDIA Earnings Nights,&quot; during which market participants usually make speculations based on earnings expectations. This can result in pre-market and intraday price increases in line with expectations, followed by a decline if the results fail to meet expectations. A slig</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26578</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index currently at 48, indicating a &quot;Neutral&quot; market sentiment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26577</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to Alternative Data, the Fear and Greed Index of cryptocurrencies today is 48 (yesterday it was 51), and the weekly average is 50, suggesting that the market remains in a &quot;Neutral&quot; state.Note: The threshold of the Fear Index is 0-100, and the indicators include: Volatility (25%) + Market Trading Volume (25%) + Social Media Hype (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26577</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>