<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Boundless will launch its native token ZKC, with approximately 6% allocated for community token sale and airdrop.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25102</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Verifiable Computation Layer Boundless announced the commencement of the launch of its native token ZK Coin (ZKC). The initial supply of the token is 1 billion. Approximately 6% of the tokens will be utilized for the Boundless Community Token Sale and airdropped to reward early contributors such as Validators and Kaito Yapper. In the community token sale, 50% of the tokens will be unlocked at the Token Generation Event (TGE), and the remaining 50% will be unlocked after six months. The airdropped tokens will be unlocked 100% at the TGE.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25102</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Treasury Company KindlyMD Completes $200 Million Convertible Note Issuance to Further Bitcoin Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25101</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the Bitcoin Treasury company KindlyMD (traded on Nasdaq: KDLY) announced the successful completion of a $200 million convertible note issuance. This issuance will be utilized to acquire a greater amount of BTC. Previously, the company had raised $540 million through a private investment in public equity (PIPE) offering.On August 15th, Nakamoto Holdings completed a merger with KindlyMD, thereby commencing Bitcoin Treasury operations. The merged company will operate under the name KindlyMD, with David Bailey, the co-founder of BTC Inc., serving as the CEO. Anchorage Digital, which is the only federally chartered digital asset bank in the United States, will provide Bitcoin custody and trading services to KindlyMD. These services will support the Bitcoin Treasury operations of the merged company following its association with Nakamoto.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25101</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TD Cowen maintains a Strategy of a $680 Price Target, predicts it will Hold 4.3% of the BTC Total Supply in 2027</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25100</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the investment bank TD Cowen maintained its bullish target price at $680 for Strategy. It predicted that by the end of 2027, Strategy would accumulate 4.3% of the total Bitcoin supply (that is, 900,000 coins), and the price of Bitcoin would reach $232,000. The current trading price of MSTR is $363, with the Bitcoin price above $116,000.Today, Strategy announced that it had relaxed its equity sale financing restrictions, allowing the issuance of common stock when the stock price is below 2.5 times its corresponding Bitcoin holdings. This move has triggered market controversy. Analysts at TD Bank expressed that the financing restrictions were initially implemented as a defensive strategy to protect the value of reserve assets but had now transformed into an opportunistic strategy aimed at accelerating shareholder value creation.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25100</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address sells 3,075 ETH, with a total value of approximately $13.25 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25098</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a whale address sold 3,075 ETH at a price of $4,310 per ETH, with a total value of approximately $13.25 million. Currently, this wallet still holds 15,708 ETH, which is worth around $67.82 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25098</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPYC&apos;s Japanese Yen stablecoin will be deployed on Ethereum, Avalanche, and Polygon.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25099</link>
      <description>August 19th: The issuer of the Japanese Yen stablecoin, JPYC, announced the completion of the registration of the Funds Transfer Service Provider. Its Japanese Yen stablecoin is planned to be deployed on Ethereum, Avalanche, and Polygon. The stablecoin is backed by highly liquid assets such as bank deposits and government bonds, with the goal of issuing 1 trillion Japanese Yen within three years.On November 10, 2021, the issuer of the Japanese Yen stablecoin, JPYC, completed a ￥500 million (approximately $4.43 million) Series A funding round, which was led by Headline Asia with the participation of Circle Ventures.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25099</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain lending company Figure has submitted a public IPO application and will trade on the Nasdaq under the ticker symbol FIGR.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25097</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per Bloomberg, the blockchain lending firm Figure Technology Solutions Inc. has officially filed an IPO application with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). It intends to be traded on Nasdaq under the code FIGR. By June 2025, the company achieved a first-half revenue of $43.8 million and a net profit of $29.1 million, in contrast to a net loss of $15.6 million in the corresponding period of the previous year.BlockBeats had previously reported that on August 5th, the blockchain lending company Figure Technology secretly submitted an IPO application.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25097</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy to Relax Equity Sale Funding Limitation, Allowing Ordinary Shares Issuance When Stock Price is Less Than 2.5 Times Bitcoin Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25095</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per Bloomberg, it is reported that MicroStrategy has seemingly loosened its equity sale financing constraints. This enables the issuance of common stock when the stock price is lower than 2.5 times its corresponding Bitcoin holdings. This provides MicroStrategy with greater flexibility in raising funds to acquire more BTC.Some proponents view this development with an optimistic attitude. They believe that the relaxation of the rules indicates MicroStrategy&apos;s long-term bullish stance on Bitcoin. By being able to raise funds at a lower cost, it may potentially further boost the price of Bitcoin. On the other hand, opposing market participants argue that since November 2024, MicroStrategy&apos;s Bitcoin premium has decreased from 3.4 times to 1.6 times. Lowering the financing restriction will further dilute shareholders&apos; equity.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25095</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Drops Below $116,000, Ethereum Falls Below $4,300</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25096</link>
      <description>Update: On August 19th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin fell below $116,000 with a 24-hour decline of 1.16%. Ethereum also dipped below $4,300 with a 24-hour decrease of 3.66%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created wallet address has accumulated 15,752 ETH, equivalent to $68.24 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25093</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a newly established wallet address received 15,752 ETH from FalconX, which was valued at $68.24 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25093</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The crypto market sees a slight rebound but remains bearish, with meme coins leading the altcoin market drop, while the three major US stock indices close flat.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25094</link>
      <description>August 19th: In the crypto market, there was a slight rebound but it still remained in a downtrend. According to the HTX market data, Ethereum rose above $4,300 last night and is currently trading at $4,314. Bitcoin rebounded this morning and is now above $116,000, priced at $116,246. The total cryptocurrency market capitalization dropped to $4.005 trillion, with a 24-hour decrease of 1.7%. The three major U.S. stock indexes closed nearly flat, with the S&amp;P 500 down 0.01%, the Nasdaq up 0.03%, and the Dow down 0.08%. Intel fell by 3.66%, but after the market closed, it rose by 5.37% as SoftBank Group signed a $2 billion investment agreement with Intel.The altcoin market generally showed a downward trend, with fan tokens leading the decline. Among them:ASR decreased by 14.4% in the last 24 hours;CYBER fell by 10% in the last 24 hours;INJ dropped by 8.26% in the last 24 hours;PROVE declined by 7.7% in the last 24 hours;MOVR decreased by 7.74% in the last 24 hours.In the U.S</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25094</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>