<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:18:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>In July, a whale/institutional investor holding 30.03 million FORM tokens transferred 8 million tokens to a CEX in less than 1 hour, realizing a total unrealized gain of $28.82 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26828</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per Cinder Monitor, this whale/institution had amassed a total of 30.03 million FORM (equivalent to 82.82 million). The average price at which they accumulated was $2.76 in early July.Today, nearly two months later, they began to move to CEX: in the past 1 hour, they transferred 8 million FORM (amounting to 29.80 million USD) to CEX, with 5 million going to Binance and 3 million to Gate.The current price of FORM has now reached $3.72. The 30.03 million FORM they accumulated in early July has already generated a profit of 28.82 million USD. There are still 22.03 million FORM (valued at 79.75 million USD) in their address.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26828</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin drops below $110,000, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach $735 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26826</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to Coinglass data, if Bitcoin drops below $110,000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach 735 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin surpasses $112,000, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEXs will only be 102 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not accurately depict the number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the asset price reaching a certain point will be impacted. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price reaching that level will trigger a more intense reaction due to a liquidity avalanche.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26826</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum briefly dropped below $4,400, with a nearly 1.17% decrease in the past hour.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26827</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum briefly fell below $4400 and is currently trading at $4405.84, experiencing a nearly 1% decrease in the past hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26827</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Issue Impacting Futures Trading Resolved, Trading Now Fully Resumed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26825</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Binance made an announcement stating that the issue that was affecting futures trading has been addressed. All trading has now resumed in its entirety.Based on community statistics, the duration of the downtime for futures trading this time was approximately 21 minutes. Binance has not yet provided the reason for the downtime.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26825</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport September Outlook: Bitcoin Consolidation Expected to Continue for 2-3 Weeks Until New Catalyst Drives Price Movement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26824</link>
      <description>August 29th. Matrixport presented the September market outlook, indicating that Bitcoin is currently in a stage where technical and macro factors are intermingled. The rare decline in August and the typically poor seasonal performance in September. This month will witness key events such as non-farm payroll data, CPI, and the Fed&apos;s interest rate meeting, which further increase uncertainty. Even if the Fed decides to cut interest rates, the market may not necessarily witness the expected rebound.Currently, Bitcoin is fluctuating in a crucial range at the boundary between the bullish and bearish sides, and most investors are choosing to wait and see. The key issue to be addressed next is whether this round of volatility is merely a period of consolidation or a precursor to a trend reversal. Bitcoin&apos;s consolidation phase is expected to continue for another 2-3 weeks until new catalytic factors drive price movements. Since August, Bitcoin has dropped by 3.9%, which is significantly lower</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant Analyst: Crypto Market Cycle Slowing Down, Anticipates Upward Trend in Fall 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26823</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan stated that the cryptocurrency market cycle is decelerating and is expected to have an uptrend in the fall of 2025. When looking at the proportion of Bitcoin held for more than one year (based on realized cap), in the past cycles (first stage and second stage), the market experienced a significant surge and reached its peak. However, in the current stage (third stage), the slope of the uptrend is gradually becoming gentle and the cycle is also getting longer.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26823</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four.meme Introduces Reward Program Update, Enhancing Point Earning Incentives</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26822</link>
      <description>August 29th. The Four.meme platform rolled out an update to its points program to ensure more equitable and motivating point acquisition. The rules were optimized as follows:Buy and Hold - At the launch on PancakeSwap, only the top 20 holders were eligible to claim points (with a limit of 1 claim per day).Liquidity Pool - The daily trading volume threshold was increased from $100 to $250.Point Creation - Daily creation rewards were eliminated.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26822</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renowned trader TechnoRevenant holds a long position in XPL worth approximately $31.1 million, representing 35.5% of Hyperliquid&apos;s total position.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26821</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per on-chain analyst @mlmabc, the renowned trader TechnoRevenant is maintaining a significant long position in XPL with low leverage on Hyperliquid. Currently, he holds 28,295,963 long contracts of XPL (approximately $31.1 million), which accounts for 35.5% of Hyperliquid&apos;s total open interest ($87.5 million). In addition, he also has $26.534 million of idle funds in USDC on Hyperliquid.It is worth noting that all these positions are leveraged at less than 1x, and he is gradually conducting a TWAP operation instead of making purchases in the market, thereby minimizing the impact on the short-term market.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26821</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures Page Appears to Be Down, Trading Data Is Not Updating in Real Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26820</link>
      <description>August 29th: Based on the information on the official website, Binance Futures might have had a downtime, and the trading data could not be updated in real-time. The official information shows that the futures transfer service has been temporarily suspended.As of the time of this writing, Binance has not yet issued an official response.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26820</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Falls Below $111,000, 24-hour Decline of 1.54%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26819</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Bitcoin fell below $111,000, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 1.54%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26819</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>