<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BMNR Ethereum Total Supply Reaches Approximately 625,000 Coins, Ranking First in Institutional Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22312</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), which is the top holder of Ethereum among US-listed crypto reserve companies, disclosed data indicating that the total holdings of BTC have reached 192 coins and the total holdings of ETH have reached approximately 625,000 coins. The company has increased its ETH holdings by 58,224 coins, with a net asset value per share of $22.77.This evening, BMNR announced a $1 billion stock buyback plan.According to RockFlow market data, Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) briefly dropped more than 14% in pre-market trading today; however, the current decline has narrowed to 11%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX will list TREEUSDT perpetual contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22311</link>
      <description>July 29th. As per an official announcement, OKX is set to officially launch the TREEUSDT perpetual contract at 10:30 p.m. (UTC+8) on July 29, 2025, across the web, app, and API. It is reported that Treehouse is a decentralized fixed income layer that has pioneered a cryptocurrency fixed income benchmark.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22311</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「ETH Version of MicroStrategy」 SharpLink: Aiming to Hold 1 Million Ether</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22310</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink (SBET) team officially declared that their objective is to possess 1 million Ethereum, and they are getting closer to the goal than you might imagine, with the process accelerating.Today, the &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink (SBET) team announced that they currently hold around 438,190 Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22310</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degen Foundation Seeks Community Input on PHASED DEGEN Token Burn</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22309</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Degen Foundation officially declared that currently, the foundation holds 32.5% of the DEGEN token supply. Although this fund could be employed for future airdrops (such as in Degen applications or other projects), it would lead to a dilution of the existing holders&apos; stakes. The foundation requires a certain number of DEGEN tokens to support development, but it is not allowed to exceed 30%. Such a significant token supply has aroused concerns among new users regarding future inflation.The Degen Foundation has put forward a plan to gradually destroy DEGEN tokens, steadily burning tokens each month until reaching a sustainable long-term development supply level. At the same time, it will also reward long-term holders. The foundation will not burn all of its holdings, but this will change the tokenomics and may potentially eliminate any large-scale airdrops in the future. The foundation is seeking community feedback on this matter.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22309</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Court Reveals Investment Details of Dragonfly and Tornado Cash, Related Issues Resolved Yesterday</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22308</link>
      <description>July 29th. As per crypto reporter Eleanor Terrett, the latest information regarding the Tornado Cash case indicates that Dragonfly has reached an agreement concerning its association with the founder of Tornado Cash. Court documents have disclosed several crucial facts:Dragonfly injected $900,000 into Tornado Cash in August 2020.In return, they acquired token purchase rights and ultimately obtained 5% of the supply of TORN tokens issued in December 2020.Dragonfly sold a portion of its holdings in August 2022 and received more than $4 million in cryptocurrency.Earlier today, BlockBeats reported that in response to the news about &quot;the US Department of Justice considering charges against Dragonfly employees in the Tornado Cash case,&quot; Dragonfly partner Haseeb stated: &quot;Monday&apos;s court records demonstrate that the US Department of Justice has clarified that media reports regarding their intentions to sue Dragonfly are incorrect. Neither Dragonfly nor any of its key personnel are the targ</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22308</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase: Coinbase Earned Around $300 Million in Trading Revenue from Circle in Q1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22306</link>
      <description>On July 29th, JPMorgan Chase put out a report indicating that the partnership between Coinbase and Circle, along with the investment in Circle&apos;s stablecoin USDC, is bringing about substantial financial advantages, such as the appreciation of equity and high-margin revenue streams. Coinbase currently possesses approximately 8.5 million shares of Circle stock. In just the first quarter of this year alone, Coinbase received approximately $300 million in distribution fees from Circle, which exceeded Circle&apos;s total net revenue of about $230 million. JPMorgan Chase estimates that by the end of the first quarter, the USDC balance on the Coinbase platform was $13 billion, generating $125 million in revenue for the company, with a profit margin ranging from 20% to 25%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22306</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea announced multiple plans ahead of the TGE, including the introduction of native ETH rewards, establishing an Ethereum Ecosystem Fund, etc.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22307</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Linea announced a series of plans prior to the token TGE. These plans include introducing native staking rewards for bridged Ethereum, launching a protocol-level Ethereum burning mechanism, designing an Ethereum-centric deflationary token, and establishing an Ethereum ecosystem fund. The aim is to transform Linea into an ETH capital hub. The bridged Ethereum native staking feature is expected to be launched in October, and the staking rewards will be reinvested in the Linea ecosystem. The Linea team stated that approximately 20% of all net transaction fees paid in ETH will be burned to reduce the supply of ETH, while the remaining 80% of net transaction fees will be used to burn LINEA tokens to reduce the fixed supply. Additionally, 85% of the token supply will be allocated to the ecosystem, with 10% reserved for early users and 75% gradually distributed through the ecosystem fund. The remaining 15% of LINEA tokens will be locked for five years and owned by the Consensys</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22307</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed Hong Kong Company Ruihe Data Intelligence Plans to Collaborate with a Third-Party Independent Institution to Develop a Virtual Cryptocurrency Exchange Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22305</link>
      <description>July 29th. The Hong Kong-listed company RichTech (03680.HK) declared that on July 29, 2025, the group reached a cooperation framework agreement with an independent third-party institution regarding the joint development of a virtual asset trading platform. (Securities Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22305</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「ETH-native Microstrategy」 SharpLink announces total holdings increased to approximately 438,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22304</link>
      <description>July 29th. The &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot;, SharpLink (SBET), officially declared that it currently holds approximately 438,190 ETH. From July 21st to 27th, SharpLink purchased about 77,210 ETH at a total cost of approximately $290 million, with an average price of around $3,756.The per-ETH share (&quot;ETH Concentration&quot;) is now about 3.4, which is higher than around 3.06 from last week. Since implementing the Ethereum Treasury strategy on June 2nd, the per-ETH share has increased by about 70%, and the cumulative staking reward has reached approximately 722 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「SOL Version of MicroStrategy」 DDC Increases Holdings by 181,300 SOL, Total Holding Reaches approximately 1.18 Million SOL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22303</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as reported by Business Insider, the &quot;SOL Version of MicroStrategy,&quot; DDC, augmented its holdings by 181,300 SOL. The total holding amounts to approximately 1.18 million SOL. Additionally, it will raise $20 million through a securities line of credit, with around $10 million of the proceeds still available for future accumulation of SOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22303</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>