<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:25:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Boya Interactive has signed a Stock Placement Agreement for a maximum financing of 441 million Hong Kong dollars, to be used for business development in the Web3 space.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25512</link>
      <description>August 21st. According to an official announcement, Boyaa Interactive International Limited declared that it has reached a placing agreement with the placing agent. The intention is to place up to 63,510,000 new shares at a placing price of HK$6.95 per share. These placing shares account for 8.93% of the total issued shares or approximately 8.20% of the total issued shares after the enlargement.The maximum total amount of funds raised through the placing is HK$441 million, and the estimated net amount is approximately HK$436 million. The funds will be utilized for business development in the Web3 field, such as Web3 game R&amp;D and promotion, infrastructure construction, project investment and strategic partnerships, as well as for the group&apos;s operational funds and general corporate purposes.Boyaa Interactive has resumed trading. As of the writing time, Boyaa Interactive (HK:00434) is trading at HK$8, with an intraday increase of 5.68%.In March of this year, Boyaa Interactive (0434.HK)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West simultaneously posted a video releasing his own cryptocurrency on the domestic social platform Xiaohongshu, following a total of three previous posts.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25511</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Kanye West simultaneously posted a video about coin issuance on the domestic social platform Xiaohongshu (Red) Book. The video was posted at 11:24 AM, which was about 1 hour later than the YZY coin issuance.According to statistics, his account had previously published a total of 3 posts.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cactus Custody Empowers OnChain to Bring the CMBC International Currency Fund RWA On Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25510</link>
      <description>August 21st. OnChain joined forces with Cactus Custody to tokenize the CCB International USD Money Market Fund as a Real World Asset (RWA) within an on-chain operation. This offers investors an auditable on-chain investment option. The fund was established on February 2nd, 2024, and as of July 31st, 2025, it ranked first in the Bloomberg Asia-Pacific category. It leads the market with characteristics like transparency, low volatility, and a verifiable net asset value. This collaboration directly addresses four major pain points in on-chain wealth management:路 The lack of on-chain auditable custodial cash equivalents;路 The low efficiency in bank-to-on-chain fund transfers;路 The difficulty in unifying risk control audits across multiple legal jurisdictions;路 The liquidity fragmentation across multiple chains.OnChain provides RWA on-chain technology services. The net asset value is calculated off-chain and regularly brought onto the chain. Shareholding and transfer are subject to whi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 05:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers&apos; Daily: Abnormal Transaction of Cryptocurrency May Involve Criminal Activities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25509</link>
      <description>August 21st. Recently, the Second Intermediate People&apos;s Court of Beijing Municipality has heard a case related to the use of cryptocurrency transactions for concealing and disguising criminal proceeds. The defendant, being aware that it was criminal proceeds, still assisted in the transfer and was sentenced to 3 years and 6 months in prison. In August 2024, Mr. Liu sold USDT (commonly known as U Coin) to Mr. He. He knew that the cash held by Mr. He was the proceeds of crime and received 200,000 yuan in cash. The whereabouts of the involved funds are currently untraceable. After investigation, the 200,000 yuan transferred by Mr. Liu was the money defrauded from others.The final judgment of the court held that Mr. Liu, knowing that it was criminal proceeds, still assisted in the transfer. His behavior constituted the crime of concealing and disguising criminal proceeds. The court sentenced Mr. Liu to the crime of concealing and disguising criminal proceeds, sentenced him to 3 years and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: YZY briefly dropped below $1</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25508</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on GMGN market data, YZY briefly fell below $1 and is currently trading at $1.0032.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRM Labs Partners with Binance and Coinbase to Launch the First Network for Real-Time Response to Crypto Crime</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25507</link>
      <description>On August 21st, TRM Labs, in conjunction with Coinbase, Binance, Kraken, PayPal, and other entities, launched the Beacon Network, establishing the world&apos;s first real-time cryptocurrency crime response network. The network aims to collaboratively track and freeze illegal crypto funds in real time through the cooperation of CEXs, payment institutions, law enforcement agencies, and security researchers.TRM Labs characterized this as the first &quot;end-to-end anti-money laundering chain&quot; for illicit crypto assets, with the process from detection to action taking only minutes. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Becomes the Silver Sponsor of Taipei Blockchain Week 2025, Promoting the Convergence of Web3 and AI</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25506</link>
      <description>August 21st. As per an announcement by WEEX, WEEX will take part as a silver sponsor in the 2025 Taipei Blockchain Week (TBW2025). This event will be held grandly from September 4th to 6th at the Songshan Cultural and Creative Park in Taipei.Being the largest immersive Web3 and AI event in Asia, the 2025 Taipei Blockchain Week will gather blockchain and cryptocurrency experts and enthusiasts from around the world. For the first time, it will introduce the theme of AI to explore the future possibilities of the integration of blockchain and artificial intelligence technologies. The event aims to drive industry innovation and development through multi-dimensional workshops, exhibitions, and interactive experiences. The WEEX trading platform has sponsored the Taipei Blockchain Week for two consecutive years, which shows its deep involvement in the Web3 field and brand influence.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: YZY Falls Below $1.2</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25505</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to GMGN market data, YZY fell below $1.2 and is currently trading at $1.15. The total trading volume since its launch is $3.972 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25505</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain trader is 3x short on YZY, currently with an unrealized gain of $168,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25504</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a trader initiated a short position in YZY with a 3x leverage. Currently, they are holding a floating profit of $168,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyStonks Risk Management Incident Participant Caroline: Previously published information regarding MyStonks was inaccurate and has now been removed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25503</link>
      <description>On August 21st, User X Caroline (@thcaroline2233) declared that the information previously provided by this account about the MyStonks platform was false and has now been removed.In a previous communication, Caroline mentioned that she was unable to withdraw $6.2 million from the on-chain security platform MyStocks due to a risk control activation. MyStonks responded in a post, indicating that they had received a regulatory enforcement request regarding a particular user. MyStonks emphasized that the security of user assets and the stable operation of the business are of the utmost importance. The platform will continuously optimize compliance measures to protect the legitimate rights and interests of all users and their funds. As a compliant platform, MyStonks will actively cooperate with any regulatory actions requested by sovereign countries.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 04:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>