<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:44:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SEC Chair: Only a tiny number of tokens meet the definition of a security, ushering in a new era for the crypto industry</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25335</link>
      <description>On August 20th, SEC Chairman Paul Atkins recently restated his favorable stance towards cryptocurrency. He emphasized that &quot;a very small number&quot; of tokens fall into the securities category. This statement represents a significant change from the regulatory attitude of the previous administration.While attending a blockchain symposium in Wyoming on Tuesday, Paul Atkins clearly stated: &quot;The SEC will actively promote the new idea that tokens themselves may not necessarily and likely do not constitute securities. In my view, very few tokens truly meet the definition of securities, with the key depending on their ecosystem and method of sale.&quot;This statement comes as the latest policy signal from the SEC following the launch of &quot;Project Crypto&quot; last month. The project has been described by the chairman as a key part of securities law &quot;modernization&quot; reform, aiming to drive the U.S. financial markets towards on-chain transformation.Paul Atkins emphasized, &quot;Especially for the crypto indu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25335</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hyperliquid team expects a per capita annual revenue of $1.043 billion, making it the company with the highest per capita revenue worldwide.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25334</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to data from DeFiLlama, the Hyperliquid protocol has generated a revenue of $95.63 million in the past 30 days, with an estimated annual revenue of $1.147 billion.In a recent interview, the founder of the company, Jeff, stated that the company&apos;s team consists of only 11 people. With an expected annual revenue of $1.147 billion, the per capita annual revenue is calculated to be $104.3 million, making it the company with the highest per capita revenue in the world.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25334</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Surges, Briefly Breaks $4,200</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25333</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum witnessed a rebound and briefly exceeded $4,200. It is currently trading at $4,197.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25333</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Data shows that options traders continue to remain optimistic, with the majority believing that the trend is not over yet</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25332</link>
      <description>August 20th. On-chain data analyst Murphy posted on social media, indicating that based on the &quot;Option Strike Heatmap&quot; data, on August 19th, there was a large-scale call option activity in the price range of $123,708 to $129,685. The total option premium size was approximately $43.32 million. At the same time, there was no net buying below the spot price, suggesting that traders were more inclined to bet on BTC rising to this range and there was little demand for put options, with almost no one actively purchasing downside protection.On the other hand, relatively larger-scale put options were sold in the price range of $97,709 to $102,430, and the total option premium size was approximately $13.14 million. This indicates that option sellers think it is unlikely for the price to drop to this level and choose to sell volatility.Therefore, the sentiment among option market traders remains optimistic. Most still believe that BTC&apos;s trend is not over and are betting that it can return to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25332</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with at least 200 points can claim a 500,000 DGC airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25331</link>
      <description>August 20th. As per official information, the trading of DecentralGPT (DGC) on Binance Alpha will commence on August 20th, 2025, at 8:00 PM (Beijing time). After the trading opens, users who possess at least 200 Alpha Points will be qualified to receive a 500,000 DGC token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the reward pool is not fully distributed, the score threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha Points. Users must confirm their claim on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours. Otherwise, it will be regarded as the user forfeiting the airdrop claim.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25331</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Current Crypto Concept Stock Institutional Participation is Insufficient, Stock Price May Further Consolidate in the Short Term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25330</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Matrixport released a new report on social media. It stated that following a strong 18-month rally, crypto concept stocks have entered a consolidation phase. During the past 18 months, the crypto concept stock index has outperformed Bitcoin significantly. However, with the recent pullbacks in the stock prices of leading companies like MicroStrategy, Coinbase, and Metaplanet, the index has started to show signs of a correction. The cooling of buying interest after Circle&apos;s listing further confirms the lack of momentum in the new stock market.Analyst Markus Thielen said that the current low institutional participation may reflect the seasonal weakness in summer. Without the support of major crypto IPOs, prices may further consolidate in the short term.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25330</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasma has announced a partnership with Fluid, with FLUD surging over 4% intraday.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25329</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, Plasma has made an announcement regarding a partnership with the DeFi protocol Fluid. This partnership will come into effect on the very first day of the Plasma testnet&apos;s launch and will be integrated into the Plasma ecosystem.Based on market data, FLUD witnessed a surge of over 4% during the day and is currently trading at $6.68.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25329</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100Group increased its holdings by 102 bitcoins, bringing the total position to 911 bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25328</link>
      <description>August 20th. As per market reports, the Swedish company H100 Group enhanced its holdings by purchasing 102.19 bitcoins, resulting in its total holdings reaching 911.29 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin Support Located in $109,600 to $106,800 High Demand Zone</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25327</link>
      <description>On August 20th, CryptoQuant analyst Axel posted on social media, indicating that this pullback is relatively gentle. Bitcoin has only dropped by 8% from its local peak. The mid-term support is at the 111-day moving average ($109,600), and the short-term holder realized price is ($106,800). This area forms a dense area of demand, and it is anticipated that there will be attempts at stabilization and a rebound in this zone.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25327</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The U.S. Treasury is set to withdraw $500-600 billion in cash from the market over the next two months, potentially leading to increased market illiquidity.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25326</link>
      <description>August 20th. The Delphi Digital Market Research Institute put out an article indicating that in the forthcoming weeks, the US Treasury Department will commence replenishing its General Account (TGA). This process will withdraw $500–600 billion in cash from the market over approximately two months. On the surface, this might seem ordinary. However, the current period is evolving into one of the most fragile liquidity environments of the past decade.In 2023, the $550 billion TGA replenishment was cushioned by more than $2 trillion of Fed reverse repo tools, healthy bank reserves, and strong overseas bond demand. Now, these cushions have disappeared. The Fed is still consuming liquidity through Quantitative Tightening (QT). Reverse repos are almost depleted. Banks are restricted by losses and capital rules. Overseas buyers from China to Japan have also withdrawn. As a result, every dollar raised by the Treasury Department this fall will be directly drawn from active market liquidity.H</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 06:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25326</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>