<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:52:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Big Shot」 Huang Licheng Increases his Position in YZY Longs, Reducing Floating Loss to $20,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25541</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), &quot;Big Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng has increased his leverage YZY long position by three times to 690,000 tokens (approximately $809,000), with an average entry price of $1.203. Currently, his unrealized loss has been narrowed down to $20,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet has released the August Income Report for Alpha Airdrop, with the highest single-account earnings reaching up to $1616.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25542</link>
      <description>August 21st. As per official channels, Binance Wallet has made public this month&apos;s Alpha Airdrop Performance Statistics. From August 1st to August 18th, a total of 24 Alpha airdrop tokens were listed. If a single account sells at the highest token price, it can receive an airdrop value of up to $1616. If sold at the end of the first day of the airdrop, the airdrop value would be roughly $1175.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25542</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin May Experience a Deeper Pullback if It Falls Below Short-Term Holder Cost of $106,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25540</link>
      <description>On August 21st, CryptoQuant analyst Axel Adler Jr. put forward that Bitcoin is continuously withdrawing from its all-time high. The one-year MVRV Z-Score has declined to nearly neutral, currently being slightly below zero. This indicates that the unrealized profits on the network are somewhat compressed compared to the one-year average level, with a greater amount of supply at the breakeven point or in a loss-making state.The key support level of Bitcoin is at the short-term holder realized price of $106,000. If the price falls below $106,000, short-term holders will be in an overall loss, and the market will be at the risk of a more significant pullback.The recovery signal would be when the Z-Score continues to rise above zero and the price regains $118,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: AriaAI (ARIA) Airdrop Claim Threshold 200 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25539</link>
      <description>August 21st, based on official information, Binance Alpha is set to list AriaAI (ARIA), and Alpha trading is scheduled to commence on August 21, 2025, at 20:00 (UTC+8). After the trading begins, users who hold at least 200 Binance Alpha Points can claim 625 ARIA tokens through an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. To claim the airdrop, it will cost 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Websea has made significant progress in deepening its presence in the Japanese market, attracting attention from the industry.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25538</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the expansion of the cryptocurrency exchange platform Websea in the Japanese market has started to yield results. The user base is growing steadily and community engagement is continuously increasing, demonstrating its strong local market acceptance and growth potential. Japan is gradually emerging as a core engine in Websea&apos;s global strategy.This interim achievement has quickly drawn the attention of the industry. Many well-known Japanese crypto media outlets such as Cointelegraph Japan, Token Economist, and Crypto Times have all recognized Websea from the aspects of strategic deployment and ecosystem development, believing that it is injecting new innovative impetus into the local digital asset industry.As one of the world&apos;s most active cryptocurrency markets, Japan has a mature regulatory system and a large user base, which has laid a solid foundation for Websea&apos;s long-term development.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gold Token XAUm has officially landed on the Sui blockchain, and the Sui Foundation will include XAUm in its strategic reserves.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25537</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Matrixport&apos;s RWA tokenization platform, Matrixdock, announced that its gold token XAUm has successfully completed on-chain deployment on the Sui Network. This marks the first successful deployment of XAUm on a non-EVM compatible chain, signifying a significant milestone in XAUm&apos;s technical architecture and network support scalability. The Sui Foundation will also allocate a portion of its reserve assets to XAUm, demonstrating its support for the project through tangible actions and further highlighting the strategic position of tokenized gold in the on-chain asset portfolio of the Web3 era.XAUm is the first gold token asset on the RWA tokenization track of the Sui Network, providing the Sui community and traditional investors with a new avenue to participate in the gold market. With the completion of XAUm&apos;s on-chain deployment and full integration into the on-chain ecosystem, users in the Sui ecosystem can conveniently access XAUm and actively engage in on-chain ecosy</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institution continues to sell 400 WBTC to receive 10,493 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25533</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to the monitoring of the Ember Group, a whale/institution has once more transferred 400 WBTC to Hyperliquid within the past 3 hours for the purpose of selling and exchanging it for 10,493 ETH (approximately $45.11 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 07:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25533</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trader Bets Successively on Counterfeit and Authentic YZY, Losing Over $800,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25536</link>
      <description>August 21st. Based on the on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), a trader used leverage on the genuine YZY coin at its highest point to break even. At one time, they saw a peak profit of $830,000 but did not realize it. Now, they are facing a floating loss of $106,000. Previously, the trader placed a bet on the fake Kanye concept meme coin YZY and suffered a loss of $700,000, resulting in a total cumulative loss of over $800,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 07:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Big Brother」 Huang Licheng is 3x leveraged long on YZY, currently facing an unrealized loss of $41,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25535</link>
      <description>On August 21, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), &quot;Big Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng initiated a 3x leverage long position on YZY in the past hour. He held 570,000 tokens (approximately $642,000), with an entry price of $1.22 per token. Currently, he is facing an unrealized loss of $41,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 07:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launchpad Platform Heaven Becomes Top Revenue Protocol in the Solana Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25534</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on defillama data, the Solana ecosystem&apos;s AMM and Launchpad platform Heaven achieved a protocol revenue of $1.02 million within the past 24 hours. This placed it as the third-largest fee-generating protocol on Solana, trailing only behind pump.fun and Axiom Pro.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 07:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25534</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>