<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea Introduces Stablecoin ATMs for Foreign Tourists</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22608</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as per the report by Decrypt, the South Korean blockchain company DaWinKS has formed a partnership with the Kaia DLT Foundation to launch a stablecoin ATM that supports the cash redemption of USDT. This ATM is capable of facilitating cash withdrawals of USDT issued on the Kaia chain and is currently accessible at various tourist and retail venues. It can only be used by users holding foreign passports and supports the exchange of 85 fiat currencies or the recharging of local transportation cards. The project is operating under South Korea&apos;s &quot;regulatory sandbox&quot; framework and is currently not available to local residents.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 Index Futures Extend Gains to 1%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22607</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on the market data from RockFlow, the gain of S&amp;P 500 Index futures expanded to 1%, with the latest trading at 6460.53 points.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22607</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has joined the Global Markets Alliance, partnering with Ondo Finance to jointly promote the on-chainization of real-world assets.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22606</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the cryptocurrency exchange Gate officially became a member of the Global Markets Alliance established by Ondo Finance. This partnership represents an important stride in bringing real-world assets (RWA) onto the blockchain and supports the alliance in modernizing access to capital markets through tokenization technology.Having more than a decade of industry experience and over 33 million users worldwide, Gate can contribute strong professional capabilities and extensive global reach to the alliance. For Gate, tokenized stocks are merely the starting point. By collaborating with key industry players, Gate is dedicated to unlocking broader investment access, higher liquidity, and more diverse investment opportunities for global users.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22606</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Chain Token Supply Surpasses Solana for 4 Consecutive Days, Zora&apos;s Issuance Exceeds the Total Supply of Letsbonk and Pump.fun</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22605</link>
      <description>On July 31st, based on the sealaunch data dashboard, as of July 26th, the on-chain token issuance of the Base chain has exceeded that of Solana for 4 consecutive days, marking a historical first.It is worth noting that in terms of the issuance market share on the Base and Solana networks, Zora has consistently ranked first since July 23rd. According to the latest published data, on July 29th, the issuance of the Zora platform reached 49,989, with a market share of 63%, surpassing the total issuance on the same day by Letsbonk (19,593) and Pump.fun (4764).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22605</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan Governor: The spread of stablecoins has a significant impact, such as affecting transactions outside of traditional banking</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22604</link>
      <description>On July 31st, Bank of Japan Governor Kuroda stated: The spread of stablecoins has a significant impact. For instance, it affects transactions that take place outside traditional banks. (Xinhua News)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22604</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Move: Over 34.7M USDC Withdrawn in a Single Transaction, One Address Reversed Deposited 20.53M USDC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22603</link>
      <description>On July 31st, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight at https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/trade, multiple whales have carried out large-scale withdrawal operations within the past 24 hours. One whale address has deposited 20.53 million USDC:The whale with the address starting with 0x6fCaD3 has withdrawn a total of 3.47 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0x477296 has withdrawn a total of 7.277 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0x2BDF1a withdrew approximately 1.5 million USDC in the last 1 hour;The whale with the address starting with 0x47729 has withdrawn a total of 5.776 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0x8d0E34 has withdrawn approximately 5 million USDC in the last 24 hours;The whale with the address starting with 0xECB63c has deposited approximately 20.53 million USDC in the last 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22603</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Fed Sees First Dual Dissent in 30 Years, BTC Quickly Rebounds After Fed Statement, $117,000 Holds as Short-Term Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22602</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as was anticipated, the Federal Reserve maintained the interest rates at their current levels. Nevertheless, during the FOMC meeting, two governors appointed by Trump (Waller and Bowman) surprisingly cast dissenting votes, which had not occurred for more than 30 years. These two individuals believe that the current policy is overly restrictive. Chairman Powell stated that no decision has been made regarding the September meeting yet, but the inflation pressure caused by tariffs may be a short-term occurrence. The language of the Fed still maintains a hawkish stance but also emphasizes that economic growth is decelerating and that policy risks coexist.On July 31st, in the early morning, the price of BTC plummeted to below 116,000, breaking through a significant liquidity band before rebounding rapidly. Within a few hours, it regained the lost ground and rose above 117,000, indicating strong buying support below. Currently, the price has entered a high-density liquidity z</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22602</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 wallets from the Satoshi era were activated after 15.3 years of dormancy, consolidating 250 BTC to 2 new addresses</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22601</link>
      <description>On July 31st, as monitored by OnchainLens, 5 wallet addresses from the Satoshi era (which are likely owned by the same entity) that had been inactive for 15.3 years consolidated 250 BTC with a value of $29.64 million into 2 new addresses.Addresses:- bc1qng4nps9ye7e5pfnd9hy687fygjgr3pq5xhsu4a- bc1q6n53469l6evqs05apy49pm7r0df0rxhv8cxndj</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22601</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin Poised to Hit $125,000 Based on Short-Term Holder Cost Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22600</link>
      <description>On July 31st, the crypto analyst @ali_charts presented a chart analysis indicating that as long as Bitcoin&apos;s support level of $105,450 is maintained. According to the short-term holder cost basis, it is anticipated to keep rising to $125,230, and there is even a possibility of reaching $141,770.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list PlaysOut (PLAY) with an airdrop threshold of 200 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22599</link>
      <description>July 31st. Binance Alpha is set to launch PlaysOut (PLAY). Users possessing at least 200 Alpha points will be eligible to receive an airdrop of 1600 PLAY tokens. In case the rewards are not completely distributed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. The act of claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points.Binance Alpha exchange platform will list PlaysOut (PLAY) on July 31, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). Binance Futures platform will list PlaysOut (PLAY) on July 31, 2025, at 17:30 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22599</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>