<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:54:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay has launched the &quot;Rising Star Recruitment Program,&quot; where the official will provide selected candidates with funding and traffic support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27849</link>
      <description>On September 5th, BiyaPay announced the commencement of the &quot;Rising Star Recruitment Program.&quot; This program is intended to recruit Chinese rising stars and provide funding and traffic support to talented teams or individuals, aiming to achieve the common growth of rising stars and the platform. Once selected, participants will be awarded a maximum monthly fixed reward of 2000 USDT, as well as quarterly rewards, special bonuses, project peripherals, and other exclusive benefits. The &quot;Rising Star Recruitment Program&quot; is an integral part of the CoinWedge BIYA Global Crypto Community Influence Program. CoinWedge builders who are selected will receive comprehensive support provided by the officials and are committed to expanding the influence of BIYA CoinWedge in the Chinese community and achieving the common growth of rising stars and the platform.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27849</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit will list Redstone (RED) KRW trading pair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27848</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Upbit is going to list the Redstone (RED) with the trading pair of Korean Won.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum breaks above $4500, the mainstream CEX cumulative short liquidation pressure will reach 1.395 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27847</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on Coinglass data, if Ethereum manages to break through $4500, the total liquidation intensity of the short positions on mainstream CEX will reach $1.395 billion.On the other hand, if Ethereum drops below $4300, the total liquidation intensity of the long positions on mainstream CEX will reach $0.712 billion.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of the contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to neighboring clusters, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree reaching a certain price level will have an impact. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that reaching that price will lead to a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27847</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list OPEN on September 8th and assign it a Seed label</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27846</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Binance will list OPEN on September 8, 2025, at 13:00 (UTC), and commence trading for the USDT, USDC, BNB, FDUSD, and TRY pairs. OPEN will have a seed label. Users will be able to start depositing OPEN on September 5, 2025, at 9:30 (UTC).It should be noted that OPEN will make its debut on Binance Alpha and be tradable on Binance Alpha (with the specific time to be announced later). However, once spot trading opens, OPEN will no longer be visible on Binance Alpha.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27846</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance HODLer Airdrop Goes Live on OpenLedger (OPEN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27845</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Binance is glad to declare that the 36th project to be launched on the HODLer Airdrops page is OpenLedger (OPEN), an AI blockchain project aiming to unlock liquidity for the monetization of data, models, and intelligent agents.During the time from 2025-08-18 00:00 (UTC) to 2025-08-21 23:59 (UTC), users who have staked BNB in Simple Earn (either flexible or locked) and/or on-chain staking products will receive the airdrop distribution. The details of the HODLer Airdrops will be announced within 24 hours, and the new tokens will be delivered to users&apos; spot accounts at least 1 hour before trading begins.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain new address has acquired 309,000 HYPE tokens and staked them, totaling over $14 million in value.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27844</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on on-chain data, a newly established wallet has just withdrawn 309,000 HYPE tokens (approximately $14.2 million) from KuCoin and pledged them with the FalconX &lt;&gt; Chorus One validator.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27844</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha New Airdrop SHARDS Point Threshold Announcement: At Least 220 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27843</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to official information, Binance Alpha is the first platform to list WORLDSHARDS (SHARDS), and Alpha trading will commence on September 5, 2025, at 19:00 (UTC+8).After the trading begins, users who hold at least 220 Binance Alpha Points can claim 4,000 SHARDS tokens as an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s &apos;Pump Signal&apos; Meme Coin, with a market cap of only $157,000, has now surged over 240%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27842</link>
      <description>On September 5th, James Wynn made a post on a social media platform, stating, &quot;Can someone come and serve as the CTO of this coin? $WIFE. I will assist in promoting it. I truly like this narrative. However, the team has ceased posting and responding.&quot; At the moment he made the post, the meme coin had a market capitalization of only $157,000. Approximately 40 minutes later, the token&apos;s market capitalization surged by more than 240% to $459,000.James Wynn then said, &quot;I hold $WIFE and $GOAT on Solana. I firmly believe that I will never purchase any shitcoin on Solana again. I will continue to hold them and provide support at the appropriate time, whether they reach the moon or return to dust. My current main focus will be on AI trading bots, my personal trading, and the Ethereum ecosystem.&quot;Currently, James Wynn is actively attempting to obtain the X account of the meme coin $WIFE.BlockBeats reminds users: Most meme coins have no practical applications and experience significant pric</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27842</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Past $112,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27841</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin has rebounded and exceeded $112,000, registering a 24-hour gain of 1.67%. Ethereum has surpassed $4,350, and the 24-hour loss has narrowed to 0.43%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27841</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US August non-farm payroll data and unemployment rate will be released tonight at 8:30 PM.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27840</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics will announce the U.S. August seasonally adjusted nonfarm payroll data and the U.S. August unemployment rate data at 20:30 this evening. The details include:· The U.S. August Seasonally Adjusted Nonfarm Payrolls (in thousands): Expected is 7.5, and the previous value was 7.3. This data reflects the changes in the number of people employed in the U.S. nonfarm sector, excluding the agricultural sector. It is obtained through sampling surveys of U.S. businesses, government agencies, and nonfarm sectors. On the first Friday of each month, the U.S. Department of Labor releases the nonfarm payroll data for the previous month.· The U.S. August Unemployment Rate: Expected is 4.30%, and the previous value was 4.20%. This data represents the percentage of the unemployed population in the labor force during a specific period (the number of job seekers who are willing to work but still do not have a job within the total employed population du</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 06:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>