<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:52:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has launched the second round of Dolomite (DOLO) airdrop.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26535</link>
      <description>August 27th. Binance Alpha has initiated the second round of the Dolomite (DOLO) airdrop. Qualified users are able to utilize Alpha Points to claim 166 DOLO tokens within 24 hours following the commencement of trading on the event page.The airdrop will be dispensed in two stages:Stage 1 (the first 18 hours): Users possessing at least 260 Alpha Points are eligible to claim the airdrop.Stage 2 (the remaining 6 hours): Users holding at least 230 Alpha Points can participate in the second-phase airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In the event that the activity is still in progress, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opens Cryptocurrency Stocks Experience a General Decline, Ethereum&apos;s Top Holder Institution BMNR Drops by 3.5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26534</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on market data, the U.S. stock market opened with the Dow down by 0.08%, the S&amp;P 500 down by 0.1%, and the Nasdaq down by 0.1%. Nvidia opened with a 0.08% increase and will release its latest financial report after the market closes. Cryptocurrency stocks are mostly in a downtrend, including:Coinbase (COIN) up by 0.04%;Circle (CRCL) down by 0.89%;MicroStrategy (MSTR) down by 0.75%;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) down by 1.4%;Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR) down by 3.5%;ETHZilla (ETHZ) down by 0.65%;BTCS (BTCS) down by 2.95%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26534</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BetterBank Hacker Returns 550 Million pDAI to Official, Equivalent to Around $2.7 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26533</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as monitored by CertiK Alert, the BetterBank hacker has converted the stolen assets into 309 Ethereum (approximately $1.4 million) and returned 550 million out of the requested 700 million pDAI (approximately $2.7 million) to the team.BlockBeats previously reported that at noon today, the DeFi platform BetterBank on PulseChain was attacked, resulting in a loss of about $5 million. The attacker exchanged some of the stolen assets for 215 ETH (about $983,000), and the deposit address is: 0xf3ba0d57129efd8111e14e78c674c7c10254acae.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26533</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI has announced an improvement to ChatGPT to better respond to user emotions and mental distress</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26532</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as per The Wall Street Journal, following reports of users resorting to chatbots for assistance during emotional breakdowns, OpenAI announced its plans to enhance ChatGPT in order to better identify and respond to users&apos; psychological and emotional distress signals. OpenAI released a blog post stating, &quot;In the recent distressing events, users in a state of extreme distress used ChatGPT, which has had a significant impact on us. This has led us to believe that it is now necessary to share more information.&quot;OpenAI indicated that the upcoming updates will assist users in returning to reality even if they do not show signs of severe self-harm. The company is also exploring ways to help users connect with therapists before they reach a severe crisis. This represents a significant departure from the current mode of operation: when someone expresses a desire to self-harm, the chatbot would recommend that they contact a suicide hotline.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26532</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s &quot;Big Three&quot; Suggests Rate Adjustment Possible at Each Policy Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26531</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the President of the New York Fed, Williams, stated that the upcoming Fed policy meeting would be a &quot;live&quot; meeting, suggesting the possibility of an interest rate adjustment. However, he did not explicitly state which course of action he would support. In an interview today, Williams said, &quot;From my point of view, I definitely consider every meeting to be live. We are making risks more balanced.&quot; After Fed Chairman Powell stated last Friday that &quot;downside risks to employment are rising&quot; and that &quot;changes in the risk balance may require us to adjust our policy stance,&quot; investors are betting that the Fed will cut interest rates at the September meeting. Williams said that the current interest rate level is &quot;moderately restrictive,&quot; indicating that the Fed can &quot;lower rates while still maintaining a certain degree of restraint in the future, but we need to accurately assess the economic conditions.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26531</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave Labs Launches New Lending Platform Horizon for Institutional Users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26530</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the decentralized lending protocol Aave Labs launched a new platform named Horizon for institutional users. This enables institutional users to use tokenized real-world assets (RWA) as collateral to borrow stablecoins. The acceptable collaterals include Superstate&apos;s short-term US Treasury bonds, cryptocurrency arbitrage funds, Circle Yield Fund, and Centrifuge&apos;s tokenized Janus Henderson product. The platform operates based on the decentralized lending protocol Aave V3, and Chainlink&apos;s oracle service provides real-time pricing data to the platform. Leading institutions like VanEck and WisdomTree have become the first batch of partners.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26530</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter Lend&apos;s public beta version is now live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26529</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Jupiter made an announcement. It stated that the public beta of Jupiter Lend is now live and is touted as the most advanced money market on Solana, which is built on Fluid. Jupiter Lend has already onboarded more than 40 insurance pools and has received over $2 million in rewards from Jup, Fluid, and partners.The public launch version will provide a loan-to-value ratio (LTV) of up to 95%, with close to zero liquidation penalties. It will also offer multi-fold vaults and generous annual percentage yields (APY).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26529</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland transferred 25,200 ETH to Coinbase, worth approximately $116 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26527</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as monitored by Whale Alert, Cumberland transferred 25,200 ETH to Coinbase Institutional approximately 5 minutes prior. The value of this transfer is around $116 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26527</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamino is about to launch a new High-Yield Treasury for USDC and USDG</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26528</link>
      <description>On August 27th, in Kamino (a liquidity protocol within the Solana ecosystem), it was announced that two new high-yield USDC and USDG pools were about to be launched, which were based on Steakhouse custody.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by Buyback News, OM Surges Over 7% in the Short Term, Breaking $0.25</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26526</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on HTX market information, due to the &quot;MANTRA Officially Announces Repurchase of $25 Million Worth of OM Tokens&quot;, OM witnessed a short-term surge of more than 7% and broke through $0.25. The market capitalization of OM is currently reported to be $2.46 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26526</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>