<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance&apos;s latest Alpha Yala (YALA) single-asset staking APY is around 66%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21453</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Binance Alpha began airdropping 200 YALA tokens to eligible users the previous day. This was based on the YALA opening price ranging from $0.33 to $0.42. Consequently, the opening return of Binance&apos;s new Alpha Yala (YALA) single-number is approximately $66.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21453</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean blockchain infrastructure provider DSRV has completed a Series B funding round of approximately $11.6 million, with participation from major Korean investment firms including Intervest.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21452</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the South Korean blockchain infrastructure service provider DSRV announced the completion of approximately 16 billion South Korean won (about $11.6 million) in Series B round 1 financing. This round of financing was participated in by leading South Korean investment institutions like Intervest and NH-SK Securities. It is expected that the second round of financing will start at the end of next month, with more financial institutions joining.DSRV currently provides nodes and infrastructure services for more than 70 global blockchain networks and manages assets worth over 40 trillion South Korean won. The company&apos;s sales in 2023 reached 10.7 billion South Korean won, with a net profit of 3 billion South Korean won. In the future, it will focus on expanding into new business areas such as stablecoins and custody and accelerate its global expansion plan in regions like the United States, Japan, and Africa. (edaily)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21452</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European FinTech company TRACTIAL has added 9.77 Bitcoin to its holdings, bringing the total position to 25.03 Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21451</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the European fintech company TRACTIAL (formerly known as BD Multimedia) has accomplished an additional allocation of 9.77 bitcoins. As a result, its total holdings have reached 25.03 bitcoins. The average cost per unit is 88,724 euros (approximately 104,286 US dollars).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21451</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Lnfi Network (LN) on July 25th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21450</link>
      <description>July 23rd. As per official announcements, Binance Alpha is set to list the Lnfi Network (LN) on July 25th. Qualified users can access the Alpha activity page once Alpha trading commences and claim the airdrop by using Alpha Points. Further details will be disclosed separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21450</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ping An Securities: Hong Kong May Adopt a Dual-track Regulatory Approach for Stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21449</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Ping An Securities released a stablecoin report indicating that Hong Kong may establish a dual-track regulatory framework of &quot;USD Stablecoins Connecting to the International Market + HKD Stablecoins Connecting to the Mainland.&quot; This not only reinforces the financial attributes of the Hong Kong Dollar but also offers an &quot;experimental field&quot; for the internationalization of the RMB. Hong Kong&apos;s definition of stablecoins is relatively extensive and not limited to a specific type of fiat-backed stablecoin. With the rapid development of the Hong Kong stablecoin market, it is expected that the market share of non-USD stablecoins will gradually increase, potentially driving the establishment of a unified international regulatory system in the future.Furthermore, the Ping An Securities report also mentioned that Hong Kong&apos;s regulatory scope for regulated stablecoin activities encompasses not only activities of issuing designated stablecoins in Hong Kong but also activities of is</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21449</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum L2 network Taiko has achieved integration with Dune.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21448</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to official information, the Ethereum L2 network Taiko has accomplished integration with Dune. Now, the on-chain data of Taiko can be viewed in real-time on Dune.Through this integration, the data of the Taiko network will be presented to developers and the community in a more transparent, open, and convenient manner.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company DigitalX increases its Bitcoin holdings by 74.7 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 499.8 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21447</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Australian-listed cryptocurrency asset management company DigitalX (ASX: DCC, OTCQB: DGGXF) announced that it has boosted its holdings by 74.7 bitcoins. The company&apos;s overall bitcoin holdings have now reached 499.8 bitcoins, with a total value of approximately $91.3 million based on current prices.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21447</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Ethereum End-of-Year Price Target $10,000, Bitcoin $250,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21446</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per Cointelegraph, Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of BitMEX, declared that by the end of this year, Bitcoin will reach $250,000 and Ethereum will reach $10,000.He further mentioned that Trump&apos;s wartime economic policies have caused a credit expansion to flow into cryptocurrencies, with stablecoin issuers purchasing Treasury bonds to offset government deficits.It is worth noting that on May 30th of this year, Arthur Hayes believed that Ethereum could rise to $5,000 this year.On July 3rd, Arthur Hayes wrote, &quot;From now until Jerome Powell delivers a speech at the Jackson Hole Fed meeting in August, the market will consolidate at a slightly lower level. If it is proven that the TGA refill is detrimental to USD liquidity, the downside is between $90,000 and $95,000. If the refill is proven to be inconsequential, Bitcoin will remain around $100,000 and will not exceed the historical high of $112,000.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21446</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four years ago, the whale that built a position in WBTC sold 1000 WBTC over the past 4 days, realizing a total profit of $107 million from their holdings.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21445</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the address which &quot;averaged $10,708 four years ago and accumulated 1074 WBTC&quot; is said to have sold 300 WBTC 9 hours ago, with a value of $35.62 million.During the past 4 days, a total of 1000 BTC has been sold, with a total value of $1.18 billion, an average selling price of $118,011, and a profit of $1.07 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21445</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Yoshihide Suga is expected to resign, triggering a short-term decline in the yen and a rise in Japanese stocks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21444</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the Nikkei 225 Index continued to rise, exceeding 41,000 points and seeing an intraday increase of over 3%. The USD/JPY pair witnessed a short-term increase of up to 60 pips, reaching above 147, with the highest reaching 147.14 and an intraday increase of 0.26%. According to Japan&apos;s &quot;Daily News&quot;, Japanese Prime Minister Shizo Abe will announce his resignation at the end of August. (Kinli)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21444</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>