<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:58:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Kingdom of Bhutan has transferred 799.69 BTC to two new addresses, approximately $92.06 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25048</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the government of the Kingdom of Bhutan has transferred 799.69 Bitcoins (valued at approximately $92.06 million) to two new wallets. This transfer may be intended for depositing into a centralized exchange.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs expects the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates three times this year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25047</link>
      <description>August 18th: Goldman Sachs anticipates that the Fed will implement three interest rate cuts this year. These cuts are expected to take place in September, October, and December. The reason for this expectation is the weak growth in US jobs. Analysts pointed out that the addition of jobs has slowed to approximately 30,000 per month. This is significantly lower than the approximately 80,000 needed for full employment. Moreover, future revisions to the data may be more negative. They believe that the risks do not only stem from trade and immigration. &quot;Compensatory hiring&quot; is on the wane, and the growth in most industries is close to zero. Goldman Sachs cautioned that although the unemployment rate remains stable, even a mild slowdown in the labor market is a cause for concern. If the unemployment rate shows a more pronounced increase, it could lead to a larger 50-basis-point rate cut.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25047</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Analysis: Powell&apos;s Jackson Hole Summit May Face Noise from Trump and Bezent</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25046</link>
      <description>On August 18th, Patrick Munnelly, the market strategist of the Tickmill Group, stated in a report that the upcoming Jackson Hole Symposium, which is scheduled to open on Friday, is anticipated to be a crucial moment for the market. At that time, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will outline the near-term policy direction of the Fed.However, he pointed out that, as usual, the different views from Trump and Bostic could bring noise. Munnelly said that the noise could stem from the ongoing discussions regarding the Fed appointment, potential legal challenges, and changes in the labor market report.He further added, &quot;Prior to this, the July FOMC meeting minutes released on Wednesday may offer valuable clues to narrowing the gap in interest rate prospects.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25046</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoRich standalone version officially launched on the BIT App</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25045</link>
      <description>On August 18th, the on-chain transaction tool GoRich officially launched its standalone version and established an exclusive operation interface within the BIT App. This upgrade indicates that GoRich has shifted from a functional module to a standalone version, further solidifying its differentiated positioning in the on-chain transaction track and providing users with a clearer and more efficient one-stop on-chain transaction experience.In the standalone version of GoRich, users can conveniently utilize core functions such as Smart Wallet Signal, on-chain transactions, asset management, etc. Users can directly use the account on the BIT trading platform to complete cross-chain asset transactions. In this case, USDT can be used not only to purchase assets but also to pay on-chain Gas, without the need to prepare an additional wallet or native tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25045</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXC Lists LINEA (LINEA) for Pre-market Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25044</link>
      <description>August 18th. As per official information, MEXC commenced the pre-trading of LINEA (LINEA) at 18:00 (UTC+8) on August 18, 2025. Users are able to trade in advance prior to the opening of the spot trading for LINEA.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25044</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Roll-Over Long ETH」 Whale Longs Again, Position Worth $1 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25043</link>
      <description>On August 18th, according to Whale Alert, the &quot;whale with a long liquidation of 12.5k USD on ETH&quot; has once again taken a long position. Currently, its two addresses have gone long on 23,500 ETH, and the position value is 100 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25043</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 650 million USDT and approximately $2.06 billion worth of OKB were transferred to OKEx within 20 minutes.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25041</link>
      <description>August 18th. Based on Whale Alert&apos;s monitoring, a significant amount of funds was transferred from an unidentified wallet to OKX within the past 20 minutes. This transfer included 652,228,192 USDT and a total of 17,157,570 OKB, which is approximately worth 2.06 billion US dollars.Previously reported, on August 15th, following the destruction of OKB, the total supply officially decreased to 21 million tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25041</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand Introduces Tourist Wallet for Foreign Visitors, Cryptocurrency Functionality Still in Sandbox Phase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25042</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as reported by CoinDesk, Thailand has initiated the Tourist Wallet for foreign tourists. This wallet is used for QR code payments to convert foreign currency into Thai Baht. However, the cryptocurrency exchange function has been temporarily suspended due to regulatory reviews and is not expected to be available until mid-August.The Bank of Thailand stated that the purpose of launching the Tourist Wallet is to address a practical issue. Currently, cross-border QR code payments are only available in countries such as Singapore, Malaysia, and upcoming partner countries. Tourists from other countries still encounter inconvenience when making payments in Thailand, and the new wallet aims to address this pain point.Tourists can top up the wallet in the following ways: using cash at service provider counters, linking a foreign debit or credit card, or through overseas bank transfers. The spending limits are as follows: a maximum of 500,000 Thai Baht (approximately $13,800)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25042</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After liquidating their long position in ETH and suffering a $6.59 million loss, a certain whale has once again gone long on ETH, with a position now totaling $100 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25040</link>
      <description>On August 18th, according to ChainInfo, a whale liquidated a long position in ETH and suffered a loss of $6.59 million. Subsequently, the whale continued to take a long position on ETH. Currently, the whale holds a long position of 23,373 ETH, with a notional value of $100 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong SFC&apos;s Thomas Atkinson: Beware of Stablecoin Hype, High Risks of Unlicensed Trading Platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25039</link>
      <description>August 18th. Terence Yeung, the Executive Director of the Intermediaries Division of the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission, stated that recently, some companies have been manipulating stock prices under the guise of applying for a stablecoin license. Investors are advised to remain rational and be vigilant against related scams.He disclosed that the division received 265 complaints related to virtual asset trading in the first half of this year, mainly concerning overseas fraud, platform infringement, or fund freezing. He also cautioned about the risks of trading on unlicensed platforms. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25039</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>