<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:39:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>China and the United States will jointly push for the resumption of the 24% tariff that has been suspended by the U.S. side and the extension of China&apos;s retaliatory measures as scheduled.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22346</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Li Chenggang, the vice minister of the Ministry of Commerce and deputy China International Trade Representative, stated on the 29th that in the past day and a half, the Chinese and American trade teams, in line with the consensus reached during the June 5th phone call between the leaders of the two countries, continued to exert their functions in the China-US economic and trade consultation mechanism and engaged in in-depth, frank, and constructive exchanges on major issues of mutual concern. According to the consensus reached by China and the United States, both sides will continue to promote the 24% equivalent tariffs that the US has suspended and the extension of China&apos;s retaliatory measures as scheduled. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22346</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority: &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; establishes a 6-month transition period and implements a classification treatment for existing stablecoin issuers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22345</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) announced that the &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; will have a 6-month transition period commencing from August 1st. Existing stablecoin issuers will undergo classified treatment: those that comply with regulatory requirements may obtain a temporary license; those that fail to meet the standards within 3 months must cease operations within 4 months; and those that do not meet the licensing criteria must cease operations within 1 month after receiving notice. Regulatory requirements encompass full reserves, same-day redemption, establishment of a presence in Hong Kong, and maintaining sufficient financial resources, among others. Initially, only a limited number of licenses will be issued, and issuers are required to implement customer due diligence and transaction monitoring and other compliance measures. Violators will face penalties such as fines, license suspension, or revocation.As of now, the HKMA has not issued any licenses. The pub</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader AguilaTrades partially liquidated their long position to 1000 BTC, worth $117.65 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22342</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, trader AguilaTrades has taken the action of closing the majority of their long positions in order to avoid liquidation. Currently, they are holding a long position of 1,000 BTC, which is valued at $117.65 million. The total loss they have incurred has exceeded $38 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22342</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Senator Introduces New Bill to Include Cryptocurrency in Collateral Asset</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22344</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Cynthia Lummis, the advocate of the &quot;Bitcoin Strategic Reserve Act&quot; and the Chair of the Senate Banking Subcommittee on Digital Assets, introduced the &quot;21st Century Mortgage Act&quot; today. This act calls on Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac to take digital assets recorded on a distributed ledger into consideration when evaluating the eligibility for single-family residential mortgages and not to require the conversion of these digital assets into dollars. The bill aims to recognize digital assets as a wealth assessment metric in order to increase homeownership opportunities for the younger generation.Previously, on June 26th, Mark Pulte, the Director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency (FHFA) in the United States, posted on social media saying: &quot;After conducting research and in line with President Trump&apos;s vision of making the US the epicenter of cryptocurrency, I have ordered Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac to prepare for business and classify cryptocurrency as an eligible asset for</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algeria Completely Bans Cryptocurrency-Related Activities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22343</link>
      <description>July 29th. As per Crypto Briefing, on July 24th, Algeria officially enacted Law No. 25 - 10, which completely prohibits cryptocurrency-related activities. The law forbids the issuance, purchase, sale, holding, utilization, and promotion of crypto assets. Additionally, it classifies cryptocurrency mining, the use of digital wallets, and the operation of exchanges as illegal activities. Offenders will face imprisonment ranging from 2 months to 1 year, along with fines ranging from 200,000 to 1,000,000 Algerian dinars (approximately $1,540 to $7,700). In the event of being linked to organized crime networks or financial crime activities, the penalties will be further increased.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22343</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflux Network has announced that it is collaborating with partners to jointly explore the innovative application of stablecoins in Belt and Road Initiative countries.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22341</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Conflux Network made an announcement that it is collaborating with AnchorX and Shanghai Lingang Cross-border Digital Finance to explore how the AxCNH stablecoin can provide support for cross-border payments and innovation in Belt and Road Initiative countries.Previously, as reported by BlockBeats on July 20th, Conflux Network reached a strategic partnership with AnchorX and Donexin. The goal is to promote the issuance of offshore RMB stablecoins, cross-border settlement, RWA, and other application scenarios in Belt and Road Initiative countries. The three parties plan to implement benchmark overseas projects in regions such as Central Asia and Southeast Asia.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22341</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bit Digital&apos;s AI Infrastructure Subsidiary Whitefiber Seeks to Raise $132.8 Million Through IPO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22340</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the U.S. listed company Bit Digital (BTBT)&apos;s artificial intelligence infrastructure subsidiary, Whitefiber Inc., is aiming to raise up to $132.8 million through an initial public offering (IPO). The company intends to issue 7.8 million shares of stock with a price ranging from $15 to $17 per share and is projected to determine the IPO pricing during the week commencing August 4th. Whitefiber was separated from Bit Digital and possesses high-performance computing data centers, offering cloud-based High Performance Computing (HPC) Graphics Processing Unit (GPU) services. The company provides cloud services for applications in the development of artificial intelligence and machine learning.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22340</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by &quot;Order System Failure,&quot; HYPE Plunges Over 7% in Nearly 2 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22339</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on market data, HYPE witnessed a drop of over 7% in the past 2 hours and is currently trading at $43.Previously, the Hyperliquid team responded on Discord to the &quot;order system malfunction preventing users from placing trades&quot; by stating that the issue is being investigated and they will promptly share any updates.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22339</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity deposited 12,981 ETH to Coinbase in the past hour, worth approximately $49.7 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22338</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Fidelity transferred 12,981 ETH to Coinbase within nearly 1 hour, with a value of approximately $49.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22338</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyth Network is pleased to announce its support for real-time price data for 85 publicly listed companies in the Hang Seng Index in Hong Kong.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22337</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Pyth Network declared its backing for the real-time price data of 85 listed companies within the Hang Seng Index of Hong Kong. The data source is furnished by institutional-grade market participants and is updated every 400 milliseconds, being published on-chain in real time.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22337</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>