<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:15:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve will announce its interest rate decision tonight, with only a 2.1% probability of a rate cut in July.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22436</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Federal Reserve will announce its interest rate decision this evening (2 a.m. Beijing Time on July 31st), and Federal Reserve Chair Powell will hold a press conference 30 minutes later.According to the &quot;FedWatch&quot; data from CME, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut in July is 2.1%, while the probability of maintaining the rate unchanged is 97.9%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22436</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: The current sentiment is diverging from the fundamentals, which may signal a cooling-off period in the market in the short term</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22435</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Matrixport released today&apos;s market analysis which stated, &quot;The current Greed and Fear Index is approaching a high level, and the slow moving average is also showing signs of a top signal. Looking back at history, whenever this indicator is in an upward phase, the Bitcoin price usually demonstrates strength; however, once it begins to decline, it often indicates a cooling-off of market sentiment, and investors need to be more cautious.&quot;&quot;In early July, we made a bullish judgment that went against the mainstream view. But as the market developed, we have also shifted to a more cautious stance, expecting Bitcoin to enter a consolidation phase in August. The latest trend of the Greed and Fear Index also validates this assessment: despite the continuous positive news, market momentum has weakened.&quot;&quot;The current divergence between sentiment and fundamentals may suggest that the market could enter a cooling-off phase in the short term. It is recommended that investors closely</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22435</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avantis, a derivatives trading platform in the Base Protocol ecosystem, has established a foundation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22434</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Base Protocol derivative trading platform Avantis announced the establishment of a foundation. Its main mission is to guarantee protocol development and security, community governance and transparency, as well as ecosystem growth and innovation.Before this announcement, Avantis completed an $8 million Series A funding round. Peter Thiel&apos;s Founders Fund and Pantera Capital took the lead in this round, with participants including Symbolic Capital, SALT Fund, and Flowdesk.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the US Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $80 million, while the Ethereum ETF saw a net inflow of $218.6 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22433</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on Farside&apos;s monitoring, the net inflow of the US Bitcoin spot ETF was $80 million yesterday, and the net inflow of the Ethereum ETF was $218.6 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22433</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has closed an ETH long position, realizing a profit of $6 million, and has withdrawn 2000 ETH from Binance.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22432</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, yesterday, a whale liquidated its long position in ETH and made a profit of $6 million.The whale withdrew $12.68 million from HyperLiquid and deposited it into Binance. Subsequently, it transferred out 2,000 ETH from Binance, which was worth $7.63 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British publicly traded company Hamak Gold makes first-time purchase of 20 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22431</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the UK-listed company Hamak Gold announced that it had made its first purchase of 20 BTC, spending approximately ￡1.7714 million. This was part of its capital allocation and balance sheet optimization strategy. At the same time, the company entered into a strategic partnership with the FCA-regulated digital asset platform Archax in order to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22431</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: The first stage airdrop threshold for GAIA (GAIA) is 233 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22430</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per official information, Binance is set to list Gaia (GAIA). Trading will commence on July 30, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). Eligible users can utilize Alpha Points to claim a 500 GAIA token airdrop within 24 hours after the start of trading on the Alpha event page. In the first phase (the first 18 hours), users who hold at least 233 Alpha Points are eligible to claim. In the second phase (the last 6 hours), users holding at least 200 Alpha Points can participate in the second-phase airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is still in progress, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $25.16 billion worth of ETH is currently queued to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $8.92 billion worth of ETH is waiting to join.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22429</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 659,673 ETH, which is approximately worth $25.16 billion. The recent peak was 744,000 ETH. The exit waiting time is approximately 11 days and 11 hours.Meanwhile, the amount of ETH queuing to join the network is approximately 233,936 ETH, worth about $8.92 billion. The expected activation delay is about 4 days and 1 hour.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may have decided to cash out after Ethereum rebounded by more than 160% from its April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also increasing the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have increased their ETH holdings and staked the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22429</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smarter Web Company announced that it has increased its holdings by 225 Bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 2050 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22428</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the UK-listed company The Smarter Web Company announced that it has increased its holdings to 225 bitcoins, with a total holding of 2050 bitcoins. The average price for this increase is $118,080.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22428</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolut to Establish Tech Hub in Manila, Philippines</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22427</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Philippine Department of Finance announced today that the UK fintech company Revolut will set up a tech hub in Manila. (Sina Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22427</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>