<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:41:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market-listed company Bit Origin has disclosed holding approximately 70.5 million DOGE coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24243</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Bit Origin, a US-listed company (stock code: BTOG), announced that by August 11th, it possessed 70,543,745 DOGE, and the average acquisition cost was $0.2268. Additionally, it had completed a rights offering of 20 million shares of Class A common stock to support the previously announced $500 million equity acquisition and convertible note financing.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24243</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address has once again accumulated 21,000 ETH, bringing its total accumulation to approximately 86,000 ETH since June 22nd.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24242</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as monitored by EmberCN, the address &quot;0x395...500&quot; continued to make a withdrawal of 21,000 ETH from Binance within the past half hour, with a value of $90.16 million.Since June 22nd when the price of ETH was $2,280, this address has been constantly withdrawing ETH from Binance. It has now accumulated as much as 86,001 ETH ($3.78 billion) at an average price of $3,023, and currently has an unrealized gain of $120 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24242</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) saw a pre-market turnaround from a decline to an increase, planning to raise $20 billion in funding to increase its ETH holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24241</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on the market data from RockFlow, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) reversed its pre-market decline and rose, currently showing an increase of 4.95%.Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) announced today its plan to raise the fundraising scale by 20 billion US dollars in order to increase its ETH holdings. The maximum total offering price specified in the prospectus of Bitmine Immersion can reach up to 20 billion US dollars. The maximum offering price specified in the first prospectus supplement can reach up to 25 billion US dollars. And the maximum offering price specified in the newly released second prospectus supplement can reach up to 200 billion US dollars, with a total of 245 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24241</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUI Postpones Robinhood Listing After Blog Post</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24240</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the SUI Network deleted a blog post this evening that announced the listing on Robinhood or prematurely released a draft document with a confidential date.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transak has completed a $16 million strategic fundraising round, with Tether and IDG Capital co-leading the investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24239</link>
      <description>August 12th. The Web3 payment infrastructure company Transak secured $16 million in a strategic financing round. IDG Capital and Tether took the lead in this round, with Primal Capital, 1kx, Protein Capital, and Fuel Ventures also participating. Transak intends to utilize this funding to expand its stablecoin payment stack and enter new markets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24239</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrade increased its long position in ETH to approximately $66.02 million, with an average entry price of $4,309.19.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24238</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), following the reaching of $4400 on the ETH price, the contract transaction whale AguilaTrades&apos;s Hyperliquid long position is now up by $1.38 million.This evening, AguilaTrades increased its long position to 15,000 ETH (approximately $66.02 million) with an average entry price of $4,309.19.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24238</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Derivatives Trading Volume Surges by 44%, USD1 Holdings Ranked Second Globally</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24237</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on the CoinDesk Data July Exchange Review Report, Gate showcased remarkable performance in the derivatives market. The monthly derivatives trading volume reached $374 billion, showing a 44% increase from the previous month. Its derivatives market share rose by 0.55% and ranked second globally, trailing only behind Binance.In the stablecoin field, Gate became the second-largest platform in terms of USD1 holdings among centralized exchanges, second only to Binance. On July 26th, Gate hosted the Ika (IKA) Launchpad and set a record by attracting more than 2.28 billion USD1 and 6.59 million GT subscriptions, with a total value of approximately $348 million.In the DeFi field, Gate Launchpool continued to perform strongly. It launched 21 new projects in July and distributed more than $2.8 million in airdrop rewards. The highest annualized yield reached 4509%, and the total staked assets increased to $2.9 billion.In terms of the user base, Gate&apos;s global registered</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24237</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale Launches DeepBook (DEEP) and Walrus (WAL) Trust Products</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24236</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to TheBlock, Grayscale has declared the commencement of DeepBook (DEEP) and Walrus (WAL) trust products, thereby offering investors the opportunity to gain exposure to the Sui ecosystem protocol tokens DEEP and WAL.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24236</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brad: Willing to act in accordance with Secretary Yellen&apos;s wishes, or accept the position of Fed Chair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24235</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the former president of the St. Louis Fed, Bullard, stated that (with regard to the possibility of taking over the position of Fed Chair). He had a conversation with Yellen last week and would be willing to act at the discretion of the U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen. If the Fed&apos;s goal is a stable low inflation rate and the Fed&apos;s independence is respected, he would be inclined to accept the position of Fed Chair. (Kyi)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24235</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CME FedWatch: Probability of September Rate Cut Rises to 91.8%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24234</link>
      <description>August 12th. Based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, following the release of the CPI data, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September has increased to 91.8%, while the probability of no rate change stands at 8.2% (prior to the CPI release, the probability of a September rate cut was 82.5%).The probability of the Fed maintaining rates in October is 2.2%, with a combined 25-basis-point rate cut probability at 31% and a combined 50-basis-point rate cut probability at 66.7%.The timings of the next two FOMC meetings are September 17th and October 29th. Traders have raised their wagers on a Fed rate cut in September and continue to bet that the Fed will cut rates in both September and December.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24234</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>