<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:30:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Brother Big Bro」 Huang Licheng holds a total of approximately $150 million worth of ETH, HYPE, BTC, and PUMP long positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28020</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight, &quot;Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng currently holds long positions in BTC, ETH, PUMP, and HYPE. The details are as follows:- He has a 25x long position in ETH with a value of $125 million. The unrealized loss is $1.8 million, and the entry price is $4,363.64, while the liquidation price is $3,211.- He has a 10x long position in HYPE with a value of $16 million and an unrealized profit of approximately $600,000.- He has a 40x long position in BTC with a value of $7.7 million and an unrealized profit of about $30,000.- He has a 5x long position in PUMP with a value of $4.66 million and an unrealized loss of about $100,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28020</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Breaks $111,000, Up 0.3% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28019</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin exceeded $111,000, witnessing a 24-hour increase of 0.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28019</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Singapore Lost SGD 456 Million in the First Half of the Year Due to Scams, with Cryptocurrency-Related Scams Accounting for 18%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28018</link>
      <description>September 7th – The data on fraud and cybercrime in the first half of 2025 was released by the Singapore Police Force. The total fraud losses amounted to approximately 456 million Singapore dollars, which was a reduction of about 66 million Singapore dollars compared to last year. There were 22,476 cases of fraud and cybercrime, representing a 21.5% decrease from the same period last year when there were 28,625 cases. Losses from cryptocurrency-related scams accounted for nearly 18% of the total losses, reaching 81.6 million Singapore dollars, mainly involving USDT, Bitcoin, and Ethereum. The Anti-Scam Center managed to recover 56.7 million Singapore dollars, including 17 million Singapore dollars in cryptocurrency. In addition, it jointly averted a potential loss of another 179 million Singapore dollars in cooperation with its partners.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28018</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: Grok Imagine is expected to release a major update in a few weeks, with testing expected to conclude by next spring.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28017</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Musk tweeted that given that Grok Imagine is still in the early stage of testing, the current testing performance is not bad. A major update will be rolled out in a few weeks, and the testing is expected to be completed in spring next year.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 08:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28017</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paxos is competing to become the issuer of the USDH stablecoin under HyperLiquid, committing to a partial buyback of HYPE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28016</link>
      <description>September 7th: The stablecoin issuer Paxos has put forward a proposal titled &quot;Paxos-Supported USDH Issuance,&quot; vying to become the issuer of HyperLiquid&apos;s stablecoin USDH. Paxos has declared that if selected as the USDH issuer, they will carry out a revenue-sharing plan. Paxos will allocate 95% of the interest from the USDH-backed reserve to repurchase HYPE and redistribute it to the ecosystem plan, partners, and users.Earlier on September 5th, Hyperliquid announced the release of the token symbol USDH for stablecoin issuance. Currently, the USDH trading pair symbol held by the Hyperliquid protocol will be released through a transparent on-chain process via validator voting. After the next network upgrade, validators will be able to vote on whether to permit a specific user address to purchase the USDH symbol. The voting process will occur entirely on-chain and be completed through Hyperliquid L1 transactions, similar to the delisting voting process. Teams that are in</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 07:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Yoshihide Suga has decided to resign</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28015</link>
      <description>September 7th: As reported by NHK, Japan&apos;s public broadcaster, Prime Minister Yoshihide Suga has made a decision to step down from his position. He stated that it was due to &quot;reluctance to cause division within the party.&quot; This decision comes ahead of the Liberal Democratic Party&apos;s decision regarding whether to hold an extraordinary presidential election on the 8th. Suga is scheduled to hold a press conference on this matter at 5 p.m. Beijing time.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 07:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28015</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X Layer On-Chain Meme Coin DOGSHIT Surpasses $37 Million Market Cap, 24-hour Growth 21.2%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28014</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to the market data of X Layer from X Layer, the on-chain Meme coin DOGSHIT on X Layer has exceeded a market capitalization of 37 million USD. It has a 24-hour increase of 21.2% and a 24-hour trading volume of 5.17 million USD. In addition, other on-chain Meme coins on X Layer have also seen increases. For example, XDOG has a 24-hour increase of 21% and is currently valued at 11.7 million USD; XPe has a 24-hour increase of 60% and is currently valued at 6 million USD; XFROG has a 24-hour increase of 960% and is currently valued at 3 million USD.BlockBeats reminds users that many Meme coins lack practical use cases. Some tokens have a low market capitalization and their prices are highly volatile. Therefore, investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 07:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28014</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutional Ethereum Holdings Overview: Bitmine&apos;s Holdings Value Surpasses $8 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28013</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on strategicethreserve data, the following treasury companies and institutions with significant changes in Ethereum holdings over the past 30 days are as follows:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) took the first place, currently holding 1.87 million ETH, with a value of approximately $8 billion, and experiencing a 124.1% increase in holdings over the past 30 days;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) ranked second, currently holding 837,000 ETH, valued at approximately $3.59 billion, with a 60.4% increase in holdings in the past 30 days;The Ether Machine (ETHM) ranked third, currently holding 495,000 ETH, valued at approximately $2.12 billion, with a 43.4% increase in holdings in the past 30 days;Ethereum Foundation ranked fourth, holding 22,960 ETH, valued at approximately $984 million, with a 1.3% decrease in holdings in the past 30 days;ETHZilla (ETHZ) ranked eighth, holding 10,220 ETH, valued at approximately $438 million, with a 24.4% increase in holdings in the pas</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 07:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28013</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: ETH Pullback with Incomplete Shakeout, Max Pain Range $2425-$2970</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28012</link>
      <description>On September 7th, on-chain data analyst Murphy released an analysis of ETH UTXO Distribution. As can be seen from the chart, the UTXO distribution of ETH shows an inverted F pattern. There is a significant accumulation at the lower and middle levels, while it is scarce at the higher levels. The bottom range from $49 to $396, after experiencing a harsh 8-year market, still holds 13.5% of the circulating supply to this day. The most stacked range is from $2425 to $2970, holding 23% of the circulating supply and serving as the strongest support level of ETH.With the current price of $4,257 as the center point, there is currently 7.52% of the chips above. In the -20% price range (that is, from $3,405 to $4,257), there is only 10.1%. This indicates that ETH has not experienced sufficient turnover during the rapid surge and retracement. Therefore, when the price of ETH continues to rise, although there are few trapped chips above, the unrealized profits of the chips at the lower levels are</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 07:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28012</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top ENA holder on Hyperliquid has opened a 10x ETH short position, with a value of approximately $12.85 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28011</link>
      <description>On September 7th, based on the monitoring of HyperInsight, the largest holder address of ENA on Hyperliquid (&quot;0x6b7...c5e9c&quot;) has taken a 5x long position on ENA and a 10x short position on ETH simultaneously. The current positions are as follows:A 5x long position in ENA with a position value of approximately $36 million, an average entry price of $0.6804, a liquidation price of $0.50, and an unrealized profit of $2.78 million.A 10x short position in ETH with a position value of approximately $12.85 million, an average entry price of $4,314, a liquidation price of $7,669, and an unrealized profit of $93,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 06:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28011</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>