<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is offering the ChatGPT Enterprise version service to all US federal government agencies.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23437</link>
      <description>August 6th. According to Fox News, the U.S. General Services Administration (GSA) has announced a partnership with OpenAI today. This partnership will provide the ChatGPT Enterprise service to all federal agencies. It is a key part of the Trump administration&apos;s Artificial Intelligence Action Plan, which aims to improve the efficiency of government work. Federal agency employees will be provided with customized training resources and guided learning programs.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23437</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A trader bought $29,000 worth of TROLL 3 months ago and made a profit of $3.78 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23436</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the trader &quot;frostx.sol&quot; spent $29,000 to purchase 21.91 million TROLL tokens three months ago. Subsequently, they sold 2.55 million TROLL tokens for $507,000. At present, they still hold 18.36 million TROLL tokens, which are worth $3.73 million.With the recent surge of TROLL, their position has appreciated by nearly 1,300 times, resulting in a profit of $3.78 million.BlockBeats previously reported that possibly due to the influence of Pump.fun&apos;s official &quot;milk&quot; campaign, various meme coins have witnessed significant gains recently. On July 23rd, Pump.fun&apos;s official Twitter account posted an image containing several Pump.fun ecosystem meme coins, including TROLL.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23436</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Listed Company Cosmos Health Raises $300 Million in Funding, Will Establish Ethereum Reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23434</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the publicly traded company Cosmos Health (Nasdaq: COSM) entered into a securities purchase agreement with U.S. institutional investors, securing up to $3 billion in senior secured convertible note financing. Under the agreement, the company will allocate 72.5% of the net proceeds from the financing to establish an Ethereum reserve, while the remaining funds will be designated for working capital and business development.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opening: Cryptocurrency Stocks Experience Mixed Performance, &apos;BNB Version of MicroStrategy&apos; BNC Soars 13%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23435</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to RockFlow market data, at the opening of the US stock market, the Dow increased by 0.19%, the S&amp;P 500 rose by 0.15%, and the Nasdaq went up by 0.19%. Cryptocurrency stocks had a mixed performance, including:- &quot;BNB Version of MicroStrategy&quot; CEA Industries (BNC) soared by 13% as it completed a $500 million private placement led by YZi Labs on August 5th to support its BNB-focused treasury strategy.- &quot;ETH Version of MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink (SBET) dropped by 5.7%.- &quot;TON Version of MicroStrategy&quot; Verb Technology (VERB) surged by 14.62%.- MicroStrategy (MSTR) rose by 0.24%.- Coinbase (COIN) decreased by 0.1%.- Circle (CRCL) rose by 0.32%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23435</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Lee: Today&apos;s ETH is like 2017&apos;s Bitcoin, and there will be regrets for those who do not bet on it at this moment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23433</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Thomas Lee, the chairman of the board of BitMine (BMNR), once again expressed his bullish view on Ethereum. He said, &quot;Many people wish they had doubled down on Bitcoin in 2017 when the price was below $1,000. Now, the price is $114,000. Today&apos;s Ethereum will experience a similar moment in 2025.&quot;Thomas Lee stated yesterday, &quot;BMNR currently holds 833,133 ETH, which is worth $3 billion. This makes it the world&apos;s largest ETH treasury and the world&apos;s third-largest cryptocurrency treasury. As Wall Street financializes blockchain and AI drives the tokenization of robotic assets, ETH will still be one of the biggest macro trends in the next 10 to 15 years.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23433</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philippines Cuts Off Access to Ten Overseas Cryptocurrency Exchanges</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23432</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per Decrypt&apos;s report, the Philippine Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) took action today by instructing major internet service providers to block access to ten overseas cryptocurrency exchanges, such as OKX, MEXC, Bybit, KuCoin, Bitget, Kraken, CoinEx, Phemex, BitMart, and Poloniex.Previously, the Philippine regulatory body had warned that cryptocurrency platforms were violating local regulations by providing services to Philippine residents without obtaining licenses and registrations. According to a new regulation that came into effect in June of this year, cryptocurrency service providers must register as local companies in the Philippines and hold a minimum paid-up capital of at least $1.8 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale transfers 8062 ETH to Coinbase Prime, with a total value of approximately $29 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23430</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to Arkham Monitoring, 2 minutes ago, Grayscale transferred 8062 ETH to Coinbase Prime, with a total value of around $29 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company Empery Digital increases its BTC holdings by acquiring an additional 88 BTC, surpassing a total holding of 4,000 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23431</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per Businesswire, the US-listed company Empery Digital (formerly Volcon) augmented its holdings by 88 BTC. Currently, its total holding amounts to 4,000.85 BTC. The cost involved is approximately $470 million, and the average acquisition price per BTC is $117,552.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23431</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Kashkari: Two rate cuts this year still seems appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23429</link>
      <description>August 6: Fed&apos;s Kashkari stated that the economy is decelerating and the Fed needs to respond to this economic slowdown. It may still be appropriate to adjust the policy rate in the short term. The answer regarding the inflation issue may take some time to become known, while the data on the economic slowdown is clear. Two rate cuts this year still seem to be appropriate. However, if inflation rises due to tariffs, the Fed may pause rate cuts or even raise rates. Adjusting the rate policy may be better than waiting. Unemployment rate data is of great importance, but the Fed is aware that this data may be revised. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23429</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Apple to Commit to $100 Billion U.S. Investment, Trump to Issue Statement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23428</link>
      <description>August 6th, in the White House, US: Apple (AAPL.O) is going to launch a new US manufacturing plan and enhance its US investment commitment by 100 billion dollars. President Trump will issue a statement regarding Apple today. (FX168)Previously, the White House announced that US President Trump will make a &quot;statement&quot; in the Oval Office at 4:30 pm Eastern Time on Wednesday (4:30 am Beijing Time the following day).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23428</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>