<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:40:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ETH &quot;Pump King&quot; Tom Lee&apos;s Recent Performance: Three Times Right on the Money, Predicts End-of-Year Target Price of $10,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26680</link>
      <description>August 28th. Tom Lee, as the newly appointed Chairman of the Board of BitMine, which is the first Ethereum treasury company, has been frequently expressing bullish views on ETH recently and successfully predicted three times in August:During the market pullback on August 19th, Tom Lee mentioned that a pullback to the range of $4075 to $4150 was healthy, and the market subsequently witnessed a rebound;On August 20th, prior to the dovish speech by the Fed Chairman Powell, Tom Lee forecasted that the market would rise due to the speech. After that, Ethereum briefly exceeded $4900;On August 26th, during another market pullback, Tom Lee predicted that ETH would bottom out in the next few hours. Once again, his prediction came true as ETH saw a rebound.In an interview on August 27th, Tom Lee made his latest prediction, stating that ETH will rise to $5500 in the coming weeks. The year-end target price is $10,000 to $12,000, and it will reach $60,000 within five years.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX will list XPL for pre-trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26679</link>
      <description>On August 28th, OKX will commence pre-trading for XPL. The pre-trading of XPL/USDT will open on August 28, 2025, at 7:00 PM (US time).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26679</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday&apos;s Sniper XPL Hedge Whale Main Address saw another movement, going long again at $0.67.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26678</link>
      <description>On August 28th, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), yesterday, the main operating address 0xb9c...6801e, which snatched the XPL hedging whale and made a profit of over $16 million on Hyperliquid, showed unusual behavior again. Early this morning, it dispersed 27.1 million USDC to 11 addresses and once again opened a 1x XPL long position worth $18.14 million, with a cumulative unrealized profit of $1.148 million. It seems that this whale has not given up &quot;manipulating&quot; the XPL price. The trading price of XPL on Hyperliquid briefly exceeded $0.8 and then fell back, and it is now trading at $0.72, with a 26% premium over the $0.571 on Binance.The address 0xb9c...6801, in cooperation with multiple whales yesterday, boosted the price to liquidate short positions and earned a total of between $38 million and $46.1 million in just one hour. The address 0xb9c...6801e, as the main address, had been holding</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26678</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has now launched Blum (BLUM), with an airdrop threshold of 230 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26677</link>
      <description>August 28th. Binance Alpha has now commenced the launch of Blum (BLUM). Users who hold at least 230 Alpha Points are eligible to claim a 700 BLUM token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In the event that the event has not ended, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26677</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institution today staked 1.5 million SOL tokens, worth $318.77 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26676</link>
      <description>August 28th. As per OnchainLens, a whale or institution has made a staking of 1.5 million SOL today, which is valued at 3.1877 billion US dollars.During the past 8 days, this whale or institution has staked a cumulative total of 2.5 million SOL, amounting to 5.058 billion US dollars. The SOL was withdrawn from Binance.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26676</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Who Staked Solana for Four Years Deposits Around 110,000 SOL to Binance, Worth $23.51 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26675</link>
      <description>August 28th. Based on OnchainLens monitoring, a whale unbonded 110,036 SOL 22 days ago, which was worth $23.51 million. And it was deposited into Binance 43 minutes ago.This whale had been staking the SOL holdings for four years. In the past 5 months, it had unbonded a total of 315,108 SOL, with a value of $53.59 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26675</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT: No Longer Providing Assistance to XRP Community, as It Has Not Brought Any Value to the Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26674</link>
      <description>On August 28th, &quot;On-chain Detective&quot; ZachXBT stated in a post that he had previously been involved in assisting with a theft incident triggered by an XRP ledger problem. However, he will no longer offer any assistance to the XRP community. ZachXBT holds the view that the XRP community has not brought any value to the industry apart from providing exit liquidity for insiders and is therefore not worthy of support. He further stated that this perspective also extends to projects such as Cardano (ADA), Pulsechain, and Hedera.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26674</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiao Feng: Crypto ETF is good, but Digital Asset Treasury is better</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26673</link>
      <description>August 28th. Xiao Feng, the Chairman and CEO of HashKey Group, declared today during Bitcoin Asia 2025 that the Digital Asset Treasury (DAT) might be the optimal approach for crypto assets to move off-chain.Xiao Feng expounded on the four core merits of DAT in contrast to ETF:Firstly, superior liquidity. The ETF creation and redemption processes consume more time, while DAT facilitates the transfer of assets more conveniently and efficiently for investors.Secondly, higher price elasticity. DAT has a greater market value fluctuation and risk isolation feature, providing more arbitrage tools for institutions.Thirdly, a more reasonable leverage design. DAT companies offer leveraged financing structures, which, compared to the price growth of cryptocurrencies themselves, can bring higher premiums to investors.Fourthly, DAT has a built-in price protection mechanism. When the stock price drops by more than the net asset value held by the company, investors have the opportunity to p</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: BTC Struggles to Break Through the Mega Whale Accumulation Zone of $93k to $118k, the Lower Support Gap Has Been Filled</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26672</link>
      <description>On August 28th, on-chain data analyst Murphy released a market chip structure analysis. One month ago, due to the rapid surge of BTC, there was almost no trading volume in the price range of $112,000 to $114,000, resulting in a gap in the chip structure (URPD). According to common experience, all &quot;gaps&quot; on URPD will be filled.One month later, as of August 27th, the gap between $112,000 and $114,000 has been completely filled, connecting the original high and low chip accumulation zones to form a large chip accumulation zone ranging from $93,000 to $118,000. Within this range, 5.59 million BTC have been accumulated. This means that from November 20, 2024, to the present, in a short period of 9 months, more than 5 million BTC have been bought in this price range, accounting for 28% of the total circulation. If we exclude chips that are lost or held in long-term &quot;HODL&quot; like Satoshi Nakamoto&apos;s holdings, this proportion is even higher.If there are no sudden &quot;black swan&quot; events, it will</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB Executive Board Member Lane Warns: Federal Reserve Independence Being Eroded, Market Trust May Be Affected</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26671</link>
      <description>August 28: The Executive Board member of the European Central Bank and the Governor of the Bank of Finland, Rehn, warned on Thursday in a speech that for the first time in decades, the independence of the Federal Reserve is facing a &quot;major&quot; challenge, posing &quot;significant&quot; risks to the market and the economy. Rehn said: &quot;Since the containment of double-digit inflation in the 1980s, the independence of the Federal Reserve has been regarded as an inviolable principle - but now this principle is being eroded. When the central bank is trusted, the public, businesses, and financial markets all believe that it will uphold price stability. This trust anchors inflation expectations.&quot; Rehn stated that the credibility brought by independence has enhanced the effectiveness of monetary policy, meaning that the central bank does not need to make &quot;drastic&quot; responses to temporary economic fluctuations. (CNBC)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>