<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:00:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 06:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>J.P. Morgan: Expects the Fed to Cut Interest Rates by 25 Basis Points in September and December</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26297</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Morgan Stanley anticipates that the Fed will reduce interest rates by 25 basis points in September and December respectively (previously it was predicted that there would be no rate cuts until 2025). (Financial Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26297</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Layer Sports Prediction App Football.Fun Surpasses $2 Million in Total Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26295</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per Dune Analytics, the Football.Fun, a sports prediction app based on the Base chain and featuring a reward mechanism, currently has a total of 11,904 active user wallet addresses. The platform has a total value locked (TVL) of 10.54 million USD and a total revenue of 2.02 million USD.According to the data on the official website, the total market value of Football.Fun&apos;s player token is currently 17.08 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26295</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Alttown (TOWN), and users holding at least 200 Alpha Points can claim an airdrop of 1,600 TOWN tokens.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26296</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to official channels, Binance Alpha is the inaugural platform to list Alttown (TOWN). Alpha trading is set to commence on August 26, 2025, at 3:00 PM (UTC+8).After the trading begins, users holding at least 200 Alpha points will be eligible to claim an airdrop of 1,600 TOWN tokens. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.To claim the airdrop, 15 Alpha points will be deducted. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Worth of ETH Long Position Added to Leveraged Trade」 Whale Whale Whale Once Again Increasing ETH Position, Currently Holding 536.12 ETH Long</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26293</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;125k USD Long Liquidation on ETH&quot; whale has increased their remaining 95k USD collateral. Now, the two addresses hold a total of 536.12 ETH (equivalent to 2.37 million USD), with an unrealized loss of 69k USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26293</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economist: Federal Reserve Subjected to Trump&apos;s &quot;Full-Scale Assault,&quot; Its Independence Is a Key Factor in Maintaining the Safe Haven Status of US Treasury Bonds and the Dollar</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26294</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Saul Eslake, who was formerly the chief economist of Merrill Lynch in Australia, stated that the dismissal of Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard signaled a clear intensification of White House intervention following President Trump&apos;s efforts to reshape the US federal government and its institutions. He further added that loyalty appears to be a standard for continuing to hold high public office. The independence of the Federal Reserve is a crucial factor in maintaining the safe haven status of US Treasuries and the US dollar. The Federal Reserve is now facing full-fledged attacks, and this will not lead to any favorable outcomes. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26294</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum drops below $4300, the mainstream CEX liquidation pressure will reach $922 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26292</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on Coinglass data, if Ethereum falls below $4300, the cumulative long liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will reach 922 million.Conversely, if Ethereum breaks through $4600, the cumulative short liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will reach 1.986 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to neighboring liquidation clusters, that is, strength. Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will have a more intense reaction due to a liquidity avalanche when it reaches that level.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26292</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has deposited $7.49 million into HyperLiquid, shorted ETH and HYPE, and simultaneously bought ETH and HYPE spot.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26291</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, within the past 40 minutes, a whale transferred 7.49 million USDC into HyperLiquid. Subsequently, it opened short positions for ETH (with a leverage of 20x) and HYPE (with a leverage of 10x). Additionally, it purchased ETH and HYPE on the spot market.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26291</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of Powell being removed as Fed Chair this year on Polymarket has decreased to 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26290</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on the data from the official website, the probability on Polymarket that &quot;Powell will be removed as the Federal Reserve Chair by 2025&quot; has decreased to 10%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26290</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol: AUBRAI TGE Scheduled for August 27</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26289</link>
      <description>On August 26th, Bio Protocol declared that the first BioAgent Launch project, Aubrai (AUBRAI), will not commence the TGE immediately after the subscription ends. Instead, it will start trading 24 hours later, which is on Wednesday, August 27th. According to the official website, Aubrai has received 11.6 times oversubscription.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26289</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Solana Launchpad Market Share in Last 24 Hours: pump.fun, Letsbonk, Meteora DBC in Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26288</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours, in the Solana launchpad market share ranking, pump.fun took the first place with 73.3%, Letsbonk came in second with 6.95%, and Meteora DBC ranked third with 5.48%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>