<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:58:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Metavesco announced the purchase of 28 ETH at an average price of $3,595.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22168</link>
      <description>July 28th. As per the report in businessinsider, the diversified holding public company Metavesco, Inc. made an announcement today. In a tactical expansion of its digital asset strategy, the company purchased 28 Ethereum (ETH) with an average price of $3,595. While Bitcoin remains the company&apos;s long-term core reserve asset, this additional purchase of Ethereum is part of a strategic move considering the increased institutional adoption and a favorable macro environment.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered&apos;s Zodia Markets Completes $18.25M Series A Funding Round, with Participation from Circle Ventures</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22167</link>
      <description>July 28th. According to official channels, Zodia Markets, a cryptocurrency trading firm that is part of Standard Chartered (STAN), declared the accomplishment of a $18.25 million Series A funding round. This round was spearheaded by Pharsalus Capital, and it saw the participation of Circle Ventures, The Operating Group, XVC Tech, Token Bay Capital, Human Capital, and other strategic investors.As per a press release issued on Monday, the Series A funding will be employed to facilitate Zodia&apos;s international expansion endeavors and to continuously develop its stablecoin payment services.CEO Usman Ahmad stated in the announcement that Zodia is targeting financial institutions and is offering them a combination of wholesale financing and continuous digital asset trading in order to &quot;reimagine traditional forex capital flows through cross-border real-time stablecoin settlements.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22167</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「SOL-native MicroStrategy」 Upexi Plans to Sell Up to $5 Billion in Common Stock to Advance SOL Reserve Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22166</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Upexi, Inc., a brand operator concentrating on consumer product development, manufacturing, and distribution, and also engaging in the cryptocurrency field (with a Nasdaq stock code: UPXI), announced today that it has reached an equity financing agreement with A.G.P./Alliance Global Partners. According to the agreement, Upexi has the autonomy to decide to sell up to $500 million of the company&apos;s common stock, subject to certain restrictions and closing conditions. This equity financing does not entail the payment of a commitment fee, and the proceeds will be utilized for general corporate purposes and to promote its Solana (SOL) reserve strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22166</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the news of a $500 million private placement establishing the BNB Treasury, pre-market trading of the VAPE stock surged by 452.11%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22164</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on rockflow data, perhaps influenced by the news of a $500 million private placement for the establishment of a BNB treasury, the US stock CEA Industries (VAPE) witnessed a remarkable 452.11% surge in pre-market trading and reached $49.It is noteworthy that the company&apos;s stock closed at just $8.88 last Friday, with a market capitalization of only $7.4669 million.BlockBeats had previously reported that CEA Industries and 10X Capital, with the backing of YZi Labs, announced a $500 million private placement to establish the world&apos;s largest publicly traded BNB financial company.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22164</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company Hyperion DeFi has announced the addition of 108,594 HYPE tokens to its holdings.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22165</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to globenewswire, Hyperion DeFi (NASDAQ: HYPD) declared that it has increased its holdings by 108,594 HYPE tokens, resulting in a total of 1,535,772 HYPE tokens in its possession. The average acquisition cost per token is $36.14. This additional purchase is intended to be ready to participate in the iHYPE (Institutional HYPE) liquidity staking pool on the Kinetiq platform.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22165</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mill City Ventures III, Ltd. has announced a $450 million private fundraising to launch the SUI Treasury Strategy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22162</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to stocktitan, the non-bank lending institution and financial company Mill City Ventures III, Ltd. (NASDAQ:MCVT) announced that it had entered into a securities purchase agreement to invest in public equity through a private placement at a price of $5.42 per share. It would purchase and sell 83,025,830 shares of common stock, with expected total proceeds of approximately $450 million (excluding placement agent fees and other offering expenses). The hedge fund Karatage was acting as the lead investor, and the Sui Foundation was also providing a matching investment. The offering was expected to close around July 31, 2025. The company planned to use approximately 98% of the net proceeds from the private placement to acquire SUI, the native token of the Sui blockchain, and approximately 2% of the net proceeds to support its short-term lending business. SUI would serve as the company&apos;s primary financial reserve asset.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22162</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEA Industries and 10X Capital, with the support of YZiLabs, have announced a $5 billion private fundraising to establish the BNB Strategic Reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22163</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the report from streetinsider, CEA Industries (NASDAQ: VAPE) and 10X Capital announced a $500 million private placement, with the support of YZi Labs, to establish the world&apos;s largest publicly traded BNB financial company. This financing is composed of two parts:· Common Stock PIPE Financing: A total of $500 million (including $4 billion in cash and $1 billion worth of cryptocurrency).· Warrant Exercise: If fully exercised, an additional $750 million in cash financing is expected to be raised.Officials stated that this PIPE received oversubscription from more than 140 institutions worldwide. The key participating institutions include: YZi Labs, Pantera Capital, Arche Capital, GSR, Borderless, Arrington Capital, Blockchain.com, Hypersphere Capital, Kenetic, dao5, Protocol Ventures, Reciprocal Ventures, G-20 Group, Three Point Capital, Propel Horizon, Exinity, Winone, Nano Labs, etc.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22163</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market News: MARA Holdings Successfully Raised $950 Million to Purchase More Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22161</link>
      <description>On July 28th. According to market information, the US-listed mining company MARA Holdings has managed to raise $950 million by means of 0% convertible bonds in order to purchase a greater amount of Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22161</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US publicly traded company Immutable Holdings announced that it holds over 48 million HBAR tokens.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22160</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per official channels, the publicly traded blockchain holding company Immutable Holdings Inc. (with the Canada Cboe code: HOLD) announced a set of strategic measures today. These include advancing its HBAR corporate treasury management strategy and realigning the executive team to facilitate business growth.The company stated that Immutable started formulating a digital asset treasury management strategy centered around the Hedera network&apos;s native cryptocurrency HBAR in 2025. This plan will be implemented through its wholly-owned subsidiary, Immutable Asset Management LLC (IAM). As of the date of this press release, IAM currently possesses over 48 million HBAR and will continue to manage this position in accordance with fund priorities and market conditions. It may potentially increase its HBAR holdings or acquire other digital assets in the future.The company views HBAR as a high-quality digital asset with long-term prospects. It takes advantage of the Hedera netw</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy did not increase its BTC holdings last week.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22159</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on market information, the US-listed company Strategy did not augment its holdings of BTC from July 21st to July 27th.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22159</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>