<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:15:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 11,370 ETH from Coinbase, approximately $40 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22274</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Arkham Monitoring, a whale has just made a withdrawal of 11,370 ETH from Coinbase (approximately $40 million), with an average price of $3,811. In the past hour, it has already achieved a profit of $400,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22274</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit will list the OMNI/KRW trading pair</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22273</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, Upbit is going to list the OMNI/KRW trading pair.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22273</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Treasury Protocol ETH Strategy Completes Over $46 Million Fundraising</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22271</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as reported by The Block, the ETH Strategy treasury accumulation protocol, which is designed to offer Ethereum leverage exposure, managed to raise 12,342 Ethereum (approximately $46.5 million) during a pre-launch fundraising round.This fundraising round was completed through three distinct channels, with the aim of attracting different types of investors. In the private sale phase, 6,900 Ethereum was raised. The public sale raised 1,242 Ethereum. Additionally, 4,200 Ethereum was obtained through redeemable warrants. All investment categories were issued STRAT tokens at varying prices, and investors are required to adhere to a four-month lock-up period, followed by a two-month linear release starting from the token generation event.ETH Strategy intends to utilize 11,817 of the Ethereum for core protocol operations, such as Ethereum staking and protocol liquidity provision. The remaining 525 Ethereum will be allocated for protocol development and growth activities, cove</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22271</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UAE bank RAKBANK partners with Bitpanda to offer cryptocurrency services to retail investors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22272</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per CoinDesk, RAKBANK, which is one of the UAE&apos;s oldest banks, has entered into a partnership with the cryptocurrency platform Bitpanda. This makes RAKBANK the first traditional bank in the UAE to provide cryptocurrency services to retail customers. Now, users are able to buy, sell, and exchange cryptocurrencies through RAKBANK&apos;s mobile banking app. The transactions are settled directly in Emirati Dirham (AED), thereby avoiding the exchange rate fees that would be incurred if USD or EUR were used for transactions. This service is made possible through Bitpanda&apos;s Dubai-regulated subsidiary, Bitpanda Broker MENA DMCC. The funds are deducted directly from users&apos; savings or current accounts, eliminating the need to transfer funds to a third-party cryptocurrency exchange.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha announces two-stage threshold for claiming the TREE airdrop: 233 points and 200 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22270</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per official information, Binance Alpha is set to be the first platform to list Treehouse (TREE). Trading will commence on July 29, 2025, at 20:00 (UTC+8).Qualified Binance users can utilize Binance Alpha Points to claim a 100 TREE token airdrop on the Alpha event page within 24 hours after the start of trading. The Binance Alpha airdrop will be distributed in two stages:Stage 1 (first 18 hours): Users possessing at least 233 Alpha Points are eligible to claim the airdrop.Stage 2 (last 6 hours): Users holding at least 200 Alpha Points can participate in the second-stage airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points per hour.Claiming the airdrop will require the expenditure of 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a forfeiture.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22270</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Reserve Concept Stock Market Pre-market Overall Down, VAPE Down 2.75%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22269</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to the market data of Rockflow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), there was a general decline in the pre-market trading of US stock cryptocurrency reserve concept stocks. The following are Ethereum reserve concept stocks:SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) decreased by 0.6% and is currently at $20.8;BTCS Inc (BTCS.US) decreased by 0.97% and is currently at $5.11;Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) decreased by 9.94% and is currently at $31.62;GameSquare (GAME.US) decreased by 0.89% and is currently at $1.11;Bit Digital (BTBT.US) decreased by 0.33% and is currently at $2.99.BNB reserve concept stocks:CEA Industries (VAPE) decreased by 2.75% and is priced at $56;Windtree (WINT) decreased by 1.09% and is priced at $0.91.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22269</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches Coin Purchase Discount through Savings.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22268</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, Binance Savings has declared the launch of a high-yield structured savings product known as Discount Buy. This offers investors an innovative crypto asset allocation solution. Users will get the chance to purchase cryptocurrency at a price that is lower than the market price or receive a fixed annual interest rate reward based on market trends.This product is suitable for users who intend to buy cryptocurrency (such as BTC, ETH) in the future at a price lower than the current price. It can automatically set the purchase price and obtain potential gains without the need to constantly keep an eye on market dynamics.When subscribing to the Discount Buy, users need to set several key parameters: the target purchase price, the knock-in price, the annual percentage rate (APR), and the settlement date.On the settlement date, one of the following three results will be triggered based on the settlement price: 100% of the principal will be use</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22268</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to List ZRC and ESPORTS Perpetual Futures Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22267</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, Binance is set to commence ZRC and ESPORTS perpetual contract trading.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22267</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address withdrew 20 million EDU from Binance, worth approximately $2.82 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22266</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet withdrew 20 million EDU from Binance, which was approximately worth $2.82 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22266</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares is launching a zero management fee SEI ETP in Europe, offering a 2% staking reward.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22265</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the report by CoinDesk, the cryptocurrency asset management firm CoinShares has introduced a new Exchange-Traded Product (ETP). This ETP enables investors to invest in SEI with zero management fees and offers a staking yield of 2%. The product, bearing the trading symbol CSEI, will be listed and available for trading on the SIX Swiss Exchange. It is the first investment instrument that provides investors with direct access to SEI in a regulated manner.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22265</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>