<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 2.43 million USDC into HyperLiquid, went long with 3x leverage, and pumped the price.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27656</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale deposited 2.43 million USDC into HyperLiquid and initiated a 3x leveraged PUMP long position.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland received 10 million WLFI tokens 2 hours ago, or may have joined the liquidity pool.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27654</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), Cumberland DRW may have entered the ranks of WLFI liquidity providers. It received 10 million WLFI tokens from BitGo 2 hours ago, with a value of approximately $2.05 million. In the past 24 hours, it has had relatively frequent small on-chain transactions. Additionally, Cumberland is also one of the liquidity providers for the TRUMP token.If this is true, WLFI now has liquidity providers including DWF, Jump, and Cumberland.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27654</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Founder Dr. Han: The Crypto Market Enters a New Stage of &quot;Dual-Engine Drive with CEX and DEX&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27655</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the founder and CEO of Gate, Dr. Han, delivered a keynote speech at the WebX 2025 Summit in Tokyo. He systematically expounded on the key roles of centralized exchanges (CEX) and decentralized exchanges (DEX) in promoting the mass adoption of Web3. Dr. Han pointed out that the long-term trend of user growth, the dual-track evolution of the market structure, and the trade-off between security and compliance jointly shape the new landscape where &quot;CEX serves as the global capital gateway and DEX acts as the on-chain finance and innovation engine.&quot;Dr. Han cited data showing that the global crypto user base has approached 700 million, accounting for 10% of the global population. The total crypto market capitalization is $3.02 trillion, officially ranking as the world&apos;s fourth-largest asset. He predicted that by 2030, crypto assets are expected to rise to $41.8 trillion, second only to gold. In terms of trading patterns, DEX has captured 23% of the spot trading volume, wh</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27655</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA is planning to launch a new AI chip in the Chinese market, with the price potentially being double that of the H20</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27653</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Market News: NVIDIA (NVDA.O) intends to introduce a new artificial intelligence chip into the Chinese market. If approved, the price might be twice that of the H20 chip. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27653</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI experienced a brief dip reaching $0.1776, hitting a new all-time low</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27652</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to HTX market data, WLFI saw a short-term decline to $0.1776 and is currently trading at $0.1834, setting a new all-time low.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27652</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Union (U), with a points threshold of 220.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27651</link>
      <description>September 4th. Binance Alpha will list Union (U), and trading on Alpha will commence on September 4, 2025, at 17:00 (UTC+8). Users who hold at least 220 Alpha points can claim a 2,700 U token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27651</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preview: August&apos;s &quot;Mini Non-Farm&quot; ADP Employment and Initial Jobless Claims for the Week will be announced tonight</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27650</link>
      <description>September 4th: The US August ADP Nonfarm Employment is scheduled to be announced this evening at 20:15. The previous value was 104,000 and the expected value is 65,000. Meanwhile, the US Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending August 30th will be announced at 20:30. The previous value was 229,000 and the expected value is 230,000. Additionally, the US August Unemployment Rate and August Seasonally Adjusted Nonfarm Employment will be disclosed tomorrow evening at 20:30.Previously, analysts have pointed out that the current labor market data is attracting much more attention than usual. Powell has made this week&apos;s nonfarm data particularly significant. If the labor market data fails to meet expectations, it will greatly boost the expectations of rate cuts and may even reawaken market expectations for a 50-basis-point rate cut either once or multiple times. Powell emphasized the downside risks that the economy and employment are facing in his speech at the Jackson Hole symposium. To</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27650</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Freya Protocol based on the USD1 ICM agreement will launch synchronously with BonkFun 2.0, and token pre-deposit is now open.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27649</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as per official information, the Bonk team, with the assistance of Solana core contributors, is set to launch the Bonkfun USD1 transaction pool ICM (Internet Capital Market) protocol Freya Protocol. This launch will be concurrent with the rollout of BonkFun 2.0 and the completion of the migration.The token pre-deposit has already begun. Holders can pre-deposit the FREYA token into the treasury and will receive an equivalent amount of Freya Protocol tokens along with a 5% pre-deposit bonus once BonkFun 2.0 is launched.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 06:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27649</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether has frozen a total of 6.45 million USDT across 11 addresses.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27648</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to the monitoring of MistTrack, Tether has frozen a total of 6.45 million USDT across 11 addresses.The issuer of USDT, Tether, can utilize the &quot;freeze&quot; function of its smart contract to restrict USDT transactions for specific blockchain addresses. The frozen addresses are unable to transfer or utilize USDT, and the freezing is typically carried out in response to law enforcement requests, to prevent the further transfer of funds from a hack, or for similar reasons.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 06:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An whale bought WLFI three days ago, spending $2 million. They are currently facing an unrealized loss of over $650,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27647</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale spent $2 million to purchase 7.4 million WLFI tokens three days prior. Currently, it is holding an unrealized loss of more than $650,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 06:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27647</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>