<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:16:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital stakes 250,000 SOL and deposits it into Binance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23348</link>
      <description>On August 6, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, 3 hours ago, Galaxy Digital undelegated 250,000 SOL tokens (amounting to $40.7 million) and deposited them into Binance.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23348</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF saw a net outflow of $196 million, marking the fourth consecutive day of outflows.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23346</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as monitored by Farside Investors, yesterday there was a net outflow of $196 million from the US Bitcoin spot ETF, marking the fourth consecutive day of net outflows. Among them, the BlackRock IBIT witnessed a net outflow of $77.4 million, and the Fidelity FBTC saw a net outflow of $99.1 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23346</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic Observer: Recently, multiple illegal projects have utilized the concept of &quot;Stablecoin Mining&quot; for illegal fundraising and rebate activities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23347</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Economic Observer released an investigation report entitled &quot;Annualized Yield Up to 540%? Investigation of Chaos in Virtual Asset Investment.&quot; The report pointed out that through journalists&apos; investigations, it was found that there are currently some virtual asset investment platforms active in the market with keywords such as decentralization, blockchain, and virtual assets. They package their projects with terms like blockchain technology, smart contracts, DeFi, and Defai (DeFi + AI).Many illegal projects are packaged with concepts such as &quot;DeFi Decentralized Finance,&quot; &quot;DApp Financial Management,&quot; and &quot;Stablecoin Mining,&quot; but in essence, they are still fundraising and rebate activities, merely using technological shells to cover up risks.From a legal perspective, investors need to bear responsibility for their own civil legal actions. They should carefully identify and participate in virtual asset investment projects, be vigilant against illegal activities disg</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23347</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale that had been quiet for 2 months undelegated over 30,000 SOL and deposited it into Binance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23345</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, following a period of two months of inactivity, a whale carried out the action of unbonding 30,010 SOL, which is equivalent to 4.9 million US dollars. Subsequently, it deposited 30,050 SOL into Binance.During the past four months, this whale, after staking for four years, has already unbonded 205,072 SOL coins with a value of 30.07 million US dollars. Currently, the whale still holds 1,108,368 SOL, which is worth 179 million US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the US Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $73.3 million, breaking a two-day streak of outflows.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23344</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as monitored by Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF yesterday was $73.3 million. Among them, BlackRock&apos;s ETHA witnessed a net inflow of $88.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX has officially launched perpetual contracts for TOWNS and PROVE and has kicked off a contract trading party.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23343</link>
      <description>August 6th. According to an official announcement, Huobi HTX launched TOWNS/USDT and PROVE/USDT perpetual contracts on August 6th, with a maximum leverage of 20 times. Simultaneously, from 11:30 on August 6th to 11:30 on August 13th (in UTC+8 time zone), Huobi HTX initiated the TOWNS and PROVE contract trading party with a total prize pool of up to $20,000.During the event, users who register and participate in TOWNS/USDT and PROVE/USDT contract trading, with a cumulative valid trading volume ≥ $10,000 USDT, will be eligible to share the prize pool based on their trading volume ranking. New contract users who complete TOWNS/USDT and PROVE/USDT contract trading will also receive exclusive benefits.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23343</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the recent market correction, analysts are divided on whether the altcoin season is coming.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23342</link>
      <description>August 6th: Following Bitcoin&apos;s recent drop to $112,000, altcoins failed to make a comeback. This has led analysts to hold diverse views on whether the altcoin season is approaching.A Bitfinex analyst stated in the Tuesday market report: &quot;Interestingly, the breakout in major coins did not translate into sustained buying in altcoins. On the contrary, the decline in altcoins and Bitcoin&apos;s weakness suggest that speculative interest is fading across the board. Thus, the market may be entering a consolidation phase. However, new macro events or strong inflows into cryptocurrency ETFs could quickly alter this situation.&quot;Cryptocurrency analyst Ted, on the other hand, said on Tuesday: &quot;This is the best opportunity to accumulate them before practical altcoins start their parabolic rises.&quot; (Contelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23342</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the Upbit listing news, PROVE experienced a short-term surge of over 40%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23341</link>
      <description>On August 6th, based on market data, PROVE witnessed a significant surge of over 40% in a short period and is currently trading at $1.4057.Previously, it was reported that Upbit will list PROVE trading pairs in KRW, USDT, and Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23341</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinList will open the PublicAI token sale on August 7th.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23340</link>
      <description>August 6th: The CoinList will commence the PublicAI (PUBLIC) token sale on August 7th at 17:00 UTC (August 8th at 1:00 in Beijing time). PublicAI is a Web3 data platform that is constructing the &quot;AI Human Layer Protocol&quot;. It is incubated by the Stanford Blockchain Accelerator and is backed by investments from the Solana and Near Foundation. A total of $10 million has been raised.The Fully Diluted Valuation (FDV) of this token sale is $70 million, and the price per PUBLIC is $0.07. A total of 28.57 million PUBLIC will be sold, accounting for approximately 2.86% of the total supply, with a 100% TGE unlock. The minimum subscription amount is $100, and payments in USDT/USDC are accepted.This sale will utilize CoinList&apos;s standard &quot;Filling from the Bottom&quot; distribution mechanism. Unsuccessful participants will receive a refund within 48 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23340</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blur and Blast Co-founders Pacman announced that they will be launching a new product.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23339</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Blur and Blast, the co-founders of Pacman, responded to a netizen&apos;s question on the X platform. They said, &quot;We sincerely thank you for your praise. Your ultimate victory is truly deserved. We are looking forward to presenting you with the products that we are about to launch.&quot;It is reported that the latest tweet from Ethereum L2 Blast&apos;s official Twitter account was posted on May 13th. There have been no posts in approximately 3 months, which has aroused concerns within the community.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 03:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23339</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>