<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:51:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Musk&apos;s Latest Compensation Plan Revealed, $1 Trillion &quot;Bet&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27871</link>
      <description>September 5th: On Friday, the board of directors of Tesla proposed a new compensation plan. Under this plan, if Musk achieves a series of extremely challenging goals within the next ten years, he will be awarded a reward worth approximately $1 trillion. In this plan, Musk will not receive any salary or bonus; his compensation will be in the form of gradually vested stocks. The unlocking conditions include a significant increase in Tesla&apos;s market value, a substantial improvement in profitability, the sale of millions of cars, and other key milestones.Board Chair Robyn Denholm stated in a letter to investors: &quot;Retaining and motivating Musk is of great significance for Tesla to become the most valuable company in history. This compensation plan is designed to align extraordinary long-term shareholder value with incentives to drive our visionary leader to achieve the best performance.&quot;The board emphasized that Musk&apos;s incentives are highly consistent with investor interests. If Tesla&apos;s</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27871</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit EU Group has applied for a MiFID II license, paving its way to the European derivatives market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27870</link>
      <description>September 5th, the cryptocurrency exchange Bybit is speeding up its expansion in Europe. The Bybit EU Group recently officially submitted an application to the Austrian Financial Market Authority (FMA), aiming to obtain an investment firm license for its subsidiary, Bybit X GmbH, in accordance with the MiFID II Austria Implementation Act.If approved, Bybit X will be capable of offering regulated derivative products across the entire European Economic Area (EEA), including futures and options. This will enlarge the business scope of the bybit.eu platform from the current MiCAR-authorized cryptocurrency spot services to the derivative market. Following the successful acquisition of the MiCAR license in May 2025, this is another crucial milestone in Bybit&apos;s European expansion strategy.The Bybit EU Group is headquartered in Vienna and officially launched the MiCAR-compliant platform bybit.eu in July 2025. Since its launch, Bybit EU has been continuously gaining strength, introducing fe</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27870</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sora Ventures Launches $1 Billion Fund to Support Asia&apos;s Bitcoin Reserve Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27869</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the Crypto VC firm Sora Ventures declared its intention to set up a $1 billion fund for investing in Asian Bitcoin reserve companies. In a press release issued on Friday, Sora Ventures mentioned that the company aims to raise $1 billion within the next 6 months and has already received an initial commitment of $200 million from regional partners and investors. This fund will be allocated to companies located in Asia that have Bitcoin on their balance sheets. This approach has attracted attention in recent years among publicly traded companies in Japan, Hong Kong, Thailand, and South Korea.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27869</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin surpasses $114,000, the total short liquidation volume on major CEXs will reach $847 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27868</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to Coinglass data, if Bitcoin manages to break through $114,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $847 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin drops below $111,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.416 billion.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of contracts that have been liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent reaching a particular price level will have an impact. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that once the price reaches that level, a more intense reaction will occur due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27868</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omni Network has announced a rebrand to Nomina, with a 1:75 OMNI to new coin NOM ratio.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27867</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the Ethereum interoperability protocol Omni Network made an announcement about its rebranding to Nomina. It presented a new name, logo, visual identity, and a brand-new product narrative to showcase its future direction.As part of this rebranding process, the Omni team is currently engaged in developing an application for token migration. Currently, existing OMNI holders and stakers do not need to take any actions. It should also be noted that the new ticker symbol for Nomina&apos;s token will be NOM. After the rebranding, NOM will become the primary token on the network (Smart Contract: 0x6e6F6d696e61decd6605bD4a57836c5DB6923340), replacing OMNI.The ratio between OMNI and NOM is 1:75. This implies that at the time of launch, the circulating supply will be 2.9 billion NOM. Based on the tokenomics plan from the previous $OMNI TGE, the total supply will be 7.5 billion NOM. Since we aim to provide all community members with the opportunity to migrate to NOM at their own c</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27867</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Foundation Completes Partial Sell-off, Withdraws 3.387M DAI from CEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27866</link>
      <description>September 5th. Based on @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, the Ethereum Foundation transferred 10,000 ETH to Kraken for sale the day before yesterday. 20 minutes ago, they withdrew 3.387 million DAI from Kraken. &quot;This indicates that a portion of these 10,000 ETH has already been sold.&quot;BlockBeats previously reported that the Ethereum Foundation announced in a blog post that during the course of several weeks this month, they would be converting 10,000 ETH through a centralized exchange to continuously support development, grants, and donations. These conversions would be carried out through multiple small orders rather than completing a large transaction all at once.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27866</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Nasdaq Tightens Cryptocurrency Stock Regulation, New Stock Purchase with Coins Requires Shareholder Approval, Institutional Bull Market Fear Likely to End</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27865</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Nasdaq is enhancing its regulation of public companies&apos; cryptocurrency purchases by means of new stock issuance. It requires some companies to obtain shareholder approval before making a purchase. This action is likely to slow down the current cryptocurrency craze and offer investors more transparency regarding risks.As of now, 124 US-listed companies have planned to raise more than $133 billion to purchase cryptocurrency, and the vast majority of them are listed on Nasdaq. In recent years, some companies have adopted a strategy similar to that of MicroStrategy, rapidly accumulating Bitcoin and other tokens in an attempt to boost their stock prices. However, with Nasdaq introducing shareholder voting and approval requirements, such funding operations may face the risk of delays or even adjustments to the transaction structure.For instance, the Nasdaq-listed company Heritage Distilling plans to purchase Story blockchain native tokens. Due to Nasdaq&apos;s new rule, its</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27865</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun transferred $9 million worth of unlocked WLFI to HTX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27863</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the blockchain analytics platform Bubblemaps declared that 2 hours previously, Justin Sun transferred $9 million of the unlocked WLFI to HTX.During the past 3 days, he has transferred a total of $10 million to centralized exchanges.This morning, BlockBeats reported that World Liberty had blacklisted Justin Sun&apos;s address, locking 540 million unlocked tokens and 2.4 billion staked tokens, expressing their view that a certain exchange has been continuously selling user tokens in an attempt to suppress the price.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 09:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27863</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategist: Non-Farm Payrolls Data Can Confirm the Fed&apos;s Dovish Stance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27864</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Francesco Sandrini, the Head of Multi-Asset Strategies at Amundi, said, &quot;Yesterday, we witnessed indications that employment might be on the wane, opening the door for a rate cut in September. Today&apos;s non-farm data &apos;to a certain extent can corroborate the Fed&apos;s dovish stance.&apos;&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 09:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. labor market is experiencing a &quot;speed bump moment,&quot; with next week&apos;s job revisions potentially reaching 800,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27862</link>
      <description>September 5th. If the market&apos;s prediction that there will be tepid US job growth in August and the unemployment rate will rise to 4.3% turns out to be correct, it will verify the weakness in the labor market and definitely settle the matter regarding the Fed&apos;s rate cut this month. Currently, US job growth appears to have entered a &quot;stall&quot; stage. Economists attribute this to President Trump&apos;s comprehensive import tariffs and immigration crackdown, which have reduced the labor force participation. The weakness in the labor market is mainly on the hiring side.Economists anticipate that nonfarm payrolls will increase by 75,000 last month, as compared to the 73,000 increase in July. Earlier, the job data for May and June were revised downwards by a total of 258,000, which angered Trump last month. Trump used this as a reason to dismiss the Bureau of Labor Statistics Commissioner Erika McEntarfer and accused her of manipulating jobs data.When the Bureau of Labor Statistics releases its p</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 09:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27862</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>