<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:20:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SafePal has partnered with 1inch to launch a WalletDrop collaboration, enhancing DeFi security and user experience.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21337</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, the Web3 wallet brand SafePal joined forces with the DEX aggregator 1inch to launch 300 sets of limited-edition co-branded hardware wallets. The purpose is to enhance the security and usability of DeFi. Against the backdrop of DEX global spot trading volume reaching a record 30% last month, this collaboration holds strategic significance.SafePal CEO and Co-founder Veronica Wong stated, &quot;In the increasingly competitive wallet market, continuous improvement and the implementation of effective user incentives and retention strategies are crucial. Due to the fact that airdrops are often associated with airdrop hunters and bot fake accounts, the Walletdrop activity with 1inch enables us to better identify and serve the user group with genuine DeFi security needs.&quot;1inch Co-founder Sergej Kunz said, &quot;Self-custody lies at the core of decentralization. As DeFi expands and attracts more mainstream users, advocating for secure self-custody practices becomes particularly importan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21337</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures to Resume Funding Rate Settlement Frequency for XTZUSDT and other Inverse Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21336</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, according to an official announcement, Binance Futures will resume the following U-based perpetual contract funding rate settlement frequency at 20:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, 2025. The funding rate settlement frequency will be adjusted to once every four hours for XTZUSDT, BROCCOLIF3BUSDT, MYXUSDT, MUSDT, and ERAUSDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&apos;s SpaceX and Tesla still hold 18,486 bitcoins, with a total profit of over $1.7 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21334</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, following today&apos;s &quot;SpaceX Moves 152 Million US Dollars Worth of BTC for the First Time in Three Years,&quot; Musk&apos;s SpaceX and Tesla still possess 18,486 bitcoins, with an average cost of approximately $32,000. Given the current bitcoin price of $118,000, SpaceX and Tesla have jointly reaped over $1.7 billion from their bitcoin investments.Tesla purchased $1.5 billion worth of bitcoin in January 2021 and has sold bitcoin in two separate transactions:It sold $272 million worth of bitcoin in the first quarter of 2021;It sold $936 million worth of bitcoin in the second quarter of 2022.Prior to today, SpaceX&apos;s most recent bitcoin transfer took place during the market downturn from May 25th, 2022, to June 10th, 2022, when SpaceX transferred 17,314 bitcoins to Coinbase.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21334</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>spacex</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delphinus Lab has announced that the Airdrop Eligibility Check Tool is now live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21335</link>
      <description>July 22nd. Delphinus Lab made an announcement stating that the Airdrop Eligibility Checking Tool has become operational. Binance Wallet&apos;s exclusive TGE Round 31 includes Delphinus Lab (ZKWASM), and the subscription period is from 4:00 PM to 6:00 PM (UTC+8) on July 22, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21335</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Watch: Market Volatility, Partial Whale Short Liquidation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21332</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight (accessible via https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD), there were changes in the holdings of a whale in the Hyperliquid contract. Some whale short positions reduced their positions, including:The whale address starting with 0x8af700 opened a new 10x short position on FARTCOIN for approximately 3.25 million tokens, with a liquidation price of $4.603. In addition, this address holds a 40x long position on BTC with an entry price of $119,865 and a liquidation price close to $91,630; a 10x short position on SUI with an entry price of $2.32 and a liquidation price of $8.278; a 20x short position on XRP with an entry price of $2.11 and a liquidation price of $5.101.The whale address starting with 0x2ba553 increased its ETH long position by 379.33 ETH. The current profit and loss (PnL) is $7,135,553.55, and the current liquidation price is $2,413.252.The whale address starting with 0x20c2d9 reduced its ETH short position by $1.116</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21332</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: U.S. Trade Negotiation Rift Persists, Crypto Market in Wait-and-See Mood, BTC Support at 116,300, Resistance at 120,000, Suggests Short-Term Range Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21333</link>
      <description>July 22: U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen declared that the U.S. is not fixated on the August 1st trade negotiation deadline and is prioritizing the quality of the agreement. She proposed that even if an agreement is not achieved by the deadline, the negotiations can persist. Nevertheless, Commerce Secretary Raimondo highlighted that August 1st is the deadline for the implementation of tariffs, and by that time, numerous countries including Brazil and Japan will be subject to high tariffs. This piece of news reflects the inconsistency within the U.S. government regarding the trade strategy. The market interprets it as continuous uncertainty in the negotiations. In response to the news, the U.S. stock market continued to reach new highs. However, investors remained vigilant about trade risks, while the crypto market exhibited high volatility.Bitunix Analyst&apos;s Advice:The short-term uncertainty in the trade negotiations may restrain the further upward potential of risk assets. Bitcoin&apos;s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21333</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafePal has partnered with 1inch to launch a Walletdrop collaboration, enhancing DeFi security and user experience.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21331</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, the Web3 wallet brand SafePal jointly launched 300 sets of limited-edition co-branded hardware wallets with the DEX aggregator 1inch. The aim is to enhance the security and usability of DeFi. Against the backdrop of last month&apos;s record-breaking 30% global DEX spot trading volume share, this collaboration holds significant strategic value.SafePal CEO and Co-Founder Veronica Wong stated, &quot;In the increasingly competitive wallet market, continuous iteration and effective user incentives and retention are crucial. Since token airdrops often attract airdrop hunters and bot fake accounts, the Walletdrop activity with 1inch can help us better identify and serve the user group with genuine DeFi security needs.&quot;1inch Co-Founder Sergej Kunz said, &quot;Self-custody is at the core of decentralization. As DeFi expands and attracts more mainstream users, advocating for a secure self-custody approach is particularly important. We are excited to collaborate with SafePal to incentivize act</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21331</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>656 Bitcoins Transferred from Binance to Institutional Custody Platform Ceffu, Valued at Approximately $77.4 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21329</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, as monitored by WhaleAlert, 656 Bitcoins were transferred from Binance to the Binance institutional custody platform Ceffu, with an approximate value of $77.4 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21329</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market: Solana Treasury Strategy Company Leads Surge in Crypto-related Stocks, MFH Up Over 18.6%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21330</link>
      <description>On July 22nd, based on market information, in the pre-market trading of US stocks, the &quot;Solana Treasury Strategy&quot; company took the lead in cryptocurrency concept stocks. These included: Mercurity Fintech Holding (MFH), which surged by more than 18.6% after previously announcing the launch of a Solana-based treasury strategy; the &quot;SOL version of MicroStrategy&quot;, DeFi Development Corporation (DFDV), which rose by 3.8% as it increased its holdings by 141,300 SOL yesterday, bringing its total holdings to approximately 1 million SOL; Thumzup Media Corporation (TZUP), which surged by more than 9.8% after its board approved a $250 million investment in cryptocurrency. Other cryptocurrency concept stocks had mixed performances: the &quot;ETH version of MicroStrategy&quot;, SharpLink, fell by 1.05%; Circle fell by 1.52%; Coinbase rose by 0.18%; MicroStrategy fell by 0.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21330</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bitcoin Treasury Company H100 Group has been approved to list on the Frankfurt Stock Exchange.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21328</link>
      <description>July 22: According to an official announcement, the Swedish listed company H100 Group has received approval for trading on the Frankfurt Stock Exchange (Open Market), and trading began today under the stock code GS9.Yesterday, the Swedish listed company H100 Group announced that it has increased its holdings of BTC by 140.25 BTC, and its total holdings have reached 510.28 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>