<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:00:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The stablecoin FRNT issued by the state of Wyoming is about to go live on Hedera</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27733</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the Wyoming Stablecoin Committee announced during a committee meeting that the first state government-issued stablecoin in the United States, the Frontier Stable Token (FRNT), is scheduled to be launched on Hedera. In the committee&apos;s second-quarter assessment, Hedera was selected as the sole candidate blockchain for FRNT because of its strict standards in terms of speed, reliability, and compliance.FRNT is the first stablecoin created under the &quot;2023 Wyoming Stablecoin Act.&quot; This is the first stablecoin issued by a U.S. state government. The token is fully backed by the U.S. dollar and short-term government bonds, with an additional 2% reserve to ensure stability. The design of FRNT aims to demonstrate how digital assets can enhance public finance by enabling faster, more transparent, and more efficient payments.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27733</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle announces that native USDC and CCTP V2 will soon be available on Plume</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27732</link>
      <description>According to official sources on September 4th, Circle announced that native USDC and CCTP V2 will soon become available on Plume.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27732</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morph: 220 Million BGB Burned and the Remaining 220 Million BGB Locked Up</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27728</link>
      <description>September 4th. As per official information, Morph has made an announcement regarding the burning of 2.2 billion BGB and the locking of the remaining 2.2 billion BGB. These locked BGB have now been placed into an independent address of the Morph Foundation. Over the subsequent 50 months, 2% will be made available on a monthly basis. The Morph Foundation will transfer BGB from the Ethereum chain to the Morph chain.Previously, it was reported that BGB will be upgraded to the Gas token and governance token of the Morph ecosystem. All BGB tokens that were governed by the Bitget team have been transferred to the Morph Foundation, with a total of 4.4 billion tokens. Out of these, 2.2 billion tokens will be burned in a one-time event, while the remaining 2.2 billion tokens will be locked and unlocked at a rate of 2% per month for liquidity incentives, scenario expansion, popularization and education, etc. In addition, the Morph Foundation will update the BGB burning mechanism and link it to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bitcoin ETF Sees Initial Dip Extend to 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27731</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the intraday decline of American Bitcoin expanded to 10%, and it is currently trading at $7.24.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27731</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Over 61% of MKR has been swapped for SKY</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27730</link>
      <description>September 4th. According to Sky (formerly known as MakerDAO), more than 61% of MKR has been swapped for SKY.The penalty for the delayed upgrade upon exchanging MKR to SKY will be determined by a governance proposal on September 18th. If the vote is in favor, the penalty will come into effect on September 22nd.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27730</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. August Markit Services PMI Final at 54.5, Expected 55.4</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27729</link>
      <description>September 4th: The ultimate value of the US August ISM Non-Manufacturing PMI came in at 54.5. The anticipated value was 55.4, while the previous value was also 55.4. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27729</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Acquires Breakout Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27727</link>
      <description>September 4th. Kraken has acquired Breakout Exchange. Breakout is a proprietary trading platform established by TraderMayne and CryptoCred.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27727</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Stock Exchange-listed company Mega Matrix has announced the submission of a $20 billion shelf registration, becoming the first publicly traded company to establish a DAT strategy in stable...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27726</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Mega Matrix Inc. (NYSE American: MPU) submitted a $20 billion F-3 universal shelf registration statement to the SEC today. This is with the aim of accelerating the strategic deployment of its stablecoin governance token treasury reserve (DAT). This registration enables MPU to issue various securities flexibly and systematically increase its holdings of leading governance tokens like ENA. The MPU management stated that this move is intended to actively participate in the stablecoin governance ecosystem through strategic holdings, thereby obtaining financial benefits and industry influence.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27726</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain 5th Anniversary Report: Record-Breaking User Base, Continued Expansion of Ecosystem, Roadmap Reveals New Upgrades</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27725</link>
      <description>On September 4th, BNB Chain announced in September that on the occasion of its fifth anniversary, the network has achieved several significant milestones in the past year. The daily active users of users reached a historic peak. The infrastructure underwent important upgrades. Security was significantly enhanced. Real World Assets (RWA) accelerated their landing. And a new phase of the technical roadmap was released synchronously, laying the foundation for the next generation of decentralized applications.The daily active users of BNB Chain exceeded 4.7 million. The average daily active users of BSC were 1.12 million, and opBNB reached a new high. The Maxwell and Lorentz hard fork reduced the block confirmation time to 0.75 seconds. The lowest Gas fee dropped to $0.001, significantly improving network speed and accessibility. Liquidity repeatedly reached new highs. BNB Chain led among all public chains. The DEX trading volume reached $319.4 billion, and the daily peak was $13.3 billi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27725</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAIGA Completes $2M Strategic Financing Round, with Participation from Amber Group</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27724</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the next-generation AI smart agent platform MAIGA completed a $2 million strategic funding round. Participants included Amber Group, Red Beard Ventures, IBC Group, TBV Ventures, and Chainlink.This is a significant milestone for MAIGA in its mission to &quot;bring AI-driven trading to everyone.&quot; Currently, MAIGA is expanding its existing products and getting ready for an upcoming token launch, leading the DeFAI wave powered by the BNB Chain.Maiga is constructing AI agents for DeFI and cryptocurrency, utilizing MCP, TEE, and multimodal technology. It is also deploying an AI agent launchpad on the BNB Chain. Maiga adopts a &quot;Proof of Trade&quot; (PoT) token model based on transaction volume.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27724</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>