<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:50:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the total netizens&apos; margin call liquidations across all exchanges amounted to $228 million, with $95.32 million in ETH liquidations.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23796</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, the total amount of liquidation across the entire network was $228 million. A total of 86,742 people were liquidated globally. The long liquidations totaled $79.64 million, and the short liquidations totaled $148 million. ETH liquidations reached $95.32 million, making it the most liquidated asset across the network.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23796</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: Base Chain MIGHTFLY, XTTA, and YETI New Coins Active</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23795</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to GMGN data, in the &quot;Hot&quot; category, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume on the Solana blockchain within the past 24 hours are TRUMP, BOSS, MOONTRUMP, LILPEPE, and GOOGLE. With the exception of TRUMP, all are newly listed meme tokens that have a low market capitalization and a small number of holders, presenting a relatively high risk.On the other hand, on the Base blockchain, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume within the past 24 hours are AERO, ZORA, MIGHTFLY, XTTA, and YETI. Both MIGHTFLY and YETI have been listed for less than 24 hours and have a low market capitalization, posing a relatively high risk. Therefore, please participate with caution.BlockBeats reminds users that most meme coins have no practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23795</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IoTeX Partners with HashKey Exchange to Co-build Digital Asset Infrastructure and AI Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23794</link>
      <description>On August 9th, as per official information, the DePIN + AI open smart platform IoTeX announced a strategic partnership today with the licensed compliant exchange platform HashKey Exchange. The two parties will jointly probe and establish digital asset infrastructure and, based on this, commence the co-construction process of the &quot;AI Eco Center&quot;.This cooperation encompasses multiple key domains, such as the construction of a digital asset service system, the identity verification (ioID) and trusted data access capabilities provided by the IoTeX Layer1 blockchain platform, as well as HashKey&apos;s comprehensive support in regulatory compliance consulting, asset custody, and auditing. Currently, HashKey Exchange has officially launched the &quot;IOTX/HKD&quot; trading pair as its fifth Hong Kong dollar asset trading pair, which is also the first asset trading pair concentrating on the AI field and holds significant market importance.This strategic partnership indicates IoTeX&apos;s continuous deepening</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23794</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWP Management has announced that its fund has raised approximately $200 million since April, all in XRP.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23793</link>
      <description>On August 9th, Digital Wealth Partners Management, LLC (DWP Management) made an announcement today. It stated that since April, its series of private investment funds have successfully raised approximately $200 million in funding. As a private fund manager that accepts investments in digital assets, all in-kind contributions up to now have been made in XRP.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23793</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flashbot Whale pfm.eth bought 2045 ETH on a FOMO chase five hours ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23792</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), Whale Trader pfm.eth made a purchase 5 hours ago. It spent 2.917 million USDC and 5.39 million USDT to buy 2,045 ETH, with an average price of $4,057.6.In the past 24 hours, they have been continuously chasing the price and bought 2,802 ETH on-chain, which is equivalent to about $11.297 million, at an average price of $4,032.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard University&apos;s endowment holds $1.17 billion worth of the BlackRock Bitcoin Spot ETF, surpassing its investment in Google&apos;s parent company, Alphabet.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23791</link>
      <description>On August 9th, as reported by The Block and disclosed on Friday, it was revealed that Harvard University&apos;s endowment held a $117 million stake in the Bitwise Bitcoin ETF by the end of the second quarter.This Bitcoin ETF investment ranked as the fifth-largest holding for the university, which was slightly higher than its investment in Google&apos;s parent company, Alphabet. The filings indicated that Harvard held nearly $114 million worth of Alphabet stock by the end of the quarter.The endowment of the Ivy League school is managed by Harvard Management Company. At the end of the last quarter, its largest holding was in Microsoft stock, with a value of over $3.1 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23791</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale/Institutional Address Cluster Accumulates Over 1,035,000 ETH in One Month</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23790</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, since July 10th, more than 1,035,000 ETH (valued at approximately $4.167 billion) has been accumulated by several unknown whales or institutions through exchanges and institutional platforms within a month.During the same time period, the price of ETH has gone up from $2,600 to $4,000, representing a 45% increase. Most of the ETH accumulated by these addresses is likely to belong to institutions or U.S. public companies holding ETH reserves (excluding SBET, as the addresses of SBET are known). The average price of the accumulated ETH is approximately $3,546.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 02:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23790</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Options Market Data Shows ETH Has Potential to Rise to $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23789</link>
      <description>On August 9th, Coindesk analyst Omkar Godbole declared that a concealed signal within the derivatives market suggests that Ethereum (ETH) might undergo an intensified upward trend, propelling its price to reach $4400 in a short time.This crucial indicator is the net Gamma exposure of market makers in the Deribit Ethereum options market. Gamma is a significant metric for options traders, quantifying how the options&apos; Delta (that is, their sensitivity to changes in the underlying asset&apos;s price) varies with market fluctuations.When market makers are in a negative Gamma state, they are compelled to purchase the underlying asset when the price rises and sell when the price falls, which typically amplifies one-sided market movements. Market makers provide liquidity to the order book, make profits from the bid-ask spread, and strive to maintain a price-neutral net exposure.According to data provider Amberdata, a notable negative Gamma accumulation has been observed in the $4000 to $4400</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23789</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institutional address withdrew approximately 10,000 ETH from Kraken 6 hours ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23787</link>
      <description>August 9th. Based on the monitoring of on-chain data analyst Yu Jin, the whale/institutional address 0xD47...3c0, which accumulated ETH through Kraken, once again accumulated ETH after half a month. Six hours ago, it withdrew 10,076 ETH (approximately $40.38 million) from Kraken.It is reported that this address has been accumulating ETH since July 19th and has now accumulated a total of 49,928 ETH (approximately $200 million), with an average price of $3,720.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23787</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: WLFI Aims to Raise $1.5 Billion to Establish a Publicly Traded Company Joining the Digital Reserve Craze</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23788</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to Bloomberg, World Liberty Financial (WLFI), which is backed by the Trump family, is in the process of discussions with major investors with the aim of establishing a publicly traded company to hold its WLFI token. This move is in line with the trend of digital asset treasury companies. Sources familiar with the matter indicate that the deal structure is still being finalized. The fundraising target is approximately $1.5 billion, and major investors in the technology and crypto industries have been reached out to for participation.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23788</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>