<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:15:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Mining Firm DMG Blockchain Solutions Plans to Establish a Multi-Currency Digital Asset Treasury Including BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21464</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the publicly traded Bitcoin mining company DMG Blockchain Solutions announced that it is assessing the institutional-grade fund management strategy of its subsidiary, Systemic Trust Company. The aim is to establish a diversified digital asset treasury. Currently, the company&apos;s digital asset investment portfolio only includes Bitcoin. It has now started to evaluate the use of existing mining rewards and additional funds raised to acquire other digital assets in addition to Bitcoin.According to BitcoinTreasuries data, DMG Blockchain Solutions currently holds approximately 341 Bitcoins and ranks 54th among publicly traded Bitcoin treasury companies. (Globenewswire)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Base Ecosystem Tokens See Significant Price Increase, with ZORA Surging Nearly 70% in a Single Day Leading the Way</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21463</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to GMGN Market Data, some tokens in the Base ecosystem witnessed significant gains today. These include:ZORA took the lead in gains with a nearly 70% increase and a circulating market cap of $131 million.SQD saw a 11.7% increase in the past 24 hours, with a circulating market cap of $111 million.PAAL experienced a 13% increase in the past 24 hours, with a circulating market cap of $122 million.Flock witnessed an 18.3% increase in the past 24 hours, with a circulating market cap of $22.94 million.NOICE had a 35.76% increase in the past 24 hours, with a circulating market cap of $9.9 million.BlockBeats reminds users that these tokens are prone to significant price volatility, and users should be cautious when investing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21463</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Or Three Wallets Belonging to the Same Whale Move 10,606 BTC After 3 Years of Dormancy, Realizing Over 6x Gains</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21462</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, 3 wallets (which may be owned by the same whale) have just made a transfer of 10,606 BTC ($126 million) after being dormant for 3 to 5 years.All 3 wallets received BTC on December 13, 2020, when the price of BTC was $18,807.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21462</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the US Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $533.8 million, while the Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net outflow for the second consecutive day.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21461</link>
      <description>July 23rd. According to Farside Investors, a net inflow of $533.8 million was witnessed in the US Ethereum spot ETF yesterday. Specifically, BlackRock&apos;s ETHA had a net inflow of $426.2 million.Yesterday, the Bitcoin spot ETF witnessed a net outflow of $68 million. For BlackRock&apos;s IBIT, there was a net outflow/inflow of 0. This indicates that it is the second consecutive day of net outflows for the Bitcoin spot ETF.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21461</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale that accumulated MKR four months ago has now exited the position, realizing a profit of $4.8 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21460</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as monitored by LookOnChain, Whale 0xacef sold all 5,420 MKR within the past 5 days, thereby realizing a profit of $4.8 million (+74%).This Whale had purchased 5,420 MKR four months ago, spending $6.56 million, and also bought 524,643 UNI, spending $3.24 million. Currently, it holds an unrealized profit of $2.4 million (+74%) on UNI.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21460</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Data Dashboard: Total Platform Trading Volume Exceeds $15.6 Billion; Total Cumulative Users Exceed 570,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21459</link>
      <description>According to the monitoring of HyperInsight, by July 21st, the Hyperliquid platform has attracted 3,056 new users, raising the total number of users to 572,868. The platform has completed over 1.16 billion transactions with a total trading volume of $15.6 billion.Disclaimer from BlockBeats: The user and trading volume data of the Hyperliquid platform generally has a 2-day lag. Therefore, the data reported today is based on information up to July 21st.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21459</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polymarket Opens 2028 US Presidential Election Prediction, Trump&apos;s Current Odds at Only 3%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21458</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, as per the official website, Polymarket has launched the prediction market for the 2028 US Presidential Election, and it has attracted more than $1.1 million in participation.As of the moment of this writing, JD Vance is in the lead with a 28% probability of winning. Next comes the Democratic candidate Gavin Newsom. Currently, President Trump is only at 3%.According to the available information, the 2028 US Presidential Election is scheduled to be held on November 7, 2028.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21458</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONK Token Shows Strong Rebound, Gas Price Hits All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21457</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on GMGN data, BONK-related tokens have witnessed significant rebounds. These include:The Bonk ecosystem development protocol GP has surged by more than 35% in the past 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $2.408 billion.BONK has seen a 5.49% increase in the past 24 hours, and its current market capitalization is $32.8 billion.The leading meme coin of LetsBONK, USELESS, has surged by 23.54% in the past 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $3.4 billion.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience high price volatility, and investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21457</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX has launched the all-new &quot;Spot Pro&quot; system, further enhancing performance and user experience.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21456</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, WEEX announced that in order to continuously enhance the trading experience, WEEX has launched the new &quot;Spot Pro&quot; system, which completely replaces the old spot system. The new system has a transaction processing speed (TPS) of 20,000, significantly improving the matching efficiency. It allows for smoother order placement and cancellation, with more timely data push. It also has smaller slippage, resulting in better execution prices. It will support more than 3,000 trading pairs, providing stronger liquidity. The fund accounts and trading accounts are isolated, enhancing the clarity of asset management.WEEX reminds users to update the App version as soon as possible and transfer assets from the original &quot;Spot&quot; account to the &quot;Spot Pro&quot; account with one click. Users who meet the conditions and complete the transfer before 17:59 on July 27th will receive 1 - 5 U contract trial funds and enjoy zero transaction fees for all coins in the &quot;Spot Pro&quot; system. After that, the sy</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lotte Card Applies for Trademark of Won-Backed Stablecoin, Bullish on Stablecoin&apos;s Application in Luxury Goods, Gold, and Other High-Value Asset Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21455</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to Yonhap News Agency, the Lotte Card Company has submitted applications for 36 trademarks related to Korean won stablecoins, including brand names and symbols. The applied trademarks comprise &quot;WONBIT,&quot; &quot;KTOKEN,&quot; &quot;LOCAMONEY,&quot; and others. The company declared that the Korean won stablecoin will be widely utilized in the future in high-value asset transactions such as used cars, luxury goods, real estate, and gold.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21455</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>