<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:50:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet has deposited 1,997,000 USDC into HyperLiquid and taken a 10x leveraged short position on BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25123</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a new wallet deposited 1.997 million USDC into HyperLiquid and initiated a 10x leveraged short position on BTC. The position value reached $19.95 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Over 90% of OKB Migration to Ethereum L1 Completed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25122</link>
      <description>On August 19th, based on official sources and on-chain data, more than 90% of OKB on Ethereum L1 has completed the cross-chain swap. This OKB cross-chain swap is a part of OKEx&apos;s implementation of the &quot;Native Gas Token - OKB Economic Model Upgrade&quot; announced on August 13th. Subsequently, OKB will exist in a new cross-chain mode across multiple chains and serve as the X Layer&apos;s native Gas token. The X Layer Layer 2 network is reported to be a highly flexible, global on-chain ecosystem that bridges the Euro-DeFi and Ethereum communities, with the vision of bringing everything on-chain.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD.AI is pleased to announce its official launch. Points earned from deposits will be used for future airdrops and public offering quotas.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25121</link>
      <description>On August 19th, USD.AI, a stablecoin protocol that provides credit to AI, announced its official launch. Users are able to deposit USDC on the Arbitrum network in order to exchange it for USDai. Subsequently, they can further pledge to obtain sUSDai. Depositors will receive points, which will be utilized for future airdrops and public sale quotas.Earlier reports indicated that USD.AI completed a Series A financing round worth $13.4 million, with Framework Ventures taking the lead and Bullish, Dragonfly, Arbitrum, and others participating.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 910,000 ETH is currently queued to exit the Ethereum PoS network, setting a new record.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25120</link>
      <description>On August 19th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, it is reported that the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is 910,461 ETH, which is approximately worth 3.91 billion USD and has reached a historical high in terms of the exit scale.At the same time, there are about 268,217 ETH queued to join the network.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, since Ethereum reached its low point in April, some stakers may have chosen to cash out significantly, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, due to regulatory optimism and institutional demand, new funds have been deposited, driving up the entry queue. Public companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have increased their ETH holdings and are staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Mitosis (MITO) Booster Event USDT Pool APY Increased to 66.25%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25119</link>
      <description>August 19th. Binance&apos;s Mitosis (MITO) Booster Event Season 1 commenced today at 8:00 AM (UTC). Presently, the APY in the BNB pool reaches as high as 117.9%, and in the USDT pool, it is as high as 66.25%.This event enables users to deposit BNB or USDT into the Simple Yield Mitosis Treasury via the Binance Wallet to obtain MITO rewards. A total of 15 million MITO rewards are available. The event does not set an Alpha Point threshold. Users can redeem their assets through the Mitosis DApp. It is crucial to note that the BNB redemption process may take up to 10 days, and the USDT redemption process may take up to 5 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cookie DAO announces Sapien Token List Snapshot is Complete</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25118</link>
      <description>August 19th. Cookie DAO made an announcement that the snapshot for the Cookie Snaps event project Sapien&apos;s whitelist has been completed. The top 100 rankings will obtain 25% of the total rewards, and the remaining 75% will be distributed proportionally based on the total whitelist. The reward distribution will occur during the TGE (August 25th), with an initial 30% being unlocked.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25118</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ethereum OG address sold 8576 ETH at an average price of $4317, amounting to $37.02 million in value.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25117</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the address 0x737...c1ca6 sold 8576 ETH within the past 2 hours at an average price of $4317, with a total value of $37.02 million.This address had received 20,756 ETH 10 years ago when the price of ETH was only $0.875. Currently, the address still holds 10,209 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25117</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cap Stablecoin Protocol Officially Launches, cUSD Minting Now Open</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25116</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the stablecoin protocol Cap within the Ethereum ecosystem officially launched, commencing the minting of cUSD and enabling users to participate in Epoch 1 of the Frontier program to earn Caps.Cap announced in April of this year that it had completed a financing round of $11 million, with the participation of entities such as Franklin Templeton and Triton Capital.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25116</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase CEO: Team is Full Steam Ahead on Everything Exchange Development</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25115</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, posted that the Coinbase team gathered in New York last week to advance the development of the Everything Exchange. They worked vigorously from 9 a.m. to 9 p.m. (and even later) every day. In the third quarter, all key project teams will continue to work hard to accelerate the Everything Exchange.Coinbase&apos;s &quot;Everything Exchange&quot; is a comprehensive, full-chain trading platform strategic project led by CEO Brian Armstrong. The goal is to integrate various assets such as cryptocurrencies, tokenized stocks, derivatives, prediction markets, and early token sales into one platform, providing an all-in-one trading experience. Brian Armstrong first proposed this plan on July 31, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25115</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader The White Whale holds a $4.1 billion ETH and SOL long position, with a recent profit of $51.6 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25114</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as monitored by EmberCN, on the Hyperliquid platform, the top trader, The White Whale, currently holds a long position in ETH and SOL worth up to $410 million. Through a main account and multiple sub-accounts, they are long 63,200 ETH across 6 addresses, with a value of $274 million; and long 745,000 SOL, worth $138 million. They initially had around $21.18 million in early July, and their account is now worth $72.78 million, with a profit of $51.60 million.BlockBeats previously reported that on July 20th, the top trader, The White Whale, made a profit of nearly $30 million in just one week. Over the past week, they went long on ETH and SOL through 4 wallets, locking in nearly $30 million in gains and securing the top spot on the Hyperliquid leaderboard.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25114</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>