<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:56:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SUI Surpasses $4.28, With Over 5% 24-hour Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22002</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on HTX market data, SUI has exceeded $4.28 and is currently trading at $4.281, showing a 24-hour increase of more than 5%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22002</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Bank Former President: Stablecoin Has an Innovative Role in Facilitating Finance, But Also Poses Systemic Financial Risks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22001</link>
      <description>On July 27th, Li Lihui, the former President of Bank of China, stated at the &quot;2025 International Monetary Forum&quot; that stablecoins play a role in providing innovative financial convenience while also presenting systemic financial risks.He noted that the United States hopes to link stablecoins to the US dollar in order to maintain its global currency hegemony. If the United States fails to improve its twin deficits, it may have an impact on the stability of its currency value. Additionally, he pointed out that Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin can relax domestic access conditions when the appropriate conditions are met, which will assist in the internationalization of the RMB.He also emphasized the need to monitor the dynamics of the decentralized financial market represented by the United States and enhance China&apos;s position in the global monetary and financial system.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22001</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last year, the whale used a flash loan to accumulate WBTC with an average price of $69,162. One hour ago, they deposited 50 WBTC to Binance for profit-taking.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22000</link>
      <description>July 27th. Based on Ashes Monitoring, a whale/institution that borrowed in a loop and purchased a cumulative total of 1,495 WBTC during the period from July to November 2024 continuously transferred out 50 WBTC ($5.9 million) to Binance one hour ago for profit-taking.It purchased 1,495 WBTC using a loop borrowing method in the second half of last year at an average price of $69,162 ($103 million). Starting from March of this year, it has been gradually transferring WBTC to Binance in batches to sell and withdraw USDC for repayment. Up to now, it has sold 923 WBTC ($92.26 million) at an average price of $99,957. It still holds 553.8 WBTC ($65.51 million).Its total profit on WBTC is currently as high as $55.62 million: $28.42 million realized profit from the sold portion and $27.20 million unrealized profit from the unsold portion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum breaks $3900, the mainstream CEX cumulative short liquidation pressure will reach 740 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21999</link>
      <description>On July 27th, according to Coinglass data, if Ethereum surpasses $3900, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will amount to 740 million.Conversely, if Ethereum drops below $3700, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach 1.528 billion.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the relative significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to the adjacent liquidation cluster, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the target price will be influenced when it reaches a particular position. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that when the price reaches that level, it will experience a more intense reaction due to a liquidity avalanche.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21999</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Securities Submits Application to Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission for Virtual Asset Service License</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21998</link>
      <description>On July 27th, Fusang Financial disclosed that its indirectly wholly-owned subsidiary, Fusang Securities Limited, submitted an application to the Securities and Futures Commission of Hong Kong on July 25, 2025. The purpose of this application is to obtain a Type 1 (Securities Trading) regulated activity license in accordance with the Securities and Futures Ordinance (Chapter 571 of the Laws of Hong Kong) in order to provide virtual asset trading and/or advisory services as an intermediary. (Sohu Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21998</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Total Market Cap Grew by 1.64% in the Past 7 Days, Surpassing $265.6 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21997</link>
      <description>On July 27th, as per DefiLlama data, the current total market value of stablecoins across the entire network is reported to be $265.65 billion, with a 1.64% increase in the past 7 days. Among them, the market dominance of USDT has dropped to 61.9% (down from 62.09% of the previous week).</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21997</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abraxas Capital once again added $5 million to its ETH short position, bringing the total to a $78.72 million unrealized loss.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21996</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on HyperInsight&apos;s monitoring, the address starting with 0x5b5, which was identified by Arkham as Abraxas Capital, has just added $5 million to its short position hedge of ETH (with 10x leverage). Currently, it still has an unrealized loss of $78.72 million. The specific information is as follows:Position Size: $299 millionEntry Price: $2,826.72Liquidation Price: $5,096.9Current P&amp;L: Unrealized Loss of $78.72 millionIn addition, the short position hedge of BTC (with 10x leverage) opened by this address has also incurred an unrealized loss of $22.3 million, and the position value is $345 million. Other major short positions include: HYPE (with 5x short), with a loss of $6.89 million; SOL (with 10x short), with a loss of $8.51 million. Currently, the overall unrealized loss of the short positions of this address is approximately $115 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21996</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Surges Above $3,800</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21995</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum has experienced a rebound and exceeded $3,800. It is currently trading at $3,815, with a 24-hour increase of 1.14%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21995</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: NVIDIA&apos;s Market Cap Exceeding $400 Billion Triggers Musk&apos;s Amazement, Now Supports Investing in US Stocks Using USDT</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21994</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on the latest data from Statista, NVIDIA has officially closed with a market capitalization of over $4 trillion, thereby becoming the first technology company in the world to break through this threshold. This remarkable achievement has not only propelled NVIDIA to surpass Microsoft and Apple and become the world&apos;s most valuable listed company in terms of market capitalization but has also exceeded the combined market capitalizations of Google&apos;s parent company Alphabet and Meta. It even surpasses the sum of the market capitalizations of retail giants such as Amazon, Walmart, and Costco.NVIDIA&apos;s stock price has surged by more than 1000% in the past two and a half years, delivering outstanding performance. In response to this, Tesla CEO Musk retweeted the relevant news on the social platform X and simply commented: &quot;Wow,&quot; expressing his admiration.Driven by the AI trend and capital enthusiasm, an increasing number of investors are eager to seize the growth dividen</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 09:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21994</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese MUFG Bank is planning to sell tokenized real estate products to investors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21993</link>
      <description>On July 27th, the trust banking arm of Japan&apos;s MUFG Bank, Mitsubishi UFJ Trust and Banking Corporation, has purchased a high-rise building in Osaka City for more than 100 billion yen (approximately 6.81 billion USD). The trust bank intends to tokenize the building and sell the digital securities to retail and institutional investors. The product will be provided to institutional investors in the form of a private real estate investment trust (REIT) for life insurance companies.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 08:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21993</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>