<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>An address has potentially accumulated 2004 ETH in the past 2 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25581</link>
      <description>August 21st. According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the address 0x7E4...00107 is reported to have accumulated 2004 ETH within the past 2 hours, which is worth 8.55 million US dollars. It withdrew 1802 ETH from Binance and repurchased 201.45 ETH on-chain using USDC with an average price of 4268.59 US dollars. Currently, 1000 ETH has been deposited into Aave.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25581</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chair Candidate Brad Calls for 100 Basis Point Rate Cut, Plans to Meet With U.S. Treasury Secretary After Labor Day</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25580</link>
      <description>August 21st - The former president of the St. Louis Fed and the front-runner for the next Federal Reserve Chair, Brad, advocated for a 100-basis-point rate cut this year and additional cuts in 2026. Brad stated in an interview on Thursday: &quot;Current interest rates are a bit on the high side. I believe we can reduce them by approximately 100 basis points by 2026. I think this will commence with a cut at the September meeting and may be followed by further actions later this year.&quot;Brad mentioned that he has been in communication with Treasury Secretary Benson regarding his candidacy for the Federal Reserve Chair and plans to &quot;possibly&quot; arrange a meeting after Labor Day on September 1st. Regarding further rate cuts next year, Brad stated that it will depend on the data performance. He also highlighted the significance of maintaining the status of the US dollar as a reserve currency. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25580</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chainlink Receives ISO 27001 and SOC 2 Compliance Certifications</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25579</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Chainlink announced that it had obtained ISO 27001 certification and SOC 2 Type 1 certification. The scope of this assessment encompasses:Chainlink Data Feeds—specifically, Price Feeds and Smart Data (including Proof of Reserve and Net Asset Value (NAV)), all based on Chainlink Data Standards;Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP)—Chainlink&apos;s interoperability standard.All reviews were carried out by the independent accounting firm Deloitte &amp; Touche LLP in accordance with the auditing standards established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25579</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave has launched on Avalanche, marking its first deployment on a non-EVM blockchain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25577</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to The Block, the decentralized lending protocol Aave has been launched on Aptos, which marks its first deployment on a non-EVM blockchain. This launch on Aptos supports native USDC, USDT, APT, and sUSDe. Moreover, the Aptos Foundation will offer user rewards and liquidity incentives to boost its adoption. In addition, Aave will also integrate Chainlink price feeds to empower the oracle security market.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25577</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMask has launched its native stablecoin mUSD</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25578</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to The Block, MetaMask has officially launched its native stablecoin, MetaMask USD (mUSD).MetaMask stated on Thursday that mUSD will be issued by Bridge, which is a stablecoin issuance platform owned by Stripe, and will be minted through M0&apos;s decentralized infrastructure. In addition, mUSD will be fully backed 1:1 by a &quot;high-quality, highly liquid asset equivalent to the US dollar&quot; and will achieve real-time transparency and cross-chain composability through M0&apos;s liquidity network.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25578</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Yiren Digital releases Q2 financial report: as of the end of Q2, it holds 11,197.5 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25576</link>
      <description>August 21st. The New York Stock Exchange-listed company Yiren Digital disclosed its unaudited financial results for the quarter ending June 30th, 2025. The fair value gain in the second quarter of 2025 was 28 million RMB (approximately 3.9 million USD). In contrast, the first quarter of 2025 witnessed a loss of 58.4 million RMB, and the same period in 2024 had a gain of 38.7 million RMB.The quarterly variation was primarily attributed to the fluctuation in the fair value of crypto assets, which was driven by the increase in Ethereum&apos;s price. As of June 30th, 2025, the company held 11,197.5 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle has minted an additional 750 million USDC on the Solana blockchain, bringing the total USDC minted on the Solana blockchain this year to 24.75 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25575</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as monitored by Onchain Lens, Circle has minted an additional 7.5 billion USDC on the Solana blockchain. By 2025, the total amount of USDC minted on the Solana network has reached 24.75 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25575</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury Mints Additional 500 Million USDC on the Solana Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25574</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as monitored by Whale Alert, the USDC Treasury has minted an extra 5 billion USDC on the Solana blockchain. This minting was carried out in two separate transactions, with 2.5 billion USDC minted in each transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25574</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKB achieved a 24-hour spot trading volume of $800 million on the OKX platform, surpassing Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25572</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the 24-hour spot trading volume of OKB on the OKX platform reached $800 million, surpassing Bitcoin ($628 million) and temporarily ranking second, only after Ethereum ($915 million). The 24-hour price increase of OKB reached 54.23%, and it is currently trading at $203.31.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25572</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Fed: Another Rate Cut Possible Later This Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25573</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the President of the Boston Fed stated that the Federal Reserve might cut interest rates one more time during this year.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25573</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>