<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:32:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Discloses Partial Investment Portfolio: Has Invested in Over 120 Companies, with a Focus on Bitcoin, Payment, and Other Sectors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21504</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Paolo Ardoino, the CEO of Tether, declared that Tether has now announced some of its investment/venture capital portfolio today. In total, Tether has made investments in over 120 companies, and this figure is anticipated to increase substantially in the forthcoming months and years. The invested companies encompass Juventus, Bitdeer, Crystal Intelligence, Rumble, Shiga Digital, and others.These investments all originate from Tether&apos;s own profits (projected to reach $13.7 billion by 2024) and do not involve the reserve assets of USDT (and other stablecoins). They fall under Tether&apos;s investment department. The emphasis is placed on key domains such as payment infrastructure, renewable energy, Bitcoin, agriculture, artificial intelligence, and tokenization.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinshares has obtained the EU MiCA License</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21503</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the cryptocurrency asset management service provider CoinShares declared that it had acquired a license regulated by the European Union&apos;s Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA). This license was granted by the French Financial Markets Authority (AMF) and encompassed CoinShares&apos; existing licenses obtained under the EU&apos;s MiFID and AIFM directives. On the same day, the company&apos;s stock price increased by 1.7% to 120 Swedish Krona (approximately $12.66). From the beginning of the year until now, the company&apos;s stock price has risen by 46%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Binance Alpha Launches COA</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21502</link>
      <description>July 23rd. Binance Alpha initiated the Alliance Games (COA).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Tokenization Platform xStocks Surpasses $300 Million in On-chain Trading Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21501</link>
      <description>July 23rd. According to Coindesk, Since its launch on Bybit, Kraken, and Solana decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms, the on-chain transaction volume of Backed&apos;s stock tokenization platform xStocks has exceeded $300 million within four weeks. This indicates a growing demand for U.S. stock tokenization.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27 to 30 for economic and trade talks with the United States.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21500</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, a reporter inquired: In early June, China and the United States held economic and trade talks in London, UK, and reached the London Agreement. Recently, there have been reports suggesting that China and the United States will soon hold the next round of economic and trade talks. Does the Ministry of Commerce have any latest news? In response, the Ministry of Commerce stated: As per the agreement between the Chinese and American sides, He Lifeng, a member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and vice premier of the State Council, will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side. China and the United States will, in accordance with the important consensus reached during the June 5th telephone conversation between the two heads of state, make good use of the China-US economic and trade negotiation mechanism and continue to conduct consultations on economic and trade issues of mutual concern in line with the princi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21500</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority Chief Executive Eddie Yue: Will Announce Summary of &quot;Stablecoin Issuer Licensing Regime&quot; Next Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21499</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to ChainNews, Eddie Yue, the Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA), issued a statement. It was noted that recently there have been scams related to the promotion of digital assets and stablecoins, resulting in losses to the public. The &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; will take effect on August 1st. According to the regulation, any unauthorized promotion of stablecoins to the Hong Kong public will be regarded as illegal starting from the effective date. Yue also mentioned that there have been a lot of rumors in the market regarding the application process recently. The HKMA will release a summary of the &quot;Stablecoin Issuer Licensing Regime&quot; next week, which will outline the HKMA&apos;s arrangements for receiving and processing license applications. Those interested are advised to stay tuned.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21499</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data shows that only 12% of the Ethereum protocol and 25% of the Solana protocol have revenue.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21498</link>
      <description>July 23rd. According to a report from Coindesk, data from DeFiLlama indicates that the Ethereum network is home to a total of 1,271 protocols. During the past 30 days, 88% (1,121 protocols) of these projects did not generate any revenue. The Solana ecosystem, which is on a smaller scale, has 264 protocols, and 75% of them have not generated any revenue in the past few days. Many protocols on these two chains have recently been unable to capture any value.Inactive smart contracts have increased storage burdens, posed security risks, and led to economic inefficiencies, thereby hindering the overall improvement of the user experience.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21498</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches ETH Dollar-Cost Averaging (DCA) Activity, Enjoy DCA Cashback and 10% APR Subsidy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21497</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, in celebration of the 10th anniversary of ETH, Bitget launched an ETH dollar-cost averaging (DCA) event. During this event, new users who create a DCA plan for the first time and invest at least 100 USDT in ETH will receive a 10% cashback on the DCA amount. The maximum cashback is 100 USDT, and the total prize pool is 10,000 USDT.In addition, if new or existing users DCA into ETH and hold it until August 6th at 0:00 (UTC+8), they can enjoy a 10% APR ETH financial management coupon based on the DCA amount. The coupon duration is 2 days, and the maximum coupon amount is 20 ETH. The rewards are awarded on a first-come, first-served basis while supplies last. The event runs from July 22nd at 15:00 to August 5th at 15:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21497</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 billion PUMP tokens reportedly moved from Binance hot wallet back to the project team&apos;s associated address</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21496</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), it is reported that 2 billion PUMP tokens have been transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to an address related to the project. A week ago, these tokens were deposited into Binance and then transferred to the address 9SnqX...seSGz. Half an hour ago, they were sent back in batches from that address.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU Surpasses BONK in Market Cap to Become the Largest Meme Coin in the Solana Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21495</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to CoinGecko data, PENGU surged by more than 19.5% within the past 24 hours and reached a market capitalization of 27.85 billion US dollars, surpassing BONK (27.01 billion US dollars) to become the Meme coin with the largest market capitalization in the Solana ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21495</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>