<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:39:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Samourai Wallet&apos;s two co-founders acknowledge cryptocurrency mixing service-related allegations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22458</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Keonne Rodriguez and William Lonergan Hill, the co-founders of Samourai Wallet, have entered pleas of guilty in the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York to charges associated with their cryptocurrency mixing service.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22458</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, Hyperliquid&apos;s contract trading volume reached $11.14 billion, a daily decrease of 10.2%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22456</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to DefiLlama data, the contract trading volume of Hyperliquid reached $11.14 billion on July 29th, showing a daily decrease of 10.2%.According to Coinglass data, the contract position size of Hyperliquid reached $13.862 billion. The Bitcoin contract position size reached $4.381 billion, with a 24-hour increase of 0.76%. The Ethereum contract position size reached $3.83 billion, with a 24-hour decrease of 4.97%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX CEO Star has published a blog post paying tribute to the tenth anniversary of Ethereum, stating a firm commitment to co-building the future on the blockchain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22457</link>
      <description>July 30th. In commemoration of Ethereum&apos;s tenth anniversary, OKX CEO Star published a blog post titled &quot;Ethereum&apos;s Tenth Anniversary: My Personal Tribute,&quot; reflecting on the shared journey with Ethereum and looking forward to the future of the blockchain. Star stated that since OKX was established in 2013, they have maintained a close collaboration with the Ethereum ecosystem. In the future, OKX will continue to provide world-class products and services to more than 1 billion users globally, driving the realization of a truly decentralized blockchain vision.In the article, he publicly recounted his first encounter with Vitalik for the first time and admitted that he had underestimated the profound significance of Ethereum&apos;s vision. Now, he highly values its ability to reshape the global financial system and trust mechanism. Star pointed out that OKX has long adhered to the open and transparent spirit advocated by Ethereum, from introducing ZK Reserves to supporting EIP-7702 and build</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22457</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launchpool Project GAIA is now open for staking, with a maximum lock-up of 50,000 BGB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22455</link>
      <description>July 30th. Currently, Bitget&apos;s Launchpool project Gaia (GAIA) is open for staking. By staking BGB, 3,858,300 GAIA is unlocked. The maximum staking limit for regular users is 5,000 BGB, and for VIP users, it is 50,000 BGB. The staking deadline is August 1st at 17:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22455</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Reserve Concept Stock Pre-market Mixed, &apos;BNB Edition Micro Strategy&apos; VAPE Down 6.05%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22454</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on the market data from Rockflow, the pre-market trading of US cryptocurrency reserve concept stocks presented mixed results. The following are the Ethereum reserve concept stocks:SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) increased by 1.57%;BTCS Inc (BTCS.US) decreased by 1.39%;Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) rose by 3.5%;GameSquare (GAME.US) went up by 1.97%;Bit Digital (BTBT.US) increased by 0.68%.For the BNB reserve concept stocks:CEA Industries (VAPE) dropped by 6.05%;Windtree (WINT) declined by 4.16%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22454</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Silent 14.5-Year Holder of 3963 BTC Ancient Whale」 transferred an additional 50 BTC half an hour ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22453</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to the on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;ancient whale that had been holding 3,963 BTC in silence for 14.5 years&quot; transferred an additional 50 BTC ($5.91 million) to the address bc1q8...kxayr half an hour ago. The current ownership of the receiving address remains unknown.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22453</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutional Ethereum Whale Holdings Change in the Last 30 Days: BMNR Holds 625,000 ETH Ranking First</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22451</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on strategicethreserve data, the following treasury companies and institutions witnessed significant changes in their Ethereum holdings over the past 30 days:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) took the lead, currently holding 625,000 ETH, which is approximately worth $23.8 billion, with a 283.1% increase in holdings during the past 30 days;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) ranked second, currently holding 438,200 ETH, approximately worth $16.7 billion, and experiencing a 132.49% increase in holdings over the past 30 days;The Ethereum Foundation ranked third, holding 238,500 ETH, approximately worth $8.977 billion, with a 6.69% decrease in holdings over the past 30 days;Bit Digital (BTBT) ranked seventh, holding 120,300 ETH, approximately worth $4.585 billion, and showing a 335.53% increase in holdings over the past 30 days;BTCS Inc (BTCS) ranked tenth, holding 70,000 ETH, approximately worth $2.669 billion, with a 379.64% increase in holdings over the past 30 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22451</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU project team&apos;s associated address has once again transferred 150 million PENGU to Binance, equivalent to approximately $5.64 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22450</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the team behind the PENGU project&apos;s affiliated address 8hQvQ...zund8 has once more deposited 150 million PENGU tokens into Binance, with a value of $5.64 million.This address previously received 1.35 billion PENGU tokens from the deployment address in December 2024. Since July, it has transferred a total of 485 million tokens to exchanges. The total value of these transfers is $17.67 million, and the average price per token is $0.03642.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22450</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has launched perpetual contract trading for A2Z and UNITE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22452</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to official channels, Gate has initiated A2Z perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT), with support for 1-20x leverage; and it will launch UNITE perpetual contract spot trading (settled in USDT) at 18:10 on July 30th (UTC+8), also providing support for 1-20x leverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22452</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Market Quietly Awaits FOMC Meeting Statement, BTC Holds Steady in Support Range, Short-Term Pressure Still Focuses on the 120,000 Level</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22449</link>
      <description>July 30th: After 30 years, a rare divergence in interest rate policy has emerged within the Federal Reserve. Board members Waller and Bowman inclined towards an immediate 25-basis-point rate cut, highlighting the risks to the labor market and the short-term inflationary impact of tariffs. However, the majority of the board still favored maintaining the current interest rates. Several institutions pointed out that this divergence would be a key observation point for the future direction of policy in the coming months.In the crypto market, BTC has recently been stable within the range of 116,000 to 119,000. There is support below 117,000, and selling pressure is concentrated in the 119,000 to 120,000 region, posing resistance to upward movement. Price fluctuations are being influenced by market expectations regarding the Fed&apos;s policy shift.Bitunix analyst recommendation: The policy divergence has intensified short-term market uncertainty. It is expected that BTC will continue to fluc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22449</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>