<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:13:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sequoia Capital: AI Wave Holds $100 Trillion Opportunity, Transformative Power to Rival Industrial Revolution</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26807</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Sequoia Capital has characterized the current wave of artificial intelligence as a profound &quot;Cognitive Revolution.&quot; It believes that its transformative power will be on a par with or even exceed that of the Industrial Revolution and holds a massive business opportunity of $10 trillion. Recently, Sequoia Capital partner Konstantine Buhler delivered a speech titled &quot;The AI Revolution: A $10 Trillion Wave, Grandier Than the Industrial Revolution.&quot; In the speech, it is clearly stated that the next battlefield for AI is the vast service industry market. Just like how SaaS software not only ate into the market share of traditional software but also significantly expanded the boundaries of the entire market, AI will also undergo disruptive reshaping and expansion in the service industry. Similarly, AI will radically reshape and expand industries such as law, accounting, and healthcare, which were traditionally dominated by large partnership firms. This will give rise to AI-dri</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 05:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26807</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 3 million USDC into HyperLiquid, shorted XPL with 1x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26806</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale deposited 3 million USDC into HyperLiquid and initiated a 1x leveraged short position on XPL.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26806</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: Bitcoin Will Become the Global Reserve Currency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26805</link>
      <description>On August 29th, CZ, the founder of Binance, stated at the BITCOIN ASIA 2025 conference that &quot;Bitcoin will become the global reserve currency.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26805</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH, SOL, and BTC Funds Flow Comparison: SOL Leads Recent Market Cap Appreciation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26804</link>
      <description>On August 29th, on-chain data analyst Murphy disclosed a comparison of the fund flows of ETH, SOL, and BTC. Realized Cap Inflows (RC-Inflows) signify the market&apos;s &quot;vote&quot; with real funds, and a faster growth indicates a higher direct flow of funds.On August 28th:The realized cap inflow of BTC was $1.17 billion, but from the 23rd to the 27th, the daily inflow was consistently less than $500 million.The realized cap inflow of ETH was $1.27 billion, and the daily inflows from the 23rd to the 27th were mostly above $500 million but below $1 billion.The realized cap inflow of SOL was $2.02 billion, and the daily inflows from the 23rd to the 27th were mostly above $1 billion.Recently, both SOL and ETH have surpassed BTC in realized cap inflow, and SOL&apos;s growth trend has slightly outperformed ETH in the past week. Previously, funds favored ETH, but now they are once again embracing SOL. This information is for educational purposes only and should not be regarded as investment advice.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26804</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSci Ecosystem AI Agent yesnoerror Announces Entry into Public Beta</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26803</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the DeSci ecosystem AI agent yesnoerror declared its entry into the public testing stage. The team is leveraging the latest AI model powered by the YNE token to review and analyze each new paper related to AI and computer science (more than 500 papers per day). yesnoerror intends to cross-chain the YNE token to Base (to be announced shortly, with technical development already completed), expand the audit scope beyond arXiv journals, and develop a personalized research AI agent in the future.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26803</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin&apos;s relative strength index (RSI) continues to decline, showing a similar bearish divergence to the 2021 bull market top.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26802</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the cryptocurrency analyst @ali_charts put out a chart analysis indicating that the Bitcoin price has been maintaining its position within a new high range. Meanwhile, the Relative Strength Index (RSI) has been on a downward trend, showing a divergence similar to that before the 2021 cycle peak.The RSI (Relative Strength Index) is a widely employed technical analysis indicator. It measures the speed and magnitude of price changes to determine whether the market is in an overbought or oversold state. The RSI ranges from 0 to 100. Values above 70 are generally regarded as overbought, suggesting that the price may be too high and at the risk of a pullback. Values below 30 are usually considered oversold, indicating that the price may be too low and is likely to rebound.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26802</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the US Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $1.789 billion, while the Ethereum Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $39.1 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26800</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as monitored by Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Bitcoin spot ETF yesterday was $178.9 million, and BlackRock IBIT received a net inflow of $63.7 million.Yesterday, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF was $39.1 million, marking the 6th consecutive day of net inflow. Among them, BlackRock ETHA witnessed a net inflow of $67.6 million, while Fidelity FETH saw a net outflow of $33.5 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Cook Faces New Mortgage Fraud Allegations Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26801</link>
      <description>August 29th: On this day, Mark Pullen, who is the Director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency, once more submitted another criminal charge regarding the third property of Federal Reserve Board Governor Cook in Massachusetts to the Department of Justice. The charge asserts that Cook obtained a mortgage of $361,000 for an apartment in Massachusetts and claimed it as a second home. Eight months later, Cook claimed to have received rental income ranging from $15,000 to $50,000 and classified it as an investment property.Cook may be engaged in Reverse Occupancy Fraud. In this type of fraud, a borrower purchases a property as an investment but initially falsely represents it as a primary or secondary residence in order to obtain a lower mortgage rate or more favorable loan terms. Subsequently, the borrower may change the property&apos;s use by declaring rental income to conform to the definition of an investment property.BlockBeats had previously reported that a judge in charge of the case</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26801</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport appeared at Bitcoin Asia2025 to discuss how Asian institutions are leading the way in seizing new opportunities in Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26799</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Matrixport was extended an invitation to attend the Bitcoin Asia Summit and took part in a panel discussion entitled &quot;Asian Institutions Leading the Commencement of a New Bitcoin Era.&quot;During the event, Matrixport&apos;s COO, Cynthia Wu, pointed out that the digital asset investment is undergoing a substantial transformation. An increasing number of investors and corporate treasuries are regarding Bitcoin as a long-term asset allocation. They are continuously accumulating rather than engaging in short-term speculation. ETFs and stock tokens have made it more accessible for the general public to invest in digital assets, significantly reducing the learning curve. In just two years, the combined market value of these two has exceeded $260 billion and is approaching the current market capitalization of stablecoins. It can be anticipated that with the proliferation of stablecoins, the market capitalization of Bitcoin still has the potential to grow tenfold in the coming years.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 04:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26799</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XPL on Hyperliquid Continues to Surge, Breaking $1.1 Mark with a 36% Premium Over Binance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26798</link>
      <description>On August 29th, on Hyperliquid (accessible via https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD), XPL continued to experience a surge and broke through $1.1. The current annualized funding rate stands at an extremely high 254%, with a 36% positive premium compared to $0.808 on Binance.Early yesterday morning, Hyperliquid implemented a new mark price calculation method for pre-market perpetual contracts. The mark price of the contract will utilize the standard mark price formula and be combined with the price of external pre-market perpetual contracts (if available).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 03:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26798</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>