<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:18:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: U.S. Fiscal Uncertainty Still Core Driver of Hard Asset Appreciation, but Short-Term Consolidation Possible</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22789</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Matrixport released its latest report indicating that the core catalyst for Bitcoin&apos;s new round of increase is gradually coming into view. Although there have been frequent positive developments in Ethereum (such as ETF inflows, increasing institutional allocations, and the SEC possibly approving staking mechanisms), the funding rate has only risen to 15%, suggesting that the market heat has not yet completely dissipated.The report mentioned that August and September have historically been relatively weak months for Bitcoin&apos;s performance throughout the year. With the latest FOMC meeting having concluded and the next meeting scheduled for September 17th, lacking short-term policy catalysts, the market may shift into a wait-and-see mode and enter a consolidation phase.Furthermore, U.S. fiscal uncertainty remains a core driver of the rise in hard assets. The recent proposal by Trump for a $5 trillion debt ceiling expansion plan has already led to a more than 10% increas</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22789</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum briefly dropped below $3,600, marking a 4.64% decrease in the last 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22788</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to HTX market data, Ethereum briefly fell below $3,600 and is currently trading at $3,611, with a 24-hour decrease of 4.64%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22788</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Reserve Concept Stock Pre-market Generally Down, BMNR Pre-market Down 6.9%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22787</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on the market data from Rockflow, the pre-market trading of US crypto stock reserve concept stocks generally declined. This includes:The largest holder of Ethereum, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), saw a 6.9% drop in the pre-market;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) experienced a 5.74% pre-market drop;MSTR saw a 3.03% pre-market drop;CRCL had a 3.71% pre-market drop;Coinbase witnessed a 11.07% pre-market drop.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22787</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions, a digital identity verification platform, has raised $30 million in funding, with participation from Polychain, Coinbase Ventures, and others.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22786</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to official channels, the digital identity verification platform Billions declared that it has successfully completed a financing round of $30 million. This round of financing was spearheaded by Polychain, Coinbase Ventures, Polygon, LibertyCityVentures, BITKRAFT Ventures, and others. The funds from this financing round will be employed to construct the first universal human-machine and artificial intelligence network.The Billions Network is a digital identity verification platform formulated to offer a future of mutual trust between humans and artificial intelligence. The platform makes use of zero-knowledge proof technology to provide a scalable and secure approach to verifying the identities of both humans and artificial intelligence.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22786</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Insider Trader」 @qwatio&apos;s short position opened this morning is now up over $3.3 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22785</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio&apos;s short positions in BTC (40x) and ETH (25x) opened this morning have now amassed a profit of over $3.3 million.This morning, the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio transferred 2.98 million USDC to Hyperliquid to initiate short positions in BTC and ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22785</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ark Invest bought 60,000 shares of Figma yesterday, worth approximately $6.93 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22784</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to Ark Invest Daily, Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest purchased 60,000 shares of Figma the previous day. Given the closing price of $115.5, the stake is valued at around $6.93 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin drops below $114,000, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach $609 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22783</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin drops below $114,000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $609 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin exceeds $116,000, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEXs will only be $73.97 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of the contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to the adjacent liquidation cluster, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the asset&apos;s price reaching a certain level will be impacted. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that when the price reaches that level, a more intense reaction will occur due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22783</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The smart money that successfully went from a long ETH position to a short position on the 30th has today transitioned from a Bitcoin short position to a long position, and has opened a long positi...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22782</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on on-chain information, a shrewd whale today converted their Bitcoin short position into a long position and established an ETH long position. As of the time of writing, the address holds a total of $3.61 million worth of 25x leveraged Ethereum longs and $1.8 million worth of 40x leveraged Bitcoin longs.Earlier, on July 30th, this shrewd whale flipped their ETH longs to shorts at an entry price of $3,803.This address has cumulatively earned nearly $36 million in profits on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22782</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch MOMOFUN (MM) on August 3rd</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22781</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on official information, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list MOMOFUN (MM) on August 3rd. Qualified users will be able to utilize their Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop on the Alpha activity page once trading commences. Further details will be made known shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22781</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ai.ac&apos;s first AI Agent Token, MIA Token, has officially landed on Binance Alpha, leading the AgentFi new era.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22780</link>
      <description>August 1st, the first AI Avatar token MIA of ai.ac officially landed on Binance Alpha, presenting a global opportunity for users to participate in the Avatar economy! ai.ac, incubated by Web3 accelerator amber.ac under the Amber Group, is a pioneering Avatar economy platform. As the first Avatar born on this platform, MIA has the capability to independently handle marketing, financing, operations, community management, value creation, and distribution, aiming to promote the Avatar economy and provide returns to its token-holding community.MIA is the core token of the MIA ecosystem and serves as the foundation of the incentive mechanism and a practical tool. Its distribution mechanism and unlocking rules are designed to ensure sustainable growth. MIA will continuously collaborate with top AI projects to advance the Avatar economy infrastructure and assist in creating an AI Avatar-driven AgentFi ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22780</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>