<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:30:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Holds Interest Rate Steady, Monitors Progress of US-EU Trade Negotiations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21700</link>
      <description>July 24th - On Thursday, the European Central Bank (ECB) maintained its key interest rate at 2%. It was waiting for clearer indications regarding the direction of EU-US trade relations. Current inflation has dropped back to the 2% target level, and the rate has been reduced from 4% to 2% since June of last year. The policy pressure on the ECB has significantly eased. The ECB stated that it would continue to adhere to a &quot;meeting-by-meeting&quot; policy without predefined interest rate paths, with all decisions based on the latest data.The statement suggested that the latest information generally aligns with previous judgments on the inflation outlook. Domestic price pressures are continuing to ease, and wage growth is slowing down. The market is still anticipating at least one more rate cut later this year. Market focus has shifted to President Lagarde&apos;s subsequent press conference, where she is likely to face intense questioning about whether to continue cutting rates in the future, the s</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21700</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy CEO: Ethereum Poised to Outperform Bitcoin in Next 3 to 6 Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21699</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Michael Novogratz, the CEO of Galaxy Digital, stated in an interview with Squawk Box that Ethereum has the potential to outperform Bitcoin within the next 3 to 6 months. (CNBC)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21699</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Keeps Interest Rates Unchanged</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21698</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the European Central Bank maintained the deposit facility rate at -2% without any change, which was in line with market expectations. After seven consecutive rate cuts in previous meetings, the main refinancing rate and the marginal lending rate remained unchanged at 0.00% and 0.25% respectively. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21698</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will accept Circle&apos;s stablecoin USYC as collateral from institutional clients</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21697</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to the report in Fortune, Circle announced that Binance will commence accepting USYC (a stablecoin that distributes yields to investors) as collateral from institutional clients. Although many institutional traders using platforms like Binance will use Bitcoin or other crypto assets as collateral, some traditional institutions still hesitate to do so.Catherine Chen, Binance VIP and Head of Institutional Business, stated that one of the reasons is the recent collapse of FTX, which has made many people wary of providing collateral on exchanges. Binance is trying to address this issue through a service called &quot;Banking Triparty&quot;. This service involves Binance partnering with traditional banks to act as custodians and using the assets held by the banks as collateral for cryptocurrency trading. She added that many partners are working with Binance to integrate USYC, which will provide faster settlement times. Binance also announced that it will integrate anot</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21697</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semler Scientific has increased its holdings by 175 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 5021 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21696</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the US-listed company Semler Scientific increased its holdings of BTC by 175 coins, raising its total holdings to 5021 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHA Asset Surpasses $10 Billion, Sets Historic Third-Fastest Record</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21695</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas said, &quot;ETHA has just broken through the $10 billion asset under management (AUM) mark within a year and has become the third fastest ETF to reach this milestone in history, only trailing behind two Bitcoin ETFs: IBIT and FBTC. It has surged from $5 billion to $10 billion in just 10 days and currently ranks among the top five in terms of fund flows in the past month and week.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21695</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deBridge Foundation is launching a Reserve Fund, which will use all protocol revenue to buy back the DBR token</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21694</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per The Block, the deBridge Foundation has initiated a Reserve Fund. 100% of the protocol revenue is dedicated to purchasing its native DBR token on the open market. As of July 24th, since its launch in June, the fund has already repurchased 1.3% of the total DBR supply, which amounts to nearly $3 million. The deBridge treasury currently holds $30.10 million in assets, including DBR, USDC, SOL, and ETH. Additionally, the fund is exploring yield strategies and has launched a public dashboard to offer real-time tracking of assets and yields.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21694</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana developers are considering increasing the network&apos;s block capacity by 66%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21693</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per Coindesk, with the growth in the demand for block space, Solana developers are contemplating a 66% augmentation in the network block capacity. According to a document disseminated by core contributors this week, the novel proposal, SIMD-0286, proposes elevating Solana&apos;s computational unit (CU) limit per block from 60 million to 100 million. The proposal is intended to enable Solana to handle a greater number of transactions and support more intricate applications like decentralized exchanges (DEX), MEV systems, and re-staking protocols without encountering the computational limit.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21693</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Value of around $23.8 billion worth of ETH is currently staked in the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $11.4 billion worth of ETH is waiting to join.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21692</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on validatorqueue data, currently around 653,000 ETH (which is approximately equivalent to $23.8 billion at the current price) is awaiting to exit the Ethereum PoS network. The waiting time for exit is approximately 11 days and 8 hours. Meanwhile, more than 312,000 ETH, amounting to $11.4 billion, is queued to join the network, and the expected activation delay is about 5 days and 10 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21692</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &quot;Hodl 14.5-Year 3,962 BTC&quot; address has transferred its 3,962 BTC to a new address.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21691</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as monitored by Whale Alert, the &quot;Dormant for 14.5 years with 3962 BTC&quot; address transferred 3962 BTC to a new address beginning with bc1qcz 15 minutes ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21691</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>