<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The game asset trading platform OVERTAKE has completed a $7 million strategic financing round, with participation from Sui and others.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25353</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, the game asset trading platform OVERTAKE declared the completion of a $7 million strategic financing round. Sui, ItemMania, ItemBay, JB Investment, Green Whale Ventures, and Immutable took part in the investment.OVERTAKE is a peer-to-peer game asset trading market established on the Sui Network, allowing for secure transactions by means of smart contract escrow.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25353</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: US Expands &quot;Stocks for Boosters&quot; to TSMC or Samsung; ETH Key Support at 4100 to 4150 for Rebound</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25352</link>
      <description>August 20th: According to insiders, the U.S. Commerce Secretary Raimondo is advocating for a government stake in exchange for subsidies under the &quot;Chip Act&quot;. The scope may potentially expand from Intel to Micron, TSMC, and Samsung. The White House has confirmed that it is collaborating with Intel on a 10% government stake deal, and some existing subsidies may be renegotiated. This move is likely to enhance the U.S.&apos;s discourse power in the AI supply chain but has also triggered governance and fiscal controversies. In the crypto market, there is a notable buying interest around 4100 - 4150 for ETH, with secondary support at 3900 - 4000.Bitunix analyst&apos;s recommendation:If the &quot;Stock-for-Subsidy&quot; plan is put into practice, it is expected that AI capital expenditures and risk appetite will rise; conversely, if policy progress is hindered, volatility will increase. It is recommended that investors focus on policy developments and the technological stock funding landscape, and avoid chas</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea&apos;s third largest exchange, Coinone, has launched the PARTI/KRW trading pair.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25351</link>
      <description>August 20th. As per an official announcement, on August 21st in local time, South Korea&apos;s third-largest exchange, Coinone, is set to open the PARTI/KRW trading pair at 12:00 (Thursday). Previously, the Particle Network announced a narrative upgrade to an RWA and stablecoin universal trading layer and landed on South Korea&apos;s second-largest exchange, Bithumb, as well as Europe&apos;s largest financial technology company, Revolut.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25351</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Son to Acquire Mining Firm Dogehash, Whose Technology Partner is Miner Manufacturer ElphaPex</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25350</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the holding company of Donald Trump&apos;s son, Thumzup (with the Nasdaq stock code: TZUP), is going to acquire Dogehash Technologies through an all-stock transaction. The company will be rebranded as &quot;Dogehash Technologies Holdings, Inc.&quot; and will be listed on Nasdaq under the new stock code &quot;XDOG.&quot; It is expected that the transaction will be completed by the end of this year.As the world&apos;s first industrial-level mining company dedicated to Dogecoin, the technology partner behind Dogehash is the mining machine manufacturer ElphaPex. The two parties have also reached a strategic partnership. Currently, DogeHash Technologies operates more than 2,500 ElphaPex DG1+ mining machines, which are mainly powered by renewable energy sources.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25350</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s eldest son&apos;s holding company will acquire the mining firm Dogehash, whose technology partner is the mining hardware manufacturer ElphaPex.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25349</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Thumzup Holding Company (NASDAQ: TZUP) of Donald Trump&apos;s son is set to acquire Dogehash Technologies in an all-stock transaction. The company will be rebranded as &quot;Dogehash Technologies Holdings, Inc.&quot; and will be traded on Nasdaq under the new ticker symbol &quot;XDOG.&quot; This transaction is anticipated to be completed by the end of the current year.As the world&apos;s first industrial-grade mining company specifically dedicated to Dogecoin, Dogehash&apos;s technology partner is the mining machine manufacturer ElphaPex. The two parties have entered into a strategic partnership, and currently, DogeHash Technologies is operating more than 2,500 ElphaPex DG1+ miners, which are mainly powered by renewable energy sources.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25349</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXC Announces Establishment of MEXC Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25348</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per official channels, MEXC announced the formation of the MEXC Foundation, which is aimed at expediting the healthy growth and inclusive popularization of the blockchain industry and the Web3 ecosystem. The foundation will stimulate innovation and educational cultivation by means of various projects and targeted support, enabling blockchain to become a genuine driving force for significant and transformative alterations.The MEXC Foundation is dedicated to promoting a comprehensive foundation for Web3 education, popularization, and social influence, with a focus on sustainable ecosystem development. In April 2025, MEXC launched a $30 million CSR program (now integrated into the MEXC Foundation) to enhance long-term social impact through global projects and partnerships. As MEXC gradually transitions from a single trading platform into a comprehensive ecosystem, it will continuously empower global communities and high-growth regions, facilitating their active partic</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25348</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address added 200 more BTC to its position 5 hours ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25347</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale address added another 200 BTC (approximately $22.72 million) to its holdings five hours ago. During the past month, this address has accumulated a total of 1721 BTC from FalconX, which amounts to approximately $196 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25347</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget will list AriaAI (ARIA) in the Innovation Zone and GameFi Zone</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25346</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Bitget will list AriaAI (ARIA) in the Innovation Zone and the GameFi Zone.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25346</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Surges Temporarily to Break $114,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25345</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin experienced a rebound and briefly exceeded $114,000. It is now trading at $113,957.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25345</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rate display indicates that the market is almost entirely bearish.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25344</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on Coinglass data, the current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rates suggest that the market is almost entirely in a bearish trend.**BlockBeats Note**: The Funding Rate is a rate set by cryptocurrency exchanges to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price. It is usually applicable to perpetual contracts and is a mechanism for the exchange of funds between long and short traders. The exchange does not collect this fee but uses it to adjust the cost or profit of traders holding contracts to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the Funding Rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the Funding Rate is above 0.01%, it indicates a generally bullish market. When the Funding Rate is below 0.005%, it indicates a generally bearish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>