<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:20:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>eToro to Launch Tokenized Stocks on the Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22336</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the online trading platform eToro announced that it will launch a tokenized US stock service on the Ethereum blockchain. This enables users to buy and trade tokenized US stocks on the blockchain as a strategic step towards a tokenized future. During a webinar held on Tuesday, eToro disclosed that it will offer a 24/5 trading service for the initial 100 popular US-listed stocks and ETFs (serving as underlying assets), allowing users to trade outside of traditional market hours. eToro has also formed a partnership with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange Group to launch spot price futures. These futures are currently available in some European markets, with plans to further expand their coverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s PEPE Long Position Partially Liquidated 8 Times in a Row, Losing Nearly $1 Million in the Past Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22334</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, James Wynn&apos;s 10x PEPE long position has consecutively undergone liquidation 8 times. In the past week, he has lost nearly $1 million, and there is only $32,000 left in the wallet.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22334</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Simply buying ETH and holding for three months will be simpler than chasing hot coins on-chain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22335</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio expressed his views on the market trend for the upcoming months. He stated, &quot;In my opinion, after a risk adjustment, the number of coins that can outperform BTC and ETH in the coming months will be quite limited. Certainly, there may be some unexpected meme coins that experience a sudden surge. However, betting on these coins in advance is similar to playing a highly difficult game. Now that the market has reached a relatively high level, I may be more inclined to hold mainstream coins and reduce high-risk speculative trading. Instead of chasing the next hot coin on-chain and experiencing significant volatility, it is much simpler to simply buy and hold ETH for three months without taking any action and then sell it to earn a 50% profit.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22335</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase Raises Robinhood Stock Price Target for 2026, Doubles It to $98</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22333</link>
      <description>July 29th: The price target for Robinhood stock at JPMorgan Chase has been doubled to $98 in 2026. Meanwhile, Robinhood is scheduled to announce its second-quarter earnings on Wednesday. JPMorgan Chase retains a Neutral rating on Robinhood and anticipates that Robinhood will earn $0.31 per share, which is an increase from $0.21 in the same period of the previous year. JPMorgan Chase holds the view that Robinhood&apos;s initiatives in cryptocurrency and tokenized finance will enhance its operational leverage and generate long-term profit potential.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22333</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve July Meeting Voter Count Drops to 11</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22332</link>
      <description>July 29th: Due to personal reasons, Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard will be absent from this week&apos;s policy meeting. As a result, the number of voting members for this interest rate decision will be decreased to 11. Governors Waller and Bowman may have different views and support a rate cut, yet the committee still has a substantial majority to maintain the interest rate at its current level. There is no one to take Governor Brainard&apos;s seat as a substitute. However, the President&apos;s vote can act as a replacement. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22332</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL drops below $180, with a 24-hour decrease of 4.23%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22331</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on HTX market data, SOL dropped below $180, showing a 24-hour percentage change of -4.23%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22331</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid: Notice of Order System Malfunction, Investigation Underway</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22330</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Hyperliquid team provided a response on Discord regarding the &quot;Order System Malfunction Preventing Users from Placing Trades&quot; issue. Currently, the matter is being investigated, and they will promptly communicate the latest information.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22330</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Stock Ethereum Reserve Concept Stocks Experience Collective Pullback, BMNR and GAME Drop Over 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22329</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on the market data from RockFlow, the concept stocks related to Ethereum reserves in the US stock market all saw a pullback. Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) and GameSquare (GAME) decreased by more than 10%, SharpLink Gaming (SBET) and Bit Digital (BTBT) dropped by more than 7%, and BTCS Inc (BTCS) declined by nearly 4%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22329</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit and Entrance Queue Sees Slight Increase, with ~$25.7 Billion ETH Queued for Exit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22328</link>
      <description>July 29th. Based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website ValidatorQueue, the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 676,000 ETH, with a recent peak of 744,000 ETH. On July 16th, this number was only 1,920 ETH, and on July 15th, there was no need to queue for exit. Calculated at the current price, approximately $25.7 billion worth of ETH is exiting the PoS network, and the withdrawal delay has extended to 11 days and 18 hours.At the same time, the staking demand for new validator activations has witnessed a turning point after a recent surge. On July 17th, there were 435,000 ETH queued to enter the network, but today, the admission queue has dropped to 245,000 ETH, worth about $9.3 billion, with a current queue time of 4 days and 6 hours.Andy Cronk, the Co-founder of the staking service provider Figment, previously stated: &quot;People unstake and sell to lock in profits when the price rises, and both retail and institutional participan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched the U-based TREE perpetual contract, with leverage ranging from 1 to 75x.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22327</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, Bitget has declared the listing of the U-index TREE perpetual contract. The leverage offered ranges from 1 to 75x. Additionally, the contract trading BOT will be launched simultaneously.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22327</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>