<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:55:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list Treehouse (TREE) U-Settled Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22318</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to an official announcement, Binance&apos;s Savings, One-Click Buy, Instant Exchange, Leverage, and Futures will list Treehouse (TREE). It will involve the listing of a TREE 1-75x leverage inverse perpetual contract on July 29, 2025, at 22:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22318</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. listed company AEHL signs $50 million financing agreement, plans to purchase Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22316</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the US-listed company Antelope Holdings Limited (AEHL) announced today that it has reached a Securities Purchase Agreement with the US investment firm Streeterville Capital. The total financing amount is $50 million. According to the agreement, the funds will be disbursed in installments within 24 months and will be used for purchasing Bitcoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22316</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Open: Cryptocurrency Stocks Mixed, &apos;BNB Version MicroStrategy&apos; VAPE Down 13%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22317</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to the market data from RockFlow, the U.S. stock market opened with the Dow Jones down by 0.01%, the Nasdaq up by 0.51%, and the S&amp;P 500 up by 0.25%. Cryptocurrency stocks fluctuated, including:The new &quot;BNB Version MicroStrategy,&quot; CEA Industries (VAPE), plunged by 13% after a 548.85% surge yesterday. CEA Industries and 10X Capital announced a $500 million private placement yesterday with the support of YZi Labs to establish the world&apos;s largest publicly traded BNB financial company;Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR) dropped by 1.2%, with the total Ethereum holdings reaching approximately 625,000 coins and ranking first in institutional holdings;ZOOZ Power Ltd. (ZOOZ) plummeted by 37% and announced a $180 million private placement today to launch a Bitcoin treasury reserve strategy;The &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy,&quot; SharpLink (SBET), fell by 1.7%; Riot Platforms (RIOT) declined by 0.52%; MicroStrategy (MSTR) dropped by 0.05%; Coinbase (COIN) rose by 0.32%</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22317</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market News: Pump.fun will increase the PUMP token buyback rate, using 100% of daily revenue for buybacks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22315</link>
      <description>July 29th: As per market intelligence, Pump.fun is set to enhance the token buyback ratio and will utilize 100% of its daily revenue for buybacks.BlockBeats Note: Pump.fun has not provided an official response yet. According to on-chain data, the protocol income of Pump.fun in the past two days was approximately $500,000, and it has repurchased PUMP tokens worth $500,000, which is in line with the speculation of the community.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22315</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase announces support for Samsung Pay for buying and depositing</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22314</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to official information, Coinbase announced that Samsung Pay will soon be accessible as a payment and deposit option. It will initially be launched for users in the United States and Canada. Coinbase users in North America will be able to utilize Samsung Pay to directly top up cryptocurrency within the Coinbase app, and there are plans to expand to other regions in the future.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22314</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Ethereum Ecosystem Projects Jointly Release &quot;Believe in somETHing&quot; Post to Celebrate Ethereum&apos;s 10th Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22313</link>
      <description>On July 29th, a number of Ethereum ecosystem projects such as the Ethereum Foundation, Ondo Finance, Metamask, Consensys, Synthetix, and others jointly posted a picture accompanied by the caption &quot;Believe in somETHing&quot; to mark the 10th anniversary of Ethereum&apos;s launch.Previously, the Ethereum Foundation announced that the 10th-anniversary celebration livestream would be held on July 30th at 14:30 UTC (22:30 Beijing time). The celebration event will be global, and within 24 hours after the event, free minting of Ethereum Torch commemorative NFTs will be available. Ethereum has introduced &quot;The Torch&quot; NFT to pay tribute to those who have shaped its development and values in its first decade, and it will assist in supporting the future development of Ethereum. In the 10 days leading up to Ethereum&apos;s 10th anniversary, this Torch NFT will symbolically be passed between wallets. On July 30th, The Torch NFT will be burned to commemorate Ethereum&apos;s founding anniversary. On that day, everyone</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22313</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMNR Ethereum Total Supply Reaches Approximately 625,000 Coins, Ranking First in Institutional Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22312</link>
      <description>On July 29th, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR), which is the top holder of Ethereum among US-listed crypto reserve companies, disclosed data indicating that the total holdings of BTC have reached 192 coins and the total holdings of ETH have reached approximately 625,000 coins. The company has increased its ETH holdings by 58,224 coins, with a net asset value per share of $22.77.This evening, BMNR announced a $1 billion stock buyback plan.According to RockFlow market data, Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) briefly dropped more than 14% in pre-market trading today; however, the current decline has narrowed to 11%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX will list TREEUSDT perpetual contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22311</link>
      <description>July 29th. As per an official announcement, OKX is set to officially launch the TREEUSDT perpetual contract at 10:30 p.m. (UTC+8) on July 29, 2025, across the web, app, and API. It is reported that Treehouse is a decentralized fixed income layer that has pioneered a cryptocurrency fixed income benchmark.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22311</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「ETH Version of MicroStrategy」 SharpLink: Aiming to Hold 1 Million Ether</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22310</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink (SBET) team officially declared that their objective is to possess 1 million Ethereum, and they are getting closer to the goal than you might imagine, with the process accelerating.Today, the &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink (SBET) team announced that they currently hold around 438,190 Ethereum.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22310</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degen Foundation Seeks Community Input on PHASED DEGEN Token Burn</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22309</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the Degen Foundation officially declared that currently, the foundation holds 32.5% of the DEGEN token supply. Although this fund could be employed for future airdrops (such as in Degen applications or other projects), it would lead to a dilution of the existing holders&apos; stakes. The foundation requires a certain number of DEGEN tokens to support development, but it is not allowed to exceed 30%. Such a significant token supply has aroused concerns among new users regarding future inflation.The Degen Foundation has put forward a plan to gradually destroy DEGEN tokens, steadily burning tokens each month until reaching a sustainable long-term development supply level. At the same time, it will also reward long-term holders. The foundation will not burn all of its holdings, but this will change the tokenomics and may potentially eliminate any large-scale airdrops in the future. The foundation is seeking community feedback on this matter.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22309</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>