<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:21:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>WLD surged over 23% in the last 24 hours, now trading at $1.298</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28117</link>
      <description>On September 8th, based on HTX market data, WLD witnessed a surge of over 23% within the past 24 hours and is currently trading at $1.298.This morning, Amber Group withdrew 4.68 million WLD from Binance, with a value of $4.92 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28117</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashKey Group is planning to launch a cryptocurrency treasury fund with an initial size exceeding $500 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28116</link>
      <description>September 8th: HashKey Group announced on September 8th that it intends to establish the largest multi-currency DAT ecosystem fund in Asia. The initial fundraising goal is projected to surpass $500 million, with a concentration on DAT projects within the Ethereum (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC) ecosystems.HashKey disclosed that the aforementioned fund will center around DAT strategies, making investments in a collection of DAT projects centered on mainstream crypto assets to construct a diversified investment portfolio. The distinctiveness lies in its structure as an open-ended fund that enables periodic subscription and redemption, aiming to be in line with the long-term operational goals and liquidity requirements of DAT.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28116</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Whale Sells Over 100,000 BTC in the Past 30 Days, Setting a New Record for the Largest Sell-off Since Mid-2022</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28113</link>
      <description>On September 8th, the CryptoQuant analyst caueconomy stated on Friday that within the past thirty days, the whale reserves (ranging from 1k to 10k BTC) have decreased by more than 100,000 bitcoins. This indicates a strong risk-off sentiment among large investors. Currently, we are still observing major participants reducing their portfolios, and this may continue to exert pressure on Bitcoin in the coming weeks.caueconomy pointed out that this selling pressure &quot;has damaged the price structure in the short term&quot; and ultimately pushed the price below $108,000. According to CryptoQuant&apos;s data, this is the largest whale sell-off since July 2022. As of Saturday, Bitcoin whales have sold off 114,920 coins in the past 30 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28113</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Gate will list LiveArt (ART)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28115</link>
      <description>September 8th. According to an official announcement, Gate is set to list LiveArt (ART) for spot trading on September 9th at 20:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28115</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched a new VIP Wealth Management event, with a USDC savings rate reaching 8.6% APR.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28114</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Bitget initiated a new round of VIP Wealth Management activity. VIPs were provided with an APR of 8.6% on USDC flexible savings. Users could access Bitget Easy Earn to participate in the corresponding subscription.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28114</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley: The Fed is expected to cut rates by 25 basis points in both September and October, compared to the previous expectation of cuts in September and December</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28112</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Morgan Stanley anticipates that the Federal Reserve will reduce interest rates by 25 basis points in both September and October. Previously, it was expected to be in September and December. (Financial Times)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Monetary Easing Expectations Fully Priced In, Interest Rate Cut Unable to Propel Bitcoin Rebound Above $120,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28111</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Rachael Lucas, a cryptocurrency analyst at BTC Markets, stated: &quot;The soft US jobs report did give rise to expectations for a more dovish stance from the Federal Reserve. Generally speaking, this kind of situation supports risk assets like Bitcoin. However, the market has already incorporated a certain degree of policy easing. At the same time, we observe that institutional investors are taking profits, while ETF fund flows remain relatively stable. The resistance level of Bitcoin is at $113,400. There is further resistance at $115,400 and $117,100. Breaking through these resistance levels indicates that the market has absorbed the recent selling pressure and is ready to retest the highs.&quot;Kronos Research&apos;s Chief Information Officer Vincent Liu also said that even if the Federal Reserve decides to lower interest rates, the Bitcoin price may still remain relatively weak. &quot;Interest rate cuts may indicate a weak economy. Meanwhile, persistent high inflation and cautious</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28111</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jia Yueting: To Announce Three Major Growth Engines of Crypto Treasury and EAI Vehicle Chain Strategy, C10 Treasury Adds $2 Million in Digital Asset Allocation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28109</link>
      <description>On September 8th, Jia Yueting posted that &quot;The scale of C10 Treasury is expanding. The three major growth engines and the EAI Vehicle Chain strategy will be announced soon. At the same time, C10 Treasury is increasing the allocation of digital assets by $2 million.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28109</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays: Expects the Fed to Cut Interest Rates Three Times This Year, by 25 Basis Points Each Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28110</link>
      <description>On September 8th, from Barclays: It is expected that the Federal Reserve will reduce interest rates three times in 2025, with each reduction being 25 basis points. These cuts are anticipated to occur in September, October, and December, surpassing the previous forecast of two 25-basis-point cuts in September and December. (FX678)Previously, Standard Chartered Bank projected a 50-basis-point rate cut by the Federal Reserve in September.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28110</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected ConsenSys-Linked Address Buys $1.2M Worth of REX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28108</link>
      <description>On September 8th, according to @Andrey_10gwei, an address suspected to be affiliated with ConsenSys purchased $1.2 million worth of REX tokens of the Linea ecosystem DEX protocol Etherex in the past two weeks.On August 16th, address 0x0521b received 1.25 million USDC from the MetaMask multisig address and then bought REX. Subsequently, the tokens from this address were transferred to a new multisig address and REX was staked.ConsenSys, a software company founded by Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin, has cryptographic projects including the crypto wallet MetaMask and the Ethereum L2 solution Linea.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 04:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28108</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>