<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:41:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed Taper Talk」: Vacancy Rate Falls Below 1 for the First Time Since Early 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27579</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, &quot;Fed Whisperer&quot; Nick Timiraos wrote that by September 2024, job openings in July had dropped to the lowest level since September 2024, and the three-month average remained at approximately 7.4 million openings.The job openings to unemployment ratio fell below 1 for the first time since the early 2021.[Here are the two images:](https://image.theblockbeats.info/file_v6/20250903/4078efb8-6466-4fc1-8dd6-7a3cc1e9bbd9.png?x-oss-process=image/quality,q_50/format,webp) [Image description: Something related to the job market data.](https://image.theblockbeats.info/file_v6/20250903/62cdd25f-5934-4d3f-86da-af9437b38911.png?x-oss-process=image/quality,q_50/format,webp) [Image description: Another aspect related to the job market data.]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27579</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bitcoin Halts Trading Again, Surges 59%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27578</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Trump family&apos;s mining firm American Bitcoin once more led to a trading halt, and the price surged by 59%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27578</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following the release of the US employment data, the probability of a Fed rate cut in September has increased to 98%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27577</link>
      <description>September 3rd: Following the release of the US employment data, the likelihood of a Fed rate cut in September has increased to 98%. (Xinhua Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27577</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve of Boston: Still Appropriate to Cut Rates Once by 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27576</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Atlanta Fed&apos;s Bostic once again emphasized that he considers a rate cut this year to be appropriate. However, this view may change based on the situations of inflation and the labor market. &quot;I believe that although price stability remains a top priority, the labor market has slowed down sufficiently. Therefore, some accommodation (possibly a rate cut of around 25 basis points) will be suitable for the rest of the year.&quot;&quot;The situation can change depending on the future path of inflation and the development of the labor market.&quot; Regarding inflation, Bostic stated that he still has concerns that the impact of tariffs on prices may last. &quot;I still think that the impact of tariffs on prices will not disappear quickly. In fact, it will not fully show up in the coming months. I will not be complacent and simply assume that expectations will remain stable and there will be no other inflation outbreak.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bitcoin triggered a temporary halt, surging 31% before the halt.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27575</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Bitcoin mining company affiliated with the Trump family, American Bitcoin, triggered a volatility trading halt, with a 31% surge before the halt. (Oriental Fortune Network)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27575</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In July, the US JOLTS Job Openings stood at 7.181 million, compared to an expected 7.378 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27572</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the number of US July JOLTs Job Openings was 7.181 million. The expected value was 7.378 million, and the previous value was revised from 7.437 million to 7.357 million. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27572</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Bank of Boston: Soft Job Market Warrants Some Policy Accommodation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27574</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Boston Fed of the Federal Reserve stated that the labor market is not significantly weak, and the risks facing the Federal Reserve&apos;s two major mandates have become more balanced. A weak employment market implies that some policy easing is appropriate. Price stability remains a top priority. (Xinhua News Agency)US Treasury yields continue to decline, with the 10-year yield decreasing by 4.1 basis points to 4.236%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27574</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Family Mining Firm American Bitcoin Applies to Raise Up to $2.1 Billion through a Market Price Offering</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27573</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Bitcoin mining company American Bitcoin owned by the Trump family has submitted an application to raise up to $2.1 billion through a market price offering.American Bitcoin, which is set to make its debut this Wednesday, will be officially listed on the Nasdaq Stock Exchange after completing a merger with Gryphon Digital Mining.Donald Trump Jr, Eric Trump, and the mining company Hut 8 will jointly own 98% of the new entity formed after the merger. The new entity will retain the name American Bitcoin and will be traded under the stock symbol ABTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27573</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dollar Index (DXY) retreats by 10 points in the short term, while spot gold edges up by $5 in the short term.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27571</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, following the release of the U.S. July JOLTs Job Openings data, the Dollar Index (DXY) witnessed a short-term decline of 10 points and is currently trading at 98.19. Spot gold prices saw a short-term increase of $5 and are now at $3556.67 per ounce.The U.S. Treasury yield continued to fall. The 10-year yield decreased by 4.1 basis points to 4.236%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27571</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Launches Ondo Special Zone, Supports Spot Trading, and Introduces 26 Popular Trading Pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27570</link>
      <description>September 3rd. Gate, a world-renowned cryptocurrency exchange, announced the launch of the Ondo Zone and simultaneously initiated spot trading. In the first phase, 26 popular Ondo trading pairs will be introduced, such as AAPLON, METAON, TSLAON, NVDAON, SPYON, QQQON, etc., providing global users with a convenient and efficient on-chain Ondo trading experience. To celebrate the official launch of the Ondo Zone, Gate will hold a CandyDrop event from September 4th at 12:00 to September 17th at 12:00 (UTC+8). Users engaging in Ondo Zone trading will have the chance to share 384,615 ONDO tokens, with a maximum of 220 ONDO tokens per person.This zone is launched through the collaboration between Gate and Ondo, adopting a compliant real-world asset tokenization model. All listed tokens are linked to publicly traded stocks, have full asset collateral, support on-chain free transfer and trading, and can achieve seamless integration across different blockchains and multiple ecosystems. The Gat</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27570</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>