<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:06:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A new address withdrew 450 Bitcoins from Binance, totaling $53.22 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24940</link>
      <description>August 17th. As per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet withdrew 450 BTC from Binance, with a value of $53.22 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24940</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Deposited 3492 ETH to Binance in the Past 24 Hours, Profiting $17.37 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24939</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale deposited 3492 ETH into Binance within the past 24 hours. The value of this deposit is $15.57 million, and the profit made is $17.37 million.Initially, two years ago, this whale withdrew 5800 ETH from Binance, with a value of $10.25 million. Currently, this whale still holds 2650 ETH, which is worth $12 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24939</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee Assesses US Crypto Reserve Policy: Bitcoin Strategic Reserve Ensures US Dominance in Future Digital Transformation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24938</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Tom Lee, the newly appointed Chairman of the Board of BitMine, retweeted a tweet by U.S. Treasury Secretary Bennett regarding the U.S. Bitcoin Strategic Reserve and replied that establishing a strategic Bitcoin reserve in the U.S. is an important step in ensuring the country&apos;s leadership in future digital transformation.In the retweeted tweet, Bennett said: &quot;Bitcoin ultimately seized by the federal government will form the foundation of the strategic Bitcoin reserve established by President Trump in the March executive order. Additionally, the Treasury Department is committed to exploring budget-neutral ways to acquire more Bitcoin to expand the reserve and fulfill the President&apos;s commitment to make the U.S. a world Bitcoin superpower.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24938</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Founder will sell $1.29 million worth of ENA to buy back an equivalent amount of SKY</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24937</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Sky (formerly known as MakerDAO), one of its co-founders @RuneKek, used investment to purchase 16.38 million SKY with 1.77 million ENA within the past 40 minutes. This 1.77 million ENA was claimed from the Ethena vesting contract that was supposed to be derived from the investment 40 minutes ago. Then, it was transferred to an address used for repurchasing SKY and exchanged for 16 million SKY. Since early June, he has used the proceeds from staking SKY (USDS and SPK) to repurchase 122 million SKY with today&apos;s ENA, with a total value of $10.21 million at an average price of $0.0836.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24937</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaplanet CEO: Target to Increase Bitcoin Holdings to 30,000 Coins This Year Remains Unchanged</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24936</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Simon Gerovich, the CEO of the publicly traded Japanese company Metaplanet, declared, &quot;The objective this year to augment the Bitcoin holdings to 30,000 coins remains unaltered (presently holding 18,113 BTC), and we are slated to own 1% of all Bitcoin by 2027, adhering to a distinct roadmap that guides daily implementation and long-term aims.&quot;Metaplanet is a company that is entirely transparent, offering reserve verification and making performance dashboard data accessible to everyone. With trust established through verification, Metaplanet, in conjunction with Strategy and other enterprises, is motivating hundreds of global firms to incorporate Bitcoin into their balance sheets, thereby fueling growth and facilitating wider adoption.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor has reissued the Bitcoin Tracker information and may disclose hodling data next week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24935</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Michael Saylor reposted Bitcoin Tracker information on the X platform and may disclose additional holding data next week. He stated, &quot;Orange Coin is too scarce.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24935</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has launched Wilder World (WILD), with an airdrop threshold of 200 Alpha Points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24934</link>
      <description>August 17th. As per official channels, users possessing at least 200 Binance Alpha Points are eligible to claim an airdrop of 100 WILD tokens. The first come, first served principle applies. In case the event is still ongoing, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.Furthermore, Binance will initiate a WILD trading competition with a prize pool of 2,500,000 WILD.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24934</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The city of Duyun in Guizhou, China is exploring a method for handling seized virtual currencies, where the assets are frozen and then confiscated to a cold wallet for physical isolation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24933</link>
      <description>After China strictly prohibited cryptocurrency trading in 2021, handling and disposing of relevant cryptocurrencies has become a difficult issue for public security bureaus across the country. Recently, a journalist from China News Service accompanied the &quot;Guardianship in the Sun&quot; rule of law public security thematic publicity event media interview team of the Ministry of Public Security to enter the Joint Custody Center of Involved Property in Duyun City, Qiannan Buyei and Miao Autonomous Prefecture, Guizhou Province, to understand the local public security&apos;s practical approach to preserving involved cryptocurrencies.During their investigations, the public security organs discovered that some criminal suspects had converted their illegally obtained proceeds into cryptocurrencies. In the process of sealing the assets, the Duyun public security authorities froze the involved cryptocurrencies and placed them in a cold wallet physically isolated within the public security authority. The</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24933</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiong&apos;an New Area Completes First Transaction of Resettlement Multinational Central Bank Digital Currency Bridge Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24932</link>
      <description>August 17th. According to a report from Xiong&apos;an which was issued on its official WeChat account, with the guidance and support of the Xiong&apos;an Branch of the People&apos;s Bank of China, the Industrial and Commercial Bank of China (ICBC) Xiong&apos;an Branch. By combining the characteristics of a digital currency bridge and the onshore and offshore integrated fund pool business of a multinational corporation, it successfully completed the first transaction of a multi-party central bank digital currency bridge for the financial clearance of the Sinochem Group Financial Limited Company, a finance company of a central enterprise.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 12:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24932</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan to Approve First JPY-Backed Stablecoin JPYC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24931</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per Nikkei News, the Japan Financial Services Agency is set to approve the country&apos;s first issuance of a yen-denominated stablecoin named JPYC this month. The Japan Financial Services Agency will register the fintech company JPYC Inc. as a funds transfer business operator, and sales are anticipated to commence a few weeks after the registration. This digital currency will be underpinned by liquid assets like government bonds to keep its value stable at 1 JPYC equaling 1 yen.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 10:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24931</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>