<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:34:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Mixed Feelings Economic Data May Force Powell to Strike a Balance in Tonight&apos;s Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25771</link>
      <description>August 22: Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is scheduled to deliver a speech at the Jackson Hole Annual Economic Symposium at 10 p.m. Beijing time on Friday. Currently, the Fed is encountering unprecedented political pressure from the United States. However, the mixed economic data may compel Powell to adopt a moderate stance, leaving key issues unresolved.Regarding the interest rate policy, some analysts anticipate a middle-of-the-road approach. Powell may potentially leave the door open for a rate cut in September to recognize the necessity for further easing due to weak job growth. Nevertheless, he will not make more definite commitments until policymakers are more certain that the rising inflation is temporary. This stance may not satisfy Trump, who advocates for a significant cut in rates to around 1%, nor investors who are betting on multiple rate cuts this year. Although the market&apos;s confidence in a September rate cut has already shown signs of wavering. (Golde</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink&apos;s Board of Directors Approves $1.5 Billion Stock Repurchase Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25770</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per an official announcement, the Ethereum treasury firm SharpLink disclosed that its board of directors had given the green light to a stock buyback plan, with a maximum buyback amount of $1.5 billion for the company&apos;s common stock.SharpLink&apos;s Co-CEO Joseph Chalom stated, &quot;At SharpLink, we are consistently committed to a rigorous capital market strategy. In the event that our stock&apos;s trading price reaches or drops below the net asset value (&apos;NAV&apos;) of the ETH we hold, issuing new shares through financing would lead to a dilution of the per-share ETH equity. In such a situation, a value-enhancing approach could be to repurchase our common stock. This plan enables us to flexibly respond to these circumstances and take prompt and decisive action.&quot;The stock buyback plan is designed to enhance market support, optimize capital allocation, and strengthen SharpLink&apos;s long-term dedication to driving sustainable shareholder value. Repurchases under this plan may be carried</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25770</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messari has released the BNB Chain Q2 2025 Report: DEX Trading Volume, Stablecoin Transaction Count, and Active Users Lead the Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25769</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the most recent BNB Chain Q2 2025 report presented by Messari indicates that the BNB Chain has maintained its robust growth during the second quarter, with record-breaking user activity and on-chain transactions. Daily active addresses and transaction volume have witnessed significant surges, and the DeFi activity remains vigorous. The DEX trading volume, stablecoin transaction count, and active users all claim the top positions across the chain, thereby solidifying its leading status within the Web3 ecosystem.**Key Highlights:**Market Capitalization and Investor Confidence: The market capitalization of BNB increased by 7.5% during the quarter, reaching $92.6 billion.On-Chain Transactions and Activity: The average daily transaction volume rose by 101.9% to 9.9 million transactions, and the average daily active addresses grew by 33.2% to 1.6 million. In May, there were 17 million new addresses.DEX Performance: The DEX trading volume ranked first across the chain,</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25769</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haycen has obtained a stablecoin issuance license in Bermuda and will launch a stablecoin pegged to the British Pound.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25768</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to CoinDesk, Haycen, a company specializing in trade finance, has obtained a license for the issuance of stablecoins in Bermuda. With the support of Northern Trust and the UK National Security Strategic Investment Fund, Haycen intends to launch a non-USD stablecoin, initially with a stablecoin pegged to the British Pound.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin experienced a brief dip touching $112,000, with a 0.68% decrease in the last 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25767</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin witnessed a brief dip and reached $112,000. Currently, it is priced at $112,045, with a 24-hour decline of 0.68%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25767</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Coinbase CEO: Manda...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25766</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Coinbase&apos;s CEO, Brian Armstrong, stated that North Korean IT workers are targeting Coinbase. He is implementing in-person training to counter North Korean hackers seeking remote work. Coinbase is mandating that all employees attend in-person training in the United States. Additionally, anyone with access to sensitive systems must be a U.S. citizen and undergo fingerprint recognition.Brian Armstrong also said that Coinbase requires prospective employees to turn on their cameras during interviews &quot;to prove they are not artificial intelligence&quot; or have not been coached.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary: In the past two days, a Bitcoin whale sold over 4600 BTC and switched to a long position on Ethereum.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25765</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on Spot On Chain&apos;s summary, in the past two days, two Bitcoin OG whales who held a total of 100,784 Bitcoins (valued at $640 million) have begun to sell Bitcoin and switch to taking a long position on Ethereum. Their current operations are as follows:1. Sold 4,621.9 Bitcoins (approximately $5.235 billion) in three wallets at a price of $113,265 per BTC.2. Purchased and staked 82,398 ETH (approximately $3.5365 billion) at an average price of $4,292, and these were distributed across two wallets.3. Established long ETH positions totaling 135,265 ETH (worth $5.837 billion) on Hyperliquid across five wallets. The most liquidation prices range from $3,487.4 to $3,612.4. Still hold 84,645 Bitcoins (worth $9.55 billion) in seven wallets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25765</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin Volatility Drop Leads Speculators to Shift to New Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25764</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, an analyst from Bytetree Asset Management pointed out that the annualized volatility of Bitcoin has decreased significantly from nearly 200% a decade ago to 38%, making its volatility comparable to that of blue-chip stocks such as Starbucks or Goldman Sachs. The analyst stated, &quot;Bitcoin used to be the wild child in the financial world, but now it is showing signs of maturity, with its extreme volatility gradually diminishing, forcing speculative traders to look for a new playground.&quot;With the influx of buy-and-hold investors from Wall Street, the behavior of the world&apos;s largest cryptocurrency is becoming more similar to that of traditional blue-chip stocks, indicating that the cryptocurrency market is entering a new development stage. (Bloomberg)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25764</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS Raises Ping An Good Doctor&apos;s Target Price to Reflect Long-Term Stablecoin/Cryptocurrency Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25763</link>
      <description>August 22: UBS issued a research report indicating that in the first half of the year, ZhongAn Online&apos;s after-tax net profit increased by 11 times year-on-year to 668 million RMB, accounting for 68% of the market&apos;s full-year profit forecast for the company. The combined ratio improved by 2.3 percentage points to 95.6% compared to the same period last year, and it may exceed market expectations. The insurance business has shifted from losses. Consequently, the target price of ZhongAn Online has been raised from 13.1 Hong Kong dollars to 22.3 Hong Kong dollars to reflect the long-term stablecoin/cryptocurrency opportunity, policy benefits in the stock market, and rolling valuation (aastocks).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25763</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAE&apos;s RAKBANK Launches BNB Trading Service</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25762</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, one of the largest banks in the UAE, RAKBANK, launched a cryptocurrency trading service via its app. Among the first 8 cryptocurrencies available to customers is BNB.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>