<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:41:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Launches Alpha 2.0 Limit Order Market Maker Program</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26694</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to official channels, Binance has initiated the Alpha 2.0 Limit Order Market Maker Program. The Alpha 2.0 Limit Order Market Maker will be exempt from trading fees for Alpha 2.0 limit order buy/sell transactions and will have exclusive access to Binance Alpha&apos;s API. All users, including but not limited to those with experience in trading on decentralized exchanges (DEX), are eligible to apply to join the Alpha 2.0 Limit Order Market Maker Program.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26694</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Assists in Freezing Nearly $50 Million in &quot;Rug Pull&quot; Scam Illegal Funds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26692</link>
      <description>August 28th. Binance joined forces with Chainalysis, the stablecoin issuer, and law enforcement agencies in the Asia-Pacific region. They assisted in freezing nearly $50 million in illegal funds related to a &quot;Rug Pull&quot; scam that occurred in June of the previous year.This funding was tied to the so-called &quot;Rug Pull&quot; scam, which has witnessed a growing trend of globalization in recent years and encompasses investment and romance fraud.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26692</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine: Cryptocurrency and Cash Total Holdings Exceed $9 Billion, Including 1,792,690 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26693</link>
      <description>On August 28th, according to prnewswire, the US-listed company Bitmine (BMNR) declared that by 5:00 PM Eastern Time on August 27th, BitMine&apos;s holdings of cryptocurrencies comprised 1,792,690 ETH, 192 Bitcoin (BTC), and $7.75 billion in debt-free cash. The total holdings of cryptocurrencies and cash at BitMine exceeded $9 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26693</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Policy Institute Donates $500,000 to Support Tornado Cash Developer Legal Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26691</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as reported by The Block, the Solana Policy Institute has made an announcement. It has contributed $500,000 to the legal defense fund of the Tornado Cash developers Roman Storm and Alexey Pertsev. These two individuals were convicted in a cryptocurrency mixer case and are now facing prison sentences. Pertsev had previously been given a 64-month prison term in the Netherlands for assisting a $1.2 billion money laundering scheme. Meanwhile, Storm was convicted this month in New York for unlicensed money transmitting. However, the jury failed to reach a unanimous verdict on the money laundering and sanctions charges.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26691</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With up to 29.9% APY, Binance announces the second round of the MyShell (SHELL) HODLer Airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26690</link>
      <description>August 28th, MyShell has entered into a partnership with Binance to launch a time-limited lock-up product. Users can subscribe to SHELL Locked Products and earn an annual percentage yield (APY) of up to a maximum of 29.9%.This lock-up product event will continue until February 27, 2026. It supports three lock-up period options: 30 days, 60 days, and 90 days, with corresponding APYs of 16.9%, 21.9%, and 29.9% respectively.On the same day, MyShell and Binance completed the second round of the HODLer airdrop. A total of 25,000,000 SHELL tokens were distributed. This round was targeted at users who participated in the Break-Even Coin (Fixed-Term and/or Flexible-Term) or on-chain staking products using BNB between 08:00 on July 24th and 07:59 on July 28th (UTC).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26690</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: DEXLAB (XLAB) Token Airdrop Event to be Postponed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26689</link>
      <description>August 28th, the airdrop event of the DEXLAB (XLAB) token will be postponed, and the specific time remains to be determined.Previously, Binance Alpha announced that Dexlab (XLAB) will be launched on August 29th.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26689</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Card Issuer Rain Completes $58 Million Series B Funding Round, Led by Sapphire Ventures</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26688</link>
      <description>August 28th: The issuer of cryptocurrency debit card, Rain, has completed a Series B funding round worth $58 million. This round was led by Sapphire Ventures and involved Dragonfly, Galaxy Ventures, Endeavor Catalyst, Samsung Next, and Lightspeed. According to another source with knowledge of the matter, the annualized consumption volume supported by Rain&apos;s debit cards has exceeded $1 billion.Rain has launched Visa-supported debit cards, enabling the spending of stablecoins wherever Visa is accepted. The company was founded in 2021 by CEO Farooq Malik and CTO Charles Yoo-Naut. Rain allows neobanks and fintech firms (such as Nuvei) to provide stablecoin payment services.Previously, on March 24th, Rain announced a funding round of $24.5 million, which was led by Norwest Venture Partners and involved Galaxy Ventures, Goldcrest, Thayer, and Hard Yaka.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several companies, including MEI Pharma, experienced a significant stock price increase prior to announcing their crypto treasury, raising suspicions of insider trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26687</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per Fortune magazine, the cancer drug developer MEI Pharma announced the commencement of a $100 million crypto treasury strategy in mid-July of this year. Just a few days prior to the announcement, MEI Pharma&apos;s stock price nearly doubled, even though there were no significant updates filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, no press releases issued, and minimal discussions on social media. MEI Pharma was not the sole company whose stock price witnessed unusual surges before announcing a cryptocurrency buying strategy. Fortune magazine discovered similar patterns in other small publicly traded companies, suggesting that insiders had prior knowledge of some announcements.A spokesperson for MEI Pharma declined to offer any comments. Spokespersons for four other companies—Kindly MD, Empery Digital, Fundamental Global, and 180 Life Sciences Corp—whose stock prices showed abnormal movements before making cryptocurrency purchases did not respo</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26687</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River TVL has surpassed $600 million in just two weeks, with the circulating supply of satUSD reaching $270 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26685</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to official information, within two weeks, the Chainabstraction Stablecoin System Protocol River TVL exceeded $600 million. The circulating supply of satUSD reached $270 million. The protocol recently ranked second in the stablecoin category within the BNB Chain ecosystem for 30 days, and within 3 weeks, it had an accumulated NFT minting volume of 130,000.River is the first Chainabstraction Stablecoin System that enables assets to remain within their original ecosystem, whether it is DeFi, the stablecoin system, or the RWA public chain ecosystem. At the same time, through satUSD, users can smoothly participate in transactions and yield opportunities in other ecosystems, aggregating dispersed liquidity and redefining the relationship between assets and opportunities.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26685</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue Reaches 1,075,000 ETH, While Over 730,000 ETH Wait to Join</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26686</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network has risen to 1,075,268 ETH, which is approximately valued at $4.95 billion. The withdrawal delay has been extended to 18 days and 16 hours.Meanwhile, the amount of ETH waiting to join the network is about 738,733 ETH, approximately valued at $3.4 billion. It is also showing an upward trend. The admission queue is currently waiting for 12 days and 20 hours.Earlier reports suggest that this situation reflects two opposing forces in the market. On one hand, some stakers may choose to cash out after Ethereum&apos;s significant increase since the April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also boosting the entry queue. This can be seen in publicly traded companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion increasing their ETH holdings and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26686</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>