<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:21:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched the U-based A2Z perpetual contract, with leverage ranging from 1 to 50x.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22515</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to an official announcement, Bitget has declared the commencement of the U-based A2Z perpetual contract. The leverage range is set from 1 to 50x. Additionally, the contract trading BOT will be made available simultaneously.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institution: Powell&apos;s Continued Ambiguity Today Is Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22513</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Peter Boockvar, the Chief Investment Officer of One Point BFG Wealth Partners, stated that Federal Reserve Chairman Powell is facing a tough task. There are some cracks emerging in the labor market. Inflation is still significantly above his targeted sustainable level of 2%. However, the financial environment is extremely loose. With a significant amount of time still remaining until the September meeting, Powell&apos;s maintaining a vague stance is beneficial to him. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22513</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuvve, a publicly traded company, approves first-time purchase of up to $3 million in HYPE</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22514</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Nuvve Holding Corp., a publicly traded electric vehicle technology firm, announced today that its board of directors has given the green light for the initial purchase of a maximum of $3 million worth of HYPE.The company also disclosed a $4.8 million common stock offering at a price of $0.95 per share to back its HYPE financial strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22514</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Belgravia Hartford secures new $5 million funding for Bitcoin purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22512</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the publicly traded Canadian company Belgravia Hartford announced that it had completed a $5 million convertible bond financing with Round 13 Digital Asset Fund.Belgravia Hartford Capital indicated that it would utilize the full $5 million to enhance its holdings of Bitcoin (currently 40.77 BTC), and further details would be announced after the purchase was completed.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polygon Network Allegedly Experiencing Outage</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22511</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to data from blockchain explorers, it appears that the Polygon network has experienced downtime. The latest block on it was recorded 2 hours ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22511</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid is planning to automatically refund users affected by API issues</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22510</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to market information, Hyperliquid intends to automatically refund users who were affected by API issues.BlockBeats reported earlier today that Hyperliquid announced on Discord that from 22:10 to 22:47 (UTC+8) last night, the API server encountered problems, resulting in delays when orders were sent to the node. This was due to a surge in traffic. There was no hacking or exploitation involved. The issue has been resolved, and further improvements are planned for the future. In addition, various levels of the technical stack will also implement additional protection measures to detect API server issues and prevent users from encountering unexpected problems.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to strong data-driven momentum, the US Dollar is poised to achieve its longest winning streak since February.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22509</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the latest data indicates that the U.S. economy is robust, and the dollar is moving towards its longest consecutive upward trend since February. The Bloomberg Dollar Spot Index increased by 0.3%, reaching its highest level since June 23rd, with the index rising for five consecutive trading days.The U.S. economic growth and inflation data released on Wednesday were both higher than expected, which supported the Federal Reserve&apos;s hawkish stance. In the second quarter, U.S. economic activity rebounded as consumer spending picked up slightly, and the Fed&apos;s preferred inflation indicator, core PCE, rose by 2.5% year-on-year.Meanwhile, ADP private sector employment data shows that the labor market remains strong. Valentin Marinov, the head of G10 currency strategy at Credit Agricole CIB, said, &quot;The market may view this data as suggesting that the Fed&apos;s future rate cuts will be slower and more postponed. If Federal Reserve Chair Powell continues to maintain his current relative</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 Capital is currently exploring issuing USD loans backed by Bitcoin as collateral.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22508</link>
      <description>On Wednesday, July 30th, according to Bloomberg, sources familiar with the matter stated that Twenty One Capital is in the process of exploring a strategic plan to offer dollar loans with Bitcoin serving as collateral. Twenty One Capital, which is backed by Cantor Fitzgerald, has currently increased its Bitcoin holdings to at least 43,500 BTC, which is about 1,500 BTC more than was originally anticipated.The company recently acquired approximately 5,800 BTC from the stablecoin issuer Tether. With the current prices, the total value of its holdings is now approximately $5.13 billion. Established in April of this year, the company aims to build one of the largest Bitcoin reserves in the world. Its backers include Tether, Bitfinex, and SoftBank. The merger plan with the SPAC company Cantor Equity Partners is progressing smoothly and is expected to go public in the near future.As digital assets are increasingly being incorporated into corporate balance sheets, public companies and fund</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Ethereum Reserve Concept Stocks Soar, with BMNR Up by 3.67%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22507</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to Rockflow market data, the US Ethereum reserves concept stocks witnessed a general increase. These include:· SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) increased by 0.72%;· Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) rose by 3.67%;· GameSquare (GAME.US) went up by 3.58%;· Bit Digital (BTBT.US) gained by 0.99%;· Coinbase (COIN.US) rose by 2.07%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three major U.S. stock indices opened higher, with Coinbase up 2.9%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22506</link>
      <description>On July 30, when the U.S. stock market opened, the Dow increased by 8 points. The S&amp;P 500 went up by 0.12%, and the Nasdaq rose by 0.19%. Coinbase (COIN.O) rose by 2.9%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>