<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:50:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Empery Digital increased its holdings by 13 Bitcoins, bringing the total holdings to 4,065 coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26175</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to market information, the Nasdaq-listed company Empery Digital enhanced its holdings by 13 Bitcoins, resulting in its total Bitcoin holdings reaching 4,065 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26175</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONK Treasury Company Safety Shot has successfully completed a $30 million financing round, with $25 million paid by BONK founding members in token form.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26174</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to a report from &quot;businessinsider&quot;, the BONK Treasury company Safety Shot announced the completion of a $30 million financing round. The lead investor was FalconX and others. The transaction involved an approximately $5 million cash registration direct issuance and a $25 million simultaneous private placement. These funds were paid in BONK tokens by the BONK founding members.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26174</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock SOL Treasury Company DFDV Raises $125 Million to Increase SOL Holdings</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26172</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the U.S. Stock SOL Treasury Company DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) announced today that it has reached a definitive agreement to carry out a $125 million equity financing at a price of $12.50 per share. The transaction is anticipated to be completed on Thursday, August 28, 2025, provided that the customary closing conditions are met.According to the terms of the subscription agreement, the company will sell approximately 4.2 million shares of common stock (at a purchase price of $12.50 per share) and warrants that can be exercised for approximately 5.7 million shares of common stock (at a purchase price of $12.4999 per share with an exercise price of $0.0001 per share). The consideration for this issuance will be in the form of a combination of cash and locked SOL, which will further enhance DFDV&apos;s strategic goal of maximizing Solana Per Share (SPS) growth. The net proceeds raised will be utilized to increase the holdings of spot SOL and discounted locked SOL in order t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26172</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haassett: Powell Unlikely to Regain Trump&apos;s Favor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26173</link>
      <description>August 25th: On this August 25th, Brian Deese, who is the Director of the White House National Economic Council, expressed that it is unlikely for Powell to regain Trump&apos;s favor.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26173</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHZilla Approves $250 Million Stock Buyback Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26170</link>
      <description>On August 25th, the Board of Directors of ETHZilla Corporation (NASDAQ: ETHZ) has given approval to a stock buyback plan. The maximum buyback amount is $2.5 billion, and this plan comes into effect immediately. Additionally, the company has announced that it currently possesses 102,237 ETH. The average purchase price of these ETH is $3,948.72, and they are currently valued at approximately $4.89 billion. Apart from ETH, ETHZilla also holds around $2.15 billion in US dollar cash equivalents.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26170</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House National Economic Council Director: Fed Considering Rate Cut Is Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26171</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Hassett, who is the Director of the White House National Economic Council, referred to the Federal Reserve and expressed that it is suitable for the Fed to think about a rate cut. It is anticipated that it will take several months for the decision on the Fed Chair nominee to be made before President Trump makes a choice. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26171</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronin is launching the &quot;Developer Revenue Share Program&quot;.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26169</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per official information, the Ethereum Layer 2 project Ronin announced the commencement of the &quot;Developer Revenue Sharing Plan.&quot; Whether it is developing games, applications, or migrating projects to Ronin, developers can enhance their earnings through this plan. The &quot;Developer Revenue Sharing Plan&quot; will allocate a portion of Sky Mavis&apos;s total revenue back to developers. When a referred user engages in any of the following transactions, the referrer can receive a reward:路 Minting NFTs on the Ronin Launchpad.路 Participating in secondary market transactions on the Ronin Marketplace.路 Making purchases through the Ronin Store and in-game transactions.路 Paying Ronin Wallet conversion fees.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26169</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webull has announced the re-opening of its cryptocurrency trading service to U.S. users.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26168</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to Bloomberg, Webull Corp. is going to resume enabling U.S. customers to buy and sell cryptocurrencies on its trading platform. This service was previously suspended during the company&apos;s 2023 listing attempt.The company announced that cryptocurrency trading will be fully accessible to U.S. users starting from Monday. Since June of this year, Webull has been the first to provide this service to Brazilian investors. The platform currently offers trading in over 50 digital assets, such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana, and it is expected to expand cryptocurrency trading services to other markets in the coming months.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JuCoin is pleased to announce a $500 million investment partnership with the Nasdaq-listed company Connexa to launch the aiRWA RWA trading platform.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26167</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per official channels, JuCoin made an announcement about entering into a partnership with Connexa Sports Technologies Inc. (Nasdaq: YYAI). The two parties are set to jointly launch the cryptocurrency exchange platform aiRWA, with a particular emphasis on Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization.It is noted that both JuCoin and Connexa have pledged to invest $250 million each. Based on this $500 million commitment, they will jointly establish this joint venture project in order to build a comprehensive infrastructure that encompasses RWA transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26167</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy bought 3,081 bitcoins last week for $356.9 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26166</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per official channels, Strategy acquired 3,081 bitcoins during the previous week at a total cost of 356.9 million US dollars, with an average price of $115,829. The company now holds a cumulative total of 632,457 bitcoins. The sources of the purchasing funds consist of: $309.9 million from MSTR common stock through ATM financing, $20.4 million from STRK via ATM financing, and funds from STRF through ATM financing.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26166</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>