<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Vitalik: &quot;I Only Support Open Source&quot; Should Be a Common Viewpoint</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24210</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin released a long article titled &quot;Thoughts on Idea-drivenness.&quot; He pointed out that &quot;I only support things that are open source&quot; should be a common perspective, and &quot;I only support things if they are open source&quot; should be an even more common one. There exists a conflict between idea-driven approaches (rooted in a philosophical framework) and data-driven approaches (stemming from empirical analysis). The idea-driven approach, or ideology, can simplify complex decision-making, facilitate social coordination, and achieve specialization. However, it may also become rigid or divorced from real goals.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24210</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX investors sue Silicon Valley law firm Fenwick &amp; West, accusing it of aiding funds misappropriation by the SBF team</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24209</link>
      <description>August 12th. As per Decrypt, FTX investors have initiated lawsuits against the Silicon Valley law firm Fenwick &amp; West in multiple legal jurisdictions. They allege that the firm had a &quot;deep involvement&quot; in the downfall of FTX and provided assistance in designing shell companies and structures, which enabled the SBF team to embezzle billions of dollars of customer funds. This law firm is the only one among the 130 firms that partnered with FTX to be accused of having knowledge and significantly aiding in the commission of fraud. The plaintiffs assert that Fenwick designed, approved, and implemented shell companies, such as North Dimension, to conceal the flow of customer funds, evade regulations, and leverage its reputation to help FTX attract more than $1.3 billion in funding. An independent auditor&apos;s report showed that the firm was involved in nearly every aspect of FTX Group&apos;s improper conduct and provided legal advice while being aware that customer funds were being misappropriated.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24209</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle&apos;s stablecoin Layer1 ARC will launch its public testnet in the fall, providing EVM compatibility.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24208</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Circle revealed details about the stablecoin Layer1 blockchain ARC. Apart from utilizing the USDC stablecoin as the native Gas token, it plans to launch a public testnet this autumn and be EVM-compatible. The objective is to offer enterprise-grade infrastructure for stablecoin payments, foreign exchange, and capital market applications. Circle stated that it will also introduce features such as a stablecoin foreign exchange engine, sub-second settlement, and optional privacy features, while seamlessly integrating with the Circle platform and maintaining interoperability with other partner blockchains.This move by Circle is intended to counter its top competitor Tether, which has been actively engaged in the development and support of two stablecoin Layer1 blockchains: Stable and Plasma. In the current approximately $260 billion stablecoin market, Circle holds a $65 billion market share, while Tether holds around $165 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USDC Treasury has minted an additional 500 million USDC on the Solana blockchain.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24207</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as monitored by Whale Alert, the USDC Treasury has minted an extra 5 billion USDC on the Solana blockchain. This minting was carried out in two transactions, with 2.5 billion USDC minted in each transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24207</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: US July CPI Forecast Data &apos;Hotter Than Expected&apos;, BTC May Retest $110,000 Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24206</link>
      <description>August 12th. The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) is scheduled to release the July CPI inflation report at 8:30 p.m. on August 12th. The market generally anticipates that due to tariff-induced price hikes, the CPI is likely to rise once again, exerting sustained pressure on the U.S. economy. According to projections, the month-on-month CPI for July is expected to increase by 0.2%, with a year-on-year growth of 2.8%; when excluding the more volatile food and energy prices, the core CPI is expected to rise by 0.3% month-on-month and 3% year-on-year.It is worthy of note that this is also the first CPI report issued by the agency after Trump dismissed the BLS commissioner, which has raised market concerns about the credibility of the data. Both Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan have cautioned that the data may be &quot;overheated&quot; and could potentially fuel ongoing inflation. If the CPI data surpasses expectations, market expectations for a September Fed rate cut may be dampened, potentially le</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24206</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market: Circle Surges 7.09% in Pre-market Trading Following the Release of Q2 2025 Earnings Report</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24205</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to the market data of Rockflow, the US stock Circle rose by 3.3% in pre-market trading. Previously, Circle released its financial report for the second quarter of 2025. As of the end of the second quarter of 2025, the circulating supply of USDC increased by 90% year-on-year and reached 61.3 billion USDC. The net loss was $482 million, mainly due to non-cash expenses related to its Initial Public Offering (IPO).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24205</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qubic Response to Monero 51% Attack Event: Continuing with Monero Experiment as Planned, Details to be Revealed in Due Course</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24204</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Qubic gave a response regarding the Monero 51% attack incident, stating, &quot;The Monero (XMR) experiment is moving forward as scheduled, and everything will be disclosed at the right moment.&quot;Previously, it was reported that Sergey Ivancheglo, the co-founder of IOTA, through his project Qubic, rapidly amassed a significant amount of Monero (XMR) hash power using the &quot;useful Proof of Work (uPoW)&quot; mechanism. On August 12th, Qubic briefly took control of 52.72% of the Monero network&apos;s hash rate (approximately 3.01 GH/s). Once surpassing 51%, Qubic has the ability to reject blocks from other mining pools, resulting in chain reorganization, double spending, or transaction censorship. The Monero community has launched resistance and defense measures, while Qubic has characterized this action as a technical demonstration rather than a malicious attack.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24204</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by the Binance Alpha listing, WAI saw a temporary peak surge of 932%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24201</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the World3 project of the AI Agent officially landed on Binance Alpha. After its launch, WAI quickly attracted strong buying interest, with an intraday peak increase of 932%. Meanwhile, WAI has been listed on the spot exchanges of Bitget and KuCoin.World3 is supported by Microsoft for Startups and has received investments from industry capitals such as Ubisoft and Animoca Brands. It aims to build a 24/7 autonomously running Web3 AI workforce. It is reported that the platform has deployed more than 110,000 AI Agents, completed more than 2 million on-chain transactions, and spans various fields such as DeFi, DAO, and GameFi.Industry analysis believes that the AI Agent of World3 has autonomous planning, long-term execution, and multi-chain interaction capabilities. Compared with traditional AI tools, its implementation and scalability are stronger. As the core payment token of the ecosystem, as the platform usage increases, the value capture potential of WAI is worth p</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24201</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Releases Q2 2025 Financial Report: Net Loss of $482 Million, USDC Circulating Supply Reaches 65.2 Billion as of August 10</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24203</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Circle released its Q2 2025 financial report. By the end of the first quarter of 2025, the circulating supply of USDC had increased by 90% year-on-year and reached 613 billion tokens. As of August 10th, 2025, it further increased by 6.4% to reach 652 billion tokens. Total revenue and reserve income saw a 53% year-on-year increase and reached $658 million.The net loss was $482 million, mainly due to significant non-cash expenses related to the initial public offering (IPO), which totaled $591 million. These included:· $424 million of stock-based compensation recognized as a result of the IPO meeting attribution conditions;· A $167 million increase in the fair value of convertible bonds due to stock price appreciation.Adjusted EBITDA increased by 52% year-on-year and reached $126 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24203</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle will launch ARC, a Layer1 blockchain focused on stablecoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24202</link>
      <description>On August 12th, based on market information, Circle is going to launch ARC, a Layer 1 blockchain that mainly focuses on stablecoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24202</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>