<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:25:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The creator of Trollface has stated that they had no intention to be involved in a Solana-based meme coin using their work, and they have ruled out the possibility of taking legal action.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23477</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per Decrypt, Carlos Ramirez, the creator of the classic internet meme &quot;Trollface,&quot; declared that he has &quot;no intention&quot; of getting involved in a meme coin based on his own creation and launched on the Solana blockchain. This is because the capitalist nature of the crypto industry would impede artistic expression. Nevertheless, he also excluded the possibility of taking legal action against the token, even though he seemed to have promoted another Troll token earlier this year and on Tuesday of this past week.Carlos Ramirez mentioned that he &quot;frequently&quot; receives token allocation invitations from meme token projects related to Trollface and said: &quot;If I can&apos;t sell, the money is of no significance to me; but if I sell, it will cause the market to crash. And truthfully, I don&apos;t want to be held accountable for someone else&apos;s financial ruin.&quot;In the past two weeks, the price of the meme coin Troll has soared by over 1,050%, with its market capitalization rising from $16.1</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23477</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, the number of transactions on the Ethereum network reached 1.87 million, nearing an all-time high.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23476</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to Etherscan data, the daily transaction volume on the Ethereum network yesterday climbed to 1.87 million transactions, nearing the all-time high of 1.96 million transactions set on January 14, 2024.Nansen&apos;s Senior Research Analyst, Jake Kenni, stated that this significant increase in transactions was primarily driven by the elevated volume of stablecoins like USDC, Tether, and the decentralized exchange Uniswap. Sara Gherghelas, DappRadar&apos;s Senior Analyst, pointed out that the passage of the &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; established a legal framework for U.S. stablecoin operations, thereby enhancing market confidence.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23476</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Partner: ETH/BTC Exchange Rate Uptrend Appears Unabated</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23475</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Partner Chris Burniske of Placeholder posted on social media, saying, &quot;The uptrend of the ETH/BTC exchange rate appears to have not come to a halt.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23475</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CIO: Institutions and Governments are Exploring Incorporating Bitcoin into Reserves; Demand May See Exponential Growth in Early Stages</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23474</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per Cointelegraph, Matt Hougan, the CIO of Bitwise, declared that institutions and governments are engaged in discussions regarding the incorporation of Bitcoin into their reserves, signifying the nascent stage of exponential demand.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23474</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the entire network has seen $172 million in total liquidations, with the majority coming from the largest short positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23473</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to Coinglass data, the total liquidation within the past 24 hours reached $172 million. The total amount of long liquidations was $71.47 million, and the total amount of short liquidations was $101 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23473</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Quad-Short ETH Whale」 with a 75% win rate narrowly avoided liquidation with a 14,000 ETH position. After adding more collateral, the liquidation price increased from $3699 to $3724.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23472</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, with less than $1 remaining, the &quot;Four Battles ETH 75% Win Rate Whale&quot; was at risk of being liquidated, with a forced settlement of 14,000 ETH.At 2 o&apos;clock in the morning, the price of ETH reached a high of $3,698.8, while the liquidation price of the whale&apos;s 70,000 ETH short position was at $3,699. As long as it did not rise by another $1, his position would be liquidated with a forced settlement of 14,000 ETH.Subsequently, he quickly withdrew funds from WhiteBIT to top up his margin, raising the liquidation price from $3,699 to $3,724.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has accumulated a total of 128,204 ETH over the past 3 days, worth $4.645 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23470</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to on-chain analyst ChainInfo, a certain whale or institution has been accumulating ETH. It created a wallet through BitGo and has continuously received 27,073 ETH ($97.62 million) from multiple institutional business platforms in the past 20 hours. Currently, within a span of 3 days, this whale has accumulated a total of 128,204 ETH worth $4.645 billion through institutional business platforms such as FalconX, Galaxy Digital, and BitGo.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23470</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parataxis Holdings to Merge with SilverBox Corp IV, Aiming to Raise $640 Million to Establish Bitcoin Treasury Company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23469</link>
      <description>August 7th. As per The Block, the crypto investment startup Parataxis Holdings declared on Wednesday that it is undergoing a merger with the special purpose acquisition company SilverBox Corp IV in order to raise $640 million for a Bitcoin treasury company that will be listed on the New York Stock Exchange. Once the merger is completed, the new company intends to list on the New York Stock Exchange under the ticker symbol PRTX.The statement indicated, &quot;This business combination will furnish Parataxis Holdings with approximately up to $240 million in funding, with the exact amount hinging on the redemption status of SBXD (SilverBox Corp IV SPAC) shareholders. This encompasses $31 million in equity funding that will be promptly utilized to purchase Bitcoin.&quot;Parataxis also mentioned that it has &quot;entered into a stock purchase agreement&quot; which enables it to &quot;issue and sell up to $400 million in equity,&quot; and further added that these combined measures &quot;could potentially provide a total of</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23469</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orca Council Releases Governance Proposal to Buy Back ORCA with up to 55,000 SOL</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23471</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the Orca Council has put forward a governance proposal. It aims to repurchase ORCA by using up to 55,000 SOL and staking it on a validator node. During a 5-day voting period followed by a 2-day cooling-off period, ORCA token holders have the right to submit veto votes. The details of the proposal are as follows:· Fund Size: All SOL and USDC in the treasury wallet. Currently, it is about 55,000 SOL and 400,000 USDC.· Execution Plan: All SOL in the treasury wallet will first be staked on an Orca validator node. Then, it will be withdrawn periodically as needed to implement the Orca buyback plan. The plan will be carried out on a decentralized exchange or in cooperation with market makers and will last for 24 months. The daily buyback cap is 2% of ORCA&apos;s 30-day average trading volume to minimize market impact.· Storage and Use of Buyback Tokens: The repurchased ORCA tokens will be held in a multisig DAO treasury wallet. The Council plans to either burn these tokens to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23471</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered: Ethereum Treasury Company Now &apos;Very Investible,&apos; Superior to U.S. Spot Ethereum ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23468</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as reported by The Block, Geoffrey Kendrick, the Global Head of Digital Assets Research at Standard Chartered Bank, stated that Ethereum Treasury Companies are currently &quot;very worthy of investment&quot; and are more attractive to investors compared to a U.S. spot Ethereum ETF. The Net Asset Value (NAV) multiple of Ethereum Treasury Companies, which is the market cap divided by the held ETH value, is currently &quot;starting to normalize&quot; and is expected to remain above 1, making it a better investment target than a U.S. spot ETH ETF. Kendrick said: &quot;I see no reason why the NAV multiple should be below 1.0, as I believe these companies present investors with a regulatory arbitrage opportunity.&quot; With the normalization of the NAV multiple, Ethereum Treasury Companies can provide better opportunities for Ethereum price appreciation, staking rewards, and per-ETH growth compared to a U.S. spot ETH ETF, which currently cannot participate in staking or decentralized finance (DeFi).Kendr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23468</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>