<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:25:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Address Deposited 35 Million USDC Within 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24127</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight at https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, significant whale fund movements were observed in the past 24 hours:Large Deposits:The whale at address 0xECB63 deposited a total of 35.43 million USDC in the past 24 hours;The whale at address 0xa86136 deposited a total of 5.19 million USDC in the past 24 hours;Whale Withdrawals:The whale at address 0x9aB1c withdrew 10 million in the past 6 hours;The whale at address 0x960b6C withdrew 3.02 million in the past 6 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24127</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: Solana Meme Season Returns, CLIPPY, SPARK, BATH Stand Out in Weekly Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24126</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to GMGN data, as the market heats up, the on-chain meme activity of Solana has made a comeback. CLIPPY, which has been live for 3 days, has seen its market capitalization exceed $28 million and is currently priced at $0.028. SPARK, which was launched 6 days ago and has been on an upward trend, has a market capitalization exceeding $65 million and is currently priced at $0.0651. BATH, which has been live for 4 days, has a market capitalization of $6.3 million and is currently priced at $0.0065.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24126</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk threatens to sue Apple over its App Store ranking monopoly behavior</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24125</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Musk tweeted, &quot;Hey App Store, why do you decline to feature X or Grok in your &apos;Essential Apps&apos; section? X is manifestly the world&apos;s number one news app, and Grok ranks fifth among all apps. Are you engaging in politics? What&apos;s the deal? The inquisitive ones want to know.&quot;Apple&apos;s actions render it impossible for any AI company other than OpenAI to attain the top position on the App Store. This is undoubtedly anticompetitive behavior. xAI will initiate legal action without delay.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24125</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $119,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24124</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin rebounded and exceeded $119,000. The 24-hour decline was narrowed to 0.12%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24124</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun Market Share Surpasses Letsbonk, Regains Top Spot in Solana Token Launchpad Ranking</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24123</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Jupiter Data, on the market share leaderboard of the Solana token issuance platform in the past 24 hours, pump.fun holds the top position with 69.7%, followed by Letsbonk at 15.2% and BAGS at 9.14%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Seizes $1 Million in Bitcoin from Russian Ransomware Group Along with Associated Servers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24122</link>
      <description>On August 12th, US and international law enforcement agencies seized 4 servers, 9 domain names, and approximately $1 million worth of bitcoin that was related to a notorious Russian ransomware group which was accused of attacking hundreds of organizations across key sectors.The US Department of Justice stated that the operation took place on July 24th and was jointly carried out by agencies from the US, Canada, Germany, Ireland, France, the UK, Ukraine, Lithuania, and other countries. The operation targeted the infrastructure related to the BlackSuit and Royal ransomware. Investigators believe that these two ransomware variants were developed by the same cybercriminal group.Authorities said that since 2022, the group has extorted over $500 million in ransom payments. The largest single ransom reached $60 million. It is alleged that during this time, they targeted over 450 victims in the US, including hospitals, schools, police departments, energy companies, and government agencies,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Plans to Introduce New Legislation, Bitcoin ATMs May Face Mandatory KYC and $1000 Transaction Limit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24121</link>
      <description>On August 12th, in accordance with Bitcoin Laws, the Wisconsin State Senate in the United States put forward a new bill named SB 386. This bill aims to mandate that all Bitcoin ATMs must fully carry out Know Your Customer (KYC) procedures. During transactions, identity information must be provided. There is a per-transaction limit of $1,000, and additional personal information needs to be collected for regulatory purposes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX/Alameda distributed 190,000 SOL to 29 addresses, with the majority flowing into CEX.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24120</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as monitored by EmberCN, FTX/Alameda redistributed 190,000 SOL (approximately $34.09 million) that was withdrawn from staking to 29 addresses 6 hours ago. Judging from previous records, most of the addresses receiving SOL are likely to further transfer the SOL to Coinbase or Binance.Since November 2023, the FTX/Alameda staking address has redeemed and transferred a total of 8,788,000 SOL (approximately $1.159 billion) through the aforementioned method, with an average transfer price of $132.Currently, the FTX/Alameda staking address still has 4,727,000 SOL (approximately $829 million) staked.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korean Trader Swarm Bets on BitMine, Net Buys Reach $259 Million Since Early July</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24119</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Bloomberg, BitMine has emerged as the most popular overseas stock among South Korean retail investors. They are still captivated by this high-risk, high-reward opportunity in the crypto realm. According to data from the Korea Securities Depository, since early July, South Korean retail investors have made net purchases of $259 million worth of BitMine stock, making it the most bought overseas security during this period.This frenzy underscores the continuous speculative enthusiasm in the South Korean retail market. Approximately one-third of the South Korean population, which is about 18 million people, is active in the digital asset market and shows interest in various things, ranging from leveraged crypto ETFs to newly listed stablecoin issuer Circle.BitMine aims to replicate Michael Saylor&apos;s strategic business model, but with a focus on Ethereum rather than Bitcoin. The company currently holds Ethereum worth $3.6 billion and ranks first globally. How</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Fear and Greed Index Drops to 68, Market Continues to Show &quot;Greed&quot; Sentiment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24118</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Alternative Data, the Crypto Fear and Greed Index for today is 68 (yesterday it was 70), with a weekly average of 60, suggesting a continued state of &quot;greed&quot; in the market.Note: The threshold for the fear index is 0 - 100 and it encompasses the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Hype (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24118</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>