<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:31:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Interest Rate Cut Will Exacerbate Historic Wealth Disparity, Asset Holders Will Outrun Inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25999</link>
      <description>On August 24th, The Kobeissi Letter issued its most recent market analysis, indicating that the anticipated rate cut will not be as forceful as what Trump anticipates, amounting to 300 basis points. The last time the Fed cut rates due to surging inflation was in the 1970s, leading to a continuous and historical widening of the wealth gap. In 1990, the wealth gap between the richest 1% and the poorest 50% of the population was $3 trillion, and now it is $40 trillion. Currently, the wealthiest 0.1% of the US population holds wealth that is 5.5 times that of the poorest 50%.In fact, the Fed has truly &quot;fallen behind&quot; in the current global rate-cutting cycle. Central banks around the world cut rates a total of 15 times in May alone, which is the fastest monthly rate-cut pace so far this year and one of the largest rate-cutting waves of this century, firmly setting the stage for the Fed&apos;s first rate cut to occur just one month later in 2025. Additionally, Fed Chairman Powell has 8 months r</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25999</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has spent $4.99 million to open a 3x leveraged long position on XPL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25998</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale deposited 4.99 million USDC into Hyperliquid and initiated a 3x leveraged long position on XPL.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25998</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Game L3 Xai Sues Musk&apos;s AI Company xAI</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25997</link>
      <description>On August 24th, the Ethereum-based game L3 Xai initiated a lawsuit against Musk&apos;s AI company xAI, alleging trademark infringement and unfair competition. The lawsuit was filed on Thursday in the Northern District of California, asserting that Musk&apos;s xAI company is causing harm to Xai&apos;s brand. Ex Populus, the Delaware-based company behind Xai, declared that it has been utilizing the XAI trademark in US commerce since June 2023, encompassing its blockchain gaming ecosystem and XAI token. The lawsuit claims that &quot;This is a typical trademark infringement case that necessitates court intervention for redress.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25997</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Alttown (TOWN) on August 26th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25996</link>
      <description>August 24th. Binance Alpha will list Alttown (TOWN) on August 26th. Eligible users can obtain the airdrop by using Alpha Points on the Alpha event page and can claim it once trading begins. More details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25996</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Interpreting the WLFI token distribution as Aave&apos;s intrinsic value is not accurate, and the 7% token distribution clause overvalues it.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25995</link>
      <description>August 24th. Mindao, the founder of the DeFi protocol dForce, expressed his viewpoints on the &quot;Can Aave Obtain 7% of WLFI Token Total Supply&quot; event. He stated that Aave&apos;s previous 10% revenue sharing partnership with Spark is relatively insignificant compared to the &quot;20% revenue sharing + 7% token allocation&quot; terms of the Aave and WLFI partnership. These terms are overly generous and do not align with the deal terms that the Trump family is willing to accept. The WLFI project is endorsed by the Trump brand. Coupled with the upcoming US crypto new policy, WLFI will be issued at USD1. The narrative of WLFI will directly transition from &quot;crypto bank&quot; to a combination of &quot;Aave + Circle&quot;, significantly increasing its valuation.Aave founder Stani.eth made a high-profile retweet yesterday, stating that &quot;at the current price, Aave&apos;s treasury will receive WLFI worth $2.5 billion, making it one of the biggest winners in this round cycle.&quot; He referred to this as the art of the deal. Subsequentl</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25995</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase&apos;s &quot;Super App&quot; Base App will open its invitation feature in two weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25994</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Jesse Pollak, the co-founder of Base, stated in an interview that two weeks later, the invitation feature would be opened in the &quot;Base App&quot; in order to accelerate the viral growth loop of the Base App and ensure that the product is of high quality for every user.On July 16th, Coinbase announced the launch of the &quot;Everything App&quot; - the &quot;Base App&quot;, aiming to attract more users to the cryptocurrency ecosystem. This new app, which replaces the Coinbase Wallet, integrates wallet, trading, and payment functions. It also incorporates social media, instant messaging, and mini-program support and runs on its self-developed Ethereum Layer 2 network Base. For Coinbase, this move is intended to break through the limitations of its core cryptocurrency exchange business and reach a broader potential user base.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25994</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Speak: Market Focus Shifts to Second Rate Cut This Year, Aggressive Easing Still Stalled by Inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25993</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Nick Timiraos, a renowned reporter from The Wall Street Journal and often dubbed the &quot;Fed Whisperer,&quot; released a new article titled &quot;Powell&apos;s Rate Cut Signal Reflects Delicate Economic Situation.&quot; The article stated that Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell is cautiously laying the groundwork for a rate cut next month. However, he has sent a subtle message to those anticipating aggressive easing, indicating that they should not expect a drastic move. The market has largely factored in a September rate cut, and the focus has now shifted to whether the Fed will consider another rate cut during the last two meetings of the year (October and December).Powell&apos;s cautious stance reflects the complex economic dynamics facing the Fed. He described the labor market as showing &quot;peculiar&quot; signs of softness despite a low unemployment rate. Meanwhile, price increases driven by tariffs are beginning to impact the economy. Powell largely adopted the rate-cut argument put forward by Fe</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25993</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list FreeStyle Classic (FST) with a point airdrop threshold of 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25992</link>
      <description>August 24th. Binance Alpha will list FreeStyle Classic (FST), and trading will open on August 24, 2025, at 5:00 PM (UTC+8). After the trading starts, users with a minimum of 200 Binance Alpha Points will be eligible to claim an airdrop of 800 FST tokens on a first-come, first-served basis.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT has published a list of 81 KOL accounts worth muting.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25991</link>
      <description>On August 24th, on-chain detective ZachXBT presented a list of 81 KOL accounts that are worthy of muting and classified them into the &apos;KOL Wall of Shame&apos; list. ZachXBT stated, &quot;Muting these accounts will optimize your feed as all of these accounts are promoting MEME token presale events.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 06:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25991</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Alert: Beware of EIP-7702 Phishing Batch Transaction Trap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25990</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Cao Yun, the founder of SlowMist, retweeted a security alert posted by ScamSniffer. It was indicated that today, another user lost approximately $1.54 million due to signing an EIP-7702 phishing batch transaction, involving ETH, BTC, and multiple tokens staked on Ethereum. The principle of EIP-7702 is to delegate the authorization of the user&apos;s EOA address to MetaMask: EIP-7702 Delegator, and to complete subsequent token transfer operations through its contract call. This phishing method has been industrialized by mainstream phishing groups. If one is inadvertently induced to make transactions, the entire account assets will be lost. Users are reminded to verify the authenticity of the website and links before confirming transactions to prevent fraud.Earlier on August 22nd, according to ScamSniffer&apos;s monitoring, a user signed a phishing batch EIP-7702 transaction disguised as a Uniswap swap trade and lost approximately $1 million in tokens and NFTs. The attacker disgu</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 05:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25990</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>