<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:58:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Trump&apos;s Tariffs Squeeze US Bitcoin Miners, Mining Companies to Face Slower Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23443</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per TheBlock, Ethan Vera, the Chief Operating Officer of Luxor Technology, declared that following the White House&apos;s imposition of high reciprocal tariffs on Bitcoin mining machines from Southeast Asia, U.S. Bitcoin miners are bracing themselves for a slowdown in growth. The latest tariff rate is set to come into effect on August 7th. This includes a 19% reciprocal tariff on ASIC mining machines from Indonesia, Malaysia, and Thailand, raising the total import tariff rate of these countries to 21.6%. The tariffs have resulted in a decrease in demand from U.S. customers, with mining machines flowing to countries with more lenient import policies like Canada. Under the 21.6% tariff, the U.S. has now become one of the least competitive regions for importing mining machines, and miners are contemplating expanding into Canada and other markets.Ethan Vera anticipates that if the tariffs have a significant impact on the industry&apos;s supply chain, Russia will become the main b</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23443</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado Cash Co-Founder Roman Storm Stuck in Legal Limbo</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23442</link>
      <description>August 6th. As per crypto journalist Eleanor Terrett, during the jury trial of Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm today, a deadlock emerged on certain charges. Judge Failla promptly gave instructions for the jury to reexamine. In the event that the deadlock persists, the court will accept a partial verdict, and the government may refile the remaining charges. The case is currently awaiting the jury&apos;s reconsideration.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23442</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor: Received the Most Important Investment Advice to &quot;Buy Bitcoin&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23441</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the founder of Strategy, Michael Saylor, responded to a community question which inquired, &quot;What is the most crucial investment advice you have ever received?&quot; He replied, &quot;Buy Bitcoin.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23441</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market News: Trump Advisor Is Pushing for Appointment of Acting Fed Board Member to Fill Vacancy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23440</link>
      <description>August 6th, Market News: Trump&apos;s advisors are advocating for the appointment of an interim Federal Reserve Board governor to fill a vacant position. The candidates for the Federal Reserve Board governor are likely to have government experience and will have to go through a Senate confirmation process. The short-term appointment of a Federal Reserve Board governor will give Trump more time to select the Federal Reserve Chair. (FXStreet)On August 2nd, the Federal Reserve announced in a statement that Federal Reserve Board Governor Cugler will resign next week, presenting an early chance for Trump to appoint a preferred candidate. Trump now has the opportunity to promptly appoint a governor to exert pressure on Chairman Powell — and this governor may potentially succeed Powell. Cugler has submitted his resignation to U.S. President Trump and will step down on August 8th to return to Georgetown University to serve as a professor. Cugler did not attend last week&apos;s Federal Reserve policy m</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part of the Pump.fun ecosystem meme coins continue to surge, with TROLL market cap surpassing 200 million US dollars.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23439</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to GMGN Market Info, some meme coins in the Pump.fun ecosystem continued their upward trend. These include:TROLL exceeded a $200 million market capitalization, with a 24-hour trading volume of $48.8 million and a 23.72% 24-hour price increase.House exceeded a $30 million market capitalization, with a 24-hour trading volume of $12.23 million and a 56.31% 24-hour price increase.MASK exceeded a $15 million market capitalization, with a 24-hour trading volume of $4.73 million and a 28.61% 24-hour price increase.BlockBeats reminds users that many meme coins have no practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23439</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. will impose an additional 25% tariff on goods from India</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23438</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the White House of the United States announced that President Trump signed an executive order to impose an additional 25% tariff on goods from India in response to India&apos;s continuous purchase of Russian oil. After Trump declared the new tariff on India, oil prices saw a short-term spike and reached an intraday high. (Oriental Fortune Network)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23438</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI is offering the ChatGPT Enterprise version service to all US federal government agencies.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23437</link>
      <description>August 6th. According to Fox News, the U.S. General Services Administration (GSA) has announced a partnership with OpenAI today. This partnership will provide the ChatGPT Enterprise service to all federal agencies. It is a key part of the Trump administration&apos;s Artificial Intelligence Action Plan, which aims to improve the efficiency of government work. Federal agency employees will be provided with customized training resources and guided learning programs.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23437</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A trader bought $29,000 worth of TROLL 3 months ago and made a profit of $3.78 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23436</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the trader &quot;frostx.sol&quot; spent $29,000 to purchase 21.91 million TROLL tokens three months ago. Subsequently, they sold 2.55 million TROLL tokens for $507,000. At present, they still hold 18.36 million TROLL tokens, which are worth $3.73 million.With the recent surge of TROLL, their position has appreciated by nearly 1,300 times, resulting in a profit of $3.78 million.BlockBeats previously reported that possibly due to the influence of Pump.fun&apos;s official &quot;milk&quot; campaign, various meme coins have witnessed significant gains recently. On July 23rd, Pump.fun&apos;s official Twitter account posted an image containing several Pump.fun ecosystem meme coins, including TROLL.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23436</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Listed Company Cosmos Health Raises $300 Million in Funding, Will Establish Ethereum Reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23434</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the publicly traded company Cosmos Health (Nasdaq: COSM) entered into a securities purchase agreement with U.S. institutional investors, securing up to $3 billion in senior secured convertible note financing. Under the agreement, the company will allocate 72.5% of the net proceeds from the financing to establish an Ethereum reserve, while the remaining funds will be designated for working capital and business development.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opening: Cryptocurrency Stocks Experience Mixed Performance, &apos;BNB Version of MicroStrategy&apos; BNC Soars 13%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23435</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to RockFlow market data, at the opening of the US stock market, the Dow increased by 0.19%, the S&amp;P 500 rose by 0.15%, and the Nasdaq went up by 0.19%. Cryptocurrency stocks had a mixed performance, including:- &quot;BNB Version of MicroStrategy&quot; CEA Industries (BNC) soared by 13% as it completed a $500 million private placement led by YZi Labs on August 5th to support its BNB-focused treasury strategy.- &quot;ETH Version of MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink (SBET) dropped by 5.7%.- &quot;TON Version of MicroStrategy&quot; Verb Technology (VERB) surged by 14.62%.- MicroStrategy (MSTR) rose by 0.24%.- Coinbase (COIN) decreased by 0.1%.- Circle (CRCL) rose by 0.32%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23435</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>