<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:46:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet integrates the Base ecosystem&apos;s decentralized exchange platform, Aerodrome, into its services.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25680</link>
      <description>August 22nd. Bitget Wallet declared a profound partnership with the Base ecosystem. It integrated the Base ecosystem&apos;s flagship decentralized exchange, Aerodrome, natively. Users are capable of directly finishing token transactions, getting involved in liquidity pools, and reaping rewards within the wallet.As the liquidity center of Base, Aerodrome adopts the ve(3,3) model to stimulate sustainable development. It offers the optimal liquidity and trading routes on core assets like cbBTC and cbETH. This integration enables users to trade and stake Base native assets conveniently in the Bitget Wallet App. At the same time, they can make gas payments through the GetGas feature without holding ETH.In addition, Bitget Wallet is going to launch a Base ecosystem zone on the &quot;Discovery&quot; page. This zone will cover the top applications of Base, including DeFi, gaming, and infrastructure. It will provide real-time market data, one-click trading, and beginner guides. Bitget Wallet also intends</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue Decreased to Approximately 841,000 ETH, Entry Queue Increased to Approximately 214,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25679</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, it is reported that the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is 841,457 ETH. The ETH exiting the PoS network is estimated to be approximately $36.18 billion at the current price. The withdrawal delay is currently reported to be 14 days and 15 hours.At the same time, there has been an increase in staking demand from new validators being activated. Today, the admission queue has risen to 214,150 ETH, which is worth around $9.2 billion. The current queue waiting time for admission is 3 days and 17 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25679</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Appoints Judge Margaret Ryan as Director of Enforcement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25678</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to official information, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) made an announcement. It stated that Judge Margaret &quot;Meg&quot; Ryan has been appointed as the Director of the Enforcement Division, and this appointment will come into effect starting from September 2, 2025.The Acting Director of the SEC&apos;s Enforcement Division, Sam Waldon, will return to his previous position as the Chief Legal Advisor of the division.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25678</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cryptocurrency Fear and Greed Index remains unchanged from yesterday, indicating that the market is still in a &quot;Neutral&quot; state.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25677</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to Alternative Data, the Fear and Greed Index of cryptocurrencies today is 50 (yesterday it was also 50), suggesting a &quot;Neutral&quot; market sentiment.Note: The Fear and Greed Index has a range from 0 to 100 and encompasses the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Hype (15%) + Market Survey (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance in the Market (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25677</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Legislators Propose Banning Public Officials from Trading Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25676</link>
      <description>August 22nd. As per Cointelegraph, the Pennsylvania House Democratic Representative Ben Waxman presented legislation intended to &quot;bar officials from reaping profits from cryptocurrency during their tenure in office.&quot;Waxman submitted the HB1812 bill on Wednesday and obtained support from eight Democratic co-sponsors. This is his reaction to what he deems as the &quot;corrupt&quot; conduct carried out by US President Donald Trump at the federal level.The Pennsylvania lawmaker alleges that Trump has been profiting from projects like his meme coin TRUMP and has been advocating for looser federal regulations on the cryptocurrency market in order to &quot;shield these schemes from examination.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25676</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Office of the Comptroller of the Currency Lifts 2022 Anti-Money Laundering Enforcement Action Against Anchorage Digital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25675</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) in the United States announced that it has issued an order to end the consent order that was issued to the crypto custodian bank Anchorage Digital in 2022.The OCC stated that the revocation of this order is to &quot;ensure the safety and soundness of Anchorage.&quot; The order issued by the regulatory agency in April 2022 was due to Anchorage&apos;s &quot;failure to establish and implement a compliance program based on anti-money laundering (AML) standards.&quot; However, the OCC indicated that the bank &quot;complies with legal requirements and there is no need to continue the order.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25675</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin breaks $115,000, the mainstream CEX aggregate short liquidation volume will reach $1.734 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25674</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin manages to break through $115,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will amount to $1.734 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin drops below $111,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.183 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not provide the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that once the price reaches that level, it will experience a stronger reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25674</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Rebounds to Reach $113,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25673</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin rebounded and touched $113,000. It is currently trading at $113,000, and the 24-hour loss has narrowed to 1.45%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Union Development Holdings Soared Over 60%, Company Plans to Acquire 20% Equity Stake in RWA Company NVTH for 100 Million Hong Kong Dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25671</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on market data, Regal World Group (00264.HK) witnessed a surge of more than 60%. The company intends to acquire a 20% equity stake in NVTH Limited, a company engaged in RWA tokenization-related business, at a cost of 100 million Hong Kong dollars. (Jinse)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list FreeStyle Classic (FST) and open airdrop claiming to eligible users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25672</link>
      <description>On August 22, according to official information, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list FreeStyle Classic (FST) on August 24. After the Alpha trading commences, eligible users can access the Alpha event page to claim the airdrop by using Binance Alpha points. Further details will be made public at a later time.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>