<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin &apos;Filling the Gap&apos; Probability is Rising, Pullback Bottom or Forming in &apos;Double Anchor Structure&apos; Middle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22767</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the on-chain data analyst Murphy stated in a post that the $117,000 Bitcoin support level has been broken through, and the probability of a &quot;gap fill&quot; is on the rise. According to Bitcoin on-chain data, the $117,000 price level is a bar with a significantly higher volume compared to other price ranges in the URPD chip structure. A total of 720,000 BTC are stacked at this single price, indicating an intense battle between bulls and bears at the $117,000 price level, resulting in significant turnover. The current price of BTC has already dropped below this key support level.Whenever a single price bar accumulates more chips, the game will reach a critical point, and the market will face a moment of short-term directional choice. The chip range from $116,000 to $119,000 has high density but lacks width, making it vulnerable to a short-term breakthrough. Currently, the market seems to be choosing a downward direction and entering the middle area of the chip ranges from $11</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22767</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UK publicly listed company Vaultz Capital has raised ￡4.3 million to expand its Bitcoin treasury strategy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22766</link>
      <description>August 1st. As per @btcNLNico, the UK-listed company Vaultz Capital secured ￡4.3 million in funding. Aura Digital took the lead in investing ￡2.6 million, with the aim of achieving a total funding target of approximately ￡6 million. Vaultz Capital declared that it will further enlarge its Bitcoin treasury and infrastructure strategy.On July 21st, Vaultz Capital augmented its Bitcoin holdings by 20 coins, resulting in the company&apos;s total holdings reaching 70 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investment Company Cardone Capital Increases its Holdings by 100 BTC Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22765</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the CEO of Real estate investment company Cardone Capital, Grant Cardone, stated that the current dip presented an opportunity to purchase more. He has once again increased his holdings of BTC by 100 coins.Cardone Capital announced in June that it had purchased approximately 1000 BTC and planned to acquire an additional 3000 BTC this year. It has become the first comprehensive company to adopt a full Bitcoin strategy that combines real estate with Bitcoin assets. The group owns 14,200 housing units and over 500,000 square feet of Class A office space. It is expected to acquire another 3000 BTC this year and add 5000 housing units to its portfolio.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22765</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainOpera AI has officially partnered with EigenLayer to jointly build a trustable on-chain AI Agent network, with a daily transaction volume exceeding 600,000 times.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22764</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to official channels, the AI Agent platform ChainOpera AI has entered into a partnership with the re-staking protocol EigenLayer. Together, they are working to advance the construction of the &quot;Runtime-Verifiable AI Agent&quot; infrastructure. The two parties will achieve end-to-end verification of the AI Agent&apos;s reasoning and execution behavior through on-chain auditing mechanisms, facilitating the evolution of AI services from a &quot;black box&quot; to &quot;trusted collaboration&quot;.Currently, ChainOpera has established a community-driven AI Agent social network that enables collaborative task completion such as transactions, predictions, and productivity with personalized virtual friends. The platform&apos;s daily interaction volume has exceeded 600,000 times, and it has over 300,000 cumulative paid users.Users can interact with multiple Agents and participate in the Prompt-to-Earn incentive mechanism at chat.chainopera.ai. Developers can build and publish Agents at agent.chainope</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22764</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Trader AguilaTrades Suffers Significant Losses in the Past Two Months, Once Saw a Peak Profit of Over $40 Million Before Ending Up &quot;Bust&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22763</link>
      <description>August 1st, based on the monitoring of HyperInsight, the contract whale AguilaTrades has endured a trading loss of approximately $8.47 million within the past 30 days and a loss of about $5.61 million in the past 7 days. Their HyperLiquid account has suffered a cumulative loss of approximately $40 million, approaching &quot;zero,&quot; with only $86,000 remaining in the account. AguilaTrades has been oscillating between long and short positions this month, employing high leverage to open positions in Bitcoin and Ethereum. Their Bitcoin positions are mainly leveraged at 40x, while their Ethereum positions are mostly leveraged at 25x. The Bitcoin long position once reached a peak profit of over $41.7 million but underwent a significant pullback during the market turmoil on July 15th.「Aguila」 means &quot;eagle&quot; in Spanish. AguilaTrades claims to have been engaged in trading activ</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22763</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will open airdrop distribution today at 15:00 UTC, with a minimum threshold of 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22762</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Binance Alpha will commence the Alpha airdrop at 15:00 (UTC+8). Users who possess at least 200 Binance Alpha points will be eligible to claim the token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. The specific airdropped token has not been made public as of now.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: New Coin WLFI Launches on Solana, OG Sees Short-Term Market Cap Surge, Base Chain Veteran Token BNKR Shows Active Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22761</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to GMGN data, within the past 6 hours on the Solana chain, the top five tokens in the &quot;Next Blue Chip&quot; sector were WLFI, PUMP, OG, MarsMi, and URANUS. WLFI and OG are new meme tokens that have been listed for less than 10 hours and have fewer than a thousand holders, presenting a significant risk.On the other hand, on the Base chain, in the past 24 hours, the top five tokens in terms of trading volume released on Clanker were BNKR, CLANKER, DRB, Fartcoin, and LUM. These five tokens have been listed for a longer time and have more than a thousand holders.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins usually lack practical use cases, experience high price volatility, and investments should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22761</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stock Concept Stock Stablecoin Plunges in the Afternoon, Guotai Junan International Falls Over 7%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22760</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to market data from RockFlow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), the afternoon decline of Hong Kong stock stablecoin concept stocks widened. YBB Digital and OSL Group fell by nearly 10%, Kinetic Investments dropped by more than 8%, Guotai Junan International dropped by more than 7%, and ZhongAn Online dropped by more than 6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury Burns 52 Million USDC on the Ethereum Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22758</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as monitored by Whale Alert, the USDC Treasury has just incinerated 52 million USDC on the Ethereum blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Adds TREE, A2Z, KERNEL, and SPK as Borrowable Assets on the Lending Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22759</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Binance has incorporated TREE, A2Z, KERNEL, and SPK into its lending platform as new borrowable assets and collateral assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>