<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:52:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Whale qianbaidu.eth has deposited $5.72 million into Hyperliquid and has purchased $3.94 million worth of HYPE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26610</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the whale &quot;qianbaidu.eth&quot; transferred $5.72 million into Hyperliquid and purchased 81,572.11 HYPE with $3.94 million. It still holds $1.787 million USDC and has placed a limit price buy order for HYPE at $48.2.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26610</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOON Foundation Announces First Airdrop Guidelines for the simpfor.fun Mirror Trading Platform on Hyperliquid</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26609</link>
      <description>August 28th: The SOON Foundation declared the initial batch of airdrop regulations for the Hyperliquid mirror trading platform simpfor.fun, anticipating the distribution of 1,500,000 SOON tokens.The airdrop will be centered around users&apos; mirror trading volume on simpfor.fun. There is a base pool of 1,000,000 SOON and an additional pool of 500,000 SOON. The additional pool will offer a 30% to 70% bonus depending on the quantity of Coming SOON NFTs held. Currently, Simpfor.fun has a user base exceeding 250 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26609</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanEck CEO: Ethereum is the &quot;Wall Street Token,&quot; Stablecoin Growth Drives Traditional Financial Institutions&apos; Demand for Ethereum</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26608</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Jan F. van Eck, the CEO and president of VanEck, stated in an interview with FOX News that Ethereum is what I refer to as a &quot;Wall Street Token.&quot; With the emergence of stablecoins, every bank - in fact, every financial services firm - must find a way to accept stablecoins. If I want to send you a stablecoin, your bank has to figure it out; otherwise, you will go to another institution that can handle it. &quot;The people on Wall Street will eventually turn around and ask: What exactly is this thing? On which chain should I develop? The answer is Ethereum.&quot;Jan F. van Eck also stated that Ethereum was indeed despised by many earlier this year at its low point for various reasons. VanEck actually has a list of &quot;actively managed ETFs.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Over 60,000 Transaction Addresses in YZY Token Trading Experienced Losses, Accounting for Over 83% of the Total Address Count</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26607</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to Bubblemaps&apos; monitoring, since its issuance, the YZY token has seen the participation of more than 70,000 addresses in transactions. Among them:51,862 people lost an amount ranging from $1 to $1,000; 5,269 people lost between $1,000 and $10,000; 1,025 people lost from $10,000 to $100,000; 108 people lost from $100,000 to $1,000,000; and 3 people lost more than $1,000,000.It is worth noting that another 11 wallets have achieved profits exceeding $1,000,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26607</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Holds $7.21 Billion Ethereum ETF, Largest Institutional Holder</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26606</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on a 13F filing, Goldman Sachs held an Ethereum ETF worth $7.21 billion, emerging as the largest institutional holder. Next in line were Jane Street (with a holding of $1.9 billion) and Millennium (with a holding of $1.86 billion). (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26606</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former US Treasury Secretary Yellen: Firing Cook is illegal and dangerous, US credibility is at risk</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26605</link>
      <description>August 28th: In reaction to the controversy that was triggered by Trump&apos;s dismissal of Federal Reserve Board Governor Powell, former U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen stated: Trump claims to have &quot;fired&quot; Powell with &quot;valid reasons.&quot; This action is not only illegal but also extremely perilous.This is a blatant attempt to politicize the Federal Reserve. It is a threat to its leadership and an attempt to make monetary policy bow to the will of the president. Such an action could lead to the end of the Fed&apos;s independence—and what will follow is the collapse of the credibility of U.S. monetary policy at home and abroad.Yellen calls on Congress to safeguard the Fed&apos;s independence. The courts must reject this illegal abuse of power. The financial industry should also voice its opposition to this direct attack on the credibility of the dollar. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26605</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate 2025 Global Fall Campus Recruitment Officially Launched, HKU Fall Recruitment Summit Kicks Off First</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26604</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the world&apos;s leading cryptocurrency exchange platform Gate officially launched its 2025 Global Autumn Campus Recruitment Plan. The first stop of the autumn recruitment event will be held at the University of Hong Kong on September 17th, thus commencing this campus tour.As a significant starting point for the global campus recruitment tour, following Hong Kong, Gate will visit several top universities around the world and provide recruitment opportunities for outstanding students in various roles such as product, research and development, design, operations, and blockchain innovation. By means of efficient interview processes and diverse career development paths, Gate anticipates welcoming more young talents to join hands in shaping the future of Web3 and digital finance.Through in-depth engagement with campuses and the embrace of young talents, Gate will continuously strengthen its global ecosystem, enabling students to break through boundaries, explore the forefront</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26604</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Korea Governor: Engaging in Dialogue with Finance Minister and Regulatory Agencies on Stablecoin Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26603</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Lee Chan-yeol, the Governor of the Bank of Korea, stated that he had held discussions with the Finance Minister and regulatory agencies regarding the stablecoin issue. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 03:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26603</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Linea team-associated address deployed or used for airdrop multiplier calculation smart contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26602</link>
      <description>August 28th. On-chain analyst Zack stated in a post that an address linked to the Linea team has a source of funds that can be traced. This address has deployed the &quot;Linea Allocation Multiplier&quot; contract on the Linea mainnet. It is possible that this contract is used for airdrop multiplier calculation. The same address had previously released the &quot;Spin to Win&quot; game to test the Linea Hub.Zach further noted that since the main criteria for Linea&apos;s airdrop will be points (LXP) and on-chain multipliers, and both are now in place, it may suggest that Linea will soon begin accepting airdrop inquiries.At the same time, Zach cautioned users that the authenticity of the contract has not been verified and advised users not to interact with it.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26602</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea&apos;s Bitplanet is set to establish a Bitcoin Treasury company, planning to purchase $40 million worth of Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26601</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per Bitcoin Magazine, Paul Lee, the Co-Founder and Managing Partner of Lobo Ventures, declared at the BITCOIN ASIA 2025 conference that Bitplanet is going to establish a Bitcoin treasury company and intends to purchase Bitcoin worth $40 million. Consequently, Bitplanet will emerge as South Korea&apos;s first global institutional Bitcoin financial company.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 02:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26601</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>