<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:54:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Insider Trader」 Adds XRP and SOL Short Positions, Total Position Shows Nearly $6 Million Unrealized Gain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22919</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio address has taken short positions of 3,333,333 XRP and 44,444.44 SOL respectively. The total value of these positions is $17.07 million, with opening prices of $2.93 for XRP and $164.18 for SOL. Currently, the total value of these four short positions exceeds $221 million, and the unrealized profit is $5.95 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22919</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether issued a total of 6 billion USDT in July, bringing the total circulating supply to increase by $20 billion since the beginning of the year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22918</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Tether issued a total of 6 billion USDT during July of this year. This occurred following the release of the Q2 2025 financial report. The report shows that as of June 30, 2025, the circulating supply of USDT has exceeded 157 billion dollars, with an increase of 20 billion dollars since the start of the year.The financial report discloses that Tether holds a combined total of 127 billion dollars in U.S. Treasury bonds. It directly holds 105.5 billion dollars and indirectly holds 21.3 billion dollars, representing an increase of approximately 8 billion dollars from the first quarter. The company achieved a net profit of 4.9 billion dollars in the second quarter, with a total profit of 5.7 billion dollars in the first half of 2025, including an operating profit of 3.1 billion dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22918</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caixin: Stablecoin Craze Cools Down, Hong Kong May Limit First Batch of Stablecoin Licenses to 3-4 Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22917</link>
      <description>August 2nd. According to the report by Caixin, from June to July of this year, the discussions on stablecoins across the Taiwan Strait once reached a fever pitch and then subsided. In Hong Kong, the scope of the first batch of stablecoin licenses may be narrowed down to three to four entities. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority realized in its communication with the People&apos;s Bank of China that, within the framework of the regulatory memorandum of understanding, the main regulatory responsibilities and risks are concentrated on the Hong Kong Monetary Authority.Several mainland Chinese banks with branches in Hong Kong and mainland Chinese securities firms with branches in Hong Kong are keen to participate in Hong Kong&apos;s compliant stablecoin business. These include Bank of China Hong Kong, Bank of Communications Hong Kong, China Construction Bank (Asia), Industrial and Commercial Bank of China (Asia), Guotai Junan International, etc., involving stablecoin issuance, custody, and other busi</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22917</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: Wall Street Quietly Accumulating Ethereum, Price Target to Reach $15,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22916</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Lee, the new chairman of BitMine, stated that traditional financial institutions are increasingly investing in cryptocurrency in a steady and quiet manner. He mentioned that ETH, the native asset of the Ethereum blockchain, is benefiting from the &quot;tokenization&quot; driven by Wall Street due to its advantages in legal clarity and technical reliability. &quot;Ethereum has never experienced downtime. This is important for banks,&quot; he said.BitMine currently holds 625,000 ETH, with total assets close to 2.8 billion US dollars and almost no debt. Lee also confirmed a $1 billion stock buyback plan and reiterated the company&apos;s goal of &quot;accumulating 5% of the total Ethereum supply.&quot;Regarding Bitcoin, the current price is $113,576.36, and it is also becoming a target for institutional investors&apos; regular purchases. Lee believes that if there is a shift in the Federal Reserve&apos;s monetary policy, especially with interest rate cuts in the coming months, Bitcoin could soar to $250,000. Lee st</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22916</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider Suggestion: Propose that a national public blockchain be built under the leadership of a central state-owned enterprise</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22915</link>
      <description>August 2nd. According to Caixin, an insider stated during an interview regarding stablecoins that currently, there is no globally influential public chain in China. Another insider proposed that a national-level core public chain should be led by central enterprises, while the development of industry-level public chains can be open to market competition.An insider said, &quot;The public chain is the infrastructure for stablecoin issuance. It is of great significance and indispensable for us to build a self-controllable, safe, and efficient financial infrastructure system for the digital financial era.&quot;A person familiar with the policy remarked, &quot;Stablecoins must be issued on a public chain. The current situation is that, whether in Hong Kong or on the mainland, China does not have a globally influential public chain. If we use a U.S. public chain, we may face future political risks such as Sino-US confrontation and may potentially be &apos;blocked&apos;.&quot;&quot;Next, we need to strengthen our</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22915</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Launched OLAXBT(AIO)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22914</link>
      <description>August 2nd. Binance Alpha has now listed OLAXBT (AIO).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22914</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week&apos;s Macro Outlook: New York Fed&apos;s 1-Year Inflation Expectation, New Tariff Red Line Sparks &quot;Final Battle&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22913</link>
      <description>August 2nd: Given the unexpectedly weak job report that was released on Friday, market expectations for a Fed rate cut witnessed a significant surge. Trump&apos;s new tariffs will come into effect on August 7th. The US will impose tariffs of at least 10% on all other countries. For countries like Switzerland and India, the punitive tariff rates are 39% and 25% respectively. Some countries may still have the opportunity to negotiate for lower tariff rates.Monday 22:00: US June Factory Orders on a Monthly Basis;Tuesday 21:45: US July final S&amp;P Global Services Purchasing Managers&apos; Index (PMI);Tuesday 22:00: US July ISM Non-Manufacturing Purchasing Managers&apos; Index (PMI);Thursday 20:30: US Initial Jobless Claims up to August 2nd;Thursday 23:00: US July New York Fed 1-Year Inflation Expectations.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 10:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22913</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Q2 Earnings Report: Raises Nearly $2.4 Billion for Bitcoin Treasury Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22912</link>
      <description>August 2nd - Lately, the Trump Media &amp; Technology Group declared its Q2 financial report. The financial assets reached approximately $3.1 billion, consisting of cash, cash equivalents, restricted cash, trading securities, and short-term investments, witnessing a year-on-year growth of nearly 800%.The company successfully raised nearly $2.4 billion for its Bitcoin treasury strategy, enabling it to accumulate around $2 billion in Bitcoin and Bitcoin-related securities by July 2025, thereby becoming one of the publicly traded companies with the largest Bitcoin reserves.In Q2, the company achieved positive operating cash flow for the first time, with a cash flow from operating activities of $2.3 million. Additionally, the company continued to make progress in its Separately Managed Account (SMA) and Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) plans, submitting multiple ETF registration statements in the second quarter and subsequent periods, such as the Truth Social Crypto Blue Chip ETF, Truth Social Bit</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Son: Buying the Dip in BTC and ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22911</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, Eric Trump, the son of former U.S. President Donald Trump, made a post on social media and stated, &quot;I&apos;ll repeat it once more: Purchase during market dips!!! BTC, ETH.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22911</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Trading Volume Continues to Shrink: XRP, ETH, BTC Remain Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22910</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit was only 2.134 billion US dollars. The XRP/KRW trading pair took the lead with a 20.39% share. ETH and BTC ranked second and third respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22910</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>