<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 03:40:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 03:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Parliament Passes First Reading of Cryptocurrency Legalization and Taxation Bill</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27626</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to a report by Cointelegraph, Ukrainian MP Yaroslav Zhelezniak disclosed that the Ukrainian parliament passed the first reading of a cryptocurrency legalization and taxation bill on Wednesday. Once the bill is ultimately signed into law, it will exert a significant influence on Ukraine&apos;s digital asset economy.In the first reading vote, the bill received the support of 246 MPs. The draft bill stipulates that digital asset profits will be subject to an 18% income tax and a 5% military tax. The announcement also noted that the bill sets a 5% preferential tax rate for fiat-crypto exchanges in the first year.The proposed 23% tax rate is in line with the recommendations of the Ukrainian financial regulator in April. The initial proposal included exemptions for cryptocurrency-to-cryptocurrency transactions and stablecoin transactions, which makes Ukraine&apos;s crypto tax regime more similar to that of crypto-friendly countries.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 03:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27626</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Self-Managed Superannuation Funds&apos; cryptocurrency holdings decreased by approximately 4% year-on-year as of June</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27625</link>
      <description>September 4th. According to a report by Cointelegraph, data released by the Australian Taxation Office (ATO) indicates that although the cryptocurrency market has witnessed an increase, the cryptocurrency holdings of Australian Self-Managed Superannuation Funds (SMSFs) have decreased by approximately 4% year-on-year.Adjusted data shows that as of June 2025, SMSFs held cryptocurrency worth 3.02 billion Australian dollars (approximately 1.97 billion US dollars), which is about 100 million Australian dollars less than the 3.12 billion Australian dollars reported in June 2024.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 03:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27625</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Accelerates AI Adoption: Aims to Have Over 50% of Daily Code Generated by AI by October</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27624</link>
      <description>September 4th: Brian Armstrong, the CEO of Coinbase, announced that approximately 40% of Coinbase&apos;s daily code is generated by AI. The goal is to increase this percentage to over 50% by October. Evidently, this code requires review and understanding, and not all of the company&apos;s business areas can utilize AI-generated code. Nevertheless, Coinbase should, on the premise of responsibility, make extensive use of AI-generated code as much as possible.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 new addresses withdrew 65,662 ETH from FalconX, totaling $293 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27623</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, 3 new addresses withdrew a combined total of 65,662 ETH from FalconX. The value of these withdrawals amounted to $293 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27623</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Stock Tokenization Platform xStocks&apos; DEX Trading Volume Reached $2.86 Million Yesterday</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27622</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to Dune Data, the stock tokenization platform xStocks established by Backed witnessed a DEX trading volume of $2.86 million yesterday. Regarding trading pairs, the tokenized Tesla achieved the highest trading volume, which was $1.52 million. Meanwhile, the tokenized MSTR and the tokenized S&amp;P 500 Index had trading volumes of $362,000 and $317,000 respectively, ranking second and third.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 02:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27622</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Increases Their Position in MKR by $5.22 Million After One Month</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27621</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a whale increased its MKR holdings once again after a month. Currently, the position is worth more than $10.34 million.5 hours ago, it withdrew another 2979 MKR from FalconX, which is approximately $5.22 million. Over the past 2 months, it has accumulated a total of 8753 MKR. The average withdrawal price is $1948. The current unrealized loss is $1.421 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 02:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27621</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address is currently selling its PEPE and PENDLE positions to swap into AAVE and ENA for repositioning purposes.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27620</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the Smart Money address 0x3737 is currently in the process of swapping his positions of PEPE and PENDLE for ENA and AAVE.During the past 16 hours, he has sold 3,887.2 billion PEPE tokens (approximately $3.84 million) and 75,413 PENDLE tokens (approximately $355,000), and then purchased 4,831 AAVE tokens (approximately $1.58 million) and 3.09 million ENA tokens (approximately $2.25 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 02:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27620</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TON Strategy has approved a $250 million stock repurchase plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27619</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the TON Treasury Company listed on the Nasdaq, its TON Strategy Board of Directors, has given approval to a stock repurchase plan. The intention is to authorize the company to repurchase up to $250 million of common stock. Under this plan, the company may repurchase shares through open market transactions or other means that comply with applicable securities laws at different times.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 02:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27619</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEIRO&apos;s top holder, Trend Research, has transferred 77.9 million NEIRO to Bybit.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27618</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), within the past 20 minutes, two addresses affiliated with LD Capital&apos;s Trend Research have made a total deposit of 77.9 million NEIRO into Bybit, with a value of $6.04 million. Trend Research is currently the largest holder of NEIRO (Big Dog), having once held more than 67% of the tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 02:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27618</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget and Bitget Wallet have launched support for over a hundred US stock token assets on Ondo.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27617</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Bitget and Bitget Wallet made an announcement. They have integrated Ondo Finance, which enables the support of over a hundred types of RWA tokenized stocks. These tokens are now accessible for on-chain trading on Bitget as well as through Bitget Wallet&apos;s RWA section.The supported assets encompass stocks of renowned companies issued by Ondo Finance, such as Apple, Tesla, Microsoft, Amazon, Nvidia, and mainstream index funds. All assets are actually held in custody by regulated U.S. custodians. The tokens can mirror the price fluctuations of the underlying assets and dividend income. The minimum investment threshold is $1. All assets are priced in USD and support 24/7 trading, offering users a more convenient experience compared to traditional brokers and banks.It is reported that, unlike other on-chain stock trading platforms, stock trading within Bitget Wallet adheres to decentralized principles. It adopts a KYB model, allowing users to trade directly without the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27617</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>