<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 03:21:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 03:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue Rises to Approximately 873,000 ETH, Equivalent to Around $3.84 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24830</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 873,682 ETH. With the current price, approximately $38.84 billion worth of ETH is exiting the PoS network. The withdrawal delay is currently reported to be 15 days and 4 hours. The number of active validators has exceeded 1.08 million, and the staked ETH accounts for 29.45% of the total supply, which is approximately 35.4 million ETH.DeFi analyst Ignas stated that the current surge in unbonded ETH mainly comes from three major liquidity staking platforms. Lido leads with 285,000 ETH in the withdrawal queue, followed by EthFi (134,000 ETH) and Coinbase (113,000 ETH). Although the surge in unbonded ETH may indicate large-scale profit-taking, recent Ethereum Treasury corporate and spot ETH ETFs are absorbing most of the selling pressure.Data from strategicethreserve.xyz shows that since May 1st, the total holdings</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 03:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24830</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address bought 49,871 HYPE tokens at an average price of $48.14.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24829</link>
      <description>On August 16th, according to on-chain data, a whale address deposited 2.4 million USDC into HyperLiquid and purchased 49,871 HYPE at an average price of $48.14 per token.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24829</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address started a 125,000 U principal roll-up long position on ETH in April, with unrealized gains peaking at $43 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24828</link>
      <description>On August 16th, as per on-chain data analyst Yujin Monitoring, a trader began to take a long position in ETH with only 125,000 USDT in April this year. Currently, the asset size has reached 25 million US dollars.In April, he withdrew 125,000 USDC from 2 addresses and started to take a long position in ETH on Hyperliquid through ChangeNOW and Kucoin. The price of the first ETH long position was $1,490, which was the lowest point of the year.After he started taking a long position in ETH, ETH has been on an upward trend all the way. He continuously added to his position through continuous unrealized gains and rolled the position from the initial few hundred ETH to the current 66,000 ETH position, with a position value of 300 million US dollars. The latest additional position was made at 9 a.m. yesterday.Currently, the address has an unrealized gain of 24.78 million US dollars. Two days ago, when ETH reached a high of $4,788, the unrealized gain even reached 43 million US dollars. T</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24828</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Stock Market Down, SBET Drops Over 15%, BLSH Down 6.82%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24827</link>
      <description>On August 16th, according to rockflow data, the U.S. stock market closed on Friday with mixed performance. The three major indices showed the following:The Dow Jones initially rose by 0.08%. The S&amp;P 500 Index fell by 0.29%, and the Nasdaq dropped by 0.4%. Cryptocurrency stocks generally declined, including:Coinbase (COIN) fell by 2.26%, with a trading volume of $25.14 billion.Circle (CRCL) rose by 7.20%, with a trading volume of $33.79 billion.MicroStrategy (MSTR) fell by 1.78%, with a trading volume of $47.94 billion.Bullish (BLSH) fell by 6.82%, with a trading volume of $6.46 billion.Bitmine (BMNR) fell by 4.37%, with a trading volume of $33.94 billion.BTCS (BTCS) fell by 1.89%, with a trading volume of $19.98 million.Bit Digital (BTBT) fell by 5.64%, with a trading volume of $77.23 million.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) fell by 15.50%, with a trading volume of $12.47 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24827</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The WLFI associated address spent 18.6 million U to buy 1911 ETH and 84.5 WBTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24826</link>
      <description>On August 16th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, an address associated with WLFI spent 18.6 million USDC to acquire 1911 ETH (amounting to 8.6 million USD, with an average price of 4500 USD) and 84.5 WBTC (equivalent to 10 million USD, having an average price of 118,343 USD). The wallet still holds 5 million USDC and there is a possibility of making further purchases.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24826</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain UNI Whale transaction address has increased its position by 115,000 UNI to lower the average price, with a total position value of $6.26 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24825</link>
      <description>On August 16th, according to on-chain analyst Ai (@ai_9684xtpa), it was observed that the address beginning with 0x4B5 swapped 1090 ETH for 415,005 UNI during the uptrend of ETH on August 13th. Subsequently, during a sharp decline, the address purchased an additional 115,005 UNI 10 hours ago to reduce the average cost, accumulating a total position worth $6.26 million of UNI. The current average cost is $11.82, resulting in an unrealized loss of $535,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 01:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24825</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday, Grayscale ETHE saw a net outflow of $100 million, while GBTC saw a net outflow of $81.8 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24824</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on the monitoring of Farside Investors, yesterday Grayscale ETHE witnessed a net outflow of $101.7 million, and GBTC experienced a net outflow of $81.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 01:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini IPO Details Revealed: Stock Ticker Symbol is GEMI, First-Half Loss of $2.825 Billion in 2022 Far Exceeds Prior Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24823</link>
      <description>August 16th: On Friday, the cryptocurrency exchange Gemini officially made its S-1 filing public. It was revealed that the registration statement was submitted confidentially as early as the beginning of June.The filing indicates that Gemini is applying to list on the Nasdaq Stock Market under the stock symbol &quot;GEMI&quot;. Although the IPO price range has not been disclosed, it has been confirmed that Goldman Sachs, Citigroup, Morgan Stanley, and Cantor are serving as lead underwriters. The assets on the Gemini platform exceed $18 billion. In the first half of this year, transaction-based trading revenue accounted for 65.5% of Gemini&apos;s revenue.The financial data reveals a more difficult operating situation for Gemini than previously known: a net loss of $282.5 million in the first half of 2025, which is a significant increase from the $41.4 million loss in the same period last year. Adjusted EBITDA deteriorated from a profit of $32 million in the same period last year to a loss of $113.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 01:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24823</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 Security Infrastructure GoPlus Announces Full API Support for Transaction Simulation Feature</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24822</link>
      <description>August 16th. Web3 security infrastructure GoPlus announced that its Security API now completely supports transaction simulation functionality. The transaction simulation API integrates a multi-dimensional security analysis model and a precision risk control system. It can offer real-time transaction simulation and security detection and is equipped with an on-chain blacklist system. This feature can be widely utilized in various Web3 products like wallet applications, DApps, cross-chain bridges, aggregators, and Web3 browsers.As the world&apos;s most widely used Web3 security infrastructure, GoPlus has an advanced AI-driven real-time, dynamic, and automated security detection engine. GoPlus currently supports most mainstream EVM chains (such as ETH, BSC, Base) as well as Solana, etc. It provides multiple API services including Token security detection, malicious address detection, NFT security detection, authorization security detection, Permit phishing signature detection, dApp security</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 01:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24822</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address newly created 13 hours ago has once again withdrawn 17,300 ETH from Kraken.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24821</link>
      <description>On August 16th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet address has carried out multiple transactions within the past 13 hours. It has once again withdrawn 17,381 ETH from Kraken, with a total value of $76.9 million. This address has now withdrawn a cumulative total of 34,973 ETH from Kraken, amounting to $154 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 01:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24821</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>