<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:54:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum breaks $4300, the total short liquidation on mainstream CEX will reach $2.411 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25311</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on Coinglass data, if Ethereum breaks through $4300, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on major CEXs will amount to $2.411 billion.Conversely, if Ethereum drops below $4000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on major CEXs will reach $1.314 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not disclose the exact number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the precise value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to neighboring clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the target price will be influenced when it reaches a specific level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that once the price reaches that level, it will undergo a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25311</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale converted 3,900 ETH to 143.26 WBTC, at a rate of 0.03673</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25309</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per the monitoring of lookIntoChain, with the decrease in the ETH/BTC ratio, Whale Address 0x6e17 exchanged 3,900 ETH (approximately $16.26 million) for 143.26 WBTC at an exchange rate of 0.03673.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25309</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Bets on Stablecoins as Key Buyers of US Debt, Driving Cryptocurrency Integration into the Financial Mainstream</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25310</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per the Financial Times, US Treasury Secretary Yellen is wagering that the cryptocurrency industry will serve as a key purchaser of US debt in the forthcoming years given that the US government aims to meet the substantial demand for new bonds.Those with knowledge of the matter stated that Yellen has solicited information from major stablecoin issuers like Tether and Circle, and these discussions are influencing the Treasury Department&apos;s plans to enhance the sales of short-term Treasury bills in the upcoming quarters.The US Treasury Department hopes that stablecoins will emerge as a crucial source of demand for US government bonds, signifying the latest indication of the White House&apos;s endeavor to incorporate cryptocurrency into the core of the US financial system. Jay Barry, the global head of rates strategy at JPMorgan, one of the largest bond market traders, said, &quot;Secretary Yellen and the Treasury undoubtedly view stablecoins as a genuine source of new demand</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25310</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monad Testnet Weekly Transaction Volume Plunges by 44.4%, Weekly Active Address Count Surges by 47.16%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25308</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to Dune Data, the weekly transaction count on the Monad testnet sharply dropped to 66.16 million, which is a 44.4% decrease. Meanwhile, the weekly active addresses witnessed a significant 47.16% increase and reached 3.28 million.The total address count on the testnet has now reached 309 million, and 97,063 new addresses were added in the past 24 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25308</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former $100M Liquidation Whale James Wynn Returns to the Derivatives Market Low-Key, Testing the Waters with an ETH Long Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25307</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as per the monitoring of HyperInsight, James Wynn, a trader who once gained fame for amassing a large amount of PEPE and getting rich, has returned to the contract trading arena after more than two months of silence. Yesterday, he initiated a small long position on ETH at a price of $4239, with a position size of approximately $151,700 and a liquidation price of $4053.52.In March of this year, James Wynn entered the contract market and attracted extensive attention due to his high-frequency and large-scale contract trades on Hyperliquid. However, due to a misjudgment of the market direction, his high-leverage BTC long position was liquidated on May 30th, instantly wiping out his $100 million position. His position opening yesterday was his first public position operation in more than 2 months.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25307</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mitosis Genesis Airdrop registration will open on August 20, with claiming expected to be available until September 10.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25306</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Mitosis officially announced that the registration for the Genesis Airdrop will commence on August 20th and the registration window will remain open until August 26th. The airdrop lookup website is now active, and claiming is expected to open prior to September 10th with a one-week claiming period. During the airdrop claiming process, users have the option to claim directly or stake for 180 days to receive additional airdrop allocations.Previously, on August 17th, the Mitosis Foundation unveiled the MITO tokenomics. The total supply of tokens is 1 billion, allocated as follows: 45.5% to the ecosystem, 15% to the team, 8.76% to investors, 10% to the foundation, 10% to the Genesis Airdrop, 2% to builder rewards, 3.5% to exchange platform marketing, 4% to initial liquidity, and 1.24% to research and development.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25306</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Season Index Drops to 45</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25305</link>
      <description>August 20th. According to the data from Coinmarketcap, the Altcoin Season Index plummeted to 45. It had briefly dropped to 29 on August 11th. This index shows that among the top 100 cryptocurrency projects in terms of market capitalization, approximately 45 projects have outperformed Bitcoin in the past 90 days.Note: The CMC Altcoin Season Index is a real-time indicator utilized to evaluate whether the cryptocurrency market is currently in an altcoin-dominated season. This index is based on the performance of the top 100 altcoins compared to Bitcoin over the past 90 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25305</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Exchange Trading Volume Rebounds, ETH, XRP, BTC Hold Top Three Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25304</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit has rebounded to $2.922 billion, showing a 11.9% increase. Among them, the ETH/KRW trading pair accounted for 17.22% of the volume and ranked first in the Korean won market. The remaining top five were: XRP, BTC, API3, ADA.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core Foundation partners with Hex Trust to provide BTC Equity Staking Service to Institutional Clients</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25303</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the Core Foundation made an announcement about a deep collaboration with the digital asset custodian Hex Trust. This collaboration involves integrating Core&apos;s Double Proof-of-Stake into Hex Trust&apos;s institutional-grade custody system. Hex Trust&apos;s fully licensed custody solution simplifies institutional access to Core&apos;s BTCFi product flow, enabling clients to scale their participation more efficiently. This collaboration will offer a secure and compliant Bitcoin yield channel for institutional investors in the Asia-Pacific and Middle East regions. Institutional clients will be able to earn real on-chain block rewards by staking Bitcoin and CORE tokens without the need to transfer or sell Bitcoin, thereby accelerating the development of the BTCFi ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25303</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst Tom Lee: Ethereum Consolidation to Continue Until Midweek, Then Will Reach New Highs, Bitcoin to Break $130,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25302</link>
      <description>On August 20th, the newly appointed Chairman of BitMine, Tom Lee, whose Fundstrat Capital fund analyst released an opinion yesterday. It was stated that the recent consolidation of Ethereum is expected to continue for another 1-2 days. However, the range of $4075-$4150 will present a good risk/reward opportunity and extend into mid-week. After that, Ethereum is supposed to rise to nearly $5100 and set a slight new high.This pullback trend is similar to what is suggested by Elliott Wave Theory (which assumes that the financial market does not move randomly but follows specific and predictable wave patterns. These patterns reflect cyclical changes in investor sentiment and can be used to identify major trends and reversal points in the market), so there is no need to worry. At the same time, Bitcoin should not fall below $111,900 and will then rise to the range of $130,000-$140,000.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 19th, the newly appointed Chairman of BitMine, Tom Lee, r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 03:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25302</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>