<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:36:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Haslet: Trump&apos;s primary task is to maintain the Fed&apos;s independence, and his voting seems to carry a partisan color.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23423</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Larry Kudlow, who is the Director of the White House National Economic Council: The top priority of Trump is to keep the Federal Reserve independent. When referring to the Fed board, Kudlow stated that their votes seem to have a partisan nature. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23423</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito AI is excited to announce that the Capital Launchpad project&apos;s Billions public sale is now live.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23422</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Kaito AI announced that the Capital Launchpad project Billions&apos; public sale is currently in progress. Billions is valued at $2 billion with the aim of raising more than $5 million. 75% will be unlocked at the Time of General Emission (TGE), and the remaining 25% will be unlocked 12 months after TGE.Kaito&apos;s official personnel, 0xWenMoon, previously stated that Capital Launchpad is not a Meme token issuance platform but is similar to the on-chain crypto angel investment platform Echo and will support investors in participating in early-stage high-potential crypto projects.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23422</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company Bakkt will acquire MHT and plans to rename it to bitcoin.jp</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23421</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per Businesswire, the publicly traded company Bakkt Holdings (BKKT) in the US announced that it has entered into a share purchase agreement with the RIZAP Group to acquire the Japanese publicly traded company MarushoHotta (MHT), with the amount remaining undisclosed. This acquisition will position Bakkt as the largest shareholder of MHT. Additionally, Bakkt has purchased the domain name &quot;bitcoin.jp&quot;, which will be utilized to rename MHT upon the approval of shareholders.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23421</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company ZOOZ has completed a $5 million private funding round to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23420</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the U.S.-listed company ZOOZ Power Ltd. (ZOOZ) successfully completed a private placement worth $5 million, thereby advancing its Bitcoin Treasury strategy.Before that, on July 29th, ZOOZ had announced a $180 million private placement to initiate a Bitcoin Treasury Reserve strategy. And this $5 million represents its first round of financing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23420</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company IREN has released its July operational report, mining output reached 728 bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23419</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per Globenewswire, the U.S.-listed company IREN released its July 2025 operational report. The company&apos;s total revenue for the month came to $86 million, achieving a new all-time peak. It had $83.6 million from its Bitcoin mining business and $2.3 million from its artificial intelligence cloud services. Regarding Bitcoin mining, IREN&apos;s average hash rate in July reached 45.4 EH/s, and it mined a total of 728 Bitcoins. In the realm of artificial intelligence cloud services, the company made a new acquisition of 2400 NVIDIA Blackwell series GPUs. The initial batch of 256 B200s had completed the delivery contract signing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23419</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marex has announced integration with J.P. Morgan&apos;s blockchain settlement system Kinexys.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23418</link>
      <description>On August 6, Marex, a global financial services platform, declared the integration with Kinexys Digital Payments. Kinexys Digital Payments is a blockchain settlement system owned by JPMorgan Chase.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23418</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: OG Whale Holding BTC for Seven to Ten Years Realizes $362 Million Profit in Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23417</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Glassnode presented a chart analysis. It was revealed that within the past 24 hours, Bitcoin holders realized profits exceeding $1 billion. Specifically, $362 million (approximately 35.8%) originated from OG whales that have held Bitcoin for 7 to 10 years. This indicates a rare phenomenon that might suggest internal transfers or actual exits. Additionally, $93 million in profits came from holders who have held Bitcoin for 1 to 2 years, and they also achieved considerable gains.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23417</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix is launching spot and perpetual contract trading for TOWNS and PROVE, respectively, and initiating token reward campaigns.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23416</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Bitunix now offers spot trading for Towns (TOWNS) and Succinct (PROVE), as well as USDT perpetual contract trading. The contracts support a leverage of up to 75x, providing diverse trading options. Both trading pairs have launched with a time-limited Token Splash event:· Take part in the TOWNS event to have a chance to share a prize pool of 120,000 TOWNS tokens.· Participate in the PROVE event to get a chance to share a prize pool of 20,000 PROVE tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company DEFT discloses its crypto holdings, which include BTC, SOL, AVAX, CORE, and SUI.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23414</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to Reuters, the publicly traded U.S. company DeFi Technologies (Nasdaq: DEFT) disclosed its financial status as of July 31st, with an increase in its holdings of BTC, SOL, and CORE in July. Currently, its main cryptocurrency holdings are as follows: 251.6 BTC, which is approximately $30 million; 61,000 SOL, approximately $11.64 million; 398,321.6 AVAX, about $9.58 million; 7,100,000 CORE, approximately $4.03 million; 4,913,918 SUI, approximately $18.5 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23414</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cao Cao Mobility Partners with Victory Securities to Explore RWA, Stablecoin Payments, and Compliant Cryptocurrency Issuance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23415</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Cao Cao Mobility announced today that it has entered into a strategic memorandum of understanding on virtual assets with the Hong Kong-licensed financial institution Victory Securities. The two parties will enhance their cooperation in three main aspects: the tokenization of real-world assets, the application of stablecoin payments, and the compliant issuance of digital currencies. Gong Xin, the executive director and CEO of Cao Cao Mobility, stated that by leveraging blockchain technology and the Web 3.0 innovative model, they will expedite the asset tokenization process in the Robotaxi industry.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23415</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>