<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:49:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>0xSun: Long ETH and Short Shitcoin Hedge Strategy currently has an overall profit of about 16%, although the price increase is not as high as ETH, the risk is lower.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24366</link>
      <description>August 13th, Smart Money, the crypto KOL 0xSun (@0xSunNFT) stated that on August 1st, the Ethereum price was approximately $3700, and it has now risen to $4660, representing a 26% increase. The short positions in altcoins witnessed a concentrated growth of 5% to 15%, with an overall profit margin of around 16%. In contrast to naked long Ethereum, a hedging strategy exerts less psychological pressure in the face of a downturn. Especially considering that Ethereum had dropped to $3360, where naked long positions might have been liquidated. However, during hedging, altcoins typically experience greater declines than Ethereum, yet the overall profit can still be enhanced, providing a better holding experience.Previously reported on August 1st, 0xSun mentioned that the current market sentiment is highly polarized between longs and shorts. He has personally initiated a hedging trade (long ETH and short a basket of altcoins), with a position ratio of approximately 1:1, believing that instit</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24366</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Big Brother Whale」 Huang Licheng has closed his ETH and HYPE long positions, with a total profit of 33.83 million US dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24365</link>
      <description>On August 13th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, &quot;Big Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng has liquidated his long positions in ETH (25x) and HYPE (5x), realizing a total profit of $33.83 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24365</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eden Network has announced the cessation of its operations and the distribution of its held 2000 ETH to EDEN holders.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24364</link>
      <description>On August 13th, the Eden Network put out an announcement saying, &quot;Archer DAO was established in 2020 with the goal of creating a novel revenue source for Ethereum miners by seizing MEV (Miner Extractable Value) profits. In July 2021, the Archer DAO community passed a governance proposal to upgrade the project and rebrand it as the Eden Network. Due to fierce competition in the MEV field and high operating expenses, after careful thought and consultation with community members, the Eden Network has announced the suspension of its operations, with immediate effect on services like Eden RPC, Eden Bundles, Mempool Stream, etc.&quot;The Eden Network currently holds 2,000 ETH, which will be distributed to EDEN token holders at a fixed rate of 0.00001506 ETH per EDEN. The redemption period will be open from today until September 30th at 23:59 (UTC), and it is limited to non-U.S. residents. Token holders who have not staked their tokens are advised to redeem them promptly and unstake, and the rem</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24364</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>odin.fun Co-founder: Company Funds Insufficient to Cover Loss, Remaining Funds on Platform Safe</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24363</link>
      <description>On August 13th, a co-founder of odin.fun posted on the X Platform in response to the previously stolen funds, stating, &quot;We discovered a significant vulnerability in our latest liquidity AMM (Automated Market Maker) update. Some malicious users (mainly related to criminal gangs in China) took advantage of this vulnerability to steal a large quantity of BTC from the platform. We are still in the process of assessing the specific amount of BTC lost, and the company&apos;s funds are not enough to cover the loss. The remaining funds on the platform are in a safe state. We have identified several groups that benefited from exploiting this vulnerability and will pursue them and file lawsuits (especially considering the amount of evidence we have, including the activities in their wallets).&quot;Earlier reports suggested that the odin.fun platform had a suspected vulnerability, resulting in approximately 58.2 BTC being transferred out.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24363</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 290,000 LINK from Binance 19 minutes ago, equivalent to $7.08 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24362</link>
      <description>On August 13th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale that had been inactive for 2 years transferred 290,000 LINK from Binance 19 minutes ago. The transferred amount is approximately worth $7.08 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24362</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch TCOM Global (TCOM) on August 15th, and eligible users can claim the airdrop using Alpha Points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24361</link>
      <description>On August 13th, according to official channels, Binance Alpha is set to become the first platform to list TCOM Global (TCOM) on August 15th. Once Alpha trading commences, eligible users can access the Alpha event page to claim an airdrop by using Alpha Points. Specific details will be disclosed separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24361</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bottom-Fishing Whale &quot;7 Siblings&quot; has currently sold 19,957 ETH and still holds approximately 280,000 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24360</link>
      <description>On August 13th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, the entity &quot;7 Siblings&quot; purchased 100,000 ETH for approximately $2,270 during last year&apos;s August 5th flash crash. Today, they sold their ETH. So far today, they have sold a total of 19,957 ETH and exchanged it for 90.44 million USDC with an average selling price of $4,532.Currently, they should still hold about 280,000 ETH ($1.3 billion). And they have bought ETH at the dip in two previous flash crashes:During last year&apos;s August 5th flash crash when ETH dropped by more than 15%, they bought 100,000 ETH at around $2,270;During this year&apos;s April 7th flash crash when ETH dropped by more than 10%, they bought 25,000 ETH at around $1,700.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana On-chain Meme Coin nub Surges Over 38% in 24 Hours, Market Cap Now at $48 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24359</link>
      <description>On August 13th, according to GMGN data, the Solana-based Meme coin nub saw a surge of over 38% in the past 24 hours. It currently has a market cap of $48 million and a 24-hour trading volume of $7 million.nubcat (with the token symbol: nub) is derived from the quirky cat character created by artist Leon Karssen more than thirteen years ago. Karssen is a Dutch artist renowned for his humorous hand-drawn style and illustration work related to skateboarding culture. He participates in daily drawing activities, and the community focuses on a playful atmosphere.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience high price volatility, and investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 04:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24359</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Meme Coins Experience Bull Run, FWOG Surges 33% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24358</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on market data, as SOL briefly exceeded $200, various meme coins in the Solana ecosystem generally experienced a price increase. These include:· FWOG rose by 33.4% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $0.06585.· FARTCOIN increased by 26.1% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $1.11.· BOME surged by 17.7% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $0.00217.· WIF rose by 11.8% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $1.031.· POPCAT went up by 11% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $0.3437.· MEW increased by 10.9% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $0.00346.· BONK rose by 8.8% in the past 24 hours and is now priced at $0.000027.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24358</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: Cryptographic Assets Such as Bitcoin and Ethereum Will Become Anchors for Fundraising by Funds and Institutions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24357</link>
      <description>On August 13th, Wang Feng, the founder of LightHash, mentioned in a post that cryptocurrency is having a profound impact on the financial industry, encompassing banks, asset management companies, and VCs. It is not merely about retail investors holding assets such as Ethereum; rather, it is about a structural consensus taking shape in the financial market. Bitcoin, Ethereum, Solana, and perhaps even XRP are likely to become the anchor assets for many funds and institutional fundraising. Traditional fund managers and General Partners (GPs) are currently altering their viewpoints, and it is still not too late to actively engage.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 04:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24357</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>