<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:58:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Data: The overall NFT trading volume in the last 24 hours has decreased by 35.7%, reaching $16.03 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22417</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the overall trading volume of the NFT market witnessed a 35.7% decrease and reached $16.03 million. Regarding the top three NFTs in terms of trading volume, all of them are Ethereum-based projects, namely CryptoPunks, Fat Penguins, and Moonbirds.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22417</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSea Team Member: Token Airdrop Will Be Evaluated Based on User Profile</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22416</link>
      <description>On July 30th, an OpenSea team member named Adam Hollander responded in the Discord community regarding the impact of historical usage records on token airdrops. He stated that OpenSea will take into consideration users&apos; &quot;profiles&quot;.For instance, there are some people who visited here during the bull market and never returned. Others have only recently shown up, with the intention of &quot;rug pulling&quot;. Meanwhile, there are also senior figures who have never left, withstood the test of the bear market, and still remain strong here. This information is being evaluated by the foundation.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LazAI&apos;s inaugural IDO project CALITH is currently priced at $0.4646, with a market capitalization exceeding $46 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22415</link>
      <description>On July 30th, LazAI&apos;s Launchpad platform, LazPad, has its first IDO project, Corrupted Alith, with its token CALITH currently priced at $0.4646 and a circulating market cap of $46 million. Since the opening price of $0.0088 on June 10th for the Token Generation Event (TGE), it has accumulated a 5163% increase and has become the AI concept token with the highest annual increase in the Metis ecosystem. It has also been listed on Netswap, the native decentralized exchange of the Metis ecosystem.Lazpad is a user-friendly on-chain AI agent launch platform that supports both open and curated dual-track securitization paths. Backed by the powerful LazAI internal incentive ecosystem and deeply integrated into the ecosystem, it aims to transform complex AI models into interoperable, composable, and tradable agent tokens. These AI agents, represented as tokens, open up a co-creation crowdfunding, public participation, and win-win development path for creators, investors, and the agents themsel</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22415</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben&apos;s fund held $54.7 million worth of Coinbase stock in the second quarter, marking the first time it has allocated to a crypto-related stock.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22414</link>
      <description>July 30th: Based on a 13F filing submitted to the SEC, the fund managed by Richard Deng, Oriental Harbor, once again augmented its holdings of US stocks. By the end of the second quarter, the Oriental Harbor Investment Fund held a total of 13 US stock positions with a value of $1.126 billion, which is equivalent to more than 8 billion yuan. This represents a notable increase from the $868 million at the end of the first quarter.The data indicates that the cryptocurrency company Coinbase was newly included in Oriental Harbor&apos;s portfolio during the second quarter, and the position was valued at approximately $54.7 million. (Sina Finance)It is worth highlighting that Richard Deng had previously disclosed in February 2021 that he had purchased a Bitcoin ETF fund and stated, &quot;I have acquired 1% of the Bitcoin ETF fund. Although it is a bit late, I am convinced that once I understand it, I should embrace it! I hope to maintain my curiosity about new things!&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22414</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized AI Infrastructure Manifold Completes $10.5M Series A Funding Round, Led by OSS Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22413</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the decentralized AI infrastructure Manifold announced that it has successfully completed a Series A funding round worth $10.5 million in order to expedite the development of its decentralized AI cloud platform, Targon. This funding round was spearheaded by OSS Capital, and was participated in by Digital Currency Group, Tobias Lütke, Ram Shriram, Zachary Smith, Jacob Steeves, Ala Shaabana, Logan Kilpatrick, and other prominent investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22413</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bitcoin Treasury company Twenty On, led by the son of the US Secretary of Commerce, has increased its Bitcoin holdings to 43,514 coins, making it the world&apos;s third-largest corporate BTC holder.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22412</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the official website of Bitcoin treasury company Twenty One Capital, which is led by the son of the U.S. Secretary of Commerce, updated its holdings data. As of now, it holds 43,514 bitcoins. With a current circulating share count of 345.47 million shares, the holding is 0.00012559 BTC per share.According to the latest data from Bitcoin Treasuries, Twenty One Capital is currently the world&apos;s third-largest corporate Bitcoin holder, following only Strategy (628,791 BTC) and MARA (50,000 BTC).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22412</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Banking Giant Revolut Considers Acquiring US Bank for Licensing</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22411</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as reported by the Financial Times, the digital banking behemoth Revolut is contemplating the acquisition of a US bank in order to swiftly obtain a US banking license.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22411</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: Referring to factors such as oil, gold, global currency market cap, the future price of Ethereum could reach $706,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22410</link>
      <description>On July 30th, a research report from ethdigitaloil.com indicates that when taking into account factors such as oil, gold, and the global currency market capitalization, etc., the market capitalization of ETH may reach $85 trillion, and the expected future price of a single ETH is projected to reach $706,000.Before this news, Bitmine, an ETH reserve-listed company, officially announced on Platform X that they have invited multiple research institutions to assess the &quot;reset value&quot; of Ethereum (Wall Street valuation), with an estimated value of $60,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22410</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Bankless team member shaaa will serve as the Listing Team Lead at Coinbase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22409</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the former member of the Bankless team, shaaa (@shaaa256), announced that he had joined Coinbase&apos;s listings team as the leader.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22409</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several KOLs have revealed that the team member of Kaito, Wen Yue, is suspected of receiving a bribe. Wen Yue has denied the accusation, stating that all payments were made directly to Kaito.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22408</link>
      <description>July 30th. Recently, several KOLs, like CryptoBrave (@cryptobraveHQ), have claimed that Kaito&apos;s Business Manager WenYue is suspected of taking bribes.Among them, CryptoBrave said that WenYue imposed an excessive listing fee on certain projects, overcharging approximately $200,000 in suspected bribes in the name of an overall fee package to ensure the project&apos;s priority listing on Kaito. The crypto influencer @SEFATUBA3 stated, &quot;WenYue demands a $30,000 bridge toll, which can be paid through white list allocation or tokens.&quot;In response to the above accusations, WenYue (@0xWenMoon) said, &quot;I have never accepted any bribes. Any payment exceeding $150,000 was for additional professional analysis services (such as the Kaito Pro platform) or to accelerate the listing schedule (for example, if the project team needed to quickly climb the rankings to align with a specific event). All payments are made directly to Kaito and not to me or any other individual.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 04:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>