<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:13:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s FedSpeak: The overall sentiment of the July meeting committee was tilted towards the hawkish side, with more officials showing openness to a rate cut in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25448</link>
      <description>On August 21st, &quot;The Fed&apos;s Whisperer&quot; Nick Timiraos stated: The minutes of the Fed&apos;s meetings usually do not disclose a great deal of new information. Instead, they reinforce the information that is already public. Firstly, based on Powell&apos;s press conference, the overall sentiment of the committee during the July meeting was hawkish (at least in comparison to the market). Secondly, there is a clear emphasis on data and forecasts. That is, after the release of the August 1st jobs report, more officials showed a willingness to consider a rate cut in September. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve meeting minutes mentioned &quot;stablecoin&quot; eight times.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25447</link>
      <description>August 21st. The minutes of this week&apos;s Federal Reserve meeting made eight references to &quot;stablecoins&quot;. Many participants engaged in discussions regarding recent and future developments related to payment stablecoins and their potential implications for the financial system. These participants pointed out that with the recent enactment of the &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; (the &quot;U.S. Stablecoin Guidance and National Innovation Act&quot;), the usage of payment stablecoins may witness an increase. Payment stablecoins contribute to enhancing the efficiency of the payment system. It has also been noticed that such stablecoins may lead to an increase in the demand for the underlying assets supporting them (including U.S. Treasuries). (Jinshi)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25447</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Taper Talk: Some Officials Suggest They May Join Rate-Cutting Camp in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25446</link>
      <description>August 21st: In Nick Timiraos&apos; latest article, titled &quot;the Fed&apos;s Whisperer&quot;, it was reported that the minutes of today&apos;s policy meeting indicated that there was widespread support within the Fed for the decision made last month to keep interest rates unchanged. Although two officials advocated for a rate cut, a few others have aligned with Bullard and Bostic, suggesting that they may support a rate cut at the Fed&apos;s next meeting on September 16th and 17th.They pointed out that the transmission of tariff increases to consumer prices has been slower than anticipated, which is expected to help ease concerns about the potential new inflationary impact resulting from rising import costs. However, the &quot;hawks&quot; who are focused on inflation noted that since the last meeting, price pressures have been on the rise, including in the services sector. Kansas City Fed President Esther George stated in a speech last week that the impact of tariffs on inflation is limited. This is partly because the F</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25446</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Certain Ancient Whale Sells Bitcoin and Goes Long on Ethereum, Holding Over 65,000 ETH in Long Positions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25442</link>
      <description>On August 21st, according to the monitoring of @mlmabc, a wallet that transferred 15,000 BTC from HTX and Binance seven years ago (which was worth $95 million at that time). In the past 8 hours, it deposited approximately 550 BTC into Hyperliquid (worth $62 million), sold them all, and transferred the USDC to two other wallets. These addresses were split to jointly go long on Ethereum. Currently, they hold a total of 65,680 ETH in the three wallets (worth $282 million) in a long position.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25442</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Downward Revision of Non-Farm Payrolls Data May Exacerbate Fed Officials&apos; Concerns About Economic Slowdown</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25445</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the minutes of the Federal Reserve&apos;s July meeting indicated that during the meeting held on July 30th, the concerns of some Federal Reserve officials about an economic slowdown had grown stronger. The minutes stated: &quot;Several participants suggested that they anticipated that the pace of economic activity in the second half of the year would be significantly slower.&quot;The minutes also further noted: &quot;Regarding the household sector, several participants observed that the deceleration in real income growth might be impeding the growth of consumer spending.&quot; It is important to note that these viewpoints were expressed several days before the release of the July jobs report, which revised down the estimated job gains for May and June by 258,000. Therefore, since the July meeting, the concerns about an economic slowdown potentially triggered by the softness in the labor market may have further intensified for some officials. (Jin10)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25445</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase to List Sapien (SAPIEN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25444</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Coinbase will make Sapien (SAPIEN) available on the Base network. It is important to note that you should not send this asset through other networks as there is a risk of losing funds. If liquidity conditions are fulfilled, trading will commence later today. Once there is an adequate supply of this asset, the SAPIEN-USD trading pair will be gradually rolled out. In some jurisdictions, support for Sapien may be restricted.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25444</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Meeting Minutes: Unemployment Rate Remains Low</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25443</link>
      <description>August 21st: The Federal Reserve made public the minutes of its July meeting. It was noted in the meeting that during the discussion on the labor market, participants pointed out that the unemployment rate remains low and that employment has either reached or is close to the estimated maximum employment level.Several participants emphasized that the low level and stability of the unemployment rate are the outcome of a combination of low recruitment and low layoff rates. Some participants indicated that according to their contacts and business survey respondents, in a situation of high uncertainty, firms are reluctant to hire or lay off workers.Regarding the outlook for the labor market, some participants mentioned possible indicators of weak labor demand, such as the slowing of job growth which is more concentrated, an increase in the unemployment rate for Black and young workers, and job switchers having lower wage gains compared to those who remain in their jobs. (Jin10)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25443</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Meeting Minutes: Stablecoins Could Increase Demand for U.S. Treasuries</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25441</link>
      <description>August 21st. The Federal Reserve disclosed the minutes of its July meeting. It was mentioned that numerous participants discussed the recent and future developments regarding payment-based stablecoins and their potential influence on the financial system. These participants pointed out that with the recent enactment of the &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; (the &quot;U.S. Stablecoin Guidance and National Innovation Act&quot;), the usage of payment-based stablecoins might increase.They stated that payment-based stablecoins contribute to enhancing the efficiency of the payment system. Additionally, they observed that such stablecoins might elevate the demand for the underlying assets supporting them (including U.S. Treasury bonds).Furthermore, the participating members who expressed their viewpoints also expressed concerns that stablecoins might have a more extensive impact on banks, the financial system, and the implementation of monetary policy. Therefore, they deserve close attention, including monitoring the var</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25441</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argot Collective has been listed on the Strategic Ethereum Reserve website, holding 2,474 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25440</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the address of the non-profit development organization Argot Collective, which received 7000 ETH in operational funding from the Ethereum Foundation, has now been included in the Strategic Ethereum Reserve (SΞR) website. There are 2,474 ETH in its reserve.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Meeting Minutes: Tariff Impact Still Poses Significant Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25439</link>
      <description>August 21st: The Federal Reserve made public the minutes of its July meeting. It was stated in the minutes that regarding the inflation outlook, participants commonly anticipated that inflation would increase in the short term. They hold the view that there remains substantial uncertainty regarding the timing, extent, and durability of the impacts of this year&apos;s tariff hikes.Regarding the timing, numerous participants pointed out that the complete effects of higher tariffs might take a certain period to be reflected in the consumer prices of goods and services. They enumerated several factors that could give rise to such delays. These factors include inventory accumulation in response to tariff increases, the slow transfer of input cost increases to the prices of final goods and services, gradual updates of contract prices, the preservation of relationships between businesses and customers, issues related to tariff collection, and ongoing trade negotiations. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25439</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>