<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Short-Term Breakout Above $195, 24-hour Gain Reaches 7.31%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25817</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, based on HTX market data, SOL experienced a brief surge and rose above $195. Currently, it is trading at $194.86, indicating a 24-hour price increase of 7.31%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25817</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Short-Term Breaks $117,000, Daily Gain Reaches 3.72%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25816</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin briefly rose above $117,000 and is currently trading at $116,989, with a daily increase of 3.72%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: It is expected to have a total interest rate cut of 75 basis points by the end of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25815</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Kathy Bostjancic, the chief economist of Nationwide, stated that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates by a total of 75 basis points before the end of the year. She pointed out, &quot;Powell has adopted a noticeably more dovish tone and significantly opened the door to a rate cut in September. He sees that the downside risks to employment are rising significantly. This supports our view that there will be a 25 basis points rate cut next month. We also continue to expect that by the end of the year, the Fed will have cut rates by a total of 75 basis points because the labor market will further weaken and the rise in inflation is only moderate and temporary.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25815</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Harker: Fed Should Stick to Moderately Constrained Monetary Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25814</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Federal Reserve&apos;s Harker expressed that the Fed has not yet attained its inflation target completely and should adhere to a moderately restrained monetary policy. It is necessary to exercise caution before taking any rate-cutting measures. It is anticipated that the inflation and unemployment rates in the United States will rise.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25814</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpol&apos;s &quot;Operation Sunbird 2.0&quot; Dismantles Major Cryptocurrency Crime Network, Arrests 1,209 People</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25813</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per The Block report, INTERPOL announced on Friday that its coordinated &quot;Operation HAEVEN 2.0&quot; has managed to apprehend 1,209 suspected cybercriminals. These criminals have collectively targeted nearly 88,000 victims. It is reported that this operation involved investigators from 18 African countries and the UK.The operation commenced in June this year and has thus far retrieved $97.4 million in funds and dismantled 11,432 pieces of malicious infrastructure. During the course of the operation, the Zambian authorities disrupted a large-scale online investment fraud scheme that promised high returns through advertising campaigns. As a result, approximately 65,000 victims invested in cryptocurrency, with the estimated fraud amounting to $300 million.In Angola, investigators have dismantled 25 cryptocurrency mining facilities. They have also arrested 60 Chinese citizens who were illegally validating blockchain transactions and seized mining and IT equipment worth ove</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25813</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Ancient Whale Deposits 300 Bitcoins Again, or Will Continue to Swap for ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25809</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as monitored by LookOnChain, the Bitcoin ancient whale has just deposited an additional 300 BTC (valued at $34.78 million) into Hyperliquid. There is a possibility that it may be swapped for ETH.In just 3 days, it has achieved an unrealized gain of $84 million:It holds 135,265 ETH ($581 million) in long positions with an average entry price of $4,295, realizing a profit of $49 million.It purchased 100,979 ETH ($435 million) in the spot market at an average price of $4,309, realizing a profit of $35 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25809</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Announces Protocol Upgrade 002, Aiming to Significantly Improve Ethereum L2 System Data Availability</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25812</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Ethereum Foundation released Protocol Update 002, which detailed the Blob Data Extension Roadmap. The plan is intended to substantially enhance the data availability of the Ethereum L2 system, providing support for real-time payments, DeFi, social media, AI applications, and other scenarios.The key updates are as follows:1. The upcoming Fusaka upgrade will introduce the PeerDAS architecture, increasing the number of Blobs in a block from the current 6 to 48.2. Progressive mainnet capacity growth will be achieved through the Blob Parameter Hard Fork (BPO), theoretically resulting in an 8x improvement in throughput.3. Bandwidth optimization technologies such as &quot;Unit-Level Message Passing&quot; will be used to reduce network redundant communication.4. The Glamsterdam upgrade (expected in mid-2026) will introduce PeerDAS v2, further expanding data availability.5. Ongoing research on Blob Pool Extension and FullDAS technology will be carried out to ensure Ethereum&apos;s c</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25812</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI increased its ETH holdings by 1076 coins at an average price of $4670</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25811</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, WLFI has just made an additional purchase of 1076 ETH, with an average price of $4670.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25811</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jito: S-1 Filed for VanEck JitoSOL ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25810</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to official channels, Jito has made an announcement that it has submitted the S-1 filing for the VanEck JitoSOL ETF. This filing is the outcome of several months&apos; worth of policy advocacy efforts carried out with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission and other regulatory bodies. It is also a result of the continuous business expansion and educational undertakings by several ecosystem contributors.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25810</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Board Governor Powell Responds to Trump&apos;s Firing Threat: No Intention to Resign, Will Not Yield to External Pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25808</link>
      <description>August 22: Federal Reserve Board Governor Powell responded to Trump&apos;s threat of dismissal by stating that he has &quot;no intention of resigning in the face of threats&quot; and emphasizing that he will not be swayed by external pressure.Earlier today, Trump declared that if Federal Reserve Board Governor Powell does not resign, he will remove her. (Straits Financial News)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>