<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:56:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale conducted a stop-loss sell-off of 130 million PUMP tokens, and currently still holds 1.17 billion tokens.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23701</link>
      <description>On August 8th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, an address sold 130 million PUMP tokens within 6 hours at an average price of $0.0033 and received 424,700 USDC in exchange. Currently, this address still holds 1.17 billion PUMP tokens (valued at approximately $3.92 million), with an unrealized loss of around $898,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23701</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hua Xing Capital Founder Bao Fan Rumored to Have Resurfaced</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23700</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to Caixin, multiple independent sources have suggested that Fang Xinghai, the founder of the Hong Kong-listed company Huaxing Capital Holdings (01911.HK), has recently been rumored to have made a reappearance. In February 2023, Fang Xinghai, the founder of the Hong Kong-listed company Huaxing Capital Holdings (01911.HK), was suddenly taken away by relevant authorities, which sent shockwaves through the venture capital circle. Subsequently, the details of the case and the progress of the investigation have not been disclosed by the authorities. Huaxing Capital responded by stating that Fang Xinghai is no longer involved in the group&apos;s daily management and operations, and his personal activities are private matters that fall outside the scope of Huaxing Capital&apos;s response.According to RockFlow market data, Huaxing Capital Holdings (01911.HK) in the Hong Kong stock market</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23700</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address held ETH for four years to break even and take profit, having accumulated 3750 ETH in 2021.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23699</link>
      <description>August 8th. According to on-chain analyst Ai (@ai_9684xtpa), an address that has been holding ETH for four years has finally reached the break-even point and cashed out. The address &apos;0x219...C3c4F&apos; sold 3000 ETH in the past hour, with a value of $11.74 million, realizing a profit of $1.24 million.During the super bull market from April to December 2021, the main funding address accumulated 3750 ETH at an average price of $3500. The value of the asset had once shrunk by 70%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23699</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The academic community has referred to Trump&apos;s attempt to seize control of statistical agencies, accusing them of &quot;employment data manipulation,&quot; as lacking evidence</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23698</link>
      <description>August 8: In this week, the University of Chicago carried out a survey among 46 American economists. Among them, 38 stated that there is no evidence indicating that the US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) employment data is inclined towards either the Republican Party or the Democratic Party. Many economists argue that Trump&apos;s attacks on the US economic data agencies pose a significant threat to official statistics. Last Friday, Trump ordered the removal of the head of the BLS (the non-farm payroll data agency), claiming without any evidence that the disappointing employment data was &quot;manipulated.&quot; The BLS later confirmed the dismissal of the head, Erika McEntarfer, and her deputy William Wiatrowski took on the acting head role.Trump had previously claimed that the BLS inflated employment numbers last year to assist the Democratic Party during the presidential election. However, the agency revised the numbers downward by more than 800,000 in August 2024, which was regarded as a setba</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23698</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IN is now available on multiple exchanges including Binance, Bybit, Bitget, KuCoin, and more.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23697</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the native token of INFINIT, IN, was listed on Binance (Alpha &amp; Futures), Bybit Futures, Bitget, KuCoin, and many other platforms. As the core driving force of the INFINIT AI-powered DeFi economy, IN enables anyone to create and monetize DeFi strategies by using more than 20 AI Agents. End users can execute these strategies with just one click.IN is utilized for value exchange within the ecosystem, granting exclusive access to products, facilitating governance voting, and achieving incentive alignment throughout the system. Additionally, users staking IN can receive protocol fees from Agent and strategy execution. This allows them to unlock advanced features such as exclusive access to top strategies and participate in key decision-making voting, including protocol upgrades, fee models, and integration solutions.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23697</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 55,664 SOL from Binance and transferred it to Kamino for staking, worth $9.72 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23696</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, the whale address BnwZvG withdrew an additional 55,664 SOL from Binance. This amount is worth $9.72 million and was deposited into the Kamino staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has deposited 1,383 ETH into a CEX, worth $5.39 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23695</link>
      <description>August 8th. Based on the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale that had been dormant for eight months deposited 1,383 ETH, which is worth $5.39 million, into a CEX and achieved a profit of $4.32 million.The whale originally withdrew 2,768 ETH with a value of $6.45 million and still retains 1,384 ETH worth $5.39 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23695</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s new Sidekick(K) launchpad opened with an approximate initial return of $92.5</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23694</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on market data, Sidekick (K) has been listed on Binance Alpha. It is currently trading at $0.37 and has a market capitalization of $41 million. Each eligible user can receive an airdrop of 250 K tokens. The estimated airdrop value per person is approximately $92.50 according to the current price.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23694</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX is now integrated with Apple Pay, supporting one-click coin purchases for users in the United States and Europe.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23693</link>
      <description>August 8th. According to official sources, the CEO of OKX, Star, retweeted the message &quot;Apple Pay has now landed on the OKX European site&quot; on the X platform and stated: &quot;This is a significant step towards the adoption of cryptocurrencies. Apple Pay has been fully integrated into the buy-crypto process on the OKX platform, enabling users in the United States and the European Economic Area (EEA) to make one-click coin purchases without the need to enter bank card information. OKX is making the crypto world simpler, more accessible, and truly mainstream.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23693</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches Sidekick (K) Spot Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23692</link>
      <description>August 8th. Bitget has launched Sidekick (K) in the Innovation Zone. The trading channel is now available, and the withdrawal channel will open at 18:00 on August 8th (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23692</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>