<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:38:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: The Crypto Reserve Frenzy is the final opportunity for a large-scale altcoin bull market, currently nearing the top but not yet over</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23031</link>
      <description>On August 4th, trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio stated in a post on his personal channel that he holds a cautiously optimistic view regarding the DAT &quot;Decentralized Asset Trusts&quot; frenzy. This frenzy is approaching its zenith but has not yet come to an end, and it may potentially be the final opportunity for altcoins to ride a globally capital-backed massive bull market.It is now evident that the majority of capital is either unable or reluctant to cross the cryptocurrency realm divide through direct token purchases. The current DAT is a subpar (but similar) imitation of a meme coin ETF. We have not actually witnessed a case where DAT has led to a significant inflow of funds into an altcoin. However, considering Traditional Finance&apos;s enthusiasm for Ethereum (ETH), this possibility is quite substantial. In theory, this influx of funds should make the performance of other crypto-native projects seem insignificant in comparison. Nevertheless, the market has not yet fully recognized this. Although</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23031</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Network Exit Queue Decreases to around 527,000 ETH, Join Queue Increases to around 150,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23030</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website validatorqueue, the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 527,128 ETH. This is a decrease from nearly 560,000 ETH yesterday and is worth approximately $18.62 billion. The recent peak of the exit queue was 744,000 ETH. Currently, the exit waiting time is approximately 9 days and 4 hours.At the same time, the amount of ETH queued to join the network is approximately 149,701 ETH, which is an increase from 123,000 ETH yesterday and is worth approximately $5.29 billion. The expected activation delay is about 2 days and 14 hours.Previously reported, this situation reflects two opposing forces in the market. On one hand, some stakers may have decided to take profits after Ethereum rebounded by more than 160% from its April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new funds deposited driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also increasi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23030</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address has seemingly sold 38,582 ETH in the past week, totaling $138 million in value.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23028</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), it is reported that the &quot;Smart Money that once bought low and sold high on WBTC and made a profit of $14.26 million&quot; has sold 38,582 ETH in the past week, with a value of $138 million. If sold, they would make a profit of $36.57 million.Since the beginning of this year, this address has withdrawn a total of 77,700 ETH from Kraken ($202 million), with an average price of only $2600; currently, they still hold 25,054 ETH on-chain, and most of them are in Aave.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23028</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The French political party National Rally plans to draft a bill to utilize surplus electricity from nuclear power plants to &quot;mine&quot; Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23029</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to the French newspaper Le Monde, the French far-right political party National Rally is in the process of preparing to draft a bill with the intention of using the surplus electricity from nuclear power plants to &quot;mine&quot; Bitcoin. During a visit to the Normandy Flamanville nuclear power plant on March 11th, the three-time presidential candidate Marine Le Pen showed her support for using the surplus electricity from nuclear reactors to &quot;mine&quot; Bitcoin. The plan entails installing high-performance computers on the premises of the French energy giant EDF. National Rally MP Aurélien Lopez-Liguori stated that he was assigned in July to convert this idea into a bill.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23029</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The total market capitalization of stablecoins increased by $17.8 billion last week, now standing at $2,674.05 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23027</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on DeFiLlama data, the current total market value of stablecoins in the crypto market is $267.05 billion, which shows an increase of $17.8 billion from last week and represents a 0.67% growth compared to the previous period. Among them, USDT accounts for 61.61% of the market value.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23027</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Looking Forward to Ethereum Reaching $3,800-$4,000 Again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23026</link>
      <description>On August 4th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio posted on his personal channel and said that these days the market situation has been extremely torturous. However, he finally managed to get through it. He almost surrendered at the bottom. Considering Bitcoin&apos;s rebound from $112,000, he decided to stick to a long position. Now he is looking forward to Ethereum pushing up again to the range of $3,800 to $4,000 and seeking opportunities for short-term trades. But he is unsure how the market will react if it deteriorates again.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23026</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai publicly listed company RSXYZ has added 31.05 Bitcoins to its holdings, bringing the total to 50 Bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23025</link>
      <description>On August 4th, the Thai-listed company RSXYZ officially announced that it has increased its holdings by 31.05 bitcoins. The average purchase price is $117,444.31. RSXYZ&apos;s total bitcoin holdings have now reached 50 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23025</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Paradigm holds 19,134,900.46 HYPE tokens, worth approximately $7.654 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23024</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per the monitoring of @mlmabc, Paradigm may hold 19,134,900.46 HYPE, which is approximately worth 7.654 billion U.S. dollars. The estimated average cost is 16.46 dollars, with a total cost of about 315 million U.S. dollars and an unrealized gain of around 450 million U.S. dollars.BlockBeats previously reported that the strategic reserve of Hyperliquid, Sonnet BioTherapeutics (SONN), was initially funded by the top crypto VC Paradigm by injecting more than 10 million HYPE that they directly purchased at the end of last year.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CME FedWatch: 82.6% Probability of 25 Basis Point Rate Cut in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23023</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut in September is 82.6%, and the probability of rates remaining unchanged is 17.4%.There is a 4.2% probability that the Fed will keep rates unchanged until October. The cumulative probability of a 25-basis-point cut is 33.1%, and the cumulative probability of a 50-basis-point cut is 62.7%.The next two FOMC meeting dates of the Fed are September 17th and October 29th.Last week, the U.S. only added 73,000 nonfarm payrolls in July, which was significantly below expectations. The data for May and June were also revised downward. Additionally, Fed Governor Quarles will resign this week, enabling Trump to appoint a preferred candidate earlier. Possibly due to the above news, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut in September by the Fed on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; rose sharply. Before the nonfarm payroll data, this figure was only 41.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23023</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hainan, China: Building a Leading Hub for Digital Economy Innovation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23022</link>
      <description>August 4th. The Hainan Province of China promulgated the &quot;Three-Year Action Plan to Accelerate the Construction of a Distinctive and Advantageous Modern Industrial System in Hainan Province,&quot; which indicated the goal of establishing a hub for the digital economy. It will stimulate the transformation of the Haikou Rejuvenation City Digital Economy Industry Cluster and the Hainan Eco-Software Park Digital Economy Industry Cluster towards development driven by innovation and application. The plan involves expediting the development of the computing power industry, fostering the growth of the data factor market, promoting the orderly flow of data security, and constructing core competitiveness in digital application scenarios based on blockchain, AI, and big data technology to drive the progress of digital health, digital entertainment, and sharing platforms. It will actively promote the development of industries such as gaming exports, data processing, semiconductor chips, and integrated</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23022</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>