<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 05:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 05:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Renmin Law School to Launch Advanced Seminar on Legal Practices in Handling Crypto Assets in Cases, Stablecoins, and RWA</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24999</link>
      <description>On August 18th, the Law School of Renmin University of China initiated an advanced seminar focusing on the disposal of virtual assets involved in cases, stablecoins, and the frontier legal practices of Real World Asset (RWA). It was stated that in recent years, cryptocurrency, as an emerging asset in the digital age, has attracted extensive attention from the industry and academia. The disposal of cryptocurrencies involved in cases is a crucial issue that encompasses judicial justice, financial regulation, and technological innovation. Stablecoins and virtual currencies based on Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization have also gradually come into being. They have demonstrated significant potential applications in areas such as cross-border payments and decentralized finance (DeFi), bringing new liquidity and investment opportunities.The Law School intends to host the Advanced Seminar on Legal Practices of Disposal of Virtual Assets Involved in Cases, Stablecoins, and RWA at Renmin Unive</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24999</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Spokesperson: GPT-5 still suffers from &quot;hallucination&quot; issues. Users are advised to verify the answers.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24998</link>
      <description>On August 18th, despite the launch of the new GPT-5 model by ChatGPT, the possibility of errors still exists. A senior executive at OpenAI emphasized this again this week. Nick Tully, the head of ChatGPT, pointed out in an interview, &quot;In terms of reliability, there is a significant discontinuity between reliability and absolute reliability.&quot;He further explained, &quot;Unless we can prove that in all aspects, not just some aspects, ChatGPT is more reliable than human experts, we will continue to recommend that you double-check the answers.&quot; (Jinshi)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24998</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Top Ethereum Treasury Companies Still Have Unrealized Gains of Over $1.2 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24997</link>
      <description>On August 18th, according to crypto KOL AB Kuai.Dong, although Ethereum has retraced by approximately 9% from its weekend high, the holdings of two leading Ethereum reserve companies remain in a profit-taking state. Based on the current Ethereum price of $4,331:BMNR, with a cost basis of $3,827, is realizing a 13.8% profit, and the total holding profit is $679 million;SBET, with a cost basis of $3,571, is achieving a 22% profit, and the total holding profit is $571 million.During this week&apos;s workdays, both companies may disclose more Ethereum accumulation data.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24997</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin breaches $117,000, the mainstream CEX total short liquidation volume will reach $5.58 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24996</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin manages to break through $117,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEX will reach 558 million.Conversely, if Bitcoin drops below $113,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEX will reach 690 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not disclose the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of the liquidated contracts. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to neighboring liquidation clusters, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the target price will be influenced when it reaches a particular position. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will experience a more intense reaction due to a liquidity avalanche once it reaches that specific point.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24996</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Whale Bro」 Continues to Long, Long Position Underwater Losses Expand to $7.48 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24995</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on on-chain data, with the continuous downturn in the crypto market, the &quot;Big Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng&apos;s long position is now facing an unrealized loss of 7.48 million US dollars. He is still actively increasing his long positions in various coins. Currently, he holds long positions in: 23,100 ETH, 175 BTC, 110,000 HYPE, and 250 million PUMP. Among them, the Ethereum long position alone is facing a nearly 7 million US dollars unrealized loss.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24995</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During the market pullback, two ETH whales synchronized their short positions, with each holding unrealized losses of over $21 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24993</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as per the monitoring of HyperInsight, during the morning pullback of ETH, two major short-selling whales concurrently adjusted their positions:The whale whose address begins with 0x20c2d9 decreased its ETH short position by $802,400. It currently has an unrealized loss of -$21,035,800 and a liquidation price of $6,074.602.The whale with the address starting with 0x8e0969 reduced its ETH short position by $802,500. Its current unrealized loss is -$1,702,200 and the liquidation price is $7,269.400.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24993</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot Gold Hits $3350 per Ounce, Up 0.44% Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24994</link>
      <description>On August 18th, spot gold surged to $3350 per ounce, with an intraday increase of 0.44%. (Oriental Wealth)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24994</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the last 24 hours, CEX net inflow was 1,079.08 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24992</link>
      <description>On August 18th, according to Coinglass data, during the past 24 hours, the total net inflow of BTC on CEX was 1,079.08 BTC. The top three CEX exchanges in terms of inflow volume are as follows:· Kraken had a net inflow of 1,404.79 BTC;· bitFlyer had a net inflow of 167.87 BTC;· Bithumb had a net inflow of 38.81 BTC.Moreover, Coinbase Pro witnessed a net outflow of 204.48 BTC and ranked first in the outflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH, XRP, and CYBER currently rank in the top three in Upbit&apos;s Korean Won market trading volume leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24991</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on CoinGecko data, in the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit has rebounded to $2.521 billion, showing a 24-hour increase of 76.0%. Among them, the ETH/KRW trading pair accounted for 15.95% of the trading volume and ranked first in the Korean won market. The remaining top five are: XRP, CYBER, STRIKE, BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24991</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Drops Below $4300</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24990</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum fell below $4300, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 3.19%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 03:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24990</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>