<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:44:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Community Announcement: The social protocol Firefly will be releasing its token soon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27958</link>
      <description>On September 6th, based on the disclosures of multiple KOLs, the social protocol Firefly is scheduled to release its token shortly.It is reported that Firefly, a social protocol, is a core project within the Mask Network ecosystem. It is a decentralized social aggregator designed to bridge Web2 and Web3 social networks, enabling users to explore on-chain activities and social interactions through a unified interface. Firefly was developed by Mask Network and launched around 2022. In February 2025, it spun off as an independent project from MaskDAO to further expand its team and innovation scope.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27958</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.P. Morgan Strategist: U.S. Economic Growth is Gradually Slowing, Does Not Believe Fed Rate Cuts Will Fuel Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27957</link>
      <description>On September 6th, David Kelly, the Chief Global Strategist of JPMorgan Asset Management, stated in a recent interview with CNBC that the weak August jobs report and other economic data suggest that the weakening trend of the US economy is intensifying. &quot;Although the current economy is not in a recession, it is gradually slowing down. All data consistently show that this already stumbling economy - like a tortoise always moving slowly forward - is now almost exhausted.&quot;Kelly also believes that given the deterioration of the job market data, the Fed&apos;s expected rate cut will not be able to boost the overall economy. &quot;I see today&apos;s stock market rise, which clearly reflects the market&apos;s expectation of an imminent rate cut. However, this does not solve the fundamental problem. The government needs to realize that if they cut rates now, it will reduce the interest income of retirees while sending more rate cut signals to the market. In that case, borrowers have no reason to borrow more mone</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 07:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27957</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mizuho Bank: The Fed Has Been Realistically &quot;Face-Slapped,&quot; Easing Cycle Set to Begin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27956</link>
      <description>September 6th. Mizuho Bank declared that the U.S. August non-farm payroll report further verified the weakening tendency in the labor market. The growth in employment, working hours, and income has regressed to the levels during the pandemic period. Regardless of inflation, it is almost certain that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates at the September meeting. A 25-basis-point rate cut is almost a certainty. However, if August inflation is weaker than expected, a 50-basis-point cut is more likely. The Fed&apos;s previous inflation forecasts have been &quot;slapped in the face&quot; by reality, while its 2026 unemployment rate forecast is at risk of not being achieved. They were overly pessimistic about inflation before and overly optimistic about the labor market. It is expected that the Fed will initiate a round of sustained easing cycle, aiming to lower interest rates to its perceived &quot;neutral level&quot; by March 2026, which is around 3%. The new Fed chair is likely to further increase stimulus</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27956</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This week, the US Bitcoin spot ETF saw a net inflow of $250 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27955</link>
      <description>On September 6th, according to data from Farside Investors, the net inflow of the U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF this week was $250 million. It includes:BlackRock IBIT: +$4.343 billionFidelity FBTC: +$25.1 millionBitwise BITB: -$76.9 millionARK ARKB: -$81.5 millionBTCO: +$2.2 millionFranklin EZBC: -$3.2 millionVanEck HODL: -$13.2 millionGrayscale GBTC: -$69.7 millionGrayscale BTCM: +$33.2 million</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 06:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27955</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Kwon&apos;s Appeal for the Return of $19.4 Million SGD Mansion Deposit Rejected by Singapore Court</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27954</link>
      <description>On September 6th, according to the report in The Straits Times, Do Kwon, the co-founder of the now-defunct blockchain company Terraform Labs, had his request to recover about 50% of the purchase price of a penthouse on Orchard Road rejected by the High Court of Singapore.Five months prior to the collapse of his cryptocurrency TerraUSD and Luna in 2022, Do Kwon had his eyes set on the $38.8 million Sculptura Ardmore apartment. High Court documents reviewed by The Straits Times show that he had selected a 7,600 square feet (approximately 706 square meters) duplex four-bedroom penthouse on the 19th floor of the apartment, which was one of only three penthouses in the development.Do Kwon had paid around $19.4 million (about 50% of the total purchase price) through an option fee and subsequent payments. However, the deal fell through, and the property was subsequently resold to another party for $34.5 million.It is reported that Sculptura Ardmore was launched by develope</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 06:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27954</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink Gaming plans to stake part of its ETH on the Linea mainnet</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27953</link>
      <description>On September 6th, as per Cointelegraph, SharpLink Gaming (SBET) intends to pledge a certain amount of its $3.6 billion Ethereum Treasury funds on the Linea network subsequent to the mainnet&apos;s launch on September 10th.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 06:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27953</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with an Alpha score of at least 224 can participate in the STAR exclusive TGE event</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27952</link>
      <description>On September 6th, Binance officially announced on social media that users whose Alpha score is greater than or equal to 224 can participate in this Starpower (STAR) exclusive TGE event through the Alpha event page. Participating in this event will consume 15 points.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 05:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong SAR Government Prepares for Third Sovereign Green Bond Issuance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27951</link>
      <description>On September 6th, according to Bloomberg, it is reported that the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region Government has appointed banks to make preparations for a potential digital bond issuance. If this issuance goes ahead, it will be the third digital bond issuance by the Hong Kong government. In 2023, the SAR government successfully issued an HK$800 million tokenized green bond under the Government Green Bond Program, which was among the first government-issued tokenized green bonds in the world. Subsequently, in 2024, it issued the world&apos;s first multi-currency digital green bonds, raising approximately HK$6 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 05:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27951</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Platform Trading Volume Rebounds, with ETH, XRP, and RED Ranking Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27950</link>
      <description>On September 6th, based on CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, Upbit&apos;s trading volume witnessed a significant surge to $20.95 billion, with an increase of 30.8%. Specifically, the ETH/KRW trading pair accounted for 17.12% of the volume and ranked first in the Korean won market. The other top five trading pairs were XRP, RED, BTC, and USDT.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 05:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27950</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDS&apos; market capitalization briefly surpassed $120 million, with a 24-hour price increase of 24.2%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27949</link>
      <description>On September 6th, according to GMGN market data, the entity card trading platform Collector Crypt within the Solana ecosystem briefly exceeded a market capitalization of $1.2 billion. Currently, it is reported at $1.04 billion, with a token price of $0.2559 and a 24-hour percentage increase of 24.2%. The fully diluted value (FDV) is currently reported at $5.14 billion, and the 24-hour total network trading volume is $39.98 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 03:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27949</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>