<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: Venture Capitalists are Fueling a New Wave of Cryptomania Sweeping Through College Campuses</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22830</link>
      <description>August 1st. According to Bloomberg, as the reputation of cryptocurrency in the U.S. public opinion arena gradually begins to cautiously recover, a wave of enthusiasm for venture capital-backed blockchain is quietly emerging on university campuses.A group of investors focusing on digital assets - including institutions such as Collab+Currency, Consensys Mesh, Artemis, and Hydra Ventures - have collectively raised approximately 600 ETH. This funding, through an initiative called Dorm DAO, is flowing to student-led blockchain clubs from Michigan to Oregon and other places.The project combines funding, research budgets, and internship opportunities, reflecting the cryptocurrency industry&apos;s realignment of its goals. Once regarded as a &quot;get-rich-quick scheme&quot; and not taken seriously by the mainstream, the field is now moving closer to &quot;traditional finance&quot; - with regulatory-compliant investment products and the cautious return of Wall Street playing a driving role. However, supporters ar</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22830</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Strong Internal Dissent within the Federal Reserve Board, Will Only Escalate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22829</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Trump said that there is a strong internal disagreement within the Federal Reserve Board, and this situation will only intensify. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22829</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian publicly traded company Belgravia Hartford increases its Bitcoin holdings to 42.38 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22828</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on the monitoring of @btcNLNico, the Canadian listed company Belgravia Hartford announced that it had increased its holdings by 42.38 bitcoins, raising its total bitcoin holdings to 83.15 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22828</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Bowman: Gradual Interest Rate Cuts Are Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22827</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Federal Reserve Board Governors Waller and Bowman issued a statement presenting distinct viewpoints.Federal Reserve Board Governor Waller indicated that the Federal Reserve ought to adjust interest rates to a level closer to the neutral range.Federal Reserve Board Governor Bowman asserted that given the slowdown in growth, a gradual reduction in interest rates is appropriate. The upward risks to price stability have subsided. (Oriental Fortune Network)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22827</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI has raised $8.3 billion, valuing the company at $300 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22826</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as reported by The New York Times, OpenAI has secured $8.3 billion in funding and has a valuation of $300 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22826</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FCA Relaxes Retail Exposure Limit for Crypto ETN Products, But Derivatives Ban Remains</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22825</link>
      <description>August 1st. As per official channels, the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) declared today that retail investors are granted the permission to trade crypto ETN products on approved UK-based Recognised Investment Exchange (RIE) platforms. This is subject to compliance with financial promotion rules to ensure the transparency of information and prevent inappropriate incentives.Although trading channels have been opened, such products still do not enjoy the protection of the UK Financial Services Compensation Scheme (FSCS). Additionally, relevant companies must abide by the Consumer Duty.The FCA&apos;s retail ban on crypto derivatives still holds true, and it will continuously monitor the market dynamics of high-risk investment products to facilitate the development of an overall regulatory framework for crypto assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22825</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: On the first day of the official implementation of the &quot;Hong Kong Stablecoin Proposal,&quot; stablecoin concept stocks experienced a widespread afternoon decline, with Brighten Securiti...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22824</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the &quot;Stablecoin Regulation Draft&quot; in Hong Kong officially came into effect. This indicates the formal establishment of a licensing regulatory mechanism for stablecoin issuers in Hong Kong. The purpose of this move is to provide a clearer legal framework for the virtual asset ecosystem, prevent systemic financial risks, and promote the development of Hong Kong as a global virtual asset center.According to BiyaPay analysts, due to the implementation of this policy, the stablecoin concept stocks in the Hong Kong stock market saw a collective decline in the afternoon. Among them, Bright Smart Securities &amp; Commodities Group (01428) fell by more than 20%, WeLab Holdings (00376) dropped by nearly 16%, LianLian Digital Finance (02598) fell by more than 9%, Goldstream Investment (01328), Sino Prosper (02562), and Guotai Junan International (01788) all fell by more than 8%. The market is generally concerned that the licensing process may be slower than expected, which may bring</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chainlink Introduces State Pricing Mechanism, Optimizing Price Accuracy for Long-Tail Assets and DEX Trading Pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22823</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per official channels, Chainlink announced the commencement of Chainlink State Pricing—a novel pricing approach tailored for tokenized assets traded on long-tail cryptocurrencies and decentralized exchanges (DEX). This approach is designed to offer enhanced price precision, market robustness, and liquidity evaluation for assets with restricted trading volume on centralized exchanges (CEX) but substantial on-chain liquidity.Presently, Chainlink State Pricing has been launched on the mainnet, and users can obtain push oracle data through Chainlink Data Feeds or access pull data services via Chainlink Data Streams. The initially supported assets by this pricing mechanism encompass wstETH, GHO, LBTC, cbBTC, ezETH, tBTC, and so on. There are future plans to continuously expand the coverage to a greater number of assets, blockchains, and DEXs in accordance with user requirements.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22823</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana On-chain July Launchpad Revenue Rankings Revealed: Letsbonk Claims Top Spot for the First Time</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22822</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on the data dashboard of Blockworks, in July, Solana&apos;s on-chain Launchpad revenue (including revenue from the Launchpad platform and Bonding Curve infrastructure service providers) ranked Letsbonk first with $37.38 million, followed by pump.fun in second place with $15.38 million, and Raydium in third place with $9.48 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22822</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: Checked into Astronaut Village, Starting Space Camp</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22821</link>
      <description>Update: On August 1st, the founder of the Tron Foundation, Justin Sun, posted on the X Platform, saying, &quot;I have checked into the astronaut village and begun space training.&quot;Earlier, there were reports suggesting that Justin Sun would take a space flight on the Blue Origin spacecraft on August 3rd.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22821</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>