<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:25:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Official Mester Skeptical of September Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27559</link>
      <description>September 3rd. Mester from the Federal Reserve stated that the Federal Reserve has recently maintained its high interest rate stance, which is in line with the recent high inflation and the strong performance of the labor market. She expressed doubts about a rate cut by the Fed at the September meeting.After Federal Reserve Chairman Powell opened the door to a rate cut in a speech last month, a rate cut is now regarded as the default option of the Fed. Mester acknowledged the slowdown in employment growth, but she stated that the labor market still appears solid due to the moderate unemployment rate and the low initial number of jobless claims.On the other hand, she believes that there is still a considerable amount of uncertainty about inflation, especially considering the pressure from tariffs. Nevertheless, traders still widely expect that a majority of Fed members will support a 25-basis-point rate cut in September, with a probability of 90%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27559</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaTON Capital has announced a funding round to acquire $100 million worth of TON tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27558</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, AlphaTON Capital Corp. (&quot;AlphaTON Capital&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;, previously known as Portage Biotech Inc.) (NASDAQ: PRTG, ATON) announced a financing round today. The purpose of this round is to acquire approximately $100 million worth of TON tokens and establish a dedicated digital asset financial company. This company is dedicated to building a strategic TON reserve.AlphaTON Capital is implementing a financial strategy that focuses on acquiring TON, managing network infrastructure, and incubating leading applications within the Telegram ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaoTian International plans to reallocate the remaining 3.575 billion Hong Kong dollars of the placement funds to Ethereum, with the expectation to fully utilize it within one month.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27557</link>
      <description>September 3rd - The Hong Kong-listed company Haotian International issued an announcement. Previously, through a special authorization, it carried out a placement of new shares, raising a net amount of approximately 492.5 million Hong Kong dollars. The original plan was as follows:72.66% for the development of an Internet data center on Malaysian land.15.68% for general working capital.11.66% for loan repayment.Usage of Funds: As of the announcement date, approximately 135 million Hong Kong dollars had been used for operations and loan repayment. The remaining 357.5 million Hong Kong dollars, which were originally planned for the development of the Internet data center, had not been used yet. The board of directors decided: On September 3, 2025, it was decided to change the purpose of the remaining funds to the purchase of the cryptocurrency Ethereum, with the expectation of fully utilizing them within one month.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArbitrumDAO has approved a total of 80 million ARB tokens for an incentive program to drive DeFi growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27555</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, ArbitrumDAO made an announcement regarding the first season of its $40 million DeFi Revival Incentive Program (DRIP). This program allocates up to 24 million ARB with the aim of accelerating the growth of decentralized finance on the Arbitrum network.The first season of DRIP focuses on a leverage loop strategy involving yield-bearing ETH and stablecoins. Incentives will be directed towards leading lending protocols such as Aave, Morpho, Fluid, Euler, Dolomite, and Silo. Users can obtain ARB rewards by borrowing selected ETH and stablecoin collateral, including weETH, wstETH, sUSDC, and syrupUSDC.The first season of DRIP emphasizes a leverage loop strategy for yield-bearing ETH and stablecoins and channels the incentive mechanism towards leading lending protocols. Users will receive ARB rewards through borrowing selected ETH and stablecoin collateral. DRIP is divided into four seasons, with a total budget of 80 million ARB tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27555</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot Gold Surges Above $3550 per Ounce, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27556</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, spot gold exceeded $3550/oz for the first time. It has seen a cumulative increase of more than $925 so far this year. (Oriental Wealth)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pineapple Financial to Launch $100 Million INJ Treasury, with Participation from FalconX, Abraxas, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27554</link>
      <description>September 3rd. The FinTech platform Pineapple Financial ($PAPL) has initiated a $1 billion digital asset treasury specifically aimed at amassing INJ. In the forthcoming weeks and months, this fund will be utilized to construct the world&apos;s largest public INJ treasury through open trading. This action will not only grant traditional financial institutions the ability to access INJ via the stock market but also enable Injective to introduce a series of unrivaled tokenized assets onto its blockchain, thereby unlocking a genuine trillion-dollar market potential. The transaction has attracted top investors from both traditional finance and the crypto realm, such as FalconX, Monarq, Abraxas, Blockchain, Canary Capital, Kraken, the Injective Foundation, and numerous other institutions.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27554</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lee: Bitmine&apos;s Cryptocurrency Reserve Velocity Far Exceeds Strategy, Currently Holding Approximately $8.98 Billion in ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27553</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Tom Lee, the chairman of BitMine, stated that &quot;BitMine ($BMNR) is the second-largest cryptocurrency reserve company in the world, holding approximately $8.98 billion worth of Ethereum. It is only second to MicroStrategy (MSTR).&quot;Moreover, BitMine achieved this scale in just a few months, while it took MicroStrategy more than 1200 days to reach the same.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27553</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor: We may see multiple interest rate cuts, depending on the data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27552</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Federal Reserve Governor Waller expressed that he thinks a rate cut should be implemented at the upcoming meeting. The yield on the U.S. 10-year Treasury bond has remained at a relatively stable level.We may witness multiple rate cuts, and whether they take place at each meeting or every other meeting will be contingent on how the data progresses. There is no need to adhere to a prearranged sequence of rate cuts.There is a hope to prevent a decline in the labor market. &quot;We are aware that there will be a slight increase in inflation at a certain point, but it will not be persistent and will be closer to the 2% target within six months.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Powell has made this week&apos;s non-farm payroll data especially important; if the labor market data falls short of expectations, it will significantly increase rate cut expectations.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27551</link>
      <description>September 3rd: Antje Praefcke, a foreign exchange analyst at Deutsche Bank, pointed out that during his speech at the Jackson Hole symposium, Powell emphasized the downside risks faced by the economy and employment. This is in order to balance the market&apos;s and the expectations of colleagues on the Federal Open Market Committee regarding interest rate cuts with the inflation risks that tariffs may bring. The focus on current labor market data has exceeded the usual level by a wide margin, and the weight of the impact of this data will also increase significantly.This naturally implies that if the labor market data fails to meet expectations, it may further significantly enhance the market&apos;s expectations of a Fed rate cut and may even rekindle expectations of one or more 50-basis-point rate cuts.If this situation occurs, it is expected that the US dollar will once again encounter a severe setback. If tomorrow&apos;s ADP data is lower than expected (the market consensus is 80,000 people),</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump family&apos;s closely affiliated Bitcoin mining company, American Bitcoin, is set to debut on the Nasdaq with the stock symbol ABTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27550</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as reported by WSJ, American Bitcoin, a Bitcoin mining and reserve company supported by two of President Trump&apos;s sons, is scheduled to be listed on the Nasdaq Stock Exchange this Wednesday after completing a merger with Gryphon Digital Mining.After the merger, Trump&apos;s elder son, Donald Trump Jr., his second son, Eric Trump, and the mining company Hut 8 will jointly own 98% of the shares of the new entity. The new entity will retain the name American Bitcoin and trade under the stock symbol ABTC.American Bitcoin has also recently been seeking acquisition targets in Asia to build a Bitcoin asset reserve. The company has started discussions with investors regarding potential acquisitions and is currently planning to acquire a publicly listed company in Japan. At the same time, it is also considering expanding into the Hong Kong market. Sources familiar with the matter stated that the company intends to replicate the MicroStrategy model by establishing a cryptocurrenc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>