<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetix Founder Releases sUSD Deprovisioning Update: Mainnet Preload Event Will Ultimately Reanchor it</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23847</link>
      <description>On August 9th, Kain, the founder of Synthetix, released the latest update regarding the sUSD de-pegging issue. The current price of sUSD is $0.990619 and is about to re-anchor. Although it has been a difficult period, with the launch of the mainnet pre-staking activities, sUSD will ultimately return to normal.Previously, on April 18th, the Synthetix stablecoin sUSD experienced a further deterioration of its de-pegging issue to $0.7. Synthetix then announced an emergency solution, where the USD 420 Pool would be launched with incentives. SNX stakers in the 420 Pool could deposit sUSD to receive a share of the 5 million SNX rewards over a period of 12 months. The deposited sUSD will be locked for one year and can be fully withdrawn after the event ends. Synthetix founder Kain commented on this emergency solution, stating, &quot;This is one of the worst instant solutions ever used to generate demand for sUSD from the user base.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23847</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades will take profit in multiple steps on the BTC and ETH long positions, aiming for a total profit of approximately $11.4 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23845</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to the monitoring of EmberCN, whale contract trader AguilaTrades. After going through several situations where floating profits turned into losses, it learned a costly lesson and began to take profits. Currently, AguilaTrades is closing positions on Hyperliquid. It has made a profit of approximately $11.4 million from going long on BTC and ETH.AguilaTrades opened long positions on BTC and ETH the day before yesterday. Two hours later, due to Trump&apos;s executive order signing, the cryptocurrency market surged. AguilaTrades took profits and rolled over the positions when the market was in profit. Yesterday, it added to the position to a notional value of $250 million. After ETH&apos;s sharp rise today, AguilaTrades started to take profits and close positions.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insight: Stablecoin Issuers are Digesting US Treasuries, with Tether Holding Over $100 Billion in US Treasury Bonds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23846</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to the report in Fortune, stablecoin issuers like Circle and Tether are purchasing a greater amount of U.S. Treasuries than most countries, which has the potential to reshape the U.S. economy. Tether disclosed the latest data indicating holdings of more than $100 billion in U.S. Treasury bonds, exceeding countries such as the UAE and Germany. Cryptocurrency proponents think that stablecoins will contribute to consolidating the U.S. dollar&apos;s dominant position globally. However, critics caution that even if stablecoins only make up a small portion of the overall market, it could still give rise to banking and financial instability, potentially draining funds from bank deposits and reducing bank liquidity.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23846</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes ironically jokes about his &quot;buy low, sell high ETH&quot; strategy: vows never to profit again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23844</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the co-founder of BitMEX, Arthur Hayes, posted a self-mocking message about &quot;selling low and buying high ETH&quot; and said, &quot;I must buy it all back. Can you forgive me @Thomas Lee? I swear I will never take profits again.&quot;A week ago, Arthur Hayes sold 2,373 ETH when the price was approximately $3,507. And he bought back ETH at a higher price four hours ago.Thomas Lee, the chairman of BitMine (BMNR), which is Ethereum&apos;s largest institutional holder, has been actively promoting ETH in the crypto community recently. His statements are as follows: &quot;Ethereum is currently at a crucial moment similar to Bitcoin in 2017. Some people will regret not betting on it at this time. As Wall Street&apos;s attention to cryptocurrency gradually increases, Ethereum is becoming the core platform in the financial market&apos;s &apos;tokenization&apos; process. This is one of the biggest macro trading events in the next decade. Based on the ETH/BTC exchange rate during the 2021 peak, ETH could rise to $16,000.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23844</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Token GEN Market Cap Surpasses $45 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate 35%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23843</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on GMGN data, the ecological AI concept token GEN of Solana briefly surged to $0.045. It currently has a market value of $45 million and a 24-hour increase of 35%.It is reported that GEN is the native token of the General Impressions (GI) project. GI is building the core infrastructure of the Agentic AI era. It is a Rust-driven intelligent agent network that provides underlying support for the trusted execution of autonomous AI, low-cost reusability, and multi-agent collaboration. As a key driver of the emergence of the Agentic Paradigm, GI is gradually becoming a key algorithm protocol for decentralized intelligent systems.BlockBeats reminds users that token prices are highly volatile, so investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 5000 ETH into Binance after hibernating for five years, bringing its total Ethereum earnings to $45.38 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23842</link>
      <description>On September 8th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale that had been inactive for five years deposited 5,000 ETH ($21.14 million) into Binance. The total profit it has now made on ETH amounts to $45.38 million.This whale had accumulated 55,001 ETH seven years ago, which was valued at $6.73 million at that time. It still holds 5,001 ETH with a value of $21.07 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23842</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale/Institutional Address Once Again Increases Its Holdings, Adding $34 Million Worth of ETH at an Average Price of $4,193</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23839</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, a Whale/Institutional address once again increased its holdings 1 hour ago by purchasing 34 million USD worth of ETH. Now it holds a total of 8,109 coins with an average purchase price of 4,193 USD.This Whale/Institutional address has spent a total of 84 million USD in the past 20 days to acquire 21,571 ETH, with an average purchase price of 3,894 USD. Currently, it has an unrealized gain of 7.12 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23839</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Token Ecosystem Experiences Overall Price Increase, CLANKER Surges Above $60</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23841</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to HTX market data, the Base ecosystem tokens witnessed a general upward trend. These include:The price of CLANKER experienced a short-term spike and broke through $60, with a 24-hour increase of 24.8% and a current value of $60 million.ZORA saw a 4.66% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $8.88 billion, approaching its all-time high.TOSHI had a 13.39% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $3 billion.KTA saw an 11.51% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $1.4 billion.DRB had a 5.3% increase in 24 hours, with a current market capitalization of $23 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23841</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes &quot;Sells Low, Buys High&quot; ETH, Chases Price Up to Reacquire $10.5M Position</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23840</link>
      <description>September 8th. As per the monitoring by LookOnChain, Arthur Hayes, the co-founder of BitMEX, sold 2,373 ETH a week ago when the price of ETH was approximately $3,507, amounting to $8.32 million.4 hours ago, he once more withdrew 10.5 million USDC to repurchase ETH at a higher price.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X.me has announced that its withdrawal feature will be officially launched in late September.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23838</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the Web2 and Web3 dual-engine AI social media platform X.me announced today that it will officially launch the &quot;Withdrawal&quot; function in late September.X.me stated that it is fully aware of users&apos; close attention to token value and asset security. Recently, X.me has been committed to a major upgrade of the platform&apos;s security protection system. By means of intelligent interception of abnormal operations + facial recognition to verify the user&apos;s identity + defense against bulk fake accounts and other cutting-edge technical iterations, X.me will safeguard users&apos; &quot;Withdrawal&quot; security from multiple dimensions.The &quot;Withdrawal function&quot; is currently in its final testing phase, and users will soon be able to withdraw XME tokens and Dogecoin.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23838</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>