<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:49:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard&apos;s European Head of Crypto: Actively Monitoring Crypto Assets, But Will Not Stray from Established Path</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27306</link>
      <description>September 2nd. Christian Rau, who is the Head of Cryptocurrency at Mastercard Europe, recently expressed in an interview that Mastercard is closely observing cryptocurrency while it will not veer away from its set direction.&quot;Our strategy has remained unchanged for 50 years: to empower people to make payments safely and in compliance, and to enable businesses to receive payments. Cryptocurrency is within this logical framework. We are not aiming to completely overhaul this system but to enhance it. We give priority to interoperability with existing solutions. Nevertheless, if no solution meets our requirements, we may consider developing our own.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27306</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK 30-Year Gilt Yield Hits Highest Level Since 1998</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27305</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the yield on UK 30-year government bonds reached a 27-year high on Tuesday. This was due to market concerns regarding governments&apos; large-scale borrowing and U.S. President Trump&apos;s attempt to dismiss Federal Reserve Board members, which led to a rise in global government borrowing costs. According to London Stock Exchange data, the 30-year UK government bond yield hit a high of 5.680%, increasing by about 4 basis points during the day and reaching the highest level since May 1998. The yield on 30-year German government bonds also rose to a 14-year high following the increase in U.S. Treasury yields.The borrowing cost for the UK&apos;s 30-year bonds is the highest among the G7 countries. This reflects concerns about the country&apos;s inflation rate, high borrowing levels, and slow economic growth. UK Chancellor of the Exchequer Rishi Sunak is expected to raise taxes in the autumn budget to continue meeting his fiscal goals, which could further complicate the challenge of accel</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27305</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four.Meme made a strategic investment in Creditlink, integrating the token health report and user credit score generated by the latter into the platform.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27304</link>
      <description>September 2nd. Four.Meme declared a strategic investment in Creditlink. Creditlink is a blockchain-based credit rating platform that has blazed a trail in establishing a transparent and data-driven trust system.In this collaborative effort, Four.Meme will incorporate token health reports and user credit scores into the platform&apos;s assessment metrics, infusing more transparency, scientific governance, and sustainable development into the meme ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump retweeted and commented on WLFI&apos;s first day of trading performance: &quot;This is just the beginning.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27303</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, Eric Trump retweeted the performance of WLFI&apos;s first day of trading and made a comment, &quot;This is merely the outset.&quot;As of the time of this writing, WLFI is reporting $0.2427. The total network trading volume has exceeded $2.8 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27303</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese cryptocurrency exchange platform Coincheck has acquired the French regulated digital asset broker Aplo.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27302</link>
      <description>September 2nd: The Japanese cryptocurrency exchange Coincheck declared the acquisition of the digital asset broker Aplo, which is regulated by France&apos;s AMF. It is anticipated that the transaction will be completed in October 2025, and all the shares of Aplo will be converted into the newly issued common stock of Coincheck.Coincheck stated that this action is aimed at supporting its expansion into the European market. (CoinDesk)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27302</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant Analyst: BTC Has Retraced Around 12% from Its New High, Which Is Completely Normal and Has Not Yet Exceeded the Historical Average Correction of 20% to 25%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27301</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, CryptoQuant analyst Darkfost stated that Bitcoin has retraced by approximately -12% since its previous all-time high, and this is within a normal range. During the current bull market cycle, the largest retracement since hitting an all-time high for the first time in March 2024 was -28%, with the average retracement ranging from -20% to -25%.The analysis indicates that this retracement has not deviated from historical patterns and is likely to continue to remain within a healthy range. Such retracements usually help to clear excessive leverage in the derivatives market during a bull market, alleviate overheated sentiment, and provide new entry opportunities for long-term investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27301</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Leaderboard Update: Whale AndreIsBack Joins WLFI Genesis Sale, Contributing 170 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27299</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the Ethena Leaderboard Whale AndreIsBack, who invested 170 ETH (approximately $580,000) eight months ago and received 38.71 million WLFI tokens at a cost of $0.015 per token. Yesterday, he received 7.74 million unlocked tokens that have not been sold yet (approximately $1.85 million). However, he is currently sitting on a $585,000 unrealized gain from his 3x short hedge position on Hyperliquid.This whale is extremely enthusiastic about participating in DeFi projects. The address 0x9cb...c06ce holds over $41.69 million in assets and has participated in a total of 21 DeFi projects. Currently, it is leading the Ethena Season3 Leaderboard with an astonishing 1.28 trillion points, accounting for 3.57% of the total reward pool.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27299</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT has disclosed the fee structure and wallet address for over 200 crypto Key Opinion Leaders (KOLs), with most KOLs not clearly stating the promotional nature of their tweets.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27300</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, ZachXBT disclosed the charging standards and wallet addresses of more than 200 crypto KOLs on the X platform yesterday. ZachXBT stated that among the more than 160 paid promoters, fewer than 5 clearly marked their posts as advertisements.ZachXBT believes that in many jurisdictions, failing to disclose the promotional nature of information may even be illegal. &quot;I have said many times that if you disclose paid promotion information for a project that you truly believe in, then paid promotion is acceptable. If you think that influential people should be allowed to secretly accept money to promote projects and mislead fans, then this indicates many problems.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27300</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Union (U) on September 4th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27298</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per an official announcement, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list Union (U) on September 4th. Eligible users can access the Alpha event page once the Alpha trading commences and claim the airdrop by using Alpha Points. Additional details will be provided separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27298</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fujian-based Group in China Organized a Pyramid Scheme in the Name of Virtual Currency and NFTs; Court of Second Instance Rejects Their Appeal</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27297</link>
      <description>September 2nd, 2023. From May to August 2023, Li and others, under the guise of issuing a certain cryptocurrency, established a hierarchical reward mechanism based on invitation relationships. They formed groups through social platforms, carried out online and offline promotions, and publicly promoted to the general public. They enticed participants to qualify for membership through activities such as purchasing cryptocurrency, staking assets, and auctioning NFTs, and received rebates based on developing a downline. By the time of the October 2023 incident, the organization had developed multiple levels and had raised funds equivalent to more than 20 million RMB.The Shishi City Procuratorate of Fujian Province determined through its review that although this organization used new concepts such as cryptocurrency and NFTs for packaging, its operating model still met the criteria of the crime of organizing and leading MLM activities as stipulated in the Criminal Law of the People&apos;s Repu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27297</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>