<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:57:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins CEO: The brand will collaborate with a Fortune Global 100 company, and will also announce six major partnership deals this year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24503</link>
      <description>On August 14th, Luca Netz, the CEO of Pudgy Penguins, stated in an interview with Odaily BlockBeats that the &quot;next partner of Pudgy Penguin is a top 100 global company, which is extremely explosive. You definitely can&apos;t guess, but I can guarantee that this will definitely be explosive news.&quot; Additionally, within the remaining time of this year, Pudgy Penguins is likely to announce six heavyweight collaborations.Furthermore, regarding the timing of Abstract Chain&apos;s coin issuance, Luca Netz said, &quot;When Abstract is officially launched, everyone should be able to clearly sense that this is a Top 4 public chain in the crypto space. If we can&apos;t achieve that, there is no need to issue coins. For us, the token must be able to create a wealth effect and take us to a new level instead of issuing just for the sake of issuing.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethereum Whale Who Shorted 20x Liquidates Shorts to Avoid Liquidation, Currently Facing $18 Million in Unrealized Losses</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24502</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a 20x short Ethereum whale this morning managed to avoid liquidation by reducing its short position. As of the time of this writing, its short position reached 10,000 ETH, and the liquidation price was $5680.It is reported that this whale has already incurred a loss of $9.88 million in this ETH (20x) short position and still has approximately $18 million in unrealized losses.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit operator partners with Vietnam&apos;s MB Bank to build the country&apos;s first cryptocurrency exchange platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24501</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to The Korea Herald, on August 13th in Seoul, South Korea&apos;s largest cryptocurrency exchange platform operator Dunamu and the Vietnam Military Commercial Joint Stock Bank (MB Bank) signed a Memorandum of Understanding. This is to collaborate on establishing Vietnam&apos;s first local digital asset exchange.Based on the agreement, Dunamu will serve as MB Bank&apos;s key strategic partner, providing technological and infrastructure support. It will also offer advice on regulatory compliance, investor protection, and talent development. This move comes after a significant development in Vietnam following the country&apos;s passage of the &quot;Digital Technology Industry Law&quot; in July this year.Data indicates that Vietnam currently has more than 20 million digital asset holders, with a trading volume exceeding $800 billion, making it the fifth-largest recipient of blockchain asset inflows globally. As one of Vietnam&apos;s top five banks, MB Bank has 33 million users and total asse</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two new addresses withdrew a total of 8.67 million US dollars worth of PEPE from Coinbase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24500</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), two new addresses have withdrawn 7.107 trillion tokens from Coinbase within the past 6 hours. The total amount withdrawn is $8.67 million, and the average withdrawal price per token is $0.0000122.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24500</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play-to-Earn Game Shrapnel Completes Two Rounds of Funding Totaling $19.5 Million, Led by Gala Games</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24499</link>
      <description>On August 14th, the blockchain game Shrapnel made an announcement that it has secured a total of $19.5 million in investment across two funding rounds. The most recent funding round was spearheaded by Gala Games, with the participation of Griffin Gaming Partners, Polychain Capital, and other entities. The funds raised will be allocated for game development and to facilitate Shrapnel&apos;s global launch and its entry into the Chinese market.It is reported that the game is scheduled to commence closed beta testing later in 2025 and open testing in early 2026. The developer of Shrapnel, Neon Machine, incurred a net loss of $11.4 million in 2024.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24499</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today Ethereum Layer 2 Tokens Surge, ARB and ZK Up Over 16%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24498</link>
      <description>On August 14th, according to HTX market information, today Ethereum Layer 2 tokens witnessed a general rise. These include:ARB increased by 16.8% and is now priced at $0.552;ZK rose by 16.9% and is now priced at $0.069;MNT surged by 9.1% and is now priced at $1.12;OP went up by 9% and is now priced at $0.8472.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24498</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Fear and Greed Index Rises to 75, Market Continues to Show &quot;Greed&quot; Sentiment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24497</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on alternative data, today&apos;s Crypto Fear and Greed Index stands at 75 (yesterday it was 73), with a weekly average of 62, suggesting a continuous &quot;greed&quot; sentiment in the market.Note: The Fear &amp; Greed Index ranges from 0 to 100 and encompasses the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Hype (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance (10%) + Google Trends (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24497</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rate indicates that the market sentiment is still not in the overheated zone.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24496</link>
      <description>On August 14th, according to Coinglass data, the current mainstream CEX and DEX funding rates suggest that the market sentiment has not entered the overheated zone. The perpetual contract funding rate of mainstream cryptocurrency assets on CEX remains only at a neutral funding rate (0.01%).BlockBeats Note: The funding rate is a fee set by cryptocurrency trading platforms to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price, typically applied to perpetual contracts. It is a mechanism for the exchange of funds between long and short traders, and the trading platform does not charge this fee. It is used to adjust the cost or profit of traders holding contracts to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the funding rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the funding rate is above 0.01%, it indicates a generally bullish market. When the funding rate is below 0.005%, it indicates a generally bearish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades placed 6 trades in 8 hours with a 0% win rate, resulting in a loss of $1.846 million, and has now opened a 25x long position in ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24494</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the contract trading whale AguilaTrades carried out 6 trades in the early morning, encompassing both long and short positions for BTC and ETH. Having a 0% winning rate, they suffered a loss of $1.846 million. Currently, they have established a 25x long position on ETH, holding 21,050 ETH (approximately $99.93 million) with an entry price of $4,750.06.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 01:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24494</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiant Capital Hackers Double Stolen Funds in 10 Months, Sell 9631 ETH in Past 2 Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24495</link>
      <description>August 14th. Based on on-chain data analyst Embermonitoring, in the past 1 hour, the Radiant Capital hacker sold 4,326 ETH and exchanged it for 20.475 million DAI.Since the day before yesterday when the selling of ETH began, the hacker has sold a total of 9,631 ETH and exchanged it for 43.937 million DAI. The average selling price is $4,562.Currently, the hacker holds 12,326 ETH and 43.937 million DAI, with a total value of $102 million. The value of the assets stolen by the hacker when they stole from Radiant Capital in October last year was $53 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 01:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24495</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>