<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Aave Protocol Surpasses $60 Billion in Total Deposits, Reaching All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23498</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to an official statement, the total value locked in the decentralized lending protocol Aave has reached $60 billion, setting a new all-time high for the protocol.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23498</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest Federal Reserve report explores using gold reserve valuation gains to fund a Bitcoin strategic reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23499</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per Cointelegraph, a recent report from the Federal Reserve delved into the possibility of using the valuation increments from gold reserves to finance the United States&apos; strategic Bitcoin reserve.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23499</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Exchange Daily Trading Volume Drops by Over 10%: PROVE, XRP, ETH Currently Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23497</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to CoinGecko data, within the past 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit decreased to 1.625 billion USD, experiencing a single-day decline of more than 10%. Among them, the new coin pair PROVE/KRW took the lead with a trading volume of 18.1%, and the remaining top five were: XRP, ETH, BTC, ENA.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23497</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumulative Profit $9.4M Smart Money Bitcoin Long Position Leveraged 40x, Average Entry Price $114,567</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23496</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on on-chain information, a whale added more than 40 times long leverage on Bitcoin just 10 minutes ago. Currently, it is holding a position size of 250 BTC with a position value of approximately $28.62 million and an entry price of $114,567.This address has accumulated a profit of $9.4 million on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 03:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past two days, the BlackRock Ethereum ETF has experienced a daily trading volume peak followed by a decrease of over 50%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23495</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to Trader T data, the daily trading volume of the Bitwise Ethereum Spot ETF (ETHA) yesterday dropped to 600 million U.S. dollars, which is a decrease of more than 50% from the previous week&apos;s high of 1.4 billion U.S. dollars. Correspondingly, the net inflow of ETHA in the past two days has also shown a declining trend along with the trading volume.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23495</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin TROLL Prototype Author: No intention to participate in any meme coin based on their work, nor will take any legal action</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23494</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per the report by Decrypt, Carlos Ramirez (also known as Whynne, the creator of Trollface) stated in his first interview in a decade that he &quot;unintentionally&quot; got entangled in the surging Solana meme coin based on his creation. This was because the capitalist nature of cryptocurrency would interfere with artistic expression.Whynne mentioned that he &quot;constantly&quot; receives tokens related to the Trollface meme coin. He has no intention of participating and will not take legal action against the rising Troll meme coin. In the past two weeks, the market value of the meme coin TROLL has surged by more than 1050%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23494</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scam Sniffer: Top-Ranked &quot;DappRadar&quot; Phishing Site in Bing Search</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23493</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Scam Sniffer tweeted to give a reminder that a phishing website for &quot;DappRadar&quot; is ranking at the top on the Bing search engine. Users are advised to verify the URL.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23493</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC Commissioner: New Liquidity Pledge Statement May Not Reflect Actual Circumstances</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23492</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Caroline Crenshaw, a commissioner of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), published a statement on the SEC&apos;s website. She stated that the new liquidity mining guidance did not clarify the application of federal securities laws to crypto assets and instead increased confusion. This statement is based on a series of untested industry assumptions, and the legal conclusions only apply if these assumptions are true.Earlier, the SEC issued a statement regarding liquidity mining activities, clearly stating that liquidity mining activities are not regarded as securities. The SEC stated that participants in liquidity mining activities do not need to register transactions with the Securities and Exchange Commission under the Securities Act, nor do they need to comply with the Securities Act&apos;s registration exemption requirements for these liquidity mining activities.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23492</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquidity Staking Protocol Soars as RPL Surges Over 19% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23491</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to HTX market data, there was a general increase in prices in today&apos;s liquidity staking protocols. These include:The price of RPL increased by 19.2% in the last 24 hours and is currently trading at $7.98.The price of SWELL increased by 18.5% in the last 24 hours and is currently trading at $0.01.The price of LDO increased by 4.4% in the last 24 hours and is currently trading at $0.9364.In previous news, the US SEC has clarified the non-securities nature of liquidity staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23491</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&apos;s Xiangyang City cracked a case of transferring illegal funds using cryptocurrency, and the defendant was sentenced to two years and six months to three years in prison.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23490</link>
      <description>July 7th. Recently, the Procuratorate of Baokang County, Xiangyang City, Hubei Province, China, initiated a public prosecution. The local court sentenced five defendants, Yao, Yang, Liu (A), Qiao, and Liu (B), to imprisonment ranging from 2 years and 6 months to 3 years for the crime of using virtual currency to transfer illegal funds to conceal and disguise the proceeds of crime. They were each fined between 5,000 yuan and 18,000 yuan.Starting from April 2024, Yang, Yao, Liu (A), and others formed a group chat through overseas messaging applications. They were aware that the upstream funds might be proceeds of illegal activities such as telecommunications fraud. They used Tether transactions to assist the upstream in transferring illegal crime funds. The group had a clear division of labor: Yang was responsible for providing funds, Yao and Liu (A) coordinated with the upstream fraudsters to receive &quot;cash-out&quot; instructions. Qiao, Liu (B), and other &quot;drivers&quot; then went to designated l</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 02:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23490</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>