<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum On-Chain Activity Not Reflected in ETH Price, Staking ETF Approval Could Further Unlock Upside Potential</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23550</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Vincent Liu, the Chief Investment Officer of Kronos Research, stated that the United States&apos; clear stance on cryptocurrency regulation and the accumulation of institutional funds have also stimulated interest in Ethereum. Recently, dozens of companies have adopted Ethereum as part of their treasury strategy to achieve balance sheet diversification and attract investors seeking exposure to digital assets. The cumulative value of ETH held by publicly traded companies has exceeded $7.5 billion. The recent surge in on-chain activity on Ethereum has not yet been fully reflected in the ETH price.Vincent Liu further added, &quot;The price of ETH has been relatively cautious. Market confidence is on the rise, but a value reassessment is still in progress.&quot; If an Ethereum staking ETF is approved, it could further unlock the potential for price appreciation and on-chain activity, making ETH an interest-bearing asset that institutions can allocate to.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23550</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Network&apos;s daily transaction volume hit a record high of 1.74 million on August 5th, with the July cumulative transaction volume also reaching an all-time high.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23551</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on The Block data, Ethereum&apos;s daily transaction volume (with a 7-day moving average) reached a record high of 1.74 million transactions on August 5th. This surpassed the previous record of 1.65 million transactions set on May 12, 2021.July also witnessed the largest monthly transaction volume in the history of the Ethereum network, with a total of 46.67 million transactions.Furthermore, on August 5th, the number of active Ethereum addresses surged to 683,520, approaching the historical high of 743,730 addresses on May 12, 2021.Presto Research analyst Min Jung stated, &quot;Ethereum&apos;s daily transaction volume has reached a record high, which reflects the significant increase in DeFi activity, with stablecoins being at the core. The market&apos;s growing interest in yield strategies, especially wagers on interest rate cuts, has led to more on-chain transactions, ranging from yield farming to capital deployment.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23551</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock ETH Strategy Stocks Surge in Pre-market Trading, BMNR and BTCS Up Over 5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23549</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on the market data from rockflow, the pre-market trading of US crypto stocks generally showed an increase. These included:Coinbase (COIN) with a pre-market increase of 0.83%.Circle (CRCL) with a pre-market increase of 1.46%.MicroStrategy (MSTR) with a pre-market decrease of 0.21%.Bitmine (BMNR) with a pre-market increase of 5.21%.BTCS (BTCS) with a pre-market increase of 5.48%.Bit Digital (BTBT) with a pre-market increase of 3.78%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) with a pre-market increase of 2.35%.CEA Industries (VAPE) with a pre-market increase of 1.95%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23549</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has partnered with WLFI to launch the USD1 Staking Program, allowing users to earn multiple rewards through coin staking.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23548</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to official channels, Gate is set to collaborate with WLFI (World Liberty Financial) to launch the USD1 Loyalty Program, thereby transforming into a crypto exchange platform that provides incentives to USD1 users. At that moment, users will be able to accumulate points by engaging in trading, holding USD1, and participating in staking, Launchpad, and other activities. Additionally, exclusive rewards for new users are awaiting their discovery.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23548</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Labs: Liquid Leverage Attracts Over $1.5 Billion in Funds Following Last Week&apos;s Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23547</link>
      <description>On August 7th, Ethena Labs made an official announcement on social media. Since its launch last week, the Liquid Leverage product has attracted more than $1.5 billion in fund inflows.Now, Aave has increased the deposit limits for sUSD and USD in the Ethereum Money Market. The sUSD limit has been raised to about $350 million, and the USD limit has been raised to about $300 million. It is expected that the proposal for adjusting the September USD limit will be announced within the next 36 hours.The increase in Aave&apos;s limits enables more users to utilize Liquid Leverage, a new feature introduced by Ethena. This allows users to obtain leveraged exposure to the sUSD interest rate while maintaining better overall position liquidity by holding USD (with no cooldown period restriction).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23547</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI: USD1 Point Program Coming Soon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23546</link>
      <description>July 8th: WLFI, a cryptocurrency project with the support of the Trump family, declared that its USD1 Points Program is on the verge of commencing. The official team is currently engaged in formulating a brand-new loyalty program tailored specifically for USD1, and the initial batch will be launched in conjunction with selected partners. This program will initially be introduced in the cryptocurrency exchange arena in partnership with certain partners, and each partner platform will establish exclusive point accrual rules for eligible USD1 users.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23546</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contract Transaction Whale AguilaTrades Reallocates 4.6M USDT to Open Long Positions for BTC and ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23545</link>
      <description>July 8th. According to on-chain analyst Ai (@ai_9684xtpa), the contract trade whale AguilaTrades deposited 4.6 million USDC as collateral to Hyperliquid 15 minutes ago and has since opened long positions for BTC and ETH. The total position is worth 98.29 million US dollars, with a realized profit of 308,000 US dollars. The specific position information is as follows:BTC: 40x long, holding 530.7497 BTC, entry price $114,856.1ETH: 25x long, holding 10,000 ETH, entry price $3,706</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23545</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB announced the completion of a $9.5 million funding round, with participation from Amber Group.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23544</link>
      <description>July 8th. As per techinasia, BOB, a project focused on constructing a Bitcoin and Ethereum hybrid DeFi chain, declared that it has secured $21 million in funding starting from December 2023.It is reported that BOB obtained $9.5 million in the latest fundraising round. The new investors involved are Anchorage, Amber Group, and Sats Ventures, along with the existing supporters Castle Island Ventures, Ledger, and RockawayX.Castle Island Ventures had previously led BOB&apos;s $10 million seed round of funding.The company recently launched its testnet and collaborated with institutions like Lombard, Amber Digital, and RockawayX to facilitate native Bitcoin DeFi transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Listed Company DL Holdings Plans to Raise Approximately $83 Million to Expand into the Blockchain Business</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23543</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to The Block, the stock price of Hong Kong-listed financial services group DL Holdings fell by more than 8% on Thursday. The company announced plans to raise 653.3 million Hong Kong dollars (approximately $83.2 million) through a rights issue to finance its blockchain business development.Based on the filings submitted to the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, DL Holdings has entered into subscription and subscription agreements. Selling shareholders will sell shares to at least six buyers at a price of 2.95 Hong Kong dollars per share through a placement agent. Subsequently, the company will immediately repurchase an equal number of new shares at the same price.The shares to be sold in this placement account for approximately 13.58% of the company&apos;s current issued share capital. After the issuance of new shares is completed, this proportion will decrease to around 11.96%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23543</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALLINDOGE Launches Ultra Edition, AI Smart Assistant Enters Utility Stage</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23542</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the AI tool platform ALLINDOGE launched its new Ultra version today. This new version is upgraded with Web3 user needs in mind. It focuses on introducing the MCP module, which supports one-line command completion for on-chain data queries, market analysis, project retrieval, document parsing, and other tasks. It has evolved from a &quot;capable of conversation&quot; intelligent assistant to an &quot;able to execute&quot; one. The main highlights of this update are as follows:· Integrated the MCP module to achieve integrated research and market analysis.· Added historical conversation records to support continuous context interaction.· Supported one-click sharing of conversation content.· Gained access to the document upload and parsing system, and the AI automatically extracts key points.· Optimized the interface for clearer and smoother operation.The ALLINDOGE team stated that the Ultra version is a turning point from &quot;passive queries&quot; to &quot;active service&quot; and will continue to i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23542</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>