<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:39:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Breaks $3800, Up 1.53% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21980</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum has gone beyond $3800, and its 24-hour growth rate is 1.53%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21980</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Proposes Establishment of World Artificial Intelligence Cooperation Organization, with Preliminary Consideration of Headquarters in Shanghai</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21979</link>
      <description>On July 27th, according to People&apos;s Daily, on the 26th, the Chinese government put forward the establishment of the World Artificial Intelligence Cooperation Organization, with an initial consideration that its headquarters would be located in Shanghai. This is an important initiative for China to adhere to multilateralism and promote global governance through consultation, joint contribution, and shared benefits. It is also a practical action for China to respond to the call of the global South, help bridge the digital and intelligent divide, and promote the ethical and inclusive development of artificial intelligence. China anticipates that the World Artificial Intelligence Cooperation Organization will become an important international public good and gradually form a widely accepted global governance framework and standard norms for artificial intelligence, ensuring that artificial intelligence continues to develop in the direction of human civilization progress. By removing</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21979</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next week will see a dense release of macroeconomic data, and the market still expects the Federal Reserve to once again stand pat.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21978</link>
      <description>On July 27th: Against the complex backdrop of escalating political pressure, the continuous evolution of trade policies, and conflicting economic signals, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell and his colleagues will enter the interest rate decision meeting in the coming week. This decision coincides with a rare data-intensive week - the U.S. government will consecutively release GDP, jobs reports, and the Fed&apos;s core inflation indicator. While the market generally anticipates that the Fed will once again maintain stability, this series of data may reshape the policy path. Economists predict that the U.S. second-quarter GDP annualized growth rate, which will be released on Wednesday of next week, is expected to reach 2.4% (a significant improvement compared to the 0.5% contraction in the first quarter), but this is mainly due to a substantial narrowing of the trade deficit. The July non-farm payroll report, which will be released on Friday, is expected to confirm a cautious trend in business</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21978</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVX Surges Above $0.06, Up Over 33% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21977</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on market data, the token NAVX of the DeFi project NAVI Protocol on the Sui chain has broken through $0.06, experiencing a more than 33% increase in the past 24 hours.NAVI Protocol recently launched a multi-wallet management system called NAVI Copilot and became the debut partner of OKX&apos;s xBTC. According to Defilama data, NAVI&apos;s BTC assets currently account for 60% of the total Sui ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21977</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The total value locked in the ZORA contract has surpassed $100 million, with the 24-hour liquidation volume ranking third only to BTC and ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21975</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on Coinglass data, the perpetual contracts for ZORA on mainstream CEXs have all shifted to negative funding rates. Binance is at -0.27%, and the long/short ratio calculated by position size for whales is 0.9826.According to HTX market information, ZORA is currently trading at $0.074, with a 24-hour price increase of 60.2%. The total trading volume of ZORA contracts on the entire network in the past 24 hours is reported to be $2.21 billion, with a 24-hour increase of 397%. The total open interest of contracts on the entire network has reached $106 million, with a 24-hour increase of 196%. In the past 24 hours, there have been $7 million worth of liquidations in ZORA contracts, with short liquidations accounting for $6.75 million, ranking only after BTC and ETH in terms of liquidation amount.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21975</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MistTrack: Beware of Malicious Google Ads Phishing Scam Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21976</link>
      <description>July 27th — SlowMist MistTrack issued a phishing security alert. Reports have been received indicating that scammers are placing malicious Google ads (such as misttrack[.]tools) in an attempt to deceive users into signing harmful transactions. Users are advised to remain vigilant, not to trust unofficial links, and to utilize anti-phishing tools to ensure their protection.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected DeFiance Capital Associated Address Acquires 30,366 ETH, Worth $114 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21973</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, a wallet that may be related to DeFiance Capital increased its holdings by 30,366 ETH within the past 28 hours. The value of this increase is $114 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21973</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The era of Parabolic Bull Market and Devastating Bear Market is over, Bitcoin&apos;s future will see continued consolidation, volatility, and upward movement.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21974</link>
      <description>July 27th. Mitchell Askew, a Blockware BTC analyst, stated that Bitcoin will no longer witness a &quot;parabolic&quot; price surge or a &quot;devastating&quot; bear market. The presence of a spot ETF has permanently reduced volatility and changed market dynamics. Bitcoin seemed to be two entirely different assets before and after the ETF launch. It is expected to reach $1 million in the next 10 years through continuous oscillation between &quot;upsurge&quot; and &quot;consolidation&quot;. This path will be boring for everyone and will drive out short-term speculators. A chart shared by Mitchell Askew shows that Bitcoin&apos;s price volatility has decreased significantly since the launch of the Bitcoin ETF in the United States in January 2024.Bloomberg&apos;s Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas had previously stated that the reduction in volatility helps Bitcoin attract larger investors and provides a first-line opportunity for its adoption as a currency. However, the cost may be the potential absence of &quot;god-tier candlesticks&quot;. The sp</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21974</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRM Labs: Russian Entity Allegedly Using Kyrgyzstan Cryptocurrency Platform to Evade Sanctions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21972</link>
      <description>On July 27th, as per Decrypt, a report issued by the blockchain intelligence firm TRM Labs indicates that Russian entities are leveraging a Kyrgyzstan cryptocurrency platform to evade sanctions. Cryptocurrency transactions related to Russia almost entirely dominate the Kyrgyzstan cryptocurrency industry, which was &quot;practically non-existent&quot; prior to the 2022 Russia-Ukraine conflict.On-chain analysis reveals that the now-defunct Russian exchange Garantex has likely rebranded as Grinex and is conducting large-scale ruble-to-crypto transactions by using Russian-backed stablecoins (such as A7A5). By the end of 2022, the trading volume of Kyrgyzstan&apos;s virtual asset service providers reached $59 million, and it soared to $4.2 billion in the first seven months of 2024. These platforms have emerged as crucial channels for Russian entities to bypass sanctions and maintain access to the global financial system.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21972</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun has withdrawn 60,000 ETH from Binance, equivalent to around 226 million USD</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21971</link>
      <description>On July 27th, as monitored by Whale Alert, the wallet address of Justin Sun withdrew 60,000 ETH from Binance, which was approximately worth $226 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 02:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21971</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>