<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:39:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Influencer Crypto Beast has reactivated their X account and rebranded as @realcryptoelio</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23386</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the cryptocurrency sleuth ZachXBT mentioned that the cryptocurrency influencer Crypto Beast has just reactivated his X account and changed his username to @realcryptoelio.It was previously reported that on July 22nd, the cryptocurrency influencer Crypto Beast deactivated his X (original Twitter) account. It was likely that he would come back online in a few days with a possible username change. Crypto Beast was exposed for manipulating the ALT crash event and had cashed out more than $11 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23386</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Whales collectively transferred $68.8 million worth of ETH to a CEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23384</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Whale 0xc156 transferred all 13,459 ETH ($49 million) into Binance 20 minutes ago. Additionally, Whale 0x46DB deposited 5,504 ETH ($19.8 million) into OKX within the past 16 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lido: SEC Clarifies the Non-Security Nature of Staked Assets, Helping Drive Institutional Adoption and DeFi Ecosystem Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23385</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Lido stated in a post that, &quot;The previous day, the U.S. SEC issued guidance affirming that liquid staking and similar receipt-like tokens like stETH do not constitute securities, thereby providing the long-awaited regulatory clarity for Lido and the entire industry. Lido&apos;s operations in the U.S. have now obtained increased regulatory clarity, eliminating the previous uncertainty that hindered institutional adoption and DeFi integration.&quot;This stance has paved the way for U.S.-based platforms, financial institutions, and users to utilize Lido more freely. Without the worry of triggering securities laws, more protocols may integrate stETH, further expanding its use cases in the DeFi space. This also reinforces the reasons for centralized exchanges and fintech platforms to support Lido&apos;s liquid staking, potentially attracting more funds.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23385</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX&apos;s seventh Launchpool event will start today at 18:00 UTC, allowing users to stake HTX to earn APEPE, ES, and SNAKES multi-mining rewards.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23383</link>
      <description>August 6th. According to an official announcement from Huobi HTX, the Huobi HTX 7th Launchpool event is set to officially commence at 18:00 (UTC+8) on August 6th and will run through September 5th at 18:00 (UTC+8). This mining period will have a duration of 30 days. By staking HTX or participating in the one-click purchase of $HTX flexible savings products, participants can share a prize pool consisting of 38,461,538,462 APEPE, 98,360 ES, and 714,285 SNAKES, with a total pool value exceeding 120,000 USDT.Launchpool links earning and airdrop channels, enabling users to mine multiple coins with a single asset. Through the &quot;one-click purchase&quot; function, users can simultaneously obtain earnings from mining and airdrop rewards. Users can participate by accessing the Huobi HTX App home page → More → Activities &amp; Rewards → Launchpool and clicking on &quot;One-Click Purchase&quot; to join, easily receiving various project airdrop rewards. The warm-up period has already started, so making early purchas</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23383</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five of the participants in the PUMP token sale have transferred 1.25 billion PUMP tokens to Kraken, causing a 72% price drop from the all-time high.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23382</link>
      <description>August 6th. Based on the on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), it appears that the five addresses that participated in the PUMP public sale and received the maximum allocation have liquidated their holdings. Compared to the price peak, they have missed out on a potential profit of $10.866 million.Four hours ago, the individual consolidated 1.25 billion PUMP from these five addresses and subsequently deposited them into Kraken, with a value of $4.06 million. Since then, the value of these tokens has decreased by 72% from their all-time high.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23382</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Authorities Freeze $4.8 Million in Coinbase User Crypto Scam Case</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23381</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Indian Enforcement Directorate (ED) launched an investigation into a large-scale cryptocurrency fraud case. It froze assets worth 428 million Indian Rupees (approximately $4.8 million) belonging to the alleged fraudster Chirag Tomar, his relatives, and associated entities. This enforcement action was carried out under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA) and involved the seizure of 18 immovable properties in Delhi and multiple bank accounts.Chirag Tomar is a key mastermind behind a cryptocurrency phishing scam that targeted Coinbase users from mid-2021 to late 2023. The scam entailed creating a fake website or using Search Engine Optimization (SEO) techniques to imitate the cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase in order to deceive users into logging in, ultimately resulting in the theft of approximately $20 million worth of cryptocurrency.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23381</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale transferred an additional 50 WBTC to Binance 1 hour ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23380</link>
      <description>August 6th: An hour ago, a whale deposited an additional 50 WBTC ($5.71 million) into Binance. If sold, they would make a profit of $2.885 million, with a cost base of $56,410.89. It is suspected that they have sold 100 WBTC from yesterday until now, with a total value of $11.44 million, and they currently still hold 88.253 WBTC.During the last bull market, this whale accumulated BTC. After four years, they are now taking profits. Their assets have gone from an 80% drawdown to doubling.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23380</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CEO: Institutional ETH Holding Will Drive Industry-Wide Benefits</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23379</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Hunter Horsley, the CEO of Bitwise, stated that the charm of crypto lies in the fact that a rising tide lifts all boats. When any of these companies increase their holdings of ETH, the rest of the companies also stand to benefit. Everyone has the same goal, which is to hope to see the success of ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23379</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Fireverse (FIR), with an airdrop eligibility threshold of 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23378</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per official information, Binance Alpha is the inaugural platform to list Fireverse (FIR) for trading. The Alpha trading will officially commence on August 6, 2025, at 19:00 (UTC+8).Once trading gets underway, users who hold at least 200 Binance Alpha points can obtain a first-served, first-come basis airdrop of 1000 FIR tokens. In case the reward pool is not completely claimed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.Claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha points. Users must confirm the receipt on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23378</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satsuma Technology has raised $217.6 million to establish a Bitcoin Treasury.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23377</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the London-based artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology concluded a financing round worth ￡163.7 million ($217.6 million), surpassing the target by 64%. Investors include ParaFi, Pantera, DCG, Kraken, and others.This funding round accepted 1,097 bitcoins, advancing its Bitcoin treasury strategy. Its current total bitcoin holdings are expected to reach 1,125.85 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23377</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>