<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:36:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Durov Holdings has announced a three-stage digital finance strategy, aiming to expand its virtual asset license business by 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21641</link>
      <description>July 24th. According to an official announcement, the Hong Kong-listed company Derun Holdings has put forward a three-stage plan for digital financial development. This plan includes:Stage One: Establishing a licensed Virtual Asset Over-the-Counter Trading (VAOTC) and Primary Brokerage business.Stage Two: Constructing an RWA Tokenization and Asset Management platform.Stage Three: Building a compliant cross-border digital asset fund ecosystem.Derun Holdings is actively expanding the business scope of its existing Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission Type 1 (Dealing in Securities), Type 4 (Securities Advisory), and Type 9 (Asset Management) licenses to cover virtual asset activities. It is expected to complete the regulatory approval process by October 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21641</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit 24-hour Trading Volume Rankings: XRP, SAHARA, STRIKE Take Top Three Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21640</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to CoinGecko data, in the previous 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit reached $8.79 billion. The XRP/KRW trading pair accounted for 20.67% of the volume and ranked first in the KRW market. The remaining top five in trading volume are: SAHARA, STRIKE, NEWT, DOGE.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: US-EU Trade Tensions Unresolved, BTC Long vs Short Tug of War, Support at 117,000, Resistance at 121,200, Suggests Watching for Breakout Direction</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21639</link>
      <description>On July 24th, EU diplomats took a tough stance, stating that if an agreement cannot be reached with the United States, they will back counter-coercion measures. The U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen responded by saying that if the EU wants to reduce the 30% tariff, they must propose an &quot;Innovative Finance Arrangement&quot; similar to that of Japan. Currently, the EU has not submitted a specific proposal. Negotiations have made only limited progress, intensifying market concerns about the escalation of transatlantic trade friction.Bitunix Analyst Suggestion:In the face of macro uncertainty, BTC is fluctuating around $119,300. The range of $120,800 to $121,200 is a short-term zone where there is intensive liquidation of long positions, posing strong potential pressure. There is obvious support around $117,000. If the level is broken below, it may trigger a new round of stop-loss selling. It is recommended that short-term traders adopt a range strategy between $117,000 and $121,200, focusing o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21639</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale conducted a stop-loss sell-off on the Base chain for a portfolio of meme coins, resulting in a $5 million loss.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21638</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, in the past 48 hours, a whale incurred a loss of $5 million while selling various tokens in the Base ecosystem. The specific transactions are as follows:It sold 1.87 million USDC for 1.08 million VIRTUAL, resulting in a loss of $1.73 million.It sold 951,000 USDC for 5.75 million AIXBT, leading to a loss of $1.7 million.It sold 188,000 USDC for 4.47 million GAME, with a loss of $1.19 million.It sold 123,000 USDC for 38,443.75 VVV, incurring a loss of $379,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21638</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Investment App Lightyear Completes $23 Million Funding Round, Led by NordicNinja</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21637</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per CNBC reports, the European investment app Lightyear has successfully completed a $23 million financing round. This round was led by NordicNinja and involved Markus Villig, the co-founder of the unicorn Bolt, as well as other Estonian tech entrepreneurs.This startup endeavors to become the &quot;European version of Robinhood&quot; and enter the commission-free trading market. Apart from the new funding, Lightyear will also introduce a brand new artificial intelligence feature. Additionally, Lightyear plans to release its own cryptocurrency product within two months, with a focus on offering an investment experience that is &quot;more inclined towards a long-term perspective.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21637</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Big Brother Ma」 Huang Licheng is Long on Chain with a total unrealized loss of $7.74 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21636</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per on-chain data, the &quot;Big Brother Whale&quot; Huang Licheng currently holds a long position with a value of $148 million on Hyperliquid, encompassing ETH, HYPE, and PUMP. At present, all are in an unrealized loss state, and the total unrealized loss is approximately $7.74 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21636</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian securitization company VERT launches Private Credit Platform on the XRP Ledger</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21635</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to CoinDesk, the Brazilian securitization company VERT has launched a blockchain-based private credit platform on the XRP Ledger and issued the first batch of Agricultural Receivables Certificates (CRA), which is worth 7 billion Brazilian reais (approximately 1.3 billion U.S. dollars).CRA is a crucial financial instrument in the Brazilian agriculture sector, which is used to package future cash flows. This issuance was carried out on the XRPL and its compatible Ethereum EVM sidechain, enabling real-time tracking of cash flows, loan events, and repayments.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21635</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KeyCorp CEO: Willing to Provide Cryptocurrency Custody Services in Collaboration with Customers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21634</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per Cointelegraph, the CEO of KeyCorp Bank stated, &quot;Cryptocurrency is, to a certain extent, a means of storing value - as long as our clients have a need for it and wish to hold it in their wallets, we will offer our cooperation.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21634</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Market Greed Index Cools Down, Today&apos;s Fear and Greed Index at 71</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21633</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on alternative data, the Fear and Greed Index of cryptocurrencies today is 71 (yesterday it was 74), and the &quot;greed&quot; sentiment in the market has cooled down.Note: The threshold of the Fear Index is 0-100, which includes indicators such as Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Activity (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21633</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renzo Protocol has adopted an Ethereum reserve strategy and currently holds 1050 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21632</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the re-staking and yield optimization protocol Renzo Protocol has entered the ranks of protocols adopting an Ethereum reserve strategy. The protocol currently holds approximately 1050 ETH (around $3.8 million), ranking 39th among institutional holdings that adopt an Ethereum reserve strategy.This data has been verified by Renzo&apos;s official X account, which further stated: &quot;Renzo is continuously injecting more Ethereum into the reserve.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>