<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:54:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 domain registrar Freename has completed a $6.5 million Series A funding round, led by Entrée Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21646</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the Web3 domain registrar Freename announced the successful completion of a $6.5 million Series A funding round. This round of funding was led by Entrée Capital. Polymorphic Capital also participated, along with its seed round investors Sparkle Ventures, Blockchain Founders Fund, and Golden Record Ventures. Additionally, new angel investors joined the round, including Mike Lobanov, the co-founder of Target Global, the Rashwan Family Office, and Aaron Schnarch, the former CEO of Coinbase Custody.The company focuses on establishing a connection between the traditional DNS and the blockchain domain system. Freename&apos;s core technology encompasses a cross-chain domain conflict management system, which supports the resolution of multiple-chain domains such as Polygon and Solana while remaining compatible with traditional browsers. Its innovative solution enables users to create custom top-level domains and generate profits through the sale of subdomains. The funds will be util</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21646</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX will attend GM Vietnam 2025 Blockchain Week as a Gold Sponsor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21645</link>
      <description>July 24th. As per the news on official social media, Huobi HTX will participate in the blockchain summit GM Vietnam 2025 as a Gold Sponsor, presenting its global layout and ecosystem strength in the Web3 field. Additionally, Huobi HTX will also jointly host the Web3 Future Night themed party with the well-known Web3 media ChainCatcher on the evening of July 31st in Hanoi. At that time, it will gather Vietnam&apos;s most active KOLs and communities to create a high-quality social environment for Web3 practitioners.It is reported that GM Vietnam - Vietnam Blockchain Week will be held at the Hanoi National Convention Center from August 1st to 2nd, attracting more than 20,000 participants and having a media exposure of 45 million, making it the largest blockchain and Web3 industry event in Vietnam.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21645</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the last 24 hours, CEX Net Inflow was 1,037.00 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21644</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on Coinglass data, in the past 24 hours, the total net inflow of BTC on CEX was 1,037.00 BTC. The top three CEX exchanges in terms of inflow volume are as follows:· Kraken: a net inflow of 1,230.29 BTC;· Binance: a net inflow of 977.69 BTC;· Gemini: a net inflow of 395.89 BTC.In addition, OKX witnessed a net outflow of 877.97 BTC and ranked first in the outflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21644</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin surpasses $120,000, the mainstream CEX total cumulative short liquidation volume will reach $1.285 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21643</link>
      <description>On July 24th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin breaks through $120,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will amount to $1.285 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin drops below $116,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will reach $1.946 billion.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree the target price will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will undergo a more intense reaction due to a liquidity avalanche once it reaches that point.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21643</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget on-chain trading has launched tokens such as Billy, memecoin, and ORGO.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21642</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Bitget Onchain Trading introduced the MEME tokens Billy, memecoin, ORGO, ZKWASM, TRUST, COA, Totakeke, and DEBT from the Solana, Base, and BNB Smart Chain ecosystems. Users are now able to commence trading on the Onchain Trading section.Bitget Onchain Trading endeavors to seamlessly link CEX and DEX, offering users a more convenient, efficient, and secure on-chain trading experience. Users can directly utilize their Bitget spot accounts (USDT/USDC) to trade popular on-chain assets. Currently, it supports prominent blockchains such as Solana (SOL), BNB Smart Chain (BSC), and Base.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21642</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Durov Holdings has announced a three-stage digital finance strategy, aiming to expand its virtual asset license business by 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21641</link>
      <description>July 24th. According to an official announcement, the Hong Kong-listed company Derun Holdings has put forward a three-stage plan for digital financial development. This plan includes:Stage One: Establishing a licensed Virtual Asset Over-the-Counter Trading (VAOTC) and Primary Brokerage business.Stage Two: Constructing an RWA Tokenization and Asset Management platform.Stage Three: Building a compliant cross-border digital asset fund ecosystem.Derun Holdings is actively expanding the business scope of its existing Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission Type 1 (Dealing in Securities), Type 4 (Securities Advisory), and Type 9 (Asset Management) licenses to cover virtual asset activities. It is expected to complete the regulatory approval process by October 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21641</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit 24-hour Trading Volume Rankings: XRP, SAHARA, STRIKE Take Top Three Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21640</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to CoinGecko data, in the previous 24 hours, the trading volume on Upbit reached $8.79 billion. The XRP/KRW trading pair accounted for 20.67% of the volume and ranked first in the KRW market. The remaining top five in trading volume are: SAHARA, STRIKE, NEWT, DOGE.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: US-EU Trade Tensions Unresolved, BTC Long vs Short Tug of War, Support at 117,000, Resistance at 121,200, Suggests Watching for Breakout Direction</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21639</link>
      <description>On July 24th, EU diplomats took a tough stance, stating that if an agreement cannot be reached with the United States, they will back counter-coercion measures. The U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen responded by saying that if the EU wants to reduce the 30% tariff, they must propose an &quot;Innovative Finance Arrangement&quot; similar to that of Japan. Currently, the EU has not submitted a specific proposal. Negotiations have made only limited progress, intensifying market concerns about the escalation of transatlantic trade friction.Bitunix Analyst Suggestion:In the face of macro uncertainty, BTC is fluctuating around $119,300. The range of $120,800 to $121,200 is a short-term zone where there is intensive liquidation of long positions, posing strong potential pressure. There is obvious support around $117,000. If the level is broken below, it may trigger a new round of stop-loss selling. It is recommended that short-term traders adopt a range strategy between $117,000 and $121,200, focusing o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21639</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale conducted a stop-loss sell-off on the Base chain for a portfolio of meme coins, resulting in a $5 million loss.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21638</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, in the past 48 hours, a whale incurred a loss of $5 million while selling various tokens in the Base ecosystem. The specific transactions are as follows:It sold 1.87 million USDC for 1.08 million VIRTUAL, resulting in a loss of $1.73 million.It sold 951,000 USDC for 5.75 million AIXBT, leading to a loss of $1.7 million.It sold 188,000 USDC for 4.47 million GAME, with a loss of $1.19 million.It sold 123,000 USDC for 38,443.75 VVV, incurring a loss of $379,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21638</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Investment App Lightyear Completes $23 Million Funding Round, Led by NordicNinja</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21637</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per CNBC reports, the European investment app Lightyear has successfully completed a $23 million financing round. This round was led by NordicNinja and involved Markus Villig, the co-founder of the unicorn Bolt, as well as other Estonian tech entrepreneurs.This startup endeavors to become the &quot;European version of Robinhood&quot; and enter the commission-free trading market. Apart from the new funding, Lightyear will also introduce a brand new artificial intelligence feature. Additionally, Lightyear plans to release its own cryptocurrency product within two months, with a focus on offering an investment experience that is &quot;more inclined towards a long-term perspective.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21637</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>