<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:14:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>New &apos;BNB Version of Yield Farming&apos; APY Expands to 789.78%, with Daily Trading Volume Reaching $5.88 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22195</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on the data from rockflow, the new &quot;BNB Version MicroStrategy&quot; of the US stock CEA Industries (VAPE) witnessed its gain widen to 789.78%. It is currently priced at $78.968, with a market value reported as $66.4392 million. After the US stock market opened, the trading volume reached $5.88 billion.BlockBeats had previously reported that CEA Industries and 10X Capital, with the backing of YZi Labs, announced a $500 million private placement to establish the world&apos;s largest publicly traded BNB financial company.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22195</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Delays Decision on Truth Social&apos;s BTC Spot ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22194</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to market information, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has postponed reaching a decision on the spot Bitcoin ETF application submitted by Truth Social.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22194</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Dalio suggests that investors allocate 15% to gold or Bitcoin, stating that holding a small amount of Bitcoin personally.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22193</link>
      <description>On July 28th, billionaire Ray Dalio proposed that investors allocate 15% of their investment portfolios to Bitcoin and gold in order to hedge against the continuously growing U.S. debt and economic instability.The founder of Bridgewater Associates, Ray Dalio, stated in the &quot;Masters of Scale&quot; podcast that the macroeconomic risks posed by the rising government debts of the U.S. and other countries have not been fully digested by the market, and the market may ultimately face a significant downturn. The U.S. government &quot;spends 40% more than it earns and cannot really cut spending. Its debt is six times its revenue, with annual interest payments reaching up to $1 trillion, which is equivalent to half of its budget deficit.&quot;Ray Dalio further explained that the U.S. government can only repay its debts by issuing more debt and &quot;the central bank (Fed) printing money.&quot; This has created a situation where the market may become increasingly panicked. Dalio believes that the triggering factor f</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22193</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX has become the first global platform to offer compliant cryptocurrency derivatives trading in the UAE</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22192</link>
      <description>July 28th. According to official channels, OKX declared that it has achieved the distinction of being the first global exchange to introduce regulated crypto derivatives targeted at retail users in the UAE. It offers products such as futures, perpetual swaps, and options, all of which support up to 5x leverage. This action not only broadens the strategic choices available to retail users in volatile markets but also showcases OKX&apos;s continuous dedication to compliance, security, and user education.It is reported that this product launch is based on the Dubai Virtual Asset Regulatory Authority (VARA)&apos;s &quot;Innovation Sandbox Framework.&quot; This framework aims to provide a controlled testing environment for innovative financial products, facilitating innovation while strengthening regulatory safeguards.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain day trader whale bought 5,267.31 ETH in the past 11 minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22191</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the whale trader whose address is 0x54d...e6029 purchased 5,267.31 ETH within the past 11 minutes at an average price of $3,797.It is reported that this whale trader, which had a 100% winning rate in three previous swing trades starting from June 2nd, has achieved a profit of $1.75 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22191</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasma Mainnet Token Sale Concludes: Raised Over $373 Million, Oversubscribed by 7x</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22189</link>
      <description>July 28th. As per official channels, Plasma has made an announcement that the public sale has come to an end. The subscription amount has exceeded 3.73 billion U.S. dollars, and the oversubscription has reached more than 7 times. Additionally, the project&apos;s mainnet Beta version will be launched, with a total locked value (TVL) of 10 billion U.S. dollars in stablecoins. This sets a record for the fastest attainment of this TVL scale in the history of blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22189</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock SQNS Plunges by Approximately 25%, Previously Announced Acquisition of 755 Bitcoins Today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22190</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on the data from rockflow, the U.S. stock Sequans Communications S.A. (SQNS) witnessed a 24.49% decline during the trading session. It is currently trading at $1.495, with a market capitalization of $213 million.BlockBeats had previously reported that SQNS announced earlier today that it had purchased 755 bitcoins at an average price of $117,296 per bitcoin (including fees). As of July 25, 2025, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings have reached 3,072 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22190</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reuters: Interactive Brokers Considers Launching a Stablecoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22188</link>
      <description>July 28th - As per Reuters, Interactive Brokers is in the process of contemplating the launch of a stablecoin for its clientele. The report pointed out that Interactive Brokers&apos; founder, Thomas Peterffy, stated that this integration would offer continuous stablecoin financing for brokerage accounts and provide asset transfer services for prominent cryptocurrencies. This is not the initial instance when this brokerage behemoth has ventured into the cryptocurrency industry.It is reported that the company incorporated cryptocurrency trading and custody services towards the end of 2021, encompassing four assets: BTC, ETH, LTC, and BCH. In March, it expanded its support to SOL, ADA, XRP, and DOGE.In addition, the company also holds a stake in the cryptocurrency exchange platform Zero Hash and has formed a partnership with the stablecoin issuer Paxos.Currently, Thomas Peterffy has not made a decision regarding how to launch the stablecoin and is contemplating integrating stablecoins is</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22188</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock VAPE Extends Gain to 686.37%, Market Cap Currently at $58.7175 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22186</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on the data from rockflow, the &quot;New BNB Version Microstrategy&quot; of the US stock CEA Industries (VAPE) has witnessed its gain expand to 686.37%. It is currently priced at $69.79, with a market value reported as $587.175 million. After the US stock market opened, the trading volume reached $342 million.BlockBeats previously reported that CEA Industries and 10X Capital, with the support of YZi Labs, announced a $500 million private placement to establish the world&apos;s largest publicly traded BNB financial company.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22186</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22187</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin has fallen below $118,000 and is currently priced at $117,959.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22187</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>