<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:45:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Analyst: Bitcoin and Ethereum Spot ETFs&apos; Total Trading Volume Yesterday on Par with Apple Stock</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24772</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas stated on social media that the combined trading volume of Ethereum and Bitcoin spot ETFs the previous day was $11.5 billion, which was on a par with the trading volume of Apple&apos;s stock.According to Rockflow data, the trading volume of Apple the previous day reached $12.083 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24772</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital has completed a $1.4 billion project financing to accelerate the development of the Helios AI data center.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24771</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as per official channels, Galaxy Digital Inc. (Nasdaq: GLXY) declared that it has successfully completed a $1.4 billion project financing. This is intended to support the continuous development of its Helios data center campus located in western Texas. The financing will cover the initial renovation and expansion work at Helios and provide the initial power supply for its Artificial Intelligence (AI) and High-Performance Computing (HPC) business. This supply will be delivered through a long-term agreement with CoreWeave Inc.Galaxy has allocated $350 million to fulfill the equity requirements, while the remaining construction costs will be financed through debt. The $1.4 billion debt financing amounts to 80% of the loan-to-cost ratio and has a term of 36 months. It is secured by all assets related to the first-phase construction of Helios.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Founder: Hoping Bitcoin Can Become Everyday Peer-to-Peer Currency as Originally Designed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24770</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Jack Dorsey, the founder of Twitter, tweeted on social media, indicating that the various businesses of Block, Inc. are dedicated to making Bitcoin a peer-to-peer electronic cash system and an everyday currency, just as it was originally envisioned.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24770</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huadao Healthcare plans to invest up to HKD 3 billion to increase its holdings in cryptocurrency.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24769</link>
      <description>August 15th. The Hong Kong-listed company Concord Medical (01931.HK) announced that in the view of the Board, purchasing and holding cryptocurrency is considered an important measure for the Group to enhance its Ethereum (ETH) reserve fund and expedite the development of the ivd.xyz trading platform&apos;s ecosystem. It is also an essential part of the Group&apos;s asset allocation strategy. After careful deliberation, the Board recommends seeking prior approval from the shareholders to obtain a purchase authorization. This authorization will enable the Board to conduct potential cryptocurrency purchases within a period of 36 months starting from the date of the special shareholder meeting, and the total purchase amount shall not exceed 3 billion Hong Kong dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24769</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Listed Company KULR Technology Extends Pre-market Gain to 24.29%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24768</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to the market data from RockFlow (refer to https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats for more information and click the link to open in a new tab), the pre-market gain of the US-listed company KULR Technology (KULR) expanded to 24.29%.Today, the US-listed company KULR Technology released its financial report for the second quarter of 2025. The quarterly revenue reached $397 million, showing a year-on-year growth of 63%. The company&apos;s net profit was $814 million, and the earnings per share was $0.22. This was mainly due to the appreciation of its Bitcoin holdings. As of now, KULR Technology&apos;s total Bitcoin holdings have reached 1021 coins. Additionally, BlackRock has already acquired a 5.6% stake in the KULR company.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will list the USELESS U Perpetual Futures Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24767</link>
      <description>On August 15th, Binance will commence the USELESS U Perpetual Contract at 20:15 (UTC+8) on 2025-08-15.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24767</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recently, three hacker groups have profited additionally due to the ETH price surge. The Radiant Capital hackers have stolen assets that have appreciated by an additional $48.3 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24766</link>
      <description>August 15th. Based on EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, three groups of hackers have recently made additional profits by selling ETH. The details are as follows:Radiant Capital hacker stole approximately $53 million in assets last October. They then exchanged it for 21,957 ETH at a price of $2,414. Starting 3 days ago, they have been selling ETH. As of now, they have sold 9,631 ETH and obtained 43.937 million DAI, with an average selling price of $4,562. The hacker now holds 12,326 ETH and 43.937 million DAI, and the total value is $101 million, which is an additional appreciation of $48.3 million compared to the stolen asset value.Infini hacker stole about 49.5 million USDC in February. They then exchanged it for 17,696 ETH at a price of $2,798. They have sold 3,540 ETH and received 13.318 million DAI, with an average price of $3,762. The Infini hacker has benefited from the rise in ETH and gained an additional $25.15 million.An unknown hacker received 17,412 ETH at the end of March from pl</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital has withdrawn 37,808 ETH from CEX in the past 24 hours, equivalent to around $172 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24764</link>
      <description>Update: On August 15th, as per TheDataNerd, within the past 24 hours, Galaxy Digital withdrew a combined total of 37,808 ETH from exchanges. This amount is approximately equivalent to $172 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24764</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Treasury and ETF Total Holdings Surpass 10 Million Coins, Accounting for 8.3% of ETH&apos;s Current Total Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24763</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to strategicethreserve data, the combined total holdings of Ethereum by treasury companies and ETFs have exceeded 10 million, accounting for approximately 8.3% of the current total supply. The top holders among treasury companies and institutions are as follows:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) takes the lead and currently holds 1.2 million ETH, with a value of around $5.33 billion;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) comes in second and currently holds 598,800 ETH, valued at around $2.77 billion;The Ether Machine (DYNX) ranks third and currently holds 345,000 ETH, with a value of around $1.6 billion;The Ethereum Foundation ranks fourth and holds 231,600 ETH, valued at around $1.07 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24763</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet will launch the Real Rice AI (RICE) TGE on August 18th.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24765</link>
      <description>August 15th. Binance Wallet will list Real Rice AI (RICE) TGE on August 18th, 2025, between 16:00 and 18:00. Qualified users will be required to use Alpha Points to participate in the subscription. Additionally, 40 million RICE tokens will be set aside for future activities, and the specific details will be announced separately.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24765</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>