<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 19:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 19:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Has Ordered Two Nuclear Submarines to be Deployed to Appropriate Region Near Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22863</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, US President Trump posted on social media and said, &quot;In view of the highly provocative remarks made by former Russian President and current Deputy Chairman of the Russian Security Council Medvedev, I have ordered two nuclear submarines to be deployed to the relevant region to ensure that these foolish and provocative remarks are not just empty words. Speech is of great significance and often leads to unexpected consequences. I hope this will not become one of those situations.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22863</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC: Crypto Market Enters Turbulent August as Trump&apos;s New Tariffs Spark Risk-Off Sentiment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22862</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, as per the report by CNBC, the crypto market witnessed a decline on Friday following Trump&apos;s announcement of &quot;reciprocal&quot; tariff adjustments for dozens of countries. Bitcoin&apos;s price demonstrated relative strength, while Ethereum, XRP, and BNB all underwent minor drops. Bitcoin once dropped to a low of $113,988.47.This decline led to a widespread long liquidation, with traders being compelled to sell assets at the market price to repay debts, thereby further driving down the price.Crypto-related stocks experienced even greater declines. Coinbase took the lead in the decline due to its poor second-quarter performance, falling by 15%; Circle declined by 4%, Galaxy Digital fell by 2%, the Ethereum treasury company Bitmine Immersion dropped by 8%, and MicroStrategy fell by 5%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22862</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the entire network has seen $812 million in liquidations, mainly from long positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22861</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to data from Coinglass, within the past 24 hours, the total liquidation across the entire network reached $8.12 billion. The total long liquidation was $7.34 billion, and the total short liquidation was $77.15 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22861</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto startup Subzero Labs has completed a $20 million seed round financing, with Pantera Capital leading the investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22858</link>
      <description>August 2nd: As per Fortune magazine, the cryptocurrency startup Subzero Labs has successfully completed a $20 million seed round of financing. This round was spearheaded by the crypto investment firm Pantera Capital, and it saw the participation of crypto venture funds Variant and Coinbase Ventures, as well as the crypto division of the high-frequency trading firm Susquehanna.Subzero Labs&apos; Co-founder and CEO, Ade Adepoju, declined to reveal the company&apos;s valuation subsequent to this financing round. He mentioned that the transaction was finalized in the first quarter of this year and encompassed a combination of equity and token warrants (that is, allocation rights to future yet-to-be-released crypto tokens).Subzero Labs intends to launch a novel blockchain named Rialo, which is crafted for real-world applications. Rialo is not a conventional Layer 1 blockchain - in Adepoju&apos;s words, it is &quot;neither Layer 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, nor 6&quot;, and he is hesitant to draw comparisons with exi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22858</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OP Labs announces the official release of the first Rust-based high-performance Rollup node, kona-node</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22860</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to official information, OP Labs declared the official launch of the first Rollup node based on Rust, named kona-node. As a Rollup node conforming to the OP Stack specification, kona-node possesses the advantages of memory safety, low resource consumption, and support for multiple proving backends, which makes it convenient to customize and expand. With only approximately 8000 lines of code, kona-node combines powerful functions and efficient performance, providing Ethereum Layer 2 solution developers with a new choice.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22860</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Crypto Special Task Force will hold a series of roundtable meetings across the United States.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22859</link>
      <description>August 2nd. According to official channels, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced that its Crypto Task Force will be visiting several cities in the United States in the upcoming months and hold a series of roundtable meetings. The purpose of these meetings is to offer more stakeholders in the crypto field the chance to have direct interactions with SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce. This event particularly extends an invitation to representatives from early-stage crypto projects that have fewer than 10 employees and have been established for less than two years, aiming to ensure a more comprehensive and diverse regulatory policy-making process.Commissioner Peirce expressed her expectation to receive feedback from those who were unable to attend the spring roundtable meeting in Washington earlier this year. She emphasized that the regulatory framework will have a significant impact on the industry. The SEC aims to achieve a more extensive outreach effect through ext</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22859</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Web Version is Now Live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22857</link>
      <description>On August 2nd, according to official information, Binance has declared the official launch of the Binance Wallet web version - a browser-based decentralized wallet that doesn&apos;t require installation or extensions. Users are able to directly carry out on-chain transactions through the Binance website without any additional setup, making it immediately ready for use. The wallet has been integrated into the Binance homepage under the &quot;Trade&quot; tab, facilitating convenient access to various decentralized exchanges (DEX).The new wallet features the Secure Auto Sign (SAS) mechanism. This mechanism ensures asset self-management while enabling quick authorization and automatic transactions, which is suitable for high-speed markets like meme coins. SAS operates within a Trusted Execution Environment (TEE), guaranteeing that the private key remains local and inaccessible to third parties.In addition, the wallet supports seamless cross-device switching. Coupled with a secure QR code authorizatio</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22857</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust and Blockchain Opportunities Fund Adjust Dividend Distribution Frequency to Twice Monthly</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22856</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per official information, Grayscale has made an announcement. Immediately, the distribution frequency of the Grayscale Bitcoin Covered Call ETF (with the ticker: BTCC) and the Grayscale Bitcoin Premium Income ETF (with the ticker: BPI) will be modified from monthly to twice a month. Both funds are set to target the 15th and the 30th of each month as the payment dates, and adjustments will be made in accordance with standard business day rules.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUI Treasury Management Company Mill City Plans to Raise Another $500 Million, Stock Price Plummets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22855</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as reported by The Block, the US-listed company Mill City Ventures III announced on Friday that it is set to repurchase up to $500 million worth of SUI tokens. Previously, the company had entered into an equity financing agreement with A.G.P./Alliance Global Partners, enabling it to sell common stock to finance its cryptocurrency treasury strategy.This announcement comes after the news on Thursday - Mill City had already spent around $277 million to purchase more than 76 million SUI tokens. The transaction took place after Mill City officially became the Sui corporate treasury manager and completed a $450 million private placement.On Friday, Mill City stated that A.G.P./Alliance Global Partners had agreed to provide an equity financing facility, allowing the company to sell up to $500 million worth of common stock. Mill City said: &quot;The equity financing does not involve any commitment fees, and all the proceeds from the financing will be utilized to advance the compan</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22855</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address holding 306 BTC has just been activated after 12.4 years of dormancy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22854</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as monitored by Whale Alert, an address that was holding 306 BTC (approximately $35.16 million) was just made active after having been dormant for 12.4 years.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22854</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>