<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:42:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Beets Introduces Gyroscope Dynamic Liquidity Pool to Sonic, Offering up to 190% APY</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23675</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the DeFi project Beets announced the launch of the Gyroscope Dynamic Liquidity Pool (E-CLP) on the X platform through Sonic. This mechanism enables yield sharing and offers an annualized yield of up to 190% in the current market conditions, thereby driving innovation and growth in the dynamic liquidity pool model.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23675</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Petition to Lugano City Council to Restore Satoshi Nakamoto Statue Gathers 1000 Signatures</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23674</link>
      <description>August 8th witnessed Paolo Ardoino, the CEO of Tether, declare that 1000 signatures have been gathered for the purpose of petitioning the Lugano City Council in Switzerland. The aim is to restore the statue of Satoshi Nakamoto which was previously cast into the lake. This statue, positioned in Lugano, Switzerland, was stolen and subsequently thrown into the lake on August 3rd. However, it was retrieved that very evening.On October 25th, 2024, the city of Lugano in Switzerland officially unveiled a statue in Ciani Park (Villa Ciani). This statue is dedicated to commemorating Bitcoin&apos;s anonymous creator, Satoshi Nakamoto. The unveiling event was organized by Tether in collaboration with the Lugano City Council under the Plan B initiative. The statue, meticulously designed by Italian artist Valentina Picozzi, took 18 months of research and 3 months of construction to be completed.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23674</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Reinforcing the View of &quot;Rate Cut in September,&quot; Near-Term Market Trend May Still Consolidate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23673</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Matrixport issued its weekly research report, stating that the market has recently entered a consolidation phase. Bitcoin has lost its momentum, and both the funding rate and trading activity have cooled down. The volume has shrunk, the funding rate remains low, and the market structure is showing signs of loosening. Meanwhile, the seasonal disturbances in August combined with external uncertainties have led to a notably cautious short-term sentiment. From a technical perspective, the $112,000 level previously provided support during this round of initial pullback, but the subsequent rebound attempts have been weak, indicating that this support level is likely to be tested again. If it is breached, the $106,000 range may once again become the focus of the market.The premise for a true bearish scenario is a sustained weakening of the US economy without a timely Fed rate cut. The current market conditions further reinforce the view that &quot;a rate cut in September is possib</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoRank: Gate Launchpool Ranks First in the Industry with 290 Listed Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23672</link>
      <description>August 8th. Based on the latest research report by CryptoRank, Gate Launchpool has cumulatively launched more than 290 projects. This number is significantly higher than Binance (108 projects) and OKX (11 projects), making it the Launchpool platform with the largest number of launched projects in the industry. The report indicates that Gate launches new projects nearly every week, showing a high level of activity.The report points out that Gate is extremely flexible in its mechanism design. For example, it has hourly reward distribution, no lock-up period, and allows multi-pool participation, which greatly enhances user experience. CryptoRank comments: &quot;The advantage of the Gate model lies not in publicity but in its highly standardized and adaptable underlying architecture, which can meet the different needs of long-term holders and short-term participants.&quot;With its high-frequency new listings and mechanism innovation, Gate Launchpool continues to expand its leading advantage and</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: US-Japan Tariff Relief News Boosts Market Sentiment, Yen-Linked Coins and AI Concept Chains See Rebound Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23671</link>
      <description>August 8th: The Japanese Chief Negotiator, Ryosei Akazawa, announced that the United States has agreed to eliminate the &quot;tariff overlay&quot; on Japan and lower automobile tariffs. However, the implementation timeline remains uncertain. This move provides some certainty to the trade agreement reached last month and is regarded as a positive development for the Japanese automotive industry and the overall export-dependent economy. Nevertheless, the timeline for reducing the automobile tariff from the current 27.5% to 15% is unclear, which puts pressure on companies such as Toyota in their financial planning. This event has alleviated market concerns about the escalating tensions between the US and Japan.Bitunix Analyst Recommendation:This news indicates a signal of policy easing, which helps to boost market confidence and the rebound potential of AI infrastructure coins mentioned yesterday after testing the support level. In terms of strategy, it is recommended to adopt a phased deploymen</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will launch Baby Shark Universe (BSU) on August 9th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23670</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Binance Alpha is set to launch Baby Shark Universe (BSU) on August 9th. Those eligible users will be able to claim the airdrop on the Alpha event page by using Alpha points once trading begins. Further details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23670</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superp announces the distribution of the second round of a 3% airdrop allocation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23669</link>
      <description>On August 8th, as per the official announcement, Superp Foundation is going to allocate 5% of the tokens for airdrop during the TGE. 2% of it has already been distributed, and the remaining 3% will be unlocked and distributed in one batch next week. The claim page is anticipated to become active on August 12th (Tuesday).</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23669</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HK Stock Concept Stocks of Digital Currency Stablecoins Soared Today, Huaxing Capital Holdings Rose by 19.39%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23668</link>
      <description>August 8th. According to RockFlow market data, Hong Kong stocks related to digital currency and stablecoin concepts showed a general upward trend today. These include: Huaxing Capital Holding (01911.HK), which rose by 19.39%; Future Data Group (08229.HK), which rose by 12.16%; New Fire Technology Holding (01611.HK), which rose by 8.12%; Jin Rong Investment (01328.HK), which rose by 12.5%; and Lanxiang Interactive (08267.HK), which rose by 8.62%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23668</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABUBU Meme Coin Market Cap Surges, Surpassing $14 Million with a 24-hour Gain of 54%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23667</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to the market information of GMGN, the market value of the Meme coin LABUBU, which is based on the trendy IP of Bubble Mart, has rebounded and exceeded 14 million US dollars. It is currently reported at 13.5 million US dollars, with a 24-hour increase of 54%.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins usually lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23667</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: BlackRock to Submit XRP Spot ETF Application to SEC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23666</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to Nate Geraci, who is the President of The ETF Store. After the Ripple appeal is resolved, BlackRock is going to submit an XRP ETF application to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission in order to promote the portfolio diversification of cryptocurrency ETFs. Nate Geraci pointed out that it would be unreasonable for BlackRock to ignore other crypto assets. If BlackRock fails to do so, it is as if it is telling the market that only BTC and ETH have value.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 06:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23666</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>