<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:54:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Announcement: Trump to Make Important Statement at 12 PM EST</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25760</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as announced by the White House, Trump is scheduled to deliver a significant statement in the Oval Office at 12:00 pm EST on Friday. The relevant parties have not yet disclosed the specific details of the statement.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Ethereum Long Position Added to Lending Pool」 Whale added a 25x long position on Ethereum, with an average entry price of $4,262.64</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25758</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a &quot;125K USD Long ETH Liquidation&quot; whale enhanced their ETH 25x long position to 4826 coins, which is approximately worth 20.67 million USD.Three hours ago, they added 800 ETH to their position, and the margin ratio reached as high as 99.42%; the current entry price is 4262.64 USD, and the liquidation price is 4194.38 USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25758</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Ethereum Developer Ecosystem is Similar to the iPhone Platform, Price Could Rise to $8,000 to $10,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25759</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Greg Magadini, the Director of Derivatives at Amberdata, stated that Bitcoin is currently like a hybrid of digital gold and a risk asset. Against the backdrop of a rising stock market and the Fed facing pressure to cut interest rates, this asset is being driven by two concurrent emotions. Although some people refer to Ethereum as a dated technology, Ethereum has a developer ecosystem similar to the iPhone platform, which enables developers to build applications directly on its infrastructure. These network effects will only continue to accumulate. Therefore, it is expected that the Ethereum price will continue to follow the rise of Bitcoin and may potentially reach the range of $8000 to $10000. (Decrypt)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25759</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet&apos;s Hemi Booster event has a participation threshold of 61 points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25757</link>
      <description>August 22nd. As per an official announcement, Binance Wallet has entered into a partnership with the Bitcoin scaling solution Hemi to launch a special Booster event. Users have the opportunity to participate in this event and receive an airdrop of 200 million HEMI tokens by fulfilling multi-stage tasks.The first stage will dispense a reward of 50 million HEMI tokens, and users possessing 61 or more Alpha Points are eligible to take part in this event.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25757</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine Congressman Proposes Establishing National Bitcoin Strategic Reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25756</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to NLNico, Philippine Congressman Miguel Villafuerte submitted HB 421. This proposal suggests that the Philippine Central Bank (BSP) should purchase 2,000 bitcoins annually for 5 years, amassing a total of 10,000 bitcoins. These bitcoins will be held for 20 years without being touched in order to strengthen national security and debt stability.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25756</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlockFi $13.2M Class Action Settlement Set to Be Approved, Final Objector Withdraws Opposition</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25755</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to Decrypt, the $13.2 million class-action settlement of BlockFi is about to be approved. The final objector, Yacov Baron, has withdrawn his opposition. This settlement will cover approximately 89,000 U.S. users who held BlockFi interest accounts between 2019 and 2022.BlockFi collapsed in 2022 due to its $680 million exposure to FTX, and this settlement offers a compensation channel for the affected investors.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25755</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: Tonight&apos;s Powell Speech Expected to Cause a 2% Price Swing for Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25754</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Pulkit Goyal, the trading lead at cryptocurrency market maker Orbit Markets, said that &quot;It is expected that the BTC options pricing will fluctuate around 2.0% based on Powell&apos;s speech at Jackson Hole. Nevertheless, if Powell&apos;s remarks deviate from the widely anticipated hints of rate cuts, there is a greater likelihood of downside volatility occurring.&quot; (CoinDesk)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25754</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Fed Harker Does Not Support Rate Cut in September, Bitcoin Breaks Below Uptrend Line, Short-Term Target at $99,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25753</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Cleveland Fed President Harker stated in an interview that he would not be in favor of a rate cut. He indicated: &quot;The current inflation level remains relatively high and has been on an upward trend over the past year. Based on the information I currently have, there is no justification for lowering interest rates in the short term.&quot; Although acknowledging certain concerns in the labor market, the unemployment rate still remains close to the ideal level of full employment. Therefore, maintaining a stance of &quot;moderate tightening&quot; still remains crucial in ensuring that inflation can continue to decline back to the target range.Influenced by this hawkish statement, Bitcoin once again tested the $112,000 level. Bitcoin (BTC) previously broke below the uptrend line since its low point of $75,000 in April of this year, forming a daily chart-level &quot;double top&quot; or 2B top pattern. Analysts at BiyaPay pointed out that if BTC effectively falls below the previous low of $111,920,</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25753</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Protocol&apos;s AI Agent project, VaderAI, has announced the discontinuation of the development of its DeFAI product related to Genesis.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25752</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Base ecosystem&apos;s AI Agent project VaderAI announced the discontinuation of the development of its DeFAI product related to Genesis. It will unlock all VADER tokens staked on VaderAI. Staking will only be possible on Virtuals with a 14-day cooldown period. Vader Yapping has been terminated, and the distribution of the next 14 days&apos; Virgen Points and token airdrop will be based on the snapshot of yesterday&apos;s stakers and yappers.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Japanese publicly traded company Convano has increased its BTC holdings by 200 coins, now owning a total of 364.93 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25751</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to the monitoring of @btcNLNico, the publicly listed Japanese company and nail salon operator Convano Co., Ltd. announced today that they have once again increased their holdings of BTC by 200 coins, and currently hold a total of 364.93 BTC.Convano plans to hold 21,000 BTC by the end of March 2027.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25751</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>