<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:54:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Since Tom Lee joined BitMine as Chairman on June 30, ETH has surged by 71% in the same period.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24169</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to Ark Invest Daily, Tom Lee became Chairman of BitMine on June 30th. At that time, the price of ETH was approximately $2,500. Now, the price of ETH has risen to $4,300, representing a 71% increase since June 30th.It is reported that since Tom Lee&apos;s joining, BitMine has shifted its strategic focus to building the world&apos;s largest Ethereum treasury company and plans to acquire 5% of the total ETH supply. Currently, its ETH holdings amount to 1.15 million coins, with a value of around $4.96 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24169</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Appoints Brian Brookshire as Bitcoin Strategy Lead</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24168</link>
      <description>August 12: The publicly listed company H100 Group in Sweden has named Brian Brookshire as the Director of Bitcoin Strategy. Brian Brookshire will collaborate closely with CEO Sander Andersen and COO Johannes Wiik. His main focus will be on further formulating the company&apos;s Bitcoin strategy, expediting the accumulation process, and enhancing communication and investor relations.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monad&apos;s recent post hints at or suggests a mainnet launch later this year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24167</link>
      <description>On August 12th, Monad sent out a tweet stating &quot;Monad Mainnet&quot; and attached an image featuring &quot;2025&quot;, suggesting that the mainnet might be launched in the latter part of this year.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24167</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US July CPI data will be released tonight at 8:30 PM.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24166</link>
      <description>On August 12th, the US July CPI data will be released tonight at 20:30 Beijing time.The market anticipates that core inflation will rebound moderately. Currently, there is a &quot;hawk-dove standoff&quot; within the Federal Reserve. If the data verifies tariff pass-through and economic uncertainty, the Fed&apos;s interest rate cut path may become more cautious. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24166</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine&apos;s trading volume reached $9.273 billion yesterday, ranking 7th in the US stock market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24165</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to data from Rockflow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), the Ethereum Treasury and the crypto mining company BitMine (BMNR) reported a trading volume of 9.273 billion USD yesterday. It ranked 7th among US stocks on that day.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24165</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fosun Confirms Application for Hong Kong Stablecoin License, Guo Guangchang Leads Team to Meet with Hong Kong Chief Executive</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24164</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as per Tencent News, Fosun has verified its application for a stablecoin license in Hong Kong and has assembled a complete team for the stablecoin license application. On August 6th, Guo Guangchang, the founder of Fosun, personally led the core stablecoin team within Fosun and other senior executives to meet with Carrie Lam, the Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region, and Paul Chan, the Financial Secretary of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region, respectively.Through its subsidiary Fosun Wealth, Fosun has already achieved progress in the digital asset field via the Starpath Technology platform. This includes participating in the distribution of a money market fund tokenization product launched by Huaxia Fund and developing a Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization platform.According to the timeline of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, institutions planning to apply can get in touch with the regulatory authority after August 1st and are req</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24164</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smarter Web Company has increased its BTC holdings by 295 coins, bringing its total holdings to 2395 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24163</link>
      <description>On August 12th, according to official information, the publicly listed company The Smarter Web Company in the UK announced that it had increased its stake in 295 bitcoins, with an average price of approximately $119,412. As a result, its total holdings reached 2395 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24163</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean Announces Pricing of $550 Million of Convertible Senior Notes Offering</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24161</link>
      <description>On August 12th, as per businesswire, DigitalOcean Holdings, Inc. (NYSE: DOCN) announced today that it has set the price for $550 million in the aggregate principal amount of 0% interest, 2030 convertible senior notes. The private offering is aimed at those reasonably believed to be qualified institutional buyers. The sale of the notes to the initial purchaser is expected to be settled on August 14, 2025, subject to the usual closing conditions.Furthermore, DigitalOcean has granted the initial purchaser a purchase option, enabling them to purchase up to an additional $75 million in the aggregate principal amount of notes within 13 days starting from the original issue date of the notes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24161</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Announces World3 (WAI) Airdrop Claim Threshold: Initially Requires 200 Alpha Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24162</link>
      <description>August 12th. According to official information, Binance Alpha is set to launch World3 (WAI) on its platform, and Alpha trading will commence on August 12th, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC+8). After the trading starts, users who hold at least 200 Binance Alpha Points can claim 800 WAI tokens through an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. Claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha Points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha event page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as giving up the airdrop.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24162</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador has been buying 1 BTC every day for 1000 consecutive days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24160</link>
      <description>August 12th. The Bitcoin Historian pointed out that El Salvador has been adhering to a daily &quot;buy-the-dip&quot; strategy for 1000 consecutive days and purchasing 1 Bitcoin each day. On-chain data indicates that the Salvadoran government currently holds a total of 6266.18 BTC, approximately $743.3 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 05:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>