<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:50:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>An address sent 200 million PENGU tokens to Binance, worth $6.12 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26642</link>
      <description>August 28th. Based on EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, half an hour ago, an address transferred 200 million PENGU to Binance, with a value of $6.12 million. In the past 2 months, this address has continuously transferred 765 million PENGU to Binance at a high price range, worth $26.57 million, and the average transfer price is $0.035.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26642</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Federal Reserve Chair Candidates with Crypto-Friendly Stance, Final Candidate List to Be Determined in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26641</link>
      <description>August 28th. The previous evening, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen declared that there are 11 prominent candidates for the position of the Federal Reserve Chair. The interviews will commence after Labor Day (which is on September 1st this year), and the final list will be submitted to President Trump. The known candidates on the list who are explicitly crypto-friendly comprise Investment Bank Jefferies&apos; Chief Market Strategist David Zervos, BlackRock&apos;s Global Chief Investment Officer Rick Rieder, Fed official Bowman, and Fed Governor Waller.David Zervos and Rick Rieder have been engaged in activities related to cryptocurrency. This includes their recent public endorsements of the eToro trading platform, the stablecoin issuer Circle Internet Group, the crypto exchange Bullish, and the crypto-based lending firm Figure Technology Solutions. David Zervos also early on gave support to Michael Saylor&apos;s MicroStrategy Bitcoin purchase strategy.As the top regulatory official of the Fed, Bowm</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26641</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boros Updates Transaction Limit and Incentive Plan, Adds BTC and ETH Multi-Term Products</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26640</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per official information, Boros made an announcement regarding the addition of new trading pairs. It launched Binance contracts with an expiration date of December 26, 2025, for both BTCUSDT and ETHUSDT. In terms of fund parameters, the initial maximum leverage available is 2x. The OI Caps are set at $10 million for BTC and $15 million for ETH. The AMM Vault limits are $20,000 for BTC and $25,000 for ETH. As of now, all Vault limits have been filled. The team indicated that leverage and fund limits will be gradually adjusted based on market performance. Regarding incentive programs, the Maker Order and AMM position rewards for this week are as follows:- The Maker Order reward for the ETHUSDT (September 2025) contract is 1,150 PENDLE, and the AMM Vault is 190 PENDLE.- The Maker Order reward for the BTCUSDT (September 2025) contract is 750 PENDLE, and the AMM Vault is 190 PENDLE.- The Maker Order reward for the ETHUSDT (September 2025) contract is 1130 PENDLE, and t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Launches USDG Automatic Earn Feature</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26639</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to an official announcement, in order to meet users&apos; dual needs for efficient asset utilization and yield, OKX has officially launched the USDG Automatic Yield Farming feature. This feature enables users to use USDG as collateral and earn yield at the same time. In the future, more related yield farming activities will be introduced. Users only need to hold at least 1 USDG in their OKX account to automatically start accruing yield without any additional fees. The yield will be settled directly to the funding account on a weekly basis.USDG is issued by Paxos Digital Singapore Pte. Ltd. (PDS) and is approved by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS). It acts as a major payment institution providing digital payment token services and complies with MAS&apos;s upcoming stablecoin framework requirements.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26639</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Leveraged Long Position on ETH Liquidated」 Whales Long Again, Position Worth $2.297 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26638</link>
      <description>On August 28th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), with the rebound of ETH, the &quot;Long ETH with $125k Liquidation&quot; whale once again fully loaded its position. Currently, two addresses have established a 25x leveraged long position in ETH with a total collateral of $92k and a value of $2.297 million. The liquidation prices are $4,488.02 and $4,490.8 respectively, and the current unrealized profit is $11k.Last night, the long position in ETH opened by the &quot;Long ETH with $125k Liquidation&quot; whale suffered another loss of $72k, leaving only $58k in the account. It is reported that the address originally started its journey of leveraged long positioning in ETH with $125k and reached a peak unrealized profit of $43 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26638</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mining company American Bitcoin, supported by the Trump family, is expected to go public in early September with the stock ticker symbol ABTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26637</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per Reuters, the merger between the mining firm American Bitcoin backed by the Trump family and Gryphon Digital Mining (GRYP.O) is anticipated to be completed shortly, with the intention of going public in early September. Donald Trump Jr, Eric Trump, and the mining company Hut 8 will jointly own 98% of the merged entity, which will retain the name American Bitcoin and be traded under the stock symbol ABTC.American Bitcoin has also been seeking acquisition targets in Asia recently in order to build a Bitcoin asset reserve. The company has started to reach out to investors regarding potential acquisitions and is currently planning to acquire a listed company in Japan, while potentially entering the Hong Kong market simultaneously. Sources familiar with the matter indicated that the company intends to follow the MicroStrategy model by establishing a cryptocurrency reserve platform through the acquisition of a publicly traded company.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26637</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Privacy Protocol Privacy Cash is now live on Solana</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26636</link>
      <description>On August 28th, the decentralized privacy protocol Privacy Cash has become live on the Solana blockchain. It offers a privacy-oriented transaction service similar to Tornado Cash. This decentralized open-source protocol complies with the regulations of the U.S. Department of the Treasury&apos;s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC). It has facilitated more than 10,000 SOL worth of private transactions.Privacy Cash enables users to deposit SOL into a privacy pool and use zero-knowledge proofs to withdraw SOL from the privacy pool to any receiving address. This ensures that the transactions between deposits and withdrawals cannot be linked, thereby protecting user privacy.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26636</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Stablecoin Market Cap Surpasses $280 Billion, Reaching a New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26635</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per the data from DefiLlama, the current total value locked of stablecoins across all networks has exceeded $280 billion, reaching a new record high. There has been a 7-day growth of 1.07%. Among them, USDT holds a market share of 59.75%, and USDC holds a market share of 24.6%.Over the past month, Tether and Circle have minted a total of $8.75 billion worth of stablecoins. The increase in on-chain minted stablecoins generally reflects the growing demand for stablecoins in the market and increased user participation. This is often associated with bullish sentiment in the cryptocurrency market, as more funds are flowing into the crypto ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26635</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fosun Wealth unveils internally incubated Web3 brand FinChain StarNet</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26634</link>
      <description>August 28th. The Web3 brand FinChain Star Chain, independently incubated by Fosun Wealth Holdings, was officially launched. It was announced that the project has signed relevant agreements with investors to complete the first round of external financing, with a financing amount of several million US dollars. Strategic investors include the Solana Foundation, Vaulta Foundation, Sonic Labs, Animoca Brands, Unified Ventures, and Tengyun Capital, etc. Fosun Wealth Holdings is a subsidiary of Fosun International Limited, a Hong Kong-listed company (stock code: 00656.HK). (Zhixun Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26634</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Asset Management Company K33 Releases 2025 Q2 Financial Report</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26633</link>
      <description>August 28th. The Bitcoin asset management company K33 presented its Q2 2025 financial report. The company&apos;s revenue reached 399 million Swedish Krona, showing a year-on-year growth of 108%. Meanwhile, K33 has submitted a MiCA license application to the Norwegian Financial Supervisory Authority and anticipates obtaining approval within the year to ensure the compliance of its products with the European regulatory framework.As of July 29th, K33 held a total of 126 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 06:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26633</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>