<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Nano Labs Surges Over 10% in Pre-market Trading, Currently Trading at $8.03</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22146</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to Rockflow market data, the pre-market trading of US stock Nano Labs surged by more than 10% and is currently at $8.03.Previously, Nano Labs announced that it has raised its holdings of BNB to 128,000 coins. Based on the current price of $850 per BNB, the total value of the company&apos;s BNB strategic reserve has exceeded $108 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22146</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs has increased its BNB holdings to 128,000 tokens, with a total value exceeding $100 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22145</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the US-listed company Nano Labs announced that it has boosted its holdings of BNB to 128,000 coins. With the current price of BNB at $850 per coin, the total value of the company&apos;s BNB strategic reserve has exceeded $108 million. This represents the latest move made by Nano Labs in its long-term BNB reserve strategy.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22145</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Foundation Buys $25,000 of SOLV and CA</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22144</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the BNB Chain Foundation provided incentives to certain addresses, with these addresses purchasing $25,000 worth of SOLV and CA tokens respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit, Bithumb, and other South Korean DAXA member platforms will delist the PUNDIAI token</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22143</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Upbit declared that the member exchanges of the Korea Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA) planned to stop trading support for Pundi AI (PUNDIAI). &quot;Just based on the explanatory materials provided by the foundation regarding the reasons for being designated as a trading alert project, the related concerns cannot be dispelled. After a comprehensive examination of the project&apos;s legitimacy, sustainability, security, and other aspects, it was determined that the project did not meet the standards to maintain trading support. Therefore, the decision was made to terminate trading support.&quot;Both Upbit and Bithumb will cease trading support for PUNDIAI on August 28th.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22143</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab Launches Cryptocurrency Payment Option in the Philippines, Partners with Triple-A and PDAX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22142</link>
      <description>July 28th: The Southeast Asian super app platform Grab announced that Grab users in the Philippines can now add funds to their GrabPay wallet using cryptocurrency. This service became feasible through Grab&apos;s cooperation with the payment service provider Triple-A and the local digital asset exchange PDAX.As early as 2024, Grab initially partnered with Triple-A in Singapore to launch the service of topping up the GrabPay wallet with cryptocurrency. Triple-A is a company focused on assisting businesses in achieving cryptocurrency payments. Building on the success in Singapore, Triple-A has now collaborated with PDAX to introduce this innovative top-up method to the Philippines, providing greater convenience and flexibility to Grab users. Users can now utilize various cryptocurrencies to top up their GrabPay wallet, including:路 Bitcoin路 Ethereum路 USD Coin (USDC)路 Tether (USDT)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22142</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXC is about to launch the StablR USD (USDR) Launchpool event, sharing a total prize pool of 85,000 USDT</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22141</link>
      <description>July 28th. According to official channels, in celebration of the listing of StablR USD (USDR), MEXC has initiated a Launchpool event. Through staking USDT, MX, and USDR, participants are able to share a reward of 70,000 USDT. Inviting new users to participate can also enable them to share an additional 15,000 USDT.Event Duration: July 28, 2025, 19:00 (UTC + 8) - August 1, 2025, 19:00 (UTC + 8)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22141</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock: Sequans drops over 9% in pre-market trading, bringing its market cap down to $283 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22139</link>
      <description>On July 28th, based on Rockflow market data, the pre-market stock price of Sequans witnessed a decline of more than 9%, resulting in its market capitalization dropping to $283 million.Earlier, Sequans announced that it had acquired 755 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 3,072 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22139</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Sequans increased its Bitcoin holdings by 755, bringing the total number of Bitcoins it holds to 3072.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22140</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Sequans, a publicly traded company in the US, has acquired 755 bitcoins, raising its total holdings to 3072 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22140</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Research Institute: ETH/BTC Ratio Breaks Above 200-day Moving Average for the First Time, ETH Expected to Rally to $10,000 in Q4</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22138</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Ryan Lee, the chief analyst of the Bitget Research Institute, stated that Ethereum has recently surged by nearly 60% and exceeded $3,800. This is mainly driven by institutional fund inflows and the increase in on-chain activities, showing clear signs of structural strength. It is worth noting that the ETH/BTC ratio has surpassed the 200-day moving average for the first time in a year, indicating that Ethereum is entering a relatively strong period.Last week, the net inflow of ETH-related spot and derivative transactions reached $2.4 billion, and large whale addresses on-chain have continued to accumulate. At the same time, the market&apos;s expectations for the Ethereum ecosystem, especially core applications such as DeFi, continue to heat up, driving a structural shift of funds towards ETH. In contrast, although Bitcoin has been stably trading above $119,000 and still has a robust technical aspect and some institutional support, ETF funds have seen slight outflows. The mark</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22138</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QCP: Market Expecting Ethereum and Bitcoin to Face Pullback Pressure Around $4,000 and $120,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22137</link>
      <description>On July 28th, QCP issued its daily market analysis report indicating that Ethereum is gradually getting close to the $4000 price level, which was last observed in December of the previous year. With the continuous inflow of funds into the Ethereum spot ETF surpassing that of the Bitcoin ETF for seven consecutive days, market attention and speculation on ETH are intensifying. Considering that the market value of ETH is currently only one-fifth of that of BTC, the threshold for attracting institutional and corporate funds is relatively lower, making the price action more sensitive.Although Ethereum has been dominating most of the headlines in recent weeks, Bitcoin has shown quiet resilience. Although the inflow of funds into the Bitcoin spot ETF has slowed down, the price trend remains stable.Bitcoin&apos;s dominance rate still remains around 60%, with almost no fluctuation in the past week, reflecting the market&apos;s long-term confidence in Bitcoin as a store of value asset rather than a wi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22137</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>