<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, a $40 million worth position was established in HYPE, and the new address has started gradually selling off HYPE and longing ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26206</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on on-chain data, the mysterious new wallet address that injected $40 million into HYPE last week has once more sold 186,000 HYPE tokens (valued at $8.6 million). It used the USDC acquired from the sale of HYPE to take a long position in the futures market, establishing a long position of 27,236 ETH ($126 million). This sale was carried out in batches, with each batch being 11,000 HYPE tokens, and each individual sale being approximately $500,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26206</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Drops Below $4600</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26205</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to HTX market data, the price of Ethereum fell below $4600, showing a 24-hour change of -5.00%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26205</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Ethereum Reserve Concept Stock Prices Plummet, BTCS Falls Over 8%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26208</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the Ethereum Reserve Concept Stocks on the US stock market generally declined, including:· SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) decreased by 3.98%;· Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) dropped by 2.49%;· BTCS (BTCS.US) fell by 8.13%;· Bit Digital (BTBT.US) declined by 1.77%;· Coinbase (COIN.US) fell by 2.95%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abraxas Capital recently purchased 120,900 PT-kHYPE tokens, bringing their total holdings to 146,500 PT-kHYPE tokens.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26207</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on on-chain data, Abraxas Capital transferred 410,000 HYPE tokens (amounting to 18.5 million USD) to HyperEVM today and then staked all the assets on Kinetiq.Subsequently, they also purchased 25,600 PT-kHYPE tokens (with a value of 1.1 million USD). In the past four days, they have accumulated a total purchase of 120,900 PT-kHYPE tokens (worth 5.4 million USD). Currently, they hold 146,500 PT-kHYPE tokens (valued at 6.5 million USD). These operations are part of their Elysium Global Arbitrage Fund and are carried out in accordance with a fully Delta neutral strategy.BlockBeats Note: A &quot;fully Delta neutral strategy&quot; indicates that the position, through hedging or arbitrage, completely eliminates the risk in terms of price direction. The source of returns comes not from speculating on price movements but from spreads, fees, liquidity incentives, time value, or arbitrage opportunities.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26207</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-chain Monitoring Platform: LIBRA Token Key Figure Hayden Davis Nets $12 Million Profit by Sniping YZY Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26204</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the Blockchain data monitoring platform Bubblemaps released an article indicating that based on the tracked fund flows, Hayden Davis, a key figure in the LIBRA token from Kelsier Labs LLC, made $12 million by snatching the YZY token at its launch.According to GMGN market data, the YZY token reached a market value of $3 billion at the time of launch and then began a one-way downward trend. Currently, the market value has dropped sharply to $550 million, with a 24-hour decline of 19.66%.BlockBeats had previously reported that scooter, a crypto KOL who was involved in leaking information about the LIBRA token, claimed that he could be 99% certain that Hayden Davis was involved in releasing the YZY token as the YZY model closely resembles the LIBRA model from a few months ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26204</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkham: Identified BTC Holding Address Worth $740 Million in the UAE, Primarily Acquired Through Mining Firm Citadel&apos;s Rewards</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26200</link>
      <description>On August 25th, in Arkham, an on-chain data monitoring platform, it was announced on social media that a relevant address in the United Arab Emirates has now been marked on the Arkham platform. The UAE&apos;s Bitcoin holdings worth $700 million have been indicated on the Arkham platform.Arkham stated that the UAE is the fourth-largest government entity holding Bitcoin on the platform, with a total BTC holding value of nearly $7.4 billion. Unlike in the United States and the United Kingdom, the UAE&apos;s Bitcoin holdings do not come from law enforcement asset seizures but rather from mining operations carried out in partnership with Citadel. As of now, they have mined approximately 9,300 BTC and still hold at least around 6,300 BTC.2pointzero holds 85% of Citadel, and the latter is 100% owned by IHC. Approximately 61% of IHC is owned by the UAE Royal Group, which is controlled by Sheikh Tahnoon Bin Zayed Al Nahyan, a member of the Abu Dhabi royal family.Through partnerships with the Phoeni</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched the U-based SOMI perpetual contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26203</link>
      <description>August 26th. According to an official statement, Bitget has declared the commencement of a U-based SOMI perpetual contract. The leverage offered ranges from 1 to 5 times. Simultaneously, the contract trading BOT will be activated.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26203</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonbirds has partnered with Football.Fun, where users holding the NFT can claim a Pro Pack card pack and 2000 Reputation Points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26202</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the official Moonbirds team made an announcement on social media that the project has entered into a partnership with the Base Layer sports prediction app Football.Fun. By linking a wallet holding Moonbirds or delegating to the user&apos;s Football.Fun account, users are eligible to receive a free Pro Pack card pack along with 2000 reputation points. Once the wallet is connected for 48 hours, the card pack and points will be automatically delivered to the user&apos;s account. BlockBeats had previously reported that, according to Dune Analytics, the Base Layer&apos;s reward-based sports prediction app Football.Fun currently has a total of 10,738 active user wallet addresses, a platform total value locked (TVL) of $10.79 million, and cumulative revenue of $1.54 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26202</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: The U.S. Will No Longer Provide Any Funding to Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26201</link>
      <description>On August 26, US President Trump said that the US will no longer provide any financial support to Ukraine in the context of the Ukraine conflict. (Forex)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26201</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary Capital Submits Canary American-Made Crypto ETF Application to SEC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26199</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per market intelligence, the digital asset management firm Canary Capital has submitted the application for the Canary American-Made Crypto ETF to the SEC. The intention is to list it on the Cboe BZX exchange under the code MRCA. The fund solely invests in crypto assets that are invented, mined, or led in the United States, thereby being a high-risk speculative product and currently awaiting approval. Canary has also put in applications for the Canary Trump Coin ETF and the Canary Staked Injective ETF.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26199</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>