<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:22:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Andre Cronje is conducting a fundraising for the on-chain trading platform Flying Tulip, with plans to issue the platform token FT.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24687</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the founder of Sonic Labs, Andre Cronje, launched a fundraising campaign for its on-chain trading platform, Flying Tulip, targeting U.S. fund companies. According to his introduction, Flying Tulip is a high-performance and fully featured trading platform constructed entirely on-chain. Its liquidity is powered by a synthetic delta neutral liquidity pool and is supported by staking rewards.Flying Tulip will issue the platform token FT with a fixed supply. There is no token inflation or token incentives. 50% belongs to investors, and 50% belongs to the foundation. The FT token has not been launched yet.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24687</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Li Lin Family Office Avenir Group Holds Approximately $1.01 Billion in BlackRock Bitcoin ETF</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24686</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on a 13F filing submitted by Avenir Group, which is a Hong Kong-based Lee&apos;s family office. Currently, this office holds a BlackRock Bitcoin ETF worth $1.01 billion, approximately 16.55 million shares. This amount has increased compared to the previously reported 14.7 million shares in May.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24686</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stock Stablecoin Concept Stocks Experience Widespread Pullback, Bright Smart Securities Financial Drops Nearly 20%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24685</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the market data from RockFlow (https://rockflow.ai/en/crypto-stocks?utm_campaign=blockBeats), Hong Kong stock stablecoin concept stocks entered a correction stage. Emperor Capital Group saw a nearly 20% decline, Hudson Medical dropped by more than 7%, WeLab Financial and Tyro Payments both fell by over 5%, while OSL Group, BC Technology Group, and Victory Securities each saw a decrease of about 3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24685</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffett Resumes Apple Sale, Selling Approximately $4.1 Billion in the Second Quarter</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24684</link>
      <description>August 15th. After half a year has passed, Berkshire once again reduced its holdings in Apple. In the second quarter, it sold 20 million shares, resulting in a reduction of its position value by $4.1 billion. Apple still remains its top holding. During the second quarter, it also significantly reduced its holdings in Bank of America by more than 26 million shares, with its stake decreasing by more than 40% within a year. Berkshire completely sold its stake in T-Mobile during this quarter. It established a new position in Cerner with more than 5 million shares, and the end-of-quarter market value was nearly $1.6 billion. Cerner&apos;s stock price surged by over 9% in after-hours trading. Berkshire also initiated a new position in Nucor Corporation with more than 6.6 million shares, and the market value exceeded $800 million. Among the top ten holdings, Berkshire only increased its position in Chevron in the second quarter by purchasing more than 3.4 million shares.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24684</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perplexity reportedly proposed to acquire Brave for around $1 billion this summer.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24683</link>
      <description>August 15th. As per TheInformation, before putting forth a $35 billion acquisition offer for Google Chrome, the artificial intelligence search company Perplexity had put forward a $1 billion acquisition of the privacy-focused browser Brave earlier this summer. However, the negotiations have come to a standstill.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24683</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bowmore will issue a tokenized whisky on the Avalanche chain, priced at $5500.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24682</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to Crowdfundinsider, the Scottish whisky maker Bowmore is going to issue a tokenized limited edition whisky on the Avalanche chain. The first &quot;Collector&apos;s Edition&quot; is priced at $5,500, and each bottle of whisky is linked to an NFT. This whisky will make its first appearance at TOKEN2049 in Singapore on September 30, 2025. At that time, the NFT can be redeemed for the physical bottle.Bowmore, which is a part of the Beam Suntory global spirits group, is one of the oldest distilleries in Scotland. This move indicates that the brand is making its first attempt in Real World Asset (RWA) tokenization, providing collectors with a new interactive experience.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24682</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday&apos;s REX-Osprey SOL Spot ETF saw a net inflow of $13 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24681</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on the monitoring of Farside Investors, the net inflow of REX-Osprey SOL Spot ETF yesterday was $13 million. As a result, the total net inflow since its listing has reached $159.3 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24681</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Rises Above $4600, 24-hour Loss Narrows to 2.8%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24680</link>
      <description>On August 15th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum saw a rebound and surpassed $4600. The 24-hour decline was narrowed to 2.8%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Protocol Level&apos;s official X account appears to have been compromised</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24679</link>
      <description>August 15th: It is suspected that the official X account of the stablecoin protocol Level has been hacked, and a fake airdrop link was posted. The replies to this tweet have been disabled. Please be vigilant in protecting your assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24679</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple High-Leverage Liquidation Whales Recently Suffer Losses, with James Wynn and AguilaTrades Both Losing Tens of Millions of Dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24678</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to EmberCN&apos;s statistics. After the contract trading whale AguilaTrades was liquidated again at 2 a.m. with only $30,000 left, several highly leveraged liquidation whales that are widely followed by the market and have a similar trading style all suffered losses. These include:Whale James Wynn, who reached a peak profit of $87 million at the end of May. Not only did he give back all the profits, but he also lost $21.77 million of the principal. At the peak by the end of May, he opened a $1.23 billion worth of BTC long position on Hyperliquid.Insider whale qwatio used a $3 million principal to make a maximum profit of $26 million, but was eventually liquidated in one go.Contract trading whale AguilaTrades ended up with a loss of $37.6 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24678</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>