<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:27:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: BTC May Undergo Chip Redistribution in the $112K-$117K Range, Breaking Above $117K to Test New High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23709</link>
      <description>August 8th. The on-chain data analyst Murphy released a market analysis, stating that BTC&apos;s breakthrough above $117,000 the previous day was significantly influenced by the favorable event of &quot;Trump signing an executive order to include cryptocurrency in the 104K.&quot; However, it was merely a short-term emotional stimulus and had not yet substantially attracted a large amount of funds. The active index of short-term investors has been continuously declining after reaching a peak in July, and there is no clear sign of an upward turning point (forming a higher high). The panic low points witnessed during the recent price corrections are also not as severe as those on December 24 and February 25, indicating that up to this point in the current market cycle, investor sentiment is generally more neutral, neither leaning towards extreme panic nor excessive optimism.According to URPD data, BTC is once again testing a key resistance level. $117,000 is the highest candle in the current entire ch</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23709</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The confirmation process of CFTC Chairman Brian Quintenz, nominated by Trump, has been stalled</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23708</link>
      <description>August 8th. According to cryptocurrency journalist Eleanor Terrett, the process of nominating Brian Quintenz, the CFTC chairman nominated by Trump, has come to a standstill. Internal emails obtained through the Freedom of Information Act showed that Quintenz might have had access to confidential CFTC information during his tenure as a director at Kalshi, a prediction market regulated by the agency. A detailed email blog post about this matter is spreading on Capitol Hill, giving rise to questions. The White House has requested the Senate Agriculture Committee to postpone the scheduled confirmation vote.Meanwhile, at the end of last month, the White House once again expressed its support for Trump&apos;s nomination of Brian Quintenz as the chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). On July 31st, the White House made it clear that Quintenz still is the top candidate for the position and is expected to be confirmed promptly.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23708</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador May Establish a Bitcoin Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23707</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the El Salvador National Bitcoin Office disclosed images related to &quot;Bitcoin Banks&quot;, with the caption &quot;Bitcoin Banks are coming to Bitcoin country&quot;, suggesting the establishment of a Bitcoin bank.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23707</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeFi platform Credix appears to have disabled its X account</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23706</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to PeckShield&apos;s monitoring, the DeFi platform Credix is reported to have deactivated its X account.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 4th, the admin account address of Credix was attacked, with an estimated loss of approximately $4.5 million. The attack involved the minting of a counterfeit acUSDC token (Credix Market Sonic USDC) that was not supported by real assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23706</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stock Exchange-listed company IVD Medical Holdings has announced the acquisition of $19 million worth of ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23705</link>
      <description>August 8th. As per CoinDesk, the Hong Kong-listed company IVD Medical Holdings announced the acquisition of $19 million (approximately 149 million Hong Kong dollars) worth of Ethereum to back its medical asset tokenization strategy. The company is in the process of developing the ivd.xyz platform based on Ethereum smart contracts, with the aim of achieving the tokenization of drug intellectual property and medical assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23705</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Makes a Big Splash Again: Withdraws Over $12 Million, Deposits Over $3.5 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23704</link>
      <description>August 8th, based on the monitoring of HyperInsight, in the past 4 hours, significant fund movements have occurred in multiple whale addresses of Hyperliquid:「Large Withdrawals」A whale withdrew approximately $2.97 million USDC from the address starting with 0x97E5b0;A whale withdrew approximately $6.92 million USDC from the address starting with 0x630DaEB;A whale withdrew approximately $2.5 million USDC from the address starting with 0xe86b057;The total withdrawals amount to approximately $12.39 million USDC.「Large Deposits」A whale deposited approximately $1.82 million USDC into the address starting with 0x7fDaFdE;A whale deposited approximately $1.70 million USDC into the address starting with 0xd47587;The total deposits amount to approximately $3.52 million USDC.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address bought $263,000 worth of ZORA last month, now showing an unrealized gain of around $1.3 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23703</link>
      <description>Update: On August 8th, as per TheDataNerd, the address &apos;0x926&apos; expended $263,000 during the previous month to acquire 18.807 million ZORA tokens. The present value of this holding amounts to $1.555 million, and it has an unrealized gain of roughly $1.3 million (an investment return of around 500%). This address has not made any sales of tokens as of yet.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23703</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market: Cryptocurrency Concept Stocks Surge, SharpLink Up by 1.97%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23702</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on the market data from RockFlow, pre-market crypto-related stocks in the US are generally on the rise. These include:Coinbase (COIN) increasing by 0.83%; Circle (CRCL) rising by 1.02%; MicroStrategy (MSTR) decreasing by 0.3%; Riot Platforms (RIOT) going up by 0.35%;ETH MicroStrategy Stocks: Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) up by 2.69%; SharpLink Gaming (SBET) up by 1.97%; Bit Digital (BTBT) up by 2.37%;BNB MicroStrategy Stocks: CEA Industries (BNC) up by 1.88%; Windtree Therapeutics (WINT) up by 0.68%;SOL MicroStrategy Stocks: DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) up by 1.71%;LTC MicroStrategy Stocks: MEI Pharma (MEIP) up by 4.71%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23702</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale conducted a stop-loss sell-off of 130 million PUMP tokens, and currently still holds 1.17 billion tokens.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23701</link>
      <description>On August 8th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, an address sold 130 million PUMP tokens within 6 hours at an average price of $0.0033 and received 424,700 USDC in exchange. Currently, this address still holds 1.17 billion PUMP tokens (valued at approximately $3.92 million), with an unrealized loss of around $898,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23701</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hua Xing Capital Founder Bao Fan Rumored to Have Resurfaced</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23700</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to Caixin, multiple independent sources have suggested that Fang Xinghai, the founder of the Hong Kong-listed company Huaxing Capital Holdings (01911.HK), has recently been rumored to have made a reappearance. In February 2023, Fang Xinghai, the founder of the Hong Kong-listed company Huaxing Capital Holdings (01911.HK), was suddenly taken away by relevant authorities, which sent shockwaves through the venture capital circle. Subsequently, the details of the case and the progress of the investigation have not been disclosed by the authorities. Huaxing Capital responded by stating that Fang Xinghai is no longer involved in the group&apos;s daily management and operations, and his personal activities are private matters that fall outside the scope of Huaxing Capital&apos;s response.According to RockFlow market data, Huaxing Capital Holdings (01911.HK) in the Hong Kong stock market</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 09:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23700</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>