<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>10x Research: Bitcoin to Provide Better Risk-Reward Entry Point if Pullback Reaches May High Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22119</link>
      <description>On July 28th, Markus Thielen, the director of 10x Research, stated that for traders aiming to participate in Bitcoin&apos;s upward trend, waiting for Bitcoin to retrace to the high support level near $111,673 in May will offer a better risk-reward entry point.In a report sent to clients, Thielen pointed out, &quot;We expect Bitcoin to retest its breakout level at $111,673 in order to provide a more favorable risk/reward entry point.&quot; He explained that the market frequently retests breakout points before a significant bull run, so the possibility of a retracement to this level cannot be ignored. Thielen further added that if a significant pullback does not take place, the optimal entry point would be above the $120,000 breakout, which marks the breakout of the downtrend line from the highs on July 14th and 23rd.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22119</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Market Cap Surpasses Strategy, SoftBank, Nike, and More Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22118</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to the data of 8marketcap, the market capitalization of BNB has reached $119.14 billion, with a 24-hour change of +7.27%. It has now surpassed companies such as Strategy ($115.09 billion), SoftBank ($112.95 billion), and Nike ($112.64 billion). Currently, BNB ranks 185th in the global asset market capitalization list.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22118</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS: Prepare for Potential Market Volatility</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22117</link>
      <description>On July 28th, UBS Wealth Management Investment Office stated that since the peak of concerns triggered by the U.S. tariff policy in April, the S&amp;P 500 Index has witnessed a nearly 30% increase. This reveals that investors are increasingly convinced that the U.S. will reach a compromise with its major trading partners. Recent data also shows that the U.S. economy has maintained its resilience, and market sentiment has been boosted by top tech companies continuously increasing their capital expenditures in artificial intelligence.UBS also warned that the recent significant gains in the past few weeks have already factored in a lot of potential positive news, and investors should be prepared for possible market volatility in the coming weeks. While the market will be encouraged by the increased certainty of U.S.-EU trade, the level of U.S. tariffs still remains about six times higher than the pre-Liberation Day level. The economic impact of these tariffs is currently unfolding, and unce</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22117</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Agent Platform Bankr is currently developing an API to support agent-based encrypted payments and an information layer.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22116</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the AI agent platform Bankr disclosed that it is in the process of developing the Bankr API. This API will enable agents or apps to utilize Bankr as a cryptographic payment or information layer. In the first phase, BNKR is used to pay for each query via x402 and obtain transaction data execution. In the second phase, wallet creation is supported, and it is completely controlled by the agent or app through Bankr.BlockBeats reported previously that on July 24th, Coinbase Ventures announced that it would provide support to Bankr through the Base Ecosystem Fund. Bankr is one of the agent platforms integrated into Coinbase&apos;s newly launched Base app. Transaction agents respond more quickly than humans, operate 24/7, and are capable of making more data-driven decisions.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22116</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Surges to Touch $860, Continues to Hit All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22115</link>
      <description>On July 28th, BNB witnessed a short-term spike and reached $860, continuously hitting a brand-new all-time high. Currently, it is trading at $855.09, and within a 24-hour period, the price has increased by 7.15%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22115</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The address bought 5073.16 ETH at a high slippage price, with an average price of $3958 per ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22114</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst AI Yi @ai_9684xtpa, an address carried out a high slippage transaction on the blockchain. It spent 20.08 million USDC to purchase 5073.16 ETH, and the trade was completed in only two transactions. The average purchase price was $3958, which was $37 higher than the ETH price on centralized exchanges at the same time ($3921).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22114</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale increased their ETH holdings with an average price of $3,916, acquiring 2,415 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22113</link>
      <description>On July 28th, as per the monitoring of EmberCN, a whale address utilized 9.45 million USDC to make a purchase of 2415 ETH on-chain within the past 2 hours. The price at which this transaction took place was $3916 per ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22113</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Over the past decade, Bitcoin has only seen price increases in August for three years, potentially entering a consolidation phase due to seasonal disturbances.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22112</link>
      <description>July 28th: According to Matrixport&apos;s analysis, &quot;A month ago, based on contrarian seasonal analysis, we proposed that Bitcoin was expected to rise to $116,000, and now this prediction has been verified by the market. The current market sentiment is gradually becoming optimistic. This week will witness a series of key events: the intensive disclosure of U.S. stock earnings reports, the delayed release of the White House&apos;s digital asset report, and the Federal Reserve interest rate decision, which may become a new round of catalysts driving market volatility.&quot;However, historical data indicates that August and September have historically been relatively weak months for Bitcoin performance. Over the past decade, the average return rate in August has been nearly zero, with only three years showing gains. Therefore, many traders often choose to lock in profits at this stage. Although we still maintain a bullish outlook for the year, considering seasonal fluctuations, the market may face a t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Dips Below $119,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22111</link>
      <description>On July 28th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $119,000, and its 24-hour growth rate narrowed to 0.63%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22111</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate launches various investment options, with BTC&apos;s annualized return currently at 13.14%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22110</link>
      <description>On July 28th, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Gate recently launched the 290th round of the Launchpool event, enabling users to stake BTC and NERO in order to earn 40,000,000 NERO tokens as rewards. This round of the event will officially commence at 20:00 (UTC+8) on July 28th and will continue until 20:00 (UTC+8) on August 11th.According to the official page, the estimated annualized yield for BTC in this round of the event is as high as 13.14%, and VIP users are also eligible to enjoy a bonus of up to 500% on the staking amount. Users can stake early, and the rewards will be automatically distributed on an hourly basis after the mining begins.At the same time, Gate has launched various BTC financial products. The current on-chain BTC staking annualized yield is 3%, and the BTC Flexible Savings Yield is 5.64%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22110</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>