<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:51:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Midday Sell-Off in US Stocks Deepens, SharpLink Tumbles Over 5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27404</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, based on market data, the US stock market witnessed a further downturn during the trading period. The Nasdaq declined by 1.6%, the Dow Jones dropped by 1.02%, and the S&amp;P 500 Index fell by 1.32%. Cryptocurrency-related stocks generally saw a decrease, including:WLFI Treasury Company&apos;s ALT5 Sigma (ALTS) saw a sharp plunge of 28.3%. On August 11th, it announced the launch of a $1.5 billion private placement for WLFI Treasury Strategic Initiative, with Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, joining the board;Bitmine (BMNR) fell by 0.76;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) dropped by 5%;Circle (CRCL) declined by 7.2%;Strategy (MSTR) went against the trend and rose by 3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27404</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Trader @ParallelAiRev Nets Another $1.78M, Tops $PUMP Leaderboard Again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27403</link>
      <description>Whale investor @ParallelAiRev created a new account to trade $PUMP, once again becoming the most profitable $PUMP trader on the weekly leaderboard. He just closed his $PUMP long, realizing another $1.78M in profit. He has earned a total of $3.37M on the $PUMP.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27403</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Transaction Data: Federal Reserve Losing Rate Control, 30-Year Treasury Yield Rises to 5%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27402</link>
      <description>September 2nd: The Kobeissi Letter released its latest market analysis indicating that the Federal Reserve will implement the first interest rate cut in 2025 within 15 days. However, the 30-year U.S. Treasury bond yield is currently approaching 5.00%. As the market absorbs the impact of the Fed&apos;s rate cut, interest rates are on the rise. Currently, there is a 90% chance of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Federal Reserve on September 17th. The market anticipates a 50-basis-point rate cut in 2025, and the likelihood of a total of 75 basis points in rate cuts this year is as high as 34%.Nevertheless, today the U.S. Treasury bond yield has soared, with the 30-year Treasury bond yield rising to 5%, a level equivalent to that during the largest financial crisis in U.S. history in 2008. While the market is gearing up for rate cuts, interest rates are actually increasing. The U.S. deficit spending is out of control, and the Federal Reserve is losing its grip on interest rates, issuing more</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27402</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol: XP Point Fix Program Deployed, Correcting Points Missed Over the Past Few Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27401</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, Bio Protocol announced an XP Distribution Update. This was due to a significant increase in stakers, which led to backend timeouts and an uneven distribution of points. The team has now implemented a fix, and today&apos;s distribution has been successfully completed. The team will reprocess all operations to address any point discrepancies from the past few days, ensuring that all XP is accounted for.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27401</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 600 Economists Call for Defending Federal Reserve Independence, Co-sign Open Letter in Support of Powell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27400</link>
      <description>September 2nd: After U.S. President Trump attempted to dismiss Federal Reserve Board Governor Lisa Cook due to suspicion of mortgage fraud, a significant number of prominent economists have expressed support for her. Nearly 600 economists have signed an open letter in favor of Cook, indicating that the bar for removing a Federal Reserve Board member is extremely high, and elected officials should refrain from taking actions that undermine the Fed&apos;s independence. The open letter was released on Tuesday and its signatories encompass Nobel laureates Claudia Goldin and Paul Romer, the former chair of the Obama administration&apos;s Council of Economic Advisers Christina Romer, as well as Ohio State University professor Trevon Logan, who co-authored a paper with Cook. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOMI experienced a brief surge after being listed on Binance Spot, reaching $0.66 before retracting to the current price of $0.44.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27399</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, Somnia (SOMI) saw a brief spike after being listed on Binance&apos;s spot trading. It reached $0.66 and is currently trading at $0.44. The current market capitalization is $70 million, and the fully diluted market capitalization is $450 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27399</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicStrategy Announces $40 Million Investment Commitment from Sonic Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27397</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, the Canadian listed company SonicStrategy Inc. (with the code on the Canadian Securities Exchange: SPTZ) announced that it has received a $40 million investment commitment from Sonic Labs. The investment will be delivered and convertible debt instruments will be issued within 5 working days. This funding is planned to be used for expanding the team, promoting product development, and accelerating market expansion.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27397</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will adjust the SOMI U Index Perpetual Futures Contract&apos;s minimum price movement.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27398</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, as per an official announcement, Binance is going to adjust the minimum price movement of the SOMIUSDT U perpetual contract at 23:45 (Beijing time) on September 2, 2025. It will be changed from 0.001 to 0.0001.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27398</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Ethena Moves Closer to Protocol Fee Sharing Plan, USDe Supply Reaches All-Time High of $12.43 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27396</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, in the past month, the supply of USDe has witnessed a remarkable 42% surge and reached a historical high of $12.43 billion. The protocol revenue has also attained its highest level since the start of the year, exceeding $61 million in August. Currently, USDe ranks as the third-largest USD stablecoin, trailing only behind USDT and USDC. Additionally, Ethena has emerged as the fifth-largest DeFi protocol in terms of deposit size. The current market attention is centered on Ethena&apos;s fee conversion plan, where ENA governance token holders are soon to have the first opportunity to receive a portion of the protocol&apos;s profit.Ethena Labs had previously set three milestones that need to be fulfilled before the activation of the protocol&apos;s fee switch:- The circulating supply of USDe needs to surpass $6 billion.- The protocol&apos;s cumulative revenue needs to reach $250 million.- The USDe token must be integrated into four of the top five centralized exchanges in terms of deriv</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27396</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot Gold Breaks $3,510/Ounce, Hits Another All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27395</link>
      <description>On September 2nd, spot gold broke through $3510 per ounce, reaching a new all-time high. (Golden Ten)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27395</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>