<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:00:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 06:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Holdings Applies to Launch XRP and Bitcoin Investment ETF in Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23361</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the Japanese financial services company SBI Holdings submitted applications for two cryptocurrency-related Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). The first fund is a Cryptocurrency ETF that will directly invest in XRP and Bitcoin. The second fund is a Digital Gold Crypto ETF that will combine gold-backed securities and digital assets, with more than 50% of the funds allocated to gold ETFs. (BeinCrypto)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23361</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean company fanC collaborates with Initech to pilot test the Korean Won stablecoin KRWIN.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23360</link>
      <description>On August 6th, as per The Korea Economic Daily, the South Korean digital token developer and issuer fanC has formed a partnership with the local financial software company Initech to carry out a trial operation of a South Korean won stablecoin. The stablecoin, named KRWIN, is pegged at a 1:1 ratio to the South Korean won. This marks the first instance where a private entity has issued a digital asset based on the South Korean won with the potential for real-world economic applications. fanC declared that this issuance is a demonstration version intended to test the technical feasibility of KRWIN, including its transferability and practical applications. The issuance will be restricted to internally selected members and partner platforms for evaluation. Once KRWIN is officially launched, it is anticipated to be utilized in domains such as payments, global remittances, and tourism.Last month, fanC submitted a trademark application for KRWIN and its associated technology to the South Ko</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>glassnode: Current Bitcoin Fragility Increasing, Its Structure Still Susceptible to External Negative Factors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23359</link>
      <description>On August 6th, glassnode presented a market report indicating that as the market is retesting the low liquidity range beneath the $114,000 threshold, the frenzy phase of Bitcoin is coming to a pause, and the market is experiencing a period of readjustment. Signals from various market sectors all suggest that the market momentum is cooling off, with a cautious holding attitude and a reduced risk appetite. The reasons for this are mainly as follows:1. The spot market has weakened significantly, with the RSI dropping from 47.4 to 35.8, breaking through its low range, indicating that the market is entering the oversold territory.2. The open interest in the futures market has decreased from $45.6 billion to $44.9 billion, suggesting a mild position unwinding.3. The ETF market net inflows have decreased by 24.9% to $269.4 million, which is well below the low range, indicating weak institutional demand.In conclusion, the market has shifted from prosperity to reassessment. With oversol</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23359</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConsenSys CEO Hints at Linea TGE Date with &quot;42&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23358</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the co-founder of Ethereum and the CEO of ConsenSys, Joseph Lubin, participated in the Linea podcast event the previous day. When it came to the community&apos;s most urgent question about the specific TGE date of Linea, he said, &quot;I think 42 is the answer to that.&quot;Furthermore, during the podcast, Joseph Lubin and others also disclosed that ConsenSys may introduce more tokens, and Linea holders may benefit. After the LINEA token is issued, the staking function may also be opened, and multiple utilities are currently in progress.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23358</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has officially become one of the first partners of the Global Dollar Network, accelerating PayFi&apos;s innovative deployment globally.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23357</link>
      <description>On August 6th, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Gate announced its formal membership in the Global Dollar Network (GDN), becoming one of the first-tier partners and continuously promoting the adoption of stablecoins and PayFi innovation. In this cooperation, Gate has completed the integration of the USDG stablecoin issued by Paxos Digital Singapore and Paxos Issuance Europe. It is now supported on the Ethereum, Solana, and Ink blockchains, bringing a compliant and transparent stablecoin usage experience to Gate&apos;s 34 million global users.Dr. Han, the Founder and CEO of Gate, stated: &quot;This partnership reflects Gate&apos;s consistent dedication to compliance innovation and the development of digital asset infrastructure. USDG will play a crucial role in driving the next generation of global payments, transactions, and PayFi applications.&quot;The Global Dollar Network is one of the fastest-growing stablecoin ecosystems globally. Its rapid growth also highlights the critical role of stableco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23357</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitBridge is transforming into a Bitcoin Reserve Company and will launch a Bitcoin-backed Loan Program</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23356</link>
      <description>August 6th. As per The Block, BitBridge Capital Strategies is set to commence trading under the stock ticker BTTL by the end of the third quarter and intends to list on Nasdaq subsequently. In contrast to other Bitcoin financial companies, BitBridge&apos;s sole concentration is on expanding the Bitcoin economy, establishing a robust Bitcoin reserve, and leveraging Bitcoin as a strategic asset to drive long-term shareholder value.BitBridge also announced the launch of its Bitcoin Respect Loan program, which is a loan product formulated to &quot;redefine how the financial system regards Bitcoin collateral.&quot; The company stated that, based on its perception of Bitcoin as a long-term stable monetary asset, it has designed a low-interest, multi-year loan program that has the potential to generate sustainable annual revenue for BitBridge.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23356</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: The total holdings of ETH by 64 Ethereum treasury entities have surpassed 3 million coins, representing approximately 2.52% of the total supply.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23355</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to the data of StrategicETHReserve, as of now, there are a total of 64 reserve strategy entities/companies of Ethereum holding more than 100 ETH. The total holdings of this group have exceeded 3 million ETH, reaching approximately 3.04 million ETH, accounting for about 2.52% of the total supply of ETH, with a value of approximately $10.87 billion.Among them, the top three entities in terms of ETH holdings are Bitmine (833,100 ETH), SharpLink Gaming (521,900 ETH), and The Ether Machine (345,400 ETH).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23355</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABCDE Co-founder Du Jun: Ethereum Expected to Rise to $20,000 This Cycle</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23354</link>
      <description>On August 6th, Du Jun, a co-founder of ABCDE, stated in a social media post that &quot;The three core elements of a public blockchain are decentralization, liveness, and security. Except for Bitcoin and Ethereum, no other public chain can simultaneously meet all three conditions. Based on this, it is anticipated that the price of Ethereum will reach $20,000.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23354</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Market Watch: Solana On-Chain DeepSeekAI, SPARK New Coin Climbing; Base Chain Blue Chips ZEN, Billy, and Others Emerging</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23353</link>
      <description>On August 6th, according to GMGN data, in the &quot;Hot&quot; sector on the Solana chain, the top five tokens in terms of market capitalization within the past 6 hours are Fartcoin, DeepSeekAI, USELESS, TROLL, and SPARK. It should be noted that DeepSeekAI and SPARK have been listed for less than 24 hours, which poses relatively higher risks. Therefore, please trade with caution.On the other hand, on the Base chain, in the &quot;Next Blue Chip&quot; sector within the past 6 hours, the top five tokens in terms of market capitalization are ZEN, XTTA, Billy, SPARK, and BOSS. Tokens in this sector have a short listing time and an unstable trading volume. Please be aware of the risks.BlockBeats reminds users that many Meme coins lack practical use cases and have significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23353</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland, Abraxas Capital continue to accumulate over 44,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23352</link>
      <description>August 6th. Based on The Data Nerd&apos;s monitoring, 10 hours ago, Cumberland withdrew 36,918 ETH from Coinbase (around $132.86 million).4 hours ago, Abraxas Capital kept on accumulating 7,191 ETH from Binance (about $25.97 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>