<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:56:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market Crypto Stocks in US Stock Market Experience Downtrend, WLFI Treasury Company&apos;s ALT5 Sigma Plunges by 12.47%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27684</link>
      <description>On September 4th, based on market data, the pre-market trading of cryptocurrency stocks in the US was generally in a downtrend. This includes:American Bitcoin (ABTC), a mining company supported by the Trump family. It surged by 16.52% on its first day of listing yesterday, but is currently down by 8.6% in pre-market trading.WLFI Treasury&apos;s ALT5 Sigma (ALTS) saw a sharp drop of 12.47%.Coinbase (COIN) is up by 0.02%.Circle (CRCL) is up by 0.8%.MicroStrategy (MSTR) is up by 0.1%.Bullish (BLSH) is down by 1.3%.Bitmine (BMNR) is down by 0.96%.BTCS (BTCS) is down by 1.3%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) is down by 2.2%.BNB Network Company (BNC) is down by 1.3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27684</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance has announced that the Gata (GATA) airdrop distribution is now complete, with trading to commence shortly.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27683</link>
      <description>September 4th. According to official channels, Binance has declared that the Gata (GATA) airdrop has been completed and the token&apos;s display and trading will commence shortly.Previously in the news, Binance Alpha is set to list Gata (GATA), with Alpha trading scheduled to begin on September 4, 2025, at 18:00 (UTC+8). After the start of trading, users who hold at least 220 Binance Alpha points can claim 500 GATA tokens through an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27683</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bitcoin is expanding its Bitcoin mining operation from 10 EH/s to 24 EH/s.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27682</link>
      <description>September 4th. As per market information, American Bitcoin (stock code ABTC), a mining company with the support of the Trump family, is going to expand its Bitcoin mining operation from 10 EH/s to 24 EH/s, representing a 2.4-fold increase.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27682</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum&apos;s Net Staking Inflow Surpasses Net Withdrawal Outflow, Reaching a New High Since September 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27681</link>
      <description>September 4th. Based on the data from the Validator Queue Tracker website, the staking entry queue of the Ethereum PoS network exceeded the exit queue today. The current entry queue is 833,000 ETH, with an approximate value of $36.6 billion, while the current exit queue is 823,000 ETH, with an approximate value of $36.2 billion.It is worth noting that there has been a substantial increase in the staking demand from new validators on the Ethereum PoS network, reaching the highest level since September 2nd, 2023, at 860,000 ETH.BlockBeats Note: The line chart data is accurate as of yesterday.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27681</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: No Reason to Doubt High-Yield Staking, Interest Subsidized by Corporate Profits</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27680</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Justin Sun responded to the inquiries regarding the &quot;Huobi HTX High-Yield Financial Product&quot; as follows:Similar to the popular instant rewards (free lunch) in the current industry, the high-yield interest rate is 100% subsidized by the group. This is essentially done to compete for users among trading platforms. The subsidy logic is also very straightforward: user growth leads to trading volume growth, which is worthwhile in the long run.Huobi HTX is still in the early stage of growth and will consider other factors after increasing asset immersion.The Merkel Tree proof has been released for nearly 34 months, ensuring fund transparency.The current group has an annual profit of tens of billions of US dollars. Therefore, no one should question our ability to subsidize, right?Finally, Justin Sun stated that there is no reason to question the Huobi HTX demand deposit financial product as funds can be withdrawn directly.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Foundation-backed accelerator, Solaris, launches second batch admissions</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27679</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the Solana Chinese community Solar, the developer education platform HackQuest, and Sonic SVM jointly launched the second season of the Solaris Accelerator. This accelerator is officially supported by the Solana Foundation and is intended to provide systematic growth and resource support to entrepreneurial teams in the Chinese-speaking community. Offline events will be held in Singapore, Shenzhen, Hong Kong, and other places.In the first season projects in 2025, a total of 7 teams graduated successfully, and 4 of them received follow-up funding. The second season will take place from September to December and will focus on supporting early-stage projects in areas such as the Internet Capital Market, Artificial Intelligence, and Payments.Mentors for this season&apos;s accelerator include the Solana Foundation Chairperson Lily Liu, the Jupiter co-founder Siong, the Backpack co-founder Cansun, the Kamino founder Mark, the Bybit Spot Head, the Byreal founder Emily, as well</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27679</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit is set to launch the NODE U Perpetual Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27678</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Bybit is going to launch the NODE U coin-margined perpetual contract.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27678</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha announces delay of the Gata (GATA) airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27677</link>
      <description>September 4th. According to official channels, Binance has declared a postponement of the Gata (GATA) airdrop. The specific distribution time will be announced at a later date.Previously, Binance Alpha was set to list Gata (GATA), and Alpha trading was scheduled to commence on September 4, 2025, at 18:00 (UTC+8). After trading begins, users who hold at least 220 Binance Alpha Points will be able to claim 500 GATA tokens through an airdrop. The first come, first served principle applies.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27677</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Burned 220M $BGB($1.09B) and Locked 220M $BGB($1.09B).</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27676</link>
      <description>In a major update for $BGB, 220M $BGB($1.09B) has been burned, and another 220M $BGB($1.09B) has been transferred to a new wallet for locking. This comes as Bitget (@bitgetglobal) and Morph(@MorphLayer) announce an exclusive strategic partnership.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27676</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeline: Powell Signals Rate Cut, Trump Seeks Fed Control</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27675</link>
      <description>September 4th: Following Powell&apos;s interest rate cut signal on August 22nd, Trump aimed to exert control over the Fed with the following chronological sequence:Powell&apos;s Attitude Shift:On August 22nd, at the Jackson Hole Symposium, Powell released a &quot;rate cut signal&quot; by citing a &quot;shift in the risk balance&quot;, which led to the probability of a rate cut in September rising from 75% to approximately 90%.Fed Governor Cunliffe Dismissed:On August 22nd, the same day as Powell&apos;s speech, Trump once again issued a threat to fire Fed Governor Cunliffe.On August 26th, Trump dismissed Fed Governor Cunliffe with immediate effect. A few hours later, Cunliffe responded, stating that there was no reason for his dismissal and he would not resign.On August 27th, a Fed spokesperson stated that Cunliffe still remained a Fed governor and could participate in the rate decision until a ruling was made.On August 28th, Cunliffe sued Trump over his dismissal from the Fed b</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27675</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>