<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:54:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun Makes Appearance at TRON.Inc Rebranding Bell-Ringing Ceremony, Initiating a New Chapter in the Integration of the Cryptocurrency Market and Traditional Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21722</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, was invited to participate in the opening bell ringing ceremony of the Nasdaq Stock Exchange as a strategic advisor of TRON.Inc to celebrate the official renaming of the Nasdaq-listed company TRON.Inc (stock code: TRON). In June of this year, the predecessor of TRON.Inc—Nasdaq-listed SRM Entertainment announced plans to launch a maximum $210 million TRON enterprise treasury strategy and rename it to Tron Inc. On July 16th, SRM Entertainment was officially renamed Tron Inc, and the stock ticker symbol on Nasdaq was changed from &quot;SRM&quot; to &quot;TRON&quot; effective July 17, 2025. This series of capital operations indicates that the integration of crypto assets with the traditional financial system is entering a new stage.Justin Sun stated: &quot;I am extremely proud to announce to everyone that TRON (TRX) has been strategically reserved by a Nasdaq-listed company. I believe that this is not only a significant milestone for TRON.Inc but also an important m</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21722</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise: Since mid-May, ETP has purchased 2.83 million ETH from publicly traded companies, representing 32 times the Ethereum network&apos;s newly minted supply.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21720</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Bitwise sent out a tweet stating, &quot;From mid-May onwards, ETPs (Exchange-Traded Products) and publicly traded companies have purchased a total of 2.83 million ETH together. Meanwhile, the Ethereum network has only issued 89,000 ETH.&quot;This indicates that the demand is 32 times the supply. This is precisely the reason why the ETH price has seen a significant surge.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Conner: The future price increase of ETH is expected to come from the global adoption of stablecoins, rather than corporate treasuries embracing it</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21721</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Eric Conner, a former Ethereum core developer, stated that &quot;in the next few years, the future price growth of Ethereum (ETH) actually does not depend on the adoption of &apos;treasury companies&apos;. The real bull market logic lies in the global adoption of stablecoins. People all over the world are eager to obtain USD exposure, and this demand will experience explosive growth. In this process, tens of billions of people may come into contact with and get to know Ethereum.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21721</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameSquare has acquired CryptoPunk #5577 from the founder of Compound in a $5.15 million USD private stock purchase.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21719</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the NASDAQ-listed company GameSquare announced that its board of directors has given the green light to the purchase of CryptoPunk #5577 from Robert Leshner, the co-founder of the DeFi protocol Compound and the CEO of Superstate. According to the acquisition agreement, GameSquare issued preferred shares worth $5.15 million to Robert Leshner. These preferred shares can be converted into approximately 3.4 million shares of GameSquare common stock at a price of $1.50 per share. This acquisition represents GameSquare&apos;s first direct investment in NFTs.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21719</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tron Inc. rang the opening bell at Nasdaq today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21718</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Tron Inc. (with the Nasdaq symbol: TRON) (hereinafter referred to as the &quot;Company&quot;), a pioneering and innovative enterprise at the convergence of blockchain, entertainment, and digital assets, rang the opening bell at the Nasdaq Stock Exchange today.This ceremony took place at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York City. It was presided over by Justin Sun, the founder of the TRON blockchain and the global advisor of Tron Inc. This event marks an important milestone for the company in its journey towards the next generation of technology and digital innovation.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21718</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine has increased its market stock issuance to 4.5 billion dollars to buy more Ethereum</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21717</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Bitmine Immersion (BMNR) raised the scale of its &quot;At-The-Market&quot; (ATM) program from $2 billion to $4.5 billion. The company submitted a prospectus supplement filing to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on July 24th, authorizing the continuous sale of common stock in the public market through two brokers, Cantor Fitzgerald and ThinkEquity. This additional issuance will supply funding for the company to further augment its ETH holdings and expand its asset reserves.Previously, it was reported that Bitmine updated its ETH holdings. As of 11:59 PM EDT on July 23, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing time today), Bitmine held a total of 566,776 ETH, with a value of over $2 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21717</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: On-chain data shows that BTC has formed a low-density buy zone in the $110,000 to $117,000 range, potentially serving as a strong support area.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21716</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Glassnode put out a post saying, &quot;The rapid ascent of BTC from $110,000 to $117,000 created an &apos;air pocket&apos; or a low-density accumulation zone on the blockchain. Since Bitcoin surged to a historical high of $122,600, the price has stayed above this range. If this support is broken through, history shows that such gaps may still develop into a bottom-building zone.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21716</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market Opens, Dow Down 0.52%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21715</link>
      <description>On July 24th, when the U.S. stock market opened, the Dow dropped by 0.52%, the S&amp;P 500 increased by 0.14%, and the Nasdaq rose by 0.37%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21715</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Falls 8.9%, Marking Its Largest Decline Since June 5</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21714</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Tesla (TSLA.O) declined by 8.9%, which marked its largest drop since June 5th.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21713</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Trump posted on Truth Social and said, &quot;Everyone is suggesting that I will annul Musk&apos;s substantial subsidies from the U.S. government, thereby ruining his company. This is completely untrue. I desire Musk, as well as all our nation&apos;s companies, to flourish. In fact, they are prospering like never before. The better they perform, the better America performs, and this is beneficial to all of us. We are setting records every day, and I hope this trend will continue.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21713</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>