<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Spot Gold Hits $3400/oz Upwards</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26663</link>
      <description>August 28th, spot gold rose and touched $3400/oz on the upside, with an intraday increase of 0.08%. (Oriental Wealth)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26663</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 12 hours, two whale addresses have increased their holdings by 175,130 HYPE tokens, with a total value of approximately $8.47 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26661</link>
      <description>On August 28th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, within the past 12 hours, two whale addresses have accumulated a total of 175,130 HYPE tokens. The total value of these tokens is approximately $8.47 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26661</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guotai Junan International Officially Launches Cryptocurrency Trading Service</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26662</link>
      <description>August 28th. According to Ming Pao, Guotai Junan International has officially initiated cryptocurrency trading services. Once clients open a crypto account, they are able to trade various coins such as BTC, ETH, AVAX, LINK, and SOL. Clients with professional investor qualifications can further make a choice to trade XRP, USDT, USDC, and other coins. In addition, clients can utilize Guotai Junan Securities (Hong Kong) securities trading services to allocate idle funds that have not been invested in the cryptocurrency market to Guotai Junan International&apos;s &quot;Wealth Management Plan.&quot; Guotai Junan International intends to introduce more advanced digital asset services in the future.On June 24th, Guotai Junan International announced that its parent company, Guotai Haitong Group, through its subsidiary Guotai Junan International Holdings Limited (Stock Code: 1788.HK), officially received approval from the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission on June 24th. This approval enables</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26662</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will open airdrop distribution today at 18:00 UTC, with a threshold of 230 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26660</link>
      <description>Update: Binance will commence the Binance Alpha airdrop claim process on August 28th at 18:00 (UTC+8). Users who hold at least 230 Alpha Points will be qualified to claim the airdropped tokens on a first-come, first-served basis. The specific airdropped token has not been announced yet.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26660</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX DeepThink: Global Liquidity Supporting Bitcoin&apos;s Strength, Core Inflation May Disrupt Markets Again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26659</link>
      <description>August 28th. Chloe (@ChloeTalk1), who is a columnist for HTX DeepThink and a researcher at HTX, pointed out in her analysis that by the end of August, the global M2 money supply of major economies reached approximately $95.116 trillion, hitting a historical high. Short-term liquidity remained loose, providing strong support for the Bitcoin price. At the same time, institutional concentration continued to rise. Bitcoin ETF holdings exceeded 1.3 million coins, and MicroStrategy added 430 BTC to its reserves again, indicating that institutional demand for allocation remained strong.Looking ahead to this week, macroeconomic data will be a core variable in market pricing. On August 28th, the revised US GDP for the second quarter will be released. Market expectations may be revised down from the initial 3.0% to 2.4%. The core PCE data to be announced on August 29th is regarded as a key inflation indicator before the Fed&apos;s September interest rate meeting. If the core PCE exceeds expectation</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26659</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strive CEO: Plans to Purchase Over $700 Million Worth of Bitcoin After IPO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26658</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Matt Cole, the CEO of Strive Funds, declared that they intend to purchase more than $700 million worth of Bitcoin following their going public.On May 27th, Strive announced the accomplishment of a $750 million private equity financing at a subscription price of $1.35 per share. There is an opportunity to expand this financing to $1.5 billion through warrants. Strive will concentrate on deploying a &quot;superior Bitcoin yield&quot; strategy portfolio. The financing will be utilized for acquiring biotech companies, distressed Bitcoin debt (such as claims related to Mt. Gox), and discounted structured Bitcoin credit products in order to build its Bitcoin reserve treasury.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26658</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Surges Past $215 to Hit Nearly 206-Day High, SOL/BTC and SOL/ETH Exchange Rates Continue to Strengthen</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26657</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on HTX market data, SOL successfully broke through $215 for the first time since February 4th, establishing a new high that has lasted for nearly 206 days. It witnessed a 24-hour increase of 6.8%. This breakthrough triggered a short liquidation of $26 million.Recently, the SOL/BTC and SOL/ETH exchange rates have been on the rise. In the past month, SOL/BTC has increased by over 28.35%, and in the past week, SOL/ETH has risen by over 8.6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26657</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-share Listed Company Highweida Explores Business Cooperation with Stablecoin RWA System Construction</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26656</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Gaorong Capital. In order to actively explore new technological fields and industrial opportunities and promote cooperation related to the construction of the RWA system for stablecoins, recently, its wholly-owned subsidiary Gaorong Information Technology Co., Ltd. has entered into a contract with Digital Asset Clearing Services Limited and subscribed for 0.50% equity interest at a cost of $250,000 to deeply participate in stablecoin and RWA technology services. (Soochow Securities)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Teams Up with BitGo to Launch Go Network OTC Settlement, Making Institutional Trading Safer and More Efficient</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26655</link>
      <description>August 28th. Gate has successfully completed the integration with Go Network&apos;s Off-Chain Settlement (OES). This enables institutional clients to benefit from Gate&apos;s abundant liquidity while ensuring the secure custody of their assets in BitGo Singapore Pte. Ltd.&apos;s licensed and insured cold wallet. With this integration, institutional investors can directly trade on the Gate platform without having to hold their assets on the exchange, thereby streamlining operations and safeguarding funds.This collaboration has introduced a trading structure that closely follows traditional financial models, achieving separate custody and trade execution operations, which significantly reduces systemic risk. The partnership between Gate and BitGo has provided institutional investors with a variety of trading products such as spot, margin, and perpetual contracts. Through automated settlement processes, operational friction and risk have been minimized to the greatest extent possible. This initiative</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26655</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Brazil Plans to File Tariff Complaint with U.S.; BTC Faces Next Resistance at 114,000, Support at 109,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26654</link>
      <description>August 28th: On August 28th, the Brazilian Finance Minister Ad?es might have filed a lawsuit in a U.S. court against the 50% tariff imposed by the U.S. government and warned against the weaponization of the U.S. dollar. This action has intensified U.S.-Brazil tensions and sparked discussions on de-dollarization, becoming a variable in emerging market fund flows and risk appetite.In terms of the cryptocurrency front, the BTC settlement heatmap shows 114,000 aggregated settlements and orders, posing a significant pressure point; the upper resistance is at 116,800; with support below at 112,000 and between 109,500 and 110,000.Bitunix analyst&apos;s suggestion: This event belongs to a long-term legal and policy game, and its short-term impact on liquidity is limited. The key still lies in the trend of the DXY and the pace of tariff implementation. If the &quot;weaponization of the U.S. dollar&quot; dispute heats up and settlement diversification spreads, it will be favorable to the BTC medium-to-long</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26654</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>