<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:35:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun&apos;s Response to Being Blacklisted: The address in question was only used for small-scale testing and was not involved in any buying or selling.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27771</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Justin Sun responded on social media regarding the incident of &quot;World Liberty blacklisting Justin Sun&apos;s address and freezing 5.4 billion unlocked tokens and 24 billion locked tokens&quot;. He stated, &quot;Our address only carried out a few general exchange deposit tests with very low amounts, and then conducted an address dispersion. There was no buying or selling involved, and it could not have any impact on the market.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27771</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI briefly surged by nearly 10% before pulling back, with a current market cap of $4.418 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27770</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on HTX market data. Possibly due to the &quot;WLFI Blacklists Justin Sun&apos;s Address&quot; news, WLFI witnessed a short-term surge of nearly 10% and then retraced. Currently, its market cap is $4.418 billion.World Liberty has placed Justin Sun&apos;s address on a blacklist, seizing 540 million unlocked tokens and 2.4 billion staked tokens. They declared that they believe a certain exchange has been continuously selling user tokens in an attempt to suppress the price.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27770</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Blacklists Justin Sun Address</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27769</link>
      <description>September 5th. Based on on-chain data, World Liberty has placed Justin Sun&apos;s address on a blacklist, immobilizing 540 million unlocked tokens and 2.4 billion staked tokens. They claimed that they think a certain exchange has been continuously selling user tokens in an attempt to suppress the price.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27769</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s &quot;Big Three&quot; Official Williams: Timely Rate Cut Is Appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27768</link>
      <description>On September 5th, the President of the New York Fed, Williams, stated that he anticipates that a rate cut will become &quot;appropriate in due course.&quot; However, he did not specify the timing or pace of such an action. Williams said on Thursday in remarks prepared for the New York Economic Club event: &quot;Looking forward, if our dual-mandate goals continue to be achieved in accordance with my baseline outlook, I expect that over time, a shift to a more neutral policy stance will be appropriate.&quot; Williams pointed out that the Fed is facing a &quot;subtle balance&quot; in terms of risks to employment and inflation.He said: &quot;On one hand, we need to maintain a balanced labor market to ensure that the impact of tariffs does not spread to a more persistent and widespread inflation. On the other hand, adopting a stance of &apos;being overly tight for too long&apos; could pose a risk to our maximum employment mission.&quot; He also stated that so far, the impact of tariffs on inflation has not been as severe as initially expe</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Previously Minted 2 Billion USDT Moved Chain Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27767</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Paolo Ardoino, the CEO of Tether, responded to a &quot;Whale Alert&quot; tweet from 1 hour ago which claimed that Tether had minted 2 billion USDT on the Ethereum blockchain. He stated, &quot;Binance has transferred 2 billion USDT from the Tron chain to the Ethereum chain as a replacement.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27767</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump family-backed crypto projects WLFI and ABTC both dropped over 20% today.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27766</link>
      <description>September 5th: The cryptocurrency projects World Liberty Financial (WLFI) and American Bitcoin (ABTC), which are endorsed by Donald Trump, both witnessed a more than 20% decline today. WLFI dropped by 24% and ABTC by 21%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27766</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripe-Backed Payment Blockchain Tempo Launched on Private Testnet Incubated by Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27765</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to official channels, the payment public chain Tempo incubated by Stripe and Paradigm has launched its private testnet. Tempo is engineered for stablecoins and real-world payments, with the intention of offering low fees, support for transferring and paying gas fees in any stablecoin, optional privacy features, and a throughput of over 100,000 transactions per second (TPS).The first batch of partners encompasses Anthropic, Coupang, Deutsche Bank, DoorDash, Lead Bank, Mercury, Nubank, OpenAI, Revolut, Shopify, Standard Chartered Bank, Visa, and several other entities.Tempo&apos;s use cases span across global payments, salary disbursement, embedded financial accounts, fast and low-cost cross-border remittances, 24/7 settlement of tokenized deposits, micropayments, intelligent contract-based payments, and more. Tempo is constructed on Reth and is compatible with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27765</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether and Circle have collectively minted stablecoins worth $12 billion in the past month.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27764</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as monitored by LookOnChain, Tether minted an additional 2 billion USDT 36 minutes ago. Within the past month, Tether and Circle have collectively minted a total of $12 billion worth of stablecoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27764</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Senate is expected to release the latest market structure legislation draft as early as today.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27763</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Crypto journalist Eleanor Terrett reported that &quot;There is a rumor that the U.S. Senate Banking Committee will soon release the latest market structure legislation today, which reflects the feedback from the public consultation before the August recess.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27763</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Williams: If the economy performs as I expect, interest rates are expected to be gradually lowered</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27762</link>
      <description>On September 5th, William from the Federal Reserve stated that if the economy operates as I anticipate, I anticipate that rates will gradually decline. Tariffs may lead to a 1.00% to 1.50% increase in inflation this year. The unemployment rate is expected to rise to approximately 4.5% next year. Thus far, tariffs do not appear to have pushed up long-term inflation. The inflation rate is expected to be 3% to 3.25% by 2025. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27762</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>