<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 05:22:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 05:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches ETH Community-wide Lottery Event, with Individuals Having the Chance to Win up to 30 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24524</link>
      <description>August 14th. Bitget has initiated an ETH Carnival Lucky Draw event. Both new and existing users are eligible to participate and share the rewards. During the event, users can acquire a lucky draw chance by fulfilling corresponding contract trading volume tasks. New users can have up to 8 draws, while existing users can have up to 7 draws. The greater the number of draw attempts, the higher the likelihood of winning the grand prize, with a maximum individual reward of 30 ETH.This event has a low entry barrier with a 1000 USDT contract trading volume. Once the task is completed, 1 draw qualification will be unlocked, and the winning rate is 100%. The total prize pool includes rewards such as ETH, JD E Cards, USDT, and more. All event rewards will be automatically credited to users&apos; accounts without the need for manual claiming.The detailed rules have been released on the Bitget official platform. Users can click the &quot;Join Now&quot; button to sign up and participate in the event. The event</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 05:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24524</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Briefly Falls Below $123,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24523</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin briefly fell below $123,000 and is currently trading at $123,084.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 05:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24523</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The WLFI OTC price is currently at $0.3, with a 24-hour trading volume exceeding $1.56 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24522</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on the market data of Whales Market, the OTC price of WLFI is currently at $0.3. The 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.56 million, and the total trading volume exceeds $30 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 05:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24522</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address withdrew 3606 ETH and 1.41 million WLD, with a total value of approximately $18.56 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24521</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, a newly established wallet made a withdrawal of 3,606 ETH (approximately $17.06 million) and 1.41 million WLD (approximately $1.55 million) 8 hours ago. The total value of this withdrawal is approximately $18.56 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24521</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Smart Money went 2x long on SOL 1 hour ago, with a position value of over $13.5 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24520</link>
      <description>Update, August 14th: Based on on-chain data, Whale Wallet X initiated a 2x long position on SOL on Hyperliquid more than an hour ago. The position value exceeded $13.5 million, with an entry price of $207.83. This address also holds 3x long positions on SUI and XRP.This address has amassed over $5 million in profits on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 210,924 LINK from Binance in just under 2 hours, totaling $5.05 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24517</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale transferred 210,924 LINK from Binance, with a value of $5.05 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24517</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Suffers ~$300K MEV Exploit Due to Misconfiguration in 0x Swapper Interaction</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24519</link>
      <description>August 14th. As per Venn Network security researcher deeberiroz, Coinbase has disclosed that it suffered a loss of approximately $300,000 in token fees to an MEV bot due to a misconfiguration in its swapper contract with the decentralized exchange protocol 0x. The contract, which was originally designed for transaction execution, was not supposed to receive token approvals. After Coinbase made a mistake and approved it, the bot triggered the contract to transfer the tokens from Coinbase&apos;s fee account.Coinbase&apos;s Chief Security Officer, Philip Martin, confirmed the incident and stated that the problem originated from an adjustment to the enterprise DEX wallet and did not affect customer funds. The team has revoked the approval and transferred the funds to a new enterprise wallet. (The Block)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24519</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azuki has partnered with the renowned watch brand Henry Mule to launch the co-branded commemorative watch Elements of Time, which is linked to a physical asset-backed token.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24518</link>
      <description>August 14th. As per official channels, Azuki has made an announcement regarding a collaboration with the Swiss luxury watch brand H. Moser &amp; Cie. This collaboration is to launch a co-branded commemorative watch known as Elements of Time. The information on the official website indicates that the Pioneer Centre Seconds series consists of four styles that represent fire, earth, water, and lightning, with each priced at $25,000. Additionally, the Pioneer Tourbillon is priced at $75,000.It is reported that this watch series is linked to Physical Blockchain Tokens (PBT), merging Swiss watchmaking art with blockchain technology and opening up a novel approach to collection, proving provenance, and experiencing future things.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24518</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guizhou Provincial Commission for Discipline Inspection in China Debunks Rumor of Female Official &quot;Mining 327 Bitcoins&quot;: It Was AI-Generated by Self-Media</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24516</link>
      <description>August 14th. An employee from the Publicity Department of the Guizhou Province Discipline Inspection Commission informed &quot;China Newsweek&quot; that the news suggesting that Jing Yaping, the former Director of the Guizhou Provincial Big Data Development Administration, used government servers to mine 327 bitcoins is &quot;a rumor&quot;. According to the source, Jing Yaping&apos;s case has nothing to do with Bitcoin.The above-mentioned employee pointed out that this news was originally fabricated by some self-media using AI (Artificial Intelligence) in an attempt to attract traffic. Later, it was reported by a media outlet, and relevant departments have already been in communication regarding this matter.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24516</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Chess Championship: OpenAI o3 Dominates to Win, Musk&apos;s Grok Shut Out in the Final</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24515</link>
      <description>On August 14th, last week, OpenAI&apos;s o3 model triumphed over xAI&apos;s Grok 4 in an artificial intelligence (AI) chess competition and emerged as the champion. The &quot;AI Chess Exhibition Match,&quot; which was held on Google&apos;s subsidiary Kaggle platform, saw eight AI models engage in a three-day elimination tournament to determine the champion, runner-up, and third-place finishers.In this competition, the AI models were required to play chess without any specific training and were only allowed to gather some chess knowledge from the internet prior to the match. In the final, OpenAI&apos;s o3 defeated Grok 4 with a score of 4-0, claiming the championship. It is notable that o3 won all three matches with a perfect 4-0 score and also swept its sibling o4 mini in the semi-finals.Earlier this year, in another tournament hosted by chess master Levy Rozman, both Grok and ChatGPT lost to the AI system Stockfish, which is specifically designed for chess.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24515</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>