<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:41:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The probability of a Fed rate cut in September has dropped to 75%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26009</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to the &quot;FedWatch Tool&quot; of CME, there is a 75% chance (down from 84.7% yesterday) that the Fed will cut rates by 25 basis points in September, and a 25% chance of keeping rates unchanged.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26009</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI Pre-market Price Drops Over 45% in Nearly 20 Hours, Currently Trading at $0.238</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26008</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to HTX market data, the pre-market trading price of WLFI (World Liberty Financial) continued to decline and dropped below $0.24. It is currently trading at $0.238, with a continuous drop of more than 45% in nearly 20 hours.According to Coinglass data, the total open interest of WLFI futures contracts is currently $1.93 billion, and the 24-hour trading volume is $19.4 billion. The current global aggregated long/short ratio is 0.9474.BlockBeats previously reported that the Trump family project World Liberty Finance (WLFI) is scheduled to be launched on Ethereum on September 1st, with open claiming and trading. Early supporters (at $0.015 and $0.05 rounds) will unlock 20%, and the remaining 80% will be determined by community vote. Tokens for the founding team, advisors, and partners will not unlock. Trading will start at 8:00 PM on September 1st Beijing time, and the 20% token claiming will begin.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Adjusts WLFIUSDT Perpetual Contract Gradient Tier Rule</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26007</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to an official announcement, OKX will make adjustments to the WLFIUSDT perpetual contract gradient tier rule on August 24, 2025, from 4:00 PM to 10:00 PM (UTC+8) in order to further enhance market liquidity.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26007</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The BTC network&apos;s daily transaction fee has recently dropped to around 4.09 BTC, marking the lowest coin-based level since late 2011.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26006</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on Glassnode data, the daily transaction fee on the BTC network has recently plummeted to approximately 4.09 BTC, reaching the lowest level denominated in coins since late 2011.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26006</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hut 8 Mining Corp Updates Equity Sales Plan, Aims to Raise $1 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26005</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Hut 8 Corp., a publicly traded Bitcoin mining company in the US, refreshed its At-The-Market (ATM) equity program. The goal is to raise up to $1 billion through stock sales. This new plan supersedes Hut 8&apos;s previous $500 million ATM program, which was set to expire in December 2024. Earlier in this week, the company started construction on a $2.5 billion artificial intelligence data center in West Feliciana Parish, Louisiana.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26005</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jup Studio&apos;s ecosystem meme coin Uranus has surpassed a market capitalization of $52 million, with a 12% price increase in the last 24 hours.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26002</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to the GMGN market data, the ecosystem meme coin Uranus of Jup Studio has a market capitalization exceeding 52 million US dollars. It has seen a 12% increase in the past 24 hours and a 24-hour trading volume of over 6.4 million US dollars.BlockBeats reminds users that the prices of meme coins are highly volatile, and users should invest cautiously.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26002</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Copy Trading Launches Customizable Copy Mode Size</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26004</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as per official information, Binance Futures copy trading users are now able to customize their copy trading position mode. The new features encompass:- Only replicate when the entry price is more favorable;- Replicate all existing positions;- Only replicate new positions.This update is being progressively rolled out on the website and app and will be fully implemented in the coming days.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26004</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>许正宇: Hong Kong Stablecoin Offers No Speculative Opportunities, Aims to Enhance Economic Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26003</link>
      <description>August 24th. According to Radio Television Hong Kong, Christopher Hui, the Secretary for Financial Services and the Treasury of Hong Kong, stated that the positioning of Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin is distinct. It is designed as a means of settlement and is another form of legal tender, with no speculative elements. He cautioned the public to be careful. Hui further mentioned that the cost of payment through the banking system can reach as high as 3%, while the cost of using a stablecoin is expected to be as low as 1%, which can help reduce cross-border payment costs and enhance economic efficiency.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 08:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26003</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum PoS Exit Queue Continues at High Levels, with Approximately $41.6 Billion USD worth of ETH Queued for Exit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26001</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website ValidatorQueue, the current exit queue of the Ethereum PoS network is temporarily reported to be 870.3k ETH and remains at a high level. Calculated at the current price, approximately $41.6 billion worth of ETH is exiting the PoS network, and the withdrawal delay has been extended to 15 days and 3 hours.Meanwhile, the staking demand for newly activated validators has slightly decreased. Today&apos;s admission queue is 143k ETH, worth about $683 million, with a current queuing time of 2 days and 12 hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26001</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: ETH Transaction Share Reaches This Cycle&apos;s Peak, ETH/BTC Exchange Rate Still Undervalued</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26000</link>
      <description>August 24th. In a post, on-chain data analyst Murphy stated that the transaction platform traffic share of ETH is calculated by taking the ratio of the USD value of ETH and BTC flowing in and out of all trading platforms, which represents the percentage of ETH. This is also a key indicator for measuring which of the two mainstream crypto assets, ETH or BTC, is receiving more attention or support from funds. On August 15th, ETH&apos;s traffic share reached as high as 48% (as indicated by the red curve in the chart), marking the highest point in this cycle so far. This ratio means that nearly half of the funds flowing in and out of the trading platforms are in ETH, almost on an equal footing with BTC, indirectly confirming the current market&apos;s high interest in ETH.If we compare nearly 10 years of this data with the ETH/BTC exchange rate curve (as shown by the blue curve in the chart), we can observe that the red and blue lines are highly synchronized. The logic is: when more funds begin to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 07:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>