<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:16:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>An address shorting ETH at 15x leverage increased their short position by 1424 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23532</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to the monitoring of Hyperinsight, a certain contract whale address has just increased its short position by 1,424.37 ETH, which is equivalent to $5,338,241. Currently, the overall ETH position of the whale is in an unrealized loss of $93,000. Its current ETH short position is valued at $18,440,000 (with a 15x leverage), and the average entry price is $3,678.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23532</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMNI Surpasses $4.8, 24h Change +26.4%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23531</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to HTX market data, OMNI has surpassed $4.8 and is currently priced at $4.83, with a 24-hour increase of 26.4%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23531</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Within 24 hours of its launch, Pendle&apos;s funding rate trading platform Boros saw its first parameter adjustment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23530</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per an official announcement, Pendle&apos;s newly launched funding rate trading platform, Boros, went live for just 24 hours. Based on market activity, the platform made its first key parameter adjustment:- The open interest (OI) cap on the BTC/USDT trading pair on Binance was raised from $10 million to $15 million.- The BTC vault limit was increased from $26,000 to $40,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23530</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with at least 200 Alpha Points can claim a 1000 X Token airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23529</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per official channels, the trading of TaleX (X) on Binance Alpha is set to commence on August 7, 2025, at 11:00 (UTC). After the trading starts, users who possess at least 200 Binance Alpha points will be qualified to receive a 1000 X token airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis. In case the reward pool is not completely distributed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour. It should be noted that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points. Users must confirm the claim on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours; otherwise, it will be regarded as a waiver of the claim.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23529</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: INFINIT (IN) Airdrop Threshold 200 Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23528</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to an official announcement, Binance Alpha and Futures will list INFINIT (IN). The opening time for Alpha Trading is August 7, 2025, at 17:00 (UTC+8). The opening time for Futures Trading is August 7, 2025, at 18:30 (UTC+8). After the trading begins, users holding at least 200 Alpha Points can claim a 500 IN token airdrop. It&apos;s first come, first served until the airdrop pool is exhausted or the event comes to an end.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Chip Tariff Exemption Conditions News Released, Technology and Blockchain Intersecting Focus, Suggests Keeping an Eye on AI Race Coins Support and Rotation Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23527</link>
      <description>On August 7th, US President Trump announced a 100% tariff on imported semiconductor products. There is an exemption for companies committed to building factories in the US, which benefits Apple (AAPL) and several other tech giants. Apple and CEO Cook simultaneously unveiled a $100 billion US manufacturing investment plan to expand their domestic supply chain layout. This move has been regarded by the market as Trump&apos;s policy of &quot;using tariffs to force fund repatriation&quot; being specifically carried out.In the crypto market, cryptocurrencies related to AI, computing power, and decentralized supply chains have witnessed capital replenishment. Although the overall crypto market has not yet broken out of its consolidation phase, the market remains highly sensitive to the themes of AI infrastructure and US manufacturing.Bitunix Analyst&apos;s Recommendation:This event reinforces US policy control over the tech supply chain and indirectly benefits AI and high-performance computing themes. Tra</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23527</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UK-based gold mining company ECR Minerals has announced that it will pursue a Bitcoin strategic reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23526</link>
      <description>On August 7th, as per @btcNLNico, the UK gold mining company ECR Minerals declared the implementation of a Bitcoin treasury strategy. The company is going to utilize up to 50% of its remaining cash and the free cash flow from gold production to purchase BTC and hold it for the long term.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23526</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Surpasses $3700 Again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23525</link>
      <description>On August 7th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum once more surpassed $3700 and is now trading at $3700.23, with a 24-hour percentage change of 0.94%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23525</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Firm: Hacker Disguises Rug Pull Contract as Crypto Trading Bot, Spreading It Through YouTube Video</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23524</link>
      <description>On August 7th, the cybersecurity firm SentinelLabs declared that it had uncovered a series of cryptocurrency scams. In these scams, hackers employed a malicious smart contract that was disguised as a trading bot to spread and pilfer funds from cryptocurrency wallets.The hackers utilized YouTube videos for marketing purposes. The videos elaborated on the nature of the cryptocurrency trading bot and demonstrated how to deploy the smart contract on the Remix Solidity compiler platform, which is a web-based Web3 project integrated development environment (IDE). The video instructions contained a link to an external website hosting weaponized smart contract code. Furthermore, the attackers took charge of the YouTube comments section and removed all negative comments.Once victims deployed the smart contract, the attacker&apos;s wallet was added and concealed behind a disguised transaction address. After users transferred funds into the contract, the scammers were able to abscond with the fund</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23524</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese fashion brand ANAP has increased its BTC holdings by 82.33 coins, bringing its total holdings to approximately 913.45 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23523</link>
      <description>On August 7th, according to an official announcement, the Japanese fashion brand ANAP Holdings revealed that it had increased its holdings by approximately 82.338 BTC and was currently holding a total of approximately 913.45 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 06:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23523</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>