<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:58:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>《Ming Pao》: JD.com has registered &quot;JCOIN&quot; and &quot;JOYCOIN,&quot; expected to be the names of its stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22261</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to Ming Pao, the Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation is set to come into effect in August. Local media referred to a registration document suggesting that JD.com&apos;s JD Coin Chain has registered &quot;JCOIN&quot; and &quot;JOYCOIN&quot;, with some noting that these names are likely the designations of its stablecoins.As per the registration document mentioned in the report, the services associated with &quot;JCOIN&quot; and &quot;JOYCOIN&quot; involve providing electronic fund transfers and cryptocurrency financial transactions via blockchain technology.JD Coin Chain is one of the Stablecoin Issuers participating in the sandbox of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority. In July of the previous year, it collaborated with Stardust Bank, a local virtual bank supported by companies such as Xiaomi and Futu, to explore a novel enterprise cross-border payment solution based on stablecoins within the sandbox.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22261</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX DeepThink: Policy Maneuvering Meets Earnings Season, Crypto Market&apos;s Short-Term Direction May Soon Become Clear</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22260</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the HTX Researcher Chloe pointed out in the latest edition of HTX DeepThink that during this week&apos;s Bank of Japan interest rate decision, the core PCE data closely watched by the Federal Reserve, and the earnings reports of multiple US tech giants will jointly influence the short-term direction of global risk assets.Currently, Japanese inflation is stabilizing, and the market is observing whether it will adjust its interest rate hike path. If the policy coordination between the US and Japan strengthens, it may stabilize the Asian foreign exchange market structure and indirectly boost the liquidity in the East Asian cryptocurrency market. The activity of users on the platforms in Hong Kong and South Korea is worthy of attention. The US non-farm payroll data (NFP) released on Friday is regarded as the &quot;key macroeconomic indicator.&quot; If employment growth slows in line with wage growth, it will provide support for the Fed&apos;s future shift to a rate cut.At the same time, the</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22260</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list IKA and TREE perpetual contract trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22259</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to official sources, Gate is scheduled to list IKA perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT) at 18:10 (UTC+8), with support for 1-20x leverage. Additionally, it will list TREE perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT) at 22:10 (UTC+8), also providing support for 1-20x leverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22259</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin surpasses $120,000, the mainstream CEX&apos;s total short liquidation volume will reach 1.04 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22258</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to data from Coinglass, if Bitcoin breaks through $120,000, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.04 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin falls below $117,000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $784 million.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the asset price will be affected when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that once the price reaches that level, it will experience a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22258</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Breaks $119,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22257</link>
      <description>On July 29th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin exceeded $119,000, and the 24-hour price change was -0.42%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22257</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet has received 3500 BTC from Gemini in the past 3 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22256</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet has received 3,500 BTC from Gemini within the past 3 days. The total value of these BTC amounts to 4.1567 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Co-Founder: SharpLink Aims to Accumulate ETH Faster than Other Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22255</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per Cointelegraph, Joe Lubin, the co-founder of Ethereum and CEO of Consensys, is one of the Ethereum Treasury Strategists at SharpLink Gaming. He anticipates that the company can amass Ethereum (ETH) for its shareholders as promptly as feasible, raising the &quot;battle cry&quot; during the corporate rush to become the foremost ETH accumulator.Joe Lubin declared: &quot;We hold the view that, on a per-share (fully-diluted) basis, our rate of ETH accumulation will outstrip that of any other Ethereum project and definitely be quicker than Bitcoin-related projects. SharpLink is accumulating funds &apos;daily&apos; through a market-price-based issuance mechanism to augment its ETH reserves, while staking existing holdings to earn rewards and achieve compound growth.&quot;SharpLink is vying with BitMine for the status of &quot;Ethereum Treasury Premier Company.&quot; According to the data from StrategicETHReserve, BitMine currently leads, holding 566,800 ETH with a market value of approximately $2.13 billion,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22255</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFX Surpasses $0.24, Up Over 29% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22254</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to HTX market data, CFX exceeded $0.24 and is currently priced at $0.2427, with a 24-hour increase of more than 29%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22254</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoPunks Floor Price Surpasses $200,000 Mark for the First Time in Over a Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22253</link>
      <description>July 29th. As per Decrypt, since August of the previous year, the floor price of CryptoPunks has been on a continuous upward trajectory, increasing from 20.45 ETH to 53.98 ETH, which represents a 163% growth. Given the current Ethereum price of approximately $3,745, the floor price of CryptoPunks has exceeded $200,000 and reached its highest point since March 8, 2024. This upward trend commenced with a large-scale &quot;buying spree&quot; last week when an address made a single transaction to purchase 45 CryptoPunks.According to CoinGecko data, the total market value of the NFT market has witnessed a significant surge, rising from $3.6 billion in early July to $6.8 billion. Historical data indicates that when Ethereum shows strong performance, it often leads to an increase in the prices of leading NFT projects on its blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22253</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Family&apos;s cryptocurrency project WLFI bought 256.75 ETH 20 hours ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22252</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, 20 hours ago, the crypto project WLFI of the Trump family spent 1 million USDC to purchase 256.75 ETH at an average price of $3,895 per ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22252</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>