<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Listed Company CDT Equity Approves Cryptocurrency Reserve Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27564</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Nasdaq-listed company CDT Equity Inc. (with the ticker symbol: CDT) announced today that its board of directors has given the green light to the adoption of a cryptocurrency reserve strategy. The plan is to convert a certain portion of its balance sheet into digital asset holdings. This action is intended to diversify the company&apos;s capital structure and offer investors with long-term strategic and financial advantages. Meanwhile, CDT is collaborating with Sarborg to develop a proprietary multi-agent AI system, which will be used for real-time cryptocurrency market analysis, automated trade execution, and asset rebalancing optimization.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27564</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webus has signed a strategic cooperation agreement with Air China, initiating member access and introducing a future XRP payment solution.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27565</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the AI-driven Mobility Solution Provider Webus International Limited (Webus or the Company, with the Nasdaq code: WETO) announced today that it has entered into a strategic cooperation agreement with the international major airline Air China Limited. Air China has more than 60 million PhoenixMiles members worldwide. Through this collaboration, Webus&apos;s travel brand Wetour will offer airport transfer and high-end customized driver services to Air China&apos;s global passengers and members.Wetour plans to provide Air China&apos;s PhoenixMiles members with access to its overseas platform and support for XRP payments. This will enable travelers to enjoy faster settlement, tokenized rewards, and blockchain-supported credentials. These credentials will be directly linked to membership benefits, and the specific implementation will be based on future business development and compliance with regulations.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27565</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Booster Program Phase 2 Project Reveel is now live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27563</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Binance Wallet declared that the second stage of the Booster Plan for the project Reveel has become active:· Participate in the second stage to share 5 million REVA rewards.· Binance users with 61 or more Alpha Points are eligible to take part.Important Notice: Tokens acquired through the Booster event will be subject to a lock-up period determined by the project team. Therefore, please make sure to understand the relevant restrictions before getting involved.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27563</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust Wallet is launching Tokenized Stocks and ETFs Service</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27562</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Binance&apos;s self-custodial crypto wallet Trust Wallet officially launched tokenized stocks and ETF services in partnership with Ondo Finance and 1inch. This launch initially took place on the Ethereum and Solana blockchains. The move is intended to utilize blockchain technology to allow global users to access traditional financial assets, thereby promoting the openness and inclusivity of the financial market. It is important to note that these RWA tokenized assets are only accessible in specific regions and adhere to U.S. market trading hours.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27562</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot: Mined 477 Bitcoins in August, Sold 450 Bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27561</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the cryptocurrency mining firm Riot Platforms released its operating data for August 2025 today. The company mined 477 bitcoins during the month, achieving a new historical high for August with a 48% year-on-year growth.In August, the company sold 450 bitcoins, resulting in a net revenue of $51.8 million. The average selling price per bitcoin was $115,035. As of the end of the month, Riot held 19,309 bitcoins and had a deployed hash rate of 36.4 EH/s, which represented a 56% year-on-year increase.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27561</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum breaks above $4500, the mainstream CEX cumulative short liquidation pressure will reach $1.316 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27560</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to Coinglass data, if Ethereum surpasses $4500, the total short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will amount to $1.316 billion. In contrast, if Ethereum drops below $4300, the total long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $0.36 billion.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the precise number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what degree reaching a certain price level will have an impact. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that when the price reaches that level, a more intense reaction will occur due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Official Mester Skeptical of September Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27559</link>
      <description>September 3rd. Mester from the Federal Reserve stated that the Federal Reserve has recently maintained its high interest rate stance, which is in line with the recent high inflation and the strong performance of the labor market. She expressed doubts about a rate cut by the Fed at the September meeting.After Federal Reserve Chairman Powell opened the door to a rate cut in a speech last month, a rate cut is now regarded as the default option of the Fed. Mester acknowledged the slowdown in employment growth, but she stated that the labor market still appears solid due to the moderate unemployment rate and the low initial number of jobless claims.On the other hand, she believes that there is still a considerable amount of uncertainty about inflation, especially considering the pressure from tariffs. Nevertheless, traders still widely expect that a majority of Fed members will support a 25-basis-point rate cut in September, with a probability of 90%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27559</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaTON Capital has announced a funding round to acquire $100 million worth of TON tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27558</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, AlphaTON Capital Corp. (&quot;AlphaTON Capital&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;, previously known as Portage Biotech Inc.) (NASDAQ: PRTG, ATON) announced a financing round today. The purpose of this round is to acquire approximately $100 million worth of TON tokens and establish a dedicated digital asset financial company. This company is dedicated to building a strategic TON reserve.AlphaTON Capital is implementing a financial strategy that focuses on acquiring TON, managing network infrastructure, and incubating leading applications within the Telegram ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27558</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaoTian International plans to reallocate the remaining 3.575 billion Hong Kong dollars of the placement funds to Ethereum, with the expectation to fully utilize it within one month.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27557</link>
      <description>September 3rd - The Hong Kong-listed company Haotian International issued an announcement. Previously, through a special authorization, it carried out a placement of new shares, raising a net amount of approximately 492.5 million Hong Kong dollars. The original plan was as follows:72.66% for the development of an Internet data center on Malaysian land.15.68% for general working capital.11.66% for loan repayment.Usage of Funds: As of the announcement date, approximately 135 million Hong Kong dollars had been used for operations and loan repayment. The remaining 357.5 million Hong Kong dollars, which were originally planned for the development of the Internet data center, had not been used yet. The board of directors decided: On September 3, 2025, it was decided to change the purpose of the remaining funds to the purchase of the cryptocurrency Ethereum, with the expectation of fully utilizing them within one month.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27557</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot Gold Surges Above $3550 per Ounce, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27556</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, spot gold exceeded $3550/oz for the first time. It has seen a cumulative increase of more than $925 so far this year. (Oriental Wealth)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27556</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>