<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:01:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Mining Firm Hut 8 Receives $330 Million Credit Support for 1.5GW Capacity Expansion Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26376</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to the report in theminermag, Hut 8 intends to establish four large-scale infrastructure projects in the United States. This will lead to a total capacity increase of 1530 megawatts (MW), as part of its transition from Bitcoin mining to a broader digital infrastructure strategy. These new projects are located in Louisiana, Texas, and Illinois, with capacities ranging from 50 MW to 1000 MW. As a result, Hut 8&apos;s potential pipeline capacity will reach over 10 GW. Once these projects become operational, Hut 8&apos;s managed platform capacity at 19 sites will exceed 2.5 GW.To ensure the implementation of this construction plan, Hut 8 is making use of various financing channels. This includes a new $200 million revolving credit facility with the digital asset investment firm Two Prime and a $130 million credit facility with Coinbase for expansion and repricing purposes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered Bank: Still forecasting ETH to reach $7500 by the end of the year, the past two days have been excellent entry points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26375</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per CoinDesk&apos;s report, Geoff Kendrick, the Global Head of Digital Assets Research at Standard Chartered Bank, stated on Tuesday that at the present price level, Ethereum (ETH) and the ETH Treasury are still undervalued.Kendrick pointed out that since the early part of June, the ETH Treasury has purchased 2.6% of the circulating ETH. When combined with the inflows into exchange-traded funds (ETFs) during the same period, the total amount of ETH purchased by both has reached 4.9% of the circulation, which is a remarkable figure.Although these inflows have been quite substantial, Kendrick emphasized that this is just the start. He had previously expected the Treasury to ultimately hold 10% of the circulating ETH, and this target now appears to be completely achievable.Despite the recent sharp drop in ETH, Kendrick still maintains his earlier prediction that Ethereum will reach $7,500 by the end of the year. He believes that the sell-off below $4,500 in the past two d</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26375</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasma Partners with WildcatFi to Build Global Payment Credit Layer</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26374</link>
      <description>August 26th, as per official channels, Plasma has made an announcement regarding a partnership with Wildcat. This partnership is aimed at jointly constructing a transparent private credit layer that will provide support to the new global financial system. WildcatFi is a credit market that can be customized and has facilitated the issuance of loans amounting to over $165 billion up to now.The collaboration is set to unlock lending models that traditional markets are unable to support. These include short-term financing facilities that enable T+0/T+1 real-time settlement. This will offer crucial support for payment financing, enabling buyers to receive goods before making payment.Plasma intends to drive the development of global payment infrastructure by integrating Wildcat&apos;s credit functionality. This will address the daily financial pain points faced by billions of users. Wildcat will be launched as a day-one partner on the Plasma mainnet test version.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26374</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMask Introduces Social Login Feature to Simplify Wallet Management</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26373</link>
      <description>August 26th: According to official information, MetaMask has declared the launch of social login functionality. This enables users to swiftly create, back up, and restore their non-custodial crypto wallets by using their Google or Apple accounts. During this process, a 12-word mnemonic phrase is generated in the background, thus obviating the need for manual recording and simplifying the conventional wallet management procedure.Users can commence using it through just two steps: logging in with their social account and setting a secure password. MetaMask reminds users that password security is of great importance. In case a password is lost, the wallet cannot be retrieved.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26373</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Fire Technology: Eric Wong Appointed as Executive Director and CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26372</link>
      <description>August 26th. As per an official announcement, Sino-Link Holdings Limited (01611.HK) disclosed that starting from August 26, 2025, Weng Xiaoqi has been appointed as an Executive Director. Du Jun has been reassigned from an Executive Director to a Non-Executive Director. Du Jun has tendered his resignation from the positions of CEO and Authorized Representative, and Weng Xiaoqi has been appointed as the CEO and Authorized Representative.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26372</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Son Invests Millions in Polymarket</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26371</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to the report of AXIOS, Donald Trump Jr., the son of former President Trump, invested tens of millions of dollars in Polymarket.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26371</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale has deposited 968 BTC into Hyperliquid, and is currently selling and exchanging it for ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26370</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as monitored by LookOnChain, 30 minutes ago, a particular Bitcoin ancient whale deposited 968 BTC into Hyperliquid (approximately $106.44 million), and is currently in the process of selling BTC to purchase ETH spot.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26370</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Media &amp; Technology Group has acquired $105 million in CRO and will stake it through Crypto.com</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26369</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per the report from Blockworks, Trump Media &amp; Technology Group announced a strategic partnership agreement with Crypto.com. This is advancing their collaboration through a parallel collaboration and purchase agreement.Under the terms of the agreement, Trump Media will adopt Crypto.com&apos;s wallet system to upgrade their in-app rewards program. Users will be able to convert their earned &quot;gems&quot; into Cronos (CRO) tokens, which can then be used to pay for subscription fees. Additionally, opening a Crypto.com account will offer free or discounted Truth+ subscriptions.Trump Media &amp; Technology Group signed a $155 million strategic partnership agreement with Crypto.com. The group has purchased approximately $105 million worth of CRO, which is about 685 million tokens. These tokens will be held and staked through Crypto.com. Furthermore, Crypto.com has acquired $50 million in common shares from Trump Media &amp; Technology Group. Both parties&apos; holdings are subject to a lock-up p</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26369</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Rises 4.36% in Pre-market Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26368</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on market data, the stock of Trump Media &amp; Technology Group (DJT.O) surged by 4.36% at the market opening and is now trading at $17.96.Previously reported, Yorkville Acquisition Corp., Trump Media &amp; Technology Group, and Crypto.com announced that the three parties have signed a definitive agreement to establish a digital asset treasury company, Trump Media Group CRO Strategy, Inc., which is focused on acquiring the native cryptocurrency token (CRO) of the Cronos ecosystem.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary Submits TRUMP ETF&apos;s S-1 Filing to the SEC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26367</link>
      <description>On August 26th, according to market information, Canary has presented the S-1 application document for the TRUMP ETF to the US SEC.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26367</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>