<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:28:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Linea: Native Yield Farming will be launched in the coming months, bridging ETH for automatic staking on the mainnet</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23181</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Linea made an announcement. In the forthcoming months, it is going to launch native staking and bridge Linea&apos;s ETH to Lido v3 for automatic staking on the Ethereum mainnet. The staking rewards that are generated will flow back into the Linea ecosystem and be distributed to liquidity providers. This will support liquidity programs and amplify rewards.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23181</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle Network is launching an end-to-end comprehensive SDK to create a universal transaction layer for RWAs, stablecoins, and digital assets.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23180</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Particle Network made a post on social media, and it announced the launch of an end-to-end universal Software Development Kit (SDK) to establish a transaction layer for RWAs (Real World Assets), stablecoins, and digital assets. Circle was designated as the first batch of cornerstone partners.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23180</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos Labs: Aave&apos;s $4.7B Exposure to Ethena Could Trigger &quot;Liquidity Crunch&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23179</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as reported by DL News, Chaos Labs, Aave&apos;s risk advisor, stated that with the continuous increase in the deposit amount of the US dollar-pegged token USDe in the protocol, Ethena&apos;s USDe stablecoin may pose a threat to Aave&apos;s robustness and trigger a liquidity crunch. In a post released on Saturday on the Aave governance forum, Chaos Labs discussed the potential risks of Aave&apos;s exposure to Ethena, which has been on the rise. Chaos Labs pointed out that when USDe holders deposit a large amount of the token into Aave and its issuer Ethena simultaneously lends out the stablecoin backing that asset, a significant risk is formed. Ethena must avoid overallocating its stablecoin reserves to Aave. Self-imposed limits on such exposure help ensure redemption reliability and market stability. Ethena has not responded immediately to a request for comment.Ethena has deposited $580 million of USDe-backed assets into Aave through a strategy known as rehypothecation. In addition, Aave&apos;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23179</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An investor spent $22,800 to buy 27.86 million TROLL tokens three months ago, and is currently enjoying a profit of over 100x.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23178</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a trader spent $22,800 three months ago to acquire 27.86 million TROLL tokens. Subsequently, the trader sold 1.28 million TROLL tokens for $162,000 and currently still holds 26.57 million TROLL tokens, which is valued at $2.48 million.With the recent surge in the price of TROLL, his position has achieved a more than 100-fold unrealized gain, and the profits are close to $2.48 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23178</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit Mid-Year Review: CEO Ben Recaps Key Events of the First Half of the Year, Invites Community to &quot;Reshape the Future&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23177</link>
      <description>On August 4th, the cryptocurrency exchange Bybit is set to host an exclusive live stream on August 6th at 8 a.m. UTC with Co-Founder and CEO Ben Zhou.This live stream, titled &quot;Shaping the Future&quot;, will allow Ben to review Bybit&apos;s multiple industry-first achievements by 2025 and disclose the company&apos;s latest efforts in enhancing security and innovation.Key highlights:- Bybit&apos;s H1 2025 Report Card: Platform breakthroughs and the redefinition of the user CeDeFi experience.- Ecosystem Growth: Spot innovation, unique wealth management solutions, regulatory breakthroughs, product innovation, and cross-regional ecosystem expansion.- Offline Community Engagement: Bybit&apos;s Summer European and Asian roadshows and events.- Technology and Vision: Ben will explore how blockchain technology is seamlessly integrated into the real world and how, through the power of the community, the industry&apos;s digital asset standards are jointly reshaped.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 03:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23177</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address swapped 1,562.7 ETH for 49.39 WBTC 3 hours ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23176</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the address 0xd47...0562e exchanged 1,562.7 ETH for 49.39 WBTC (approximately $5.81 million) three hours ago. At the time of the swap, the price of ETH was $3,721 and the price of BTC was $114,627.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 02:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somnia has launched the Foundation&apos;s Twitter account</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23175</link>
      <description>On August 5th, the gaming and entertainment blockchain project Somnia announced that the foundation has initiated the opening of an official Twitter account.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 02:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23175</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: ETH Long Position Take Profit Reached</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23174</link>
      <description>On August 5th, trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio announced in his personal channel that he had realized profits from his long position in ETH.Previously, on August 2nd, Eugene stated that he &quot;had once again taken a long position on ETH. The bullish sentiment in August was hyped up prematurely by the market, but $113,000 BTC and $3,500 ETH still represent reasonable entry points. The stop-loss is set below $112,000 and $3,400. Although the hype regarding Data Availability Technology (DAT) may gradually wane, there is still significant structural buying in the current market, so it is not advisable to quickly shift to a bearish outlook.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 02:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23174</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shitcoin Season Index Rebounds to 43</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23173</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per Coinmarketcap data, the Altcoin Season Index has gone up to 43. It had dropped to 34 on August 1st. This index indicates that among the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, approximately 43 projects have outperformed Bitcoin in the past 90 days.Note: The CMC cryptocurrency Altseason Index is a real-time indicator employed to determine whether the current cryptocurrency market is in an altcoin-dominated season. This index is based on the performance of the top 100 altcoins relative to Bitcoin over the past 90 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 02:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23173</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「3963 BTC Ancient Whale HODLer Dormant for 14.5 Years」 transfers out 108 BTC Again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23172</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;ancient whale that had been dormant while holding 3963 BTC for 14.5 years&quot; transferred 108 BTC to an address affiliated with Wintermute, which was worth approximately $12.42 million.10 hours ago, they recharged 0.001 BTC into the Wintermute Deposit address for a small-scale test or a possible upcoming sale. Currently, this ancient whale still holds 3360 BTC in their wallet, approximately $385 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 02:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23172</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>