<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:41:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink CEO: Satoshi Nakamoto Could Return When Bitcoin Faces Quantum Computing Threat</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28055</link>
      <description>On September 7th, according to Decrypt, since Bitcoin&apos;s creator Satoshi Nakamoto left his last message in 2011 stating &quot;I&apos;ve moved on to other things,&quot; he has remained unidentifiable. However, Joseph Chalom, the Co-CEO of SharpLink Gaming, has put forward a &quot;bold theory&quot;: if Bitcoin faces a survival threat from quantum computing, Satoshi Nakamoto may make a reappearance.Some experts think that quantum computing could bring a &quot;survival crisis&quot; to Bitcoin in the next decade. The Bitcoin community has started to discuss how to make the network quantum-resistant. Some have proposed achieving quantum resistance through a hard fork, while others have suggested freezing the Bitcoin held by Satoshi Nakamoto that is vulnerable to quantum attacks.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28055</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: September Interest Rate Cut Likely, Options Traders Expect Stock Market to Remain Stable</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28054</link>
      <description>September 7th. Given that a rate cut by the Federal Reserve in September is almost a certainty, options traders generally anticipate that the stock market will trade steadily on Thursday prior to the release of CPI data. Nevertheless, if the data indicates an increase in inflation, this bet may conceal latent risks. The underlying logic for the market&apos;s expectation of a rate cut is quite straightforward: U.S. job growth has come to a standstill, and the economy requires stimulation. The weak employment data on Friday further reinforced this expectation, prompting investors to fully absorb the anticipated 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed next week. The market&apos;s response to this was muted: U.S. stocks edged lower on Friday, the fear index inched up but still remained well below the crucial level of 20 and mostly stayed below this level since June.Looking ahead, options traders are wagering that the S&amp;P 500 index will witness around a 0.7% two-way fluctuation after Thursday&apos;s CPI rele</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28054</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll: Trump Approval Rating at 43%, Lowest Approval for Handling Inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28053</link>
      <description>On September 7th, a poll jointly carried out by the NBC News Decision Desk and the survey platform SurveyMonkey indicated that the overall approval rating of U.S. President Trump is 43%, while 57% of the respondents expressed disapproval of his performance in office. Regarding economic issues, inflation and the cost of living are the ones that most concern the public. Only 39% of the respondents approved of his handling of inflation. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28053</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cathie Wood: Current Unemployment Rate Exceeds Prior Cycle Peaks of 2008-2009, Signaling Rate Cuts Again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28052</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Cathie Wood, the CEO of ARK Invest, tweeted and said, &quot;We anticipate that the productivity-driven prosperity we expect will shorten the duration of unemployment. However, the current unemployment rate is higher than the peak of each cycle before the 2008 - 2009 (crisis). This once again emphasizes the need for interest rate cuts.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28052</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FutureCrest Acquisition, led by Tom Lee, has submitted an IPO application aiming to raise $250 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28049</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Tom Lee, the chairman of BitMine, led a blank check company (SPAC) named FutureCrest Acquisition. They submitted a filing to the U.S. SEC on Friday and planned to raise up to $250 million through an initial public offering (IPO).Tom Lee, who is known in the media for his optimistic views on cryptocurrency, also emphasized his previous Bitcoin price predictions in the IPO prospectus. FutureCrest Acquisition stated that when seeking acquisition targets, the company would leverage the management team&apos;s expertise and social capital in fields such as AI, digital assets, fintech, infrastructure, robotics, and communications. Additionally, the company is optimistic about opportunities in business intelligence, productivity software, and digital health.FutureCrest Acquisition plans to list on the Nasdaq under the stock symbol FCRSU. The company confidentially submitted its filings on August 5, 2025. Cantor Fitzgerald is the exclusive bookrunner for this transaction.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28049</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha and Futures will list Avantis (AVNT)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28051</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Binance Alpha will list and commence trading for Avantis (AVNT) on September 9, 2025, at 21:00 (UTC+8). Furthermore, the Binance Futures platform will initiate the AVNTUSDT perpetual contract on September 9, 2025, at 23:00 (UTC+8), offering up to 50x leverage. All eligible Binance users will be entitled to a token airdrop. Eligible users must claim the airdrop through the Alpha activity page by using Alpha Points between September 9, 2025, at 21:00 (UTC+8) and September 10, 2025, at 21:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28051</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter: JLP Liquidity Pool TVL Surpasses $2 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28050</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Jupiter tweeted, &quot;The TVL of the JLP Liquidity Pool has exceeded 2 billion US dollars.&quot;According to the data on the official website, the current JLP APY is 17.58%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28050</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessant: Job Data Shows Trump&apos;s Criticism of Fed&apos;s Slow Action Was Right</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28048</link>
      <description>On September 7th, US Treasury Secretary Yellen stated that the employment data indicates that Trump&apos;s criticism of the Fed&apos;s slow action was valid. The revised employment projections for 2024 may be reduced by 800,000 jobs. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor once again shares Bitcoin Tracker information, hinting at another BTC purchase.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28047</link>
      <description>On September 7th, Michael Saylor, the founder of Strategy, once again shared information related to the Bitcoin Tracker and stated, &quot;Require more orange.&quot; According to the previous pattern, Strategy always discloses additional Bitcoin purchase information on the second day after such news is released.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28047</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polkadot will release important news tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28046</link>
      <description>On September 7th, the Polkadot team said, &quot;There will be a significant release the day after tomorrow.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 11:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28046</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>