<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:50:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Base Network Experiencing Anomaly: No New Block Generated for Over 27 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23200</link>
      <description>On August 5th, based on Base Browser data, it is possible that the Base network encountered an anomaly where no new blocks were generated for more than 27 minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>《GENIUS Act》 Leads to Surge in Revenue-Sharing Stablecoin Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23199</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to Cointelegraph, since the enactment of the July &quot;GENIUS Stablecoin Act,&quot; the supply of yield-generating stablecoins has witnessed a significant surge. The data indicates that the primary beneficiaries are Ethena&apos;s USDe and Sky&apos;s USDS. Both of these stablecoins can earn yield when staked within their respective protocols.According to DefiLlama data, as of July 18th, the circulating supply of USDe has grown by 70% and reached $9.49 billion, ranking third among all stablecoins in terms of market capitalization. During the same period, the circulating supply of USDS has increased by 23% and reached nearly $4.81 billion, ranking fourth in terms of market capitalization.Anthony Yim, the co-founder of analytics firm Artemis, stated, &quot;Despite the &apos;GENIUS Act&apos; prohibiting the issuance of yield-bearing stablecoins in the United States, the supply of such stablecoins has grown substantially and has become an &apos;unexpected winner.&apos;&quot; Julio Moreno, the Head of Research a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23199</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CIO: Uniswap&apos;s current market cap is undervalued, equivalent to the size of the world&apos;s 400th largest financial services company</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23198</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Matt Hougan, the CIO of Bitwise, said, &quot;Uniswap&apos;s current valuation of $6 billion appears to be too low. If it were a company, it would rank as the 400th largest financial services firm globally, approximately on a par in size with Norway&apos;s savings and insurance company Storebrand.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23198</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B increased its holdings by 62 BTC, bringing the total holdings to 2075 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23197</link>
      <description>August 5th: The European publicly traded company Capital B (formerly known as The Blockchain Group) enhanced its Bitcoin holdings by 62 coins, resulting in a total of 2075 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23197</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Figure to File for IPO, Market Confidence Rebounding but BTC Faces Short-Term Pressure, Recommend Monitoring 112,000 Support</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23196</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Figure Technology Solutions (FTS) quietly submitted an IPO application to the US SEC, emerging as a new entrant in this year&apos;s cryptocurrency industry IPO boom. FTS specializes in blockchain financial infrastructure and has witnessed rapid growth in the HELOC loan and cryptocurrency exchange sectors. This IPO is anticipated to attract the participation of major investment banks like Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan, and is in discussions with institutions such as BlackRock and SoftBank, demonstrating that traditional capital has regained confidence in the cryptocurrency industry.In terms of the cryptocurrency market, the price of BTC has recently retraced from its peak, with trading volume remaining sluggish, indicating that the short-term direction remains uncertain. After a short-term rebound, it has not yet broken through the 115,000 resistance level, with 112,000 serving as the key short-term support.Analysts at Bitunix suggest: The FTS IPO news is conducive to boostin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 06:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23196</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Schiff: September Rate Cut Not Set in Stone, Inflation May Be Higher Than Expected</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23195</link>
      <description>On August 5th, economist and cryptocurrency critic Peter Schiff tweeted and said, &quot;A September rate cut is not a certainty at all. The inflation data released between now and the next Federal Reserve meeting may be higher than anticipated. The fact that the market has risen in the expectation of a rate cut actually makes the possibility of a cut lower. Stronger inflationary pressure will override the impact of the slowing growth in jobs.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 05:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23195</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Updates the US Dollar Stablecoin Accounting Rules Staff Guide, With Some Stablecoins Being Considered as Cash</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23194</link>
      <description>On August 5th, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) updated its staff guidance on stablecoin accounting rules. The key point of the new guidance is that if a stablecoin pegged to the U.S. dollar has a collateralized redemption mechanism and its value stability is pegged to another asset type, it may be classified as &quot;cash equivalent&quot;.While the SEC is formulating broader cryptocurrency regulatory rules, this latest interim guidance is part of Chairman Paul Atkins&apos; efforts to remove restrictive measures. For instance, in April of this year, the SEC clearly stated that a &quot;covered&quot; U.S. dollar stablecoin is not regarded as a security and confirmed that entities engaged in stablecoin issuance and redemption activities do not need to register with the agency for such activities.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 05:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23194</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: The Federal Reserve should adjust its dual mandate target and readjust its monetary policy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23193</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Brij Khurana, the Fixed Income Portfolio Manager of Wellington Management, stated that the Federal Reserve plans to update its statement every 5 years, detailing how it will fulfill its dual mandate of maximizing employment and maintaining price stability. The Federal Reserve last issued this statement during the 2020 COVID-19 pandemic and adopted a framework focusing on a 2% long-term average inflation rate.Later this year, when the Federal Reserve releases its next statement, it should carefully reconsider its dual mandate and adjust its monetary policy to move towards maximizing productivity. Since 2008, the annual growth rate of US productivity has slowed down to 1.6%, which is lower than the 2.4% over the previous 18 years. Placing emphasis on accelerating productivity again will enable the Federal Reserve to achieve its dual mandate goals without unintended negative consequences such as exacerbated income inequality and rising debt levels, both of which dampen pr</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 05:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23193</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Man James Howells Refuses to Give Up Search for Lost 8000 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23192</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per The Block, earlier this week, several posts emerged on social media stating that UK Newport IT engineer James Howells had officially concluded his search for the lost 8,000 BTC. James Howells got in touch with The Block through a private message on the social platform X and said, &quot;No, I haven&apos;t &apos;given up.&apos; Part of the story circulating in the public is true, but it&apos;s not exactly as the story unfolds.&quot;Howells explained that on July 1st, he formally made an offer to the leadership of the Newport City Council, their legal team, and a member of parliament to purchase and excavate the Newport landfill site, with an estimated value ranging from $33 million to $40 million. To raise funds for the acquisition, Howells had announced plans to launch an Ordinal-based token in October representing 21% of the value of the lost wallet. Despite the substantial offer amount, Howells claims that Newport has not responded or acknowledged receiving the offer. So, as things stand no</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 05:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will conduct wallet maintenance for USDC withdrawals on the Ethereum mainnet, Polygon, and other networks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23191</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to official channels, Binance will carry out wallet maintenance for USD Coin (USDC) on Ethereum (ETH), Polygon (POL), Arbitrum (ARB), Base (BASE), and Optimism (OP) at 15:00 (UTC+8) on August 6th, 2025.To facilitate this maintenance, Binance will halt USD Coin (USDC) withdrawals on Ethereum (ETH), Polygon (POL), Arbitrum (ARB), Base (BASE), and Optimism (OP) starting from 15:00 (UTC+8) on August 6th, 2025. The maintenance is projected to last for 2 hours, and withdrawals will resume automatically upon the completion of the maintenance.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 04:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23191</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>