<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 12:26:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 12:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The high-profile ETH whale has once again transferred 2120 BTC to HyperUnit for swapping ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26973</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the highly visible BTC whale that swapped a significant amount of ETH has once again deposited 2120 BTC (valued at $230 million) into HyperUnit for the exchange of ETH, and 1120 BTC is currently still unsold.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26973</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperscale Data is planning to sell common stock to raise $125 million to purchase BTC and XRP</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26972</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per PR Newswire, the U.S. listed company Hyperscale Data (NYSE: GPUS) declared that it had set up a &quot;market issuance&quot; equity issuance plan. The company may from time to time sell its common stock in order to raise a total of up to 125 million U.S. dollars. A portion of the proceeds from this fundraising will be utilized to purchase Bitcoin and expand its Michigan data facility. Another part will be used to purchase XRP. The rest will be allocated for working capital and general corporate purposes, which may include repaying, refinancing, redeeming, or repurchasing future debt or equity.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26972</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI: Protocol governance power will be fully controlled by a multisig during security risks or major adverse events</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26971</link>
      <description>August 30th. As per the official website, World Liberty Financial (referred to as the WLF Protocol) declared in a governance statement that the WLF Protocol or any associated protocols might encounter &quot;significant adverse events,&quot; meaning any event that obstructs the intended and prolonged normal operation of the WLF Protocol or any related protocols. Or it might encounter &quot;security risks,&quot; referring to any event that leads to the cessation of the WLF Protocol&apos;s operation or endangers the security of users utilizing the WLF Protocol.During a period of significant adverse events or security risks, the governance control of the WLF Protocol will be solely in the hands of a multi-signature until the normal governance operations of the WLF Protocol can be restored.Previously reported, the unlocking of the WLFI token is scheduled to officially start at 8:00 AM EST on September 1st, and the relevant functionality page is now available.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26971</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador will distribute its Bitcoin reserve among 14 wallet holders to mitigate potential quantum computing threats</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26970</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per Cointelegraph, El Salvador has redistributed its Bitcoin reserve to 14 new wallet addresses in order to address potential quantum computing threats.The El Salvador Bitcoin Office indicated that by dividing the funds into smaller quantities, the potential impact of a quantum attack can be reduced. Each Bitcoin address can hold a maximum of 500 bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26970</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Macro Outlook: The Fed to Release Beige Book, August Non-Farm Payrolls on the Horizon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26969</link>
      <description>August 30th. During this week, the cryptocurrency market witnessed a notable sell-off. However, this occurred following a solid performance in the previous week. Owing to the reduction in volatility and the upcoming release of key data next week, some relatively weak highs have taken shape. Bitcoin is at risk of a double top and has failed to offer significant defense against its impact. Meanwhile, Ethereum retraced further after reaching a new high last Saturday. Here are the key points that the market will focus on in the new week (all times are Beijing time):Wednesday 21:00, 2025 FOMC Voter, St. Louis Fed President Muli Saleem will deliver a speech on the U.S. economy and monetary policy;Thursday 01:30, 2026 FOMC Voter, Minneapolis Fed President Kashkari participates in a fireside chat;Thursday 02:00, The Fed releases the Beige Book on economic conditions;Thursday 23:30, FOMC Permanent Voter, New York Fed President Williams speaks at the New York Economics Club;Friday 07:0</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26969</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale sold 197 BTC and quickly went short with over $60 million in BTC using 3x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26967</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale disposed of 197 Bitcoins at an average price of $108,398 per Bitcoin (amounting to $21.35 million). Subsequently, it opened a 3x leveraged short position involving 561 Bitcoins (valued at $60.89 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26967</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan Police in China Bust Virtual Currency Investment Blind Date Fraud Case, Arrest 30 Suspects</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26968</link>
      <description>August 30th. According to reports from Huanqiu.com, the Dongxihu Sub-bureau of the Wuhan Public Security Bureau in Hubei Province has taken action against a group that was posing as a tech company to engage in telecom fraud. The individuals involved in this case created a &quot;high-quality blind date female&quot; scenario to befriend others and lured netizens to a fake cryptocurrency investment platform. The police on the scene arrested 30 criminal suspects and seized more than 40 work computers used for fraud, over 50 work phones, more than 100 scripts, packaging materials for personas, and photos.The suspects would send a fake investment website to the victims after winning their trust and entice them to purchase cryptocurrency and invest in the fake platform. The scammers had full control over the profits, but the &quot;withdrawal&quot; process always failed. Currently, 27 individuals involved have been placed under criminal detention, and 3 individuals have been administratively detained. The polic</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address received 1506 BTC, approximately $163.58 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26964</link>
      <description>On August 30th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established address received 1506 bitcoins that were transferred from Galaxy Digital. The value of these bitcoins is $163.58 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26964</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX CEO Star: OKX never raises funds from users, but serves as a technology provider for user Earn.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26966</link>
      <description>August 30th. OKX CEO Star shared on social media that the asset size of OKX Earn has surpassed billions of dollars and generates billions of dollars in revenue for millions of users worldwide every year. OKX has always adhered to a core principle: it never raises funds from users but only serves as a technical service provider for users to earn. It helps users efficiently and conveniently access staking on various chains, various DeFi protocols, and institutional borrowers, enabling users to obtain a stable return safely and conveniently in the blockchain world.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26966</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monetary Authority of Macau, Benjamin Chan: The &quot;Digital Macau&quot; project is scheduled to conduct a sandbox test by the end of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26965</link>
      <description>On August 30th, Alvin Huang, the Acting Chairman of the Administrative Committee of the Monetary Authority of Macau, stated today at the 7th Greater Bay Area Financial Forum that Macau is actively promoting the development of the &quot;Digital Macau&quot; project. It is planned to conduct a sandbox test by the end of the year and strengthen data connection and integration with interbank digital currencies. In the future, the Greater Bay Area and Macau will achieve interconnected data currencies to promote financial innovation and collaborative development. (Oriental Wealth)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26965</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>