<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT: BlockDAG Network as a Scam Project</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25062</link>
      <description>On August 18th, on-chain sleuth ZachXBT took to social media to state that the BlockDAG Network is a fraudulent project or an investment scam. This project has been conducting a presale for more than 1.5 years, claiming that the presale is &quot;about to end soon,&quot; while regularly transferring investor funds to various exchange accounts and using false data for marketing to fuel the retail FOMO sentiment.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25062</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHZilla has officially launched its new brand, with a total holding of 94,675 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25061</link>
      <description>On August 18th, as per official channels, ETHZilla Company (traded on NASDAQ: ETHZ) announced the formal launch of a new brand today. This marks a significant step in the company&apos;s transformation towards an Ethereum strategic reserve. The formerly known 180 Life Sciences Corp will shift its main non-traditional business to establish an Ethereum (ETH) reserve platform that is &quot;owned and served by the community.&quot; Commencing immediately, the company&apos;s common stock and public warrants will trade on Nasdaq under the new ticker symbols &quot;ETHZ&quot; and &quot;ETHZW&quot; respectively. Meanwhile, the original ticker symbols &quot;ATNF&quot; and &quot;ATNFW&quot; will be discontinued simultaneously, and shareholders do not need to take any action regarding this transformation.After successfully completing a $425 million private investment in public equity (PIPE) through common stock and pre-funded warrants, and a $156.25 million convertible note issuance, the company has amassed 94,675 ETH at an average purchase price of $3,902</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25061</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMNR holds 1.26% of the circulating supply of ETH, while the total holdings of 69 companies amount to 3.38%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25060</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on the data from strategicethreserve, BitMine (BMNR) increased its holdings by 373,000 ETH this week. As a result, its total holdings reached 1.52 million ETH, which is approximately 1.26% of the total ETH supply.In total, the 69 companies that hold ETH jointly hold 4.09 million ETH, accounting for approximately 3.38% of the total ETH supply and valued at around $17.43 billion.Furthermore, all ETFs currently hold 6.56 million ETH, which is approximately 5.42% of the total ETH supply and valued at around $27.97 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25060</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Fed&apos;s Talkbox」: Overall PCE inflation rate is expected to be moderate in July, with a year-over-year increase of 2.6%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25059</link>
      <description>On August 18th, Nick Timiraos, a reporter from The Wall Street Journal known as the &quot;Fed Whisperer&quot;, posted on social media. It was stated that economists anticipate that the July core PCE inflation rate will be 0.28% (equivalent to an annual rate of 3.4%) after converting CPI and PPI data to the PCE index. This is expected to result in a year-on-year increase of 2.9%. The overall PCE inflation rate is predicted to be more moderate, with a month-on-month increase of 0.21% and a year-on-year increase remaining at 2.6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25059</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: PLUME Listing Delayed Due to HODLer Airdrop Event Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25058</link>
      <description>On August 18th, Binance posted on social media that they are aware that some users are currently restricted from taking part in the PLUME HODLer airdrop. The team has recognized the problem and is actively working to fix it as soon as possible. As a result, the listing time for PLUME will be adjusted according to the development of the situation.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25058</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine (BMNR) increased its ETH holdings by 373,000 coins last week, bringing the total holdings to 1.52 million ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25055</link>
      <description>On August 18, the US-listed company BitMine Immersion Technologies announced today that the total value of its cryptocurrency holdings exceeds $6.612 billion. As of 11:59 PM EST on August 17, the company holds 1,523,373 ETH (with a unit price of $4,326, sourced from Bloomberg) and 192 BTC.Thomas Lee, the chairman of BitMine and the Fundstrat analyst, stated: &quot;Within a single week, our ETH holdings have increased by $1.7 billion to $6.6 billion (with an additional 373,000 units, increasing from 1.15 million units to 1.52 million units), confirming the support of institutional investors for our &apos;5% Ethereum Strategy.&apos; As we have always emphasized, whether it is the net asset value growth per share of crypto assets or stock liquidity, BitMine is at the forefront of institutional crypto asset holdings.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25055</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet Launches OpenEden Booster Event, Alpha Points Must Be Greater Than 61</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25057</link>
      <description>August 18th. According to official information, Binance Wallet has initiated the OpenEden Booster event. In this event, users can partake in multi-stage tasks and share 20 million EDEN as an airdrop. The first stage offers 5 million EDEN, and those with more than 61 Binance Alpha points are eligible to participate.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25057</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will cease to support Neo Legacy network token deposits and withdrawals</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25056</link>
      <description>On August 18th, according to official information, because the Neo Legacy network is about to be closed, Binance will stop supporting the withdrawal of all tokens through the Neo Legacy network (NEO) starting from October 15, 2025, at 16:00 (UTC).After 16:00 (UTC) on August 25, 2025, any deposits made through the Neo Legacy network (NEO) will not be credited and may lead to asset losses. Except for the Kepple (QLC) token, users can still deposit or withdraw NEO (NEO) and NeoGas (GAS) through other networks.BlockBeats previously reported that Neo officially announced at the end of April this year that it will shut down the Neo Legacy network on October 31, 2025.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroStrategy Increased Its Bitcoin Holdings by 430 Coins Last Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25054</link>
      <description>On August 18th, MicroStrategy purchased 430 bitcoins. The average price per bitcoin during the period from August 11th to August 17th was $119,666. In total, the amount spent was $51.40 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25054</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Powell May Avoid Signaling Ease This Friday, Inflation Rebound Gives Him Reason to Remain Cautious</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25053</link>
      <description>August 18th. The market generally anticipates that the Fed will reduce interest rates by 25 basis points in September. Nevertheless, analysts from HSBC and Bank of America pointed out that although there are weak employment data and they are facing political pressure, Powell may refrain from sending a dovish signal during his speech at the Jackson Hole Symposium this Friday. Worries about stagflation risks and the inflation rebound might be the reasons for him to remain cautious. (Bloomberg)BlockBeats Note: At 10:00 PM on this Friday, Fed Chair Powell will give a speech at the Jackson Hole Economic Policy Symposium.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25053</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>