<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 01:29:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 01:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase and PayPal to Continue Offering Stablecoin Rewards in Response to &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; Regulatory Controversy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23158</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to Decrypt, during last Thursday&apos;s earnings call, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong stated that the company will keep providing holding rewards for USDC to users. He regarded this program as a key differentiator to attract users.Although the &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; prohibits stablecoin issuers from paying interest or returns, Armstrong clarified: &quot;We are not the issuer. It&apos;s not interest that is being paid; it&apos;s a reward.&quot; Currently, Coinbase offers a 4.1% annual percentage yield (APY) on USDC deposits to US users.This act specifically targets issuers like USDC&apos;s issuer Circle and does not prohibit exchanges from providing rewards. A Senate staffer explained that the act aims to prevent stablecoins from being treated as traditional deposit instruments.In addition, PayPal is also following a similar strategy. It offers a 3.7% APY to users holding its stablecoin PYUSD to attract more customers.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 01:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23158</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US SEC Releases Interim Stablecoin Accounting Treatment Guidance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23157</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to Bloomberg, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is building on the foundation of preliminary cryptocurrency accounting rules. It has issued a new staff guidance stating that certain stablecoins can be regarded as cash equivalents.When this interim guidance was released, the SEC was formulating regulatory rules for security tokens. Under the leadership of SEC Chairman Paul Atkins, the Commission has started to gradually revoke some of the more stringent policies, including accounting guidance that was previously considered to be impeding traditional lending institutions from entering the crypto market.According to the latest guidance, holding certain stablecoins pegged to the U.S. dollar, if these stablecoins have a guaranteed redemption right and are value-anchored to another class of assets, can be classified as cash equivalents.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 01:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23157</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ETH Whale with 75% Win Rate in Four Trades] Adds to ETH Short Position, Currently Facing $2.32 Million Unrealized Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23156</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to ChainNews, [Four-time ETH Bear Whale] added 3.32 million USDC as collateral in the early morning, raising its ETH short position to 27,000 ETH (with a nominal value of approximately $100 million).This whale&apos;s ETH short position has gone from having a floating profit of $12.25 million to having a floating loss of $2.32 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23156</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale Activity: A large SOL whale dramatically reduced its short position, realizing a $24 million floating loss; Two addresses deposited a total of $25 million USDC in one day</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23155</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight, there has been a rebound in the market in the past 24 hours. There have been large fund movements in 2 whale addresses, which include:The whale address starting with 0x9324A1 has accumulated a total deposit of approximately 3.91 million USDC.The whale address starting with 0x5b5d51 has accumulated a total deposit of approximately 22.01 million USDC.Regarding derivative holdings: The whale address starting with 0x4a207d2 has changed its 130.45 BTC holdings from a short position to a long position. The liquidation price has dropped from $201,000 to $56,000. During the same period, the short position of SOL at this address has decreased by 121,969.92 coins. The liquidation price has been adjusted to $395.9, and it is currently at a floating loss of $2,422.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23155</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A British Man Abandons Retrieval of Hard Drive Containing 8,000 Bitcoins at a Certain Landfill Site</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23154</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to Cointelegraph, James Howells, an IT engineer from Newport, UK, has concluded a 12-year search without being able to recover what he thinks are 8,000 bitcoins (now valued at approximately $920 million) that were stored on a hard drive buried in a municipal landfill site in South Wales.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23154</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve&apos;s September Interest Rate Cut Probability Soars to 94.4%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23153</link>
      <description>On August 5th, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of the Fed maintaining the interest rate unchanged in September is 5.6%, and the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 94.4%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23153</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaplanet Launches Official Merchandise Online Store PlanetGear</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23152</link>
      <description>August 5th. According to official channels, Metaplanet has declared the formal inauguration of the PlanetGear online store. This store is committed to integrating the philosophy and culture of Bitcoin into modern lifestyle design and launching relevant merchandise.According to the announcement, PlanetGear has selected clothing, accessories, and limited-edition items that reflect the worldview of MetaPlanet and Bitcoin Magazine Japan. It aims to serve as a bridge between Bitcoin culture and daily life.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: White House Prepares to Issue Executive Order Punishing Banks for Discriminating Against Cryptocurrency Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23151</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as reported by The Wall Street Journal, the White House is getting ready to enhance pressure on large banks in reaction to their supposed discriminatory behavior towards conservative individuals and cryptocurrency companies. The White House is devising to issue an executive order that poses a threat of fining banks which refuse to serve customers for political motives.A draft of the executive order that was accessed by The Wall Street Journal shows that the order will instruct banking regulators to conduct investigations into whether any financial institutions have violated the Equal Credit Opportunity Act, antitrust laws, or consumer financial protection laws.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23151</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Adam Weitsman Announces Acquisition of Over 5000 NFTs from Yuga Labs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23150</link>
      <description>On August 5th, the billionaire Adam Weitsman made a post on social media. He said, &quot;I am making a long-term investment in Otherside. I am directly acquiring more than 5000 Otherdeeds, Mega Kodas, and Weapon Kodas from Yuga Labs to continuously enhance my collection. I have also promised to make a series of acquisitions in the open market this year. I will spare no effort to help Othersidemeta achieve success.&quot;Adam Weitsman is an American entrepreneur, investor, and philanthropist. Currently, he serves as the CEO of Upstate Shredding – Weitsman Recycling, which is one of the largest privately owned scrap metal processing companies on the East Coast of the United States, processing over 1 million tons of steel and 25 million pounds of nonferrous metals annually. In 2021, he founded Viridium LLC and entered the cryptocurrency mining field.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23150</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Mobile&apos;s second phone, Seeker, has started shipping, and the native token SKR has not been released yet.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23149</link>
      <description>August 5th. Solana Mobile announced on social media that its second phone, Seeker, began shipping on August 4th, 2025.During this time, the Solana Mobile ecosystem will introduce the native token SKR to provide incentives for developers and users to participate in the development of the mobile Web3 ecosystem. However, the SKR token has not been officially launched yet.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23149</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>