<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:08:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 01:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Abraxas Capital holds a cryptocurrency short position worth over $9.199 billion, currently with a unrealized loss of over $1.066 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27449</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to Arkham&apos;s monitoring, two accounts of Abraxas Capital have taken short positions on the Hyperliquid platform, with a total shorting value of more than $9.199 billion in cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), HYPE, and WLFI. Currently, the loss has exceeded $1.066 billion.The liquidation prices for their Bitcoin were $151,530 and $149,910 respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27449</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIMG Inc. has raised $55 million to acquire 500 Bitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27448</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Business group CIMG Inc. (with Nasdaq code: IMG), which focuses on digital health and sales development, announced that it had completed the previously announced common stock sale transaction on September 2, 2025. The company sold 2.2 billion shares at a price of $0.25 per share, raising a total of $55 million in funds and exchanging this for 500 bitcoins.CIMG&apos;s Chairman and CEO, Wang Jianshuang, stated: &quot;In the future, the company plans to continuously increase its digital asset reserves and seek partnerships with artificial intelligence and the crypto ecosystem.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana-based Meme Coin MITCH Market Cap Surges Past $37 Million, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27447</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on GMGN data, the Solana-based Meme coin MITCH has a market capitalization exceeding 37 million US dollars and is currently at 37.2 million US dollars, reaching an all-time high. The trading volume in the first 4 hours of trading is 26 million US dollars.Mitch (also known as idrawline) posted on his Telegram personal channel, stating that he launched his personal creator token MITCH on Pump.fun. He mentioned that he purchased the entire token supply during the pre-sale phase and additionally invested 20,000 US dollars. Currently, all tokens will be held indefinitely in his wallet god.sol and will not be sold, burned, or locked. He also mentioned that he will focus on live streaming, gaming, and trading in the future and will randomly give away funds during each live broadcast. His main goal is to &quot;have fun.&quot;BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility, and investment should be approached</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27447</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian chain restaurant Tahini’s has announced it will be increasing its Bitcoin holdings.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27446</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Canadian chain restaurant Tahini&apos;s announced last night on the X platform that it has just made a purchase of Bitcoin. However, it did not disclose the specific purchase amount or the holding status. According to Thestreet, Tahini&apos;s has been purchasing Bitcoin since 2020 and has continuously been buying cryptocurrency. Currently, even a Bitcoin ATM has been installed in its restaurant.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27446</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump: WLFI Online Transaction Price Surges Nearly 20x from Initial Launch Price, Market Cap Ranks 27th in Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27445</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Eric Trump, the son of former US President Donald Trump, tweeted, &quot;The initial launch of the WLFI token was completed just 10 and a half months ago, and at that time, the price was $0.015. In the past 24 hours, the trading price of WLFI has fluctuated from approximately $0.20 to $0.28, which is nearly 20 times the initial issuance price (and the trading volume on the first day alone reached around $3.1 billion), pushing us into the top 10 global cryptocurrency assets in terms of trading volume and ranking 27th in terms of market capitalization.&quot;&quot;Yesterday&apos;s public launch is merely the starting point, and the company&apos;s fundamental position in the industry is unrivaled. The future of WLFI is boundless.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27445</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI burned 47 million WLFI from the unlocked Treasury wallet, and has repurchased 649.8 million WLFI.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27444</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, WLFI burned 47 million WLFI ($11.34 million) from the already unlocked treasury wallet 6 hours ago. The official explanation was to commemorate the buyback and burn governance proposal. In addition, after they started trading the day before yesterday, they repurchased 2 million USD1 on-chain with 649.8 million WLFI at a price of $0.308.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27444</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOL Surpasses $210, 24-hour Growth Rate 6.4%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27443</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on HTX market data, SOL has exceeded $210 and achieved a 24-hour increase of 6.4%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27443</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale sold 3819 ETH at an average price of $4286.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27442</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale sold 3,819 ETH at an average price of $4,286 and received 16.37 million USDT in exchange. Among them, 1,500 ETH had been held by the whale for two years. Currently, the whale still holds 308.66 ETH, which is worth $1.33 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27442</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MKR briefly broke through $1800, with a 24-hour price increase of 8.64%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27441</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to HTX market data, MKR briefly went above $1800 and is currently trading at $1739.5, with a 24-hour increase of 8.64%.Earlier on September 2nd, Sky (formerly MakerDAO) founder Rune Christensen stated on social media, &quot;After significantly reducing the core expenses of Sky Core, the profit page has been updated. Based on the annualization calculation of fees for the past three months, it now shows real-time stable fee income and savings rate expenses. The current annualized profit has reached $3.38 billion.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27441</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflect Money has completed a $3.75 million seed funding round, with a16z CSX leading the investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27440</link>
      <description>September 3rd. The Reflect Money stablecoin project announced the accomplishment of a seed round financing amounting to $3.75 million. This round was led by the CSX Accelerator of a16z crypto, and it saw the participation of Solana Ventures, Equilibrium, BigBrain Holdings, and Colosseum.The Reflect protocol tokenizes on-chain DeFi strategies. It converts the deposited USDC into interest-bearing &quot;USDC+&quot; while maintaining liquidity. Reflect is scheduled to launch its mainnet in early September, with initial support provided for USDC on Solana.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>