<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:20:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Surges Above $900 This Morning, Setting a New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25883</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on market data, BNB briefly exceeded $900 this morning, reaching a peak of $900.71 and hitting a new all-time high, with a 24-hour price increase of 4.29%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25883</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewpoint: The Crypto Treasury Company Craze is Fading, Excess Returns Hard to Replicate</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25882</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, Adam Reeds, the co-founder and CEO of Ledn, believes that the recent market trends suggest that the enthusiasm for coin hoarding among digital asset treasury companies is reaching a turning point.Adam Reeds stated that Bitcoin treasury companies were once a revolutionary innovation in the industry, but the ability to achieve a 3x return may be fading. Over the past five years, MicroStrategy has witnessed a 24x increase, while Bitcoin has seen a 10x increase, making it difficult to replicate such excessive returns.Adam Reeds believes that the signs of the past week indicate that the crypto treasury fever, mainly following the Strategy model, is cooling down. The total market value of DAT companies has dropped below $150 billion, and the cumulative market value of the Bitcoin treasury has decreased from $165 billion a month ago to $134 billion (even though Bitcoin&apos;s price has been relatively stable). The stock price of Strategy has also fallen from a high of $455 in J</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25882</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ondo Finance to Launch Tokenized Stocks on September 3rd</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25881</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to official information, Ondo Finance is scheduled to launch tokenized stocks on September 3rd.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25881</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pendle TVL Surpasses $10 Billion, Achieves New All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25880</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, TN Lee, a co-founder of Pendle, announced that the TVL of Pendle has exceeded 10 billion USD, reaching a new record high.TN Lee pointed out that Pendle&apos;s rapid and strong growth from a niche experiment to a cornerstone of DeFi is mainly attributed to the community.The 10 billion USD TVL is not the end of the growth, and Pendle is confident in achieving even greater success.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 02:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The current mainstream CEXs still generally maintain a neutral funding rate for ETH contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25879</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, based on Coinglass data, although Ethereum reached a historical high this morning, the current mainstream CEX ETH contract funding rates still remain generally neutral, as shown in the specific data below.BlockBeats Note: The funding rate is a fee set by cryptocurrency trading platforms to maintain the balance between the contract price and the underlying asset price. It is usually applicable to perpetual contracts and is a fund exchange mechanism between long and short traders. The trading platform does not collect this fee. It is used to adjust the cost or profit of traders holding the contract to keep the contract price close to the underlying asset price.When the funding rate is 0.01%, it represents the baseline rate. When the funding rate is greater than 0.01%, it indicates a generally bullish market. When the funding rate is less than 0.005%, it indicates a generally bearish market.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 01:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25879</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「PEPE Flashbot Whale」 increased their position by 1,837 billion PEPE 9 hours ago, with a 100% successful trading record in PEPE price swings, but still remains at a loss of $7.25 million overall.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25878</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;PEPE Whales with 100% Win Rate&quot; withdrew 1.837 trillion PEPE from Binance 9 hours ago at an average price of 0.00001107. The withdrawn amount was worth $2.035 million. Meanwhile, he still holds 13.1 trillion PEPE with an average cost of approximately $0.00001683, and there is still an unrealized loss of $7.25 million. Since establishing his position in June 2024, his PEPE holdings have once shrunk by 69%, but he still holds the vast majority of the tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 01:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25878</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several issuers have submitted a revised version of the XRP spot ETF application, adding support for XRP creation and redemption.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25877</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, asset management companies such as Grayscale, Bitwise, Canary, CoinShares, Franklin, 21Shares, and WisdomTree all submitted updated statements this Friday regarding their proposed spot XRP ETF. This once again shows the eagerness of financial firms to obtain listing approval from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission.Bloomberg ETF analyst James Seyffart stated that the appearance of these applications is almost definitely in response to feedback from the SEC. This is a good sign, but it is also largely expected.The updated filings seem to have changed the structure of some funds, enabling XRP or cash creation and cash or in-kind redemption instead of just cash creation and redemption.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 01:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25877</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain swing trading address FOMO bought 1966 ETH this morning, after liquidating its position when ETH was at $4203 5 days ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25876</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale address beginning with 0x8062 sold 2,277 ETH for 4,203 five days ago (approximately $9.57 million) and then bought back 1,966 ETH five hours ago driven by a FOMO sentiment, also amounting to approximately $9.57 million. The average price was $4,869. Currently, this address is at a loss of $188,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 01:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25876</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Major &quot;Bankruptcy&quot; Contract Whales Return, Opening Unilateral Long and Short Positions Differs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25875</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight, with Ethereum reaching a new all-time high and triggering a market breakout, the three major whale traders who had previously suffered significant losses (losing tens of millions of dollars to zero), namely James Wynn, AguilaTrades, and the &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio, have all returned to participate in the market. Their current positions are as follows:· James Wynn still holds a 25x long position in ETH with an entry price of $4,239 and an unrealized profit of $20,000.· AguilaTrades opened a 25x short position after Ethereum&apos;s new high with an entry price of $4,833 and an unrealized profit of $11,700.· The &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio opened a 3x short position on XPL and holds 20,000 coins with an entry price of $0.5768.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 01:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25875</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &quot;Bitcoin Ancient Whale&quot; ETH Spot + Perpetual Long Position&apos;s Overall Unrealized Gain has increased to $161 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25874</link>
      <description>On August 23rd, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a whale or institution that has held 10,606 BTC for up to 7 years previously opened positions on Hyperliquid. It has achieved a profit of $1.12 billion. Currently, the position is still making a profit of $161 million, and the current holdings are as follows:Spot: It is holding 118,277 ETH, which is valued at $571 million and has a profit of $87 million.Derivatives: It is holding a long position of 135,265 ETH, which is valued at $653 million and has a profit of $73 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 01:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25874</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>