<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 05:47:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 05:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Total Open Interest of WLFI Futures Contracts Surges by 26.77% in the Past 24 Hours, Currently Standing at $589 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27015</link>
      <description>August 31st: The cryptocurrency project World Liberty Finance (WLFI) of the Trump family is set to officially launch tomorrow. In the past 24 hours, the total open interest of WLFI futures contracts across the network has witnessed a surge of 26.77% and now stands at $5.89 billion.In addition, the Hyperliquid platform indicates that the pre-trading price of WLFI is currently at $0.311, with an annualized funding rate of 11.38%. The number of long positions exceeds that of short positions. On Binance, the pre-trading price of WLFI is at $0.2986, with a funding rate of 0.005%, and there are slightly more long positions than short positions.World Liberty Finance (WLFI) is scheduled to be launched on Ethereum on September 1st, opening up for claiming and trading. Early supporters (at $0.015 and $0.05 rounds) will be able to unlock 20%, while the remaining 80% will be subject to a community vote. Tokens held by the foun</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 05:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27015</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September Federal Reserve Board Composition Forecast: Trump Camp May Have a Four to Three Edge</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27014</link>
      <description>August 31st. Apart from Tim Cook who is currently engaged in a court battle with Trump, the Federal Reserve Board of Governors (with a full membership of 7) also comprises Powell and two governors appointed by Biden (Jefferson and Barr), and they, like Cook, are in alignment with Powell. In addition, there are two governors appointed by Trump during his first term (Waller and Bowman), and both of them voted in favor of rate cuts in July. Trump has nominated his advisor Stephen Moore to fill the vacancy caused by Cugler&apos;s resignation. The Senate Banking Committee will hold a confirmation hearing for Moore next Thursday. If approved promptly, he may join the Fed in time for the September meeting, indicating that Trump will have at least three supporters on the Federal Reserve Board. Furthermore, if the court rules that Trump can dismiss Cook, he will promptly nominate her successor, potentially enabling him to obtain a majority (four out of seven) on the board. This ruling is unlikely to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 05:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27014</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARK, a meme coin, saw its market cap briefly surpass $20 million, with a 24-hour price increase of over 48.56%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27013</link>
      <description>On August 31st, based on GMGN data, the on-chain AI virtual creature concept Meme token SPARK&apos;s market capitalization briefly exceeded $20 million. Currently, it is at $18.6 million. It has a 24-hour price increase of 48.56% and a 24-hour trading volume of $4.1 million.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins often lack practical use cases and experience high price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 04:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27013</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EigenCloud has announced the latest developments in the project and plans to expand its applications in multiple areas.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27012</link>
      <description>On August 31st, EigenCloud declared its most recent project plan. This plan will be employed to provide support for applications in various fields such as Artificial Intelligence (AI), A2A, DeFi, zkTLS, Real World Assets (RWAs), DeFAI, DePIN, Intelligent Agents, Rollups, and Oracles.On June 17th, Eigen Labs announced the commencement of the Ethereum Re-Staking Protocol EigenCloud. a16z crypto is set to invest $70 million by directly purchasing EIGEN tokens. This follows a16z&apos;s additional investment of $100 million in EigenLayer in February 2024. EigenCloud is constructed on top of the EigenLayer Re-Staking Protocol and integrates functions like Data Availability (EigenDA), Generalized Computation (EigenCompute), and Dispute Resolution (EigenVerify). The platform enables developers to cryptographically verify off-chain activities, offering the same level of trust guarantees as on-chain activities. Currently, more than $12 billion in re-staked assets safeguard over 200 decentralized se</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 04:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27012</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renowned trader TechnoRevenant holds approximately a $28.9 million long position in XPL, representing 13.4% of the total network holdings.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27011</link>
      <description>On August 31, as per the monitoring of HyperInsight, the renowned trader TechnoRevenant holds a substantial long position with low leverage in XPL on Hyperliquid. There are 13 different addresses involved, and the total value of the long position is approximately $28.9 million, accounting for 38% of the total open interest ($76.15 million) on Hyperliquid. All of these positions have a leverage of less than 1x.According to Coinglass data, the current global open interest in XPL futures is reported to be $216 million, with a 24-hour increase of 3.99%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 03:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27011</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APE Token to Expand to the Solana Blockchain and Undergo DeFi Integration</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27010</link>
      <description>On August 31st, the ApeCoin team officially declared the commencement of the R.A.I.D (Rapid ApeCoin Integration Deployment) strategy. The intention is to transform ApeCoin from a governance token into a &quot;cultural token&quot; and stimulate the growth of its ecosystem. The APE project initially intends to expand to the Solana blockchain and undergo DeFi integration.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 03:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27010</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s previously shilled meme coin GOAT has surged over 67.4% in the past 24 hours, with a current market cap of $12.5 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27006</link>
      <description>On August 31st, based on GMGN data, James Wynn&apos;s previously promoted meme coin Goatcoin (GOAT) witnessed a surge of over 67.4% in the past 24 hours. It currently has a market capitalization of $12.5 million and a 24-hour trading volume of $7.2 million.On August 27th, James Wynn made a post on Platform X promoting the meme coin Goatcoin (GOAT) and stating that &quot;its market capitalization is expected to reach several billion dollars.&quot; On that day, GOAT responded with a surge of over 200%, pushing its market capitalization beyond $10 million.BlockBeats reminds users that meme coins usually lack practical use cases and experience significant price fluctuations. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 02:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27006</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Bitcoin and Gold Under Pressure Simultaneously as Market Enters Risk-Off Mode</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27008</link>
      <description>August 31st. During this month, the data of Bitcoin and Gold ETF shows that the recent fund flows have deviated from historical trends. Usually, the flows of funds in both assets are opposite, but this time both experienced outflows simultaneously. This rare phenomenon reflects the current macroeconomic environment and investor sentiment. The outflows of Bitcoin have not had an impact on Gold. And until the policy path of the Fed becomes clear, both will continue to face pressure.Bitcoin ETF witnessed outflows for six consecutive days and lost nearly $2 billion alone in August. At the same time, major Gold ETFs such as GLDM also experienced outflows of $449 million in a week. Bitcoin ETF finally rebounded at the end of August, with four consecutive days of inflows. Gold ETF also showed net inflows in the last few days of August 2025, similar to the rebound trend of Bitcoin ETF.The uncertainties of the Fed&apos;s monetary policy, persistent inflationary pressures, and signs of a weak lab</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 02:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 16.27 billion WLFI tokens have been transferred to the Lockbox contract, estimated to be worth 4.83 billion US dollars.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27007</link>
      <description>On August 31st, according to on-chain data, around 16.27 billion WLFI tokens have been transferred to the Lockbox contract, which makes up 16.27% of the total token supply. Given the current contract price of $0.297, the value is approximately $4.83 billion.BlockBeats reported previously that the WLFI token will officially start unlocking at 8:00 AM EST on September 1st, and the relevant functionality page (Lockbox) has been launched. Users needed to activate between August 25th and August 31st in order to be able to claim 20% of the unlocked tokens starting from September 1st.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 02:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27007</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>