<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria SEC Chief: Country is Open to Stablecoin Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21783</link>
      <description>On July 25th, Emmanuel Agama, the Director General of the Nigerian SEC, recently declared that the country is receptive to stablecoin companies. Firms that adhere to Nigeria&apos;s evolving digital asset regulations will encounter a conducive environment for innovation. &quot;Nigeria is open to stablecoin business, yet the prerequisite is to safeguard our market and empower the Nigerian people.&quot; (Decrypt)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21783</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought 1862 ETH 8 hours ago, with an average purchase price of $3750.63</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21782</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a large investor purchased 1862 ETH 8 hours ago. Currently, this investor is facing an unrealized loss of $237,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21782</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Ecosystem AI Project The Innovation Game Market Cap Surpasses $47 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate Reaches 55.4%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21781</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to the GMGN market information, the Base protocol AI project The Innovation Game (TIG) has exceeded a market capitalization of 47 million US dollars. Currently, it stands at 47.25 million US dollars, with a 24-hour price increase of 55.4% and a 24-hour trading volume of 10.64 million US dollars.Information shows that The Innovation Game (TIG) is a protocol aimed at accelerating algorithm innovation through the coordination of global intelligence. Its core is a novel Proof of Work mechanism called &quot;Optimized Proof of Work&quot; (OPoW).BlockBeats reminds users that relevant token prices are highly volatile, and users should invest with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21781</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle CEO: Circle Stablecoin Network is now officially live.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21780</link>
      <description>On July 25th, Jeremy Allaire, the co-founder and CEO of Stablecoin issuer Circle, announced that the Circle Stablecoin Network has officially launched Sei. A large number of USDC-integrated applications are set to become live.Earlier reports showed that native USDC had already officially launched on the Sei network with CCTP V2. Circle Mint fully supports native USDC on Sei, offering institutional users access to USDC liquidity through Sei&apos;s high-performance infrastructure. By leveraging Sei&apos;s high-performance architecture, more than 13 cross-chain stablecoin transfers have been achieved without bridges and without slippage.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21780</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin drops below $116,000, the mainstream CEX&apos;s cumulative long liquidation depth will reach $1.039 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21779</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to Coinglass data, if Bitcoin drops beneath $116,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.039 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin surges above $118,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEXs will reach $671 million.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of the contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart illustrates the extent to which the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will encounter a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade once it reaches that particular point.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21779</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes bought 2.16 million ENA today, accumulating a total of 7.76 million ENA.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21778</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Arthur Hayes purchased 2.16 million ENA today from platforms like Binance, with a value of around $1.03 million.Arthur Hayes now holds a cumulative total of 7.76 million ENA, which is worth $3.73 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21778</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 7.95 million USDC into HyperLiquid, leveraging three times to long ETH, SOL, PENGU, and other coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21776</link>
      <description>On July 25th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, within the past 36 hours, a whale transferred $7.95 million into HyperLiquid and established multiple long positions with a leverage of 3x in ETH, SOL, PENGU, FARTCOIN, and HYPE.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs appoints Ms. Yang Can as Senior Vice President of Subsidiary to Strengthen Digital Currency Reserve Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21777</link>
      <description>On July 25th, the Nasdaq-listed company Nano Labs Ltd (NA) announced the appointment of Ms. Yang Can as the Senior Vice President of its wholly-owned subsidiary Nano bit HK Limited. Ms. Yang will be in charge of leading the implementation of Nano bit&apos;s digital currency strategic reserve plan and providing support for the company&apos;s vigorous development in the global crypto financial ecosystem.Ms. Yang Can has more than 15 years of financial investment experience. She previously managed a $600 million Bitcoin liquidity fund at Aquarius Capital and participated in NIO&apos;s Series B financing. Dr. Kong Jianping, the Chairman of Nano Labs, stated that Ms. Yang will assist in optimizing the company&apos;s asset-liability structure, improving capital efficiency, and enhancing BNB reserve capabilities.As of now, Nano Labs has accumulated approximately 120,000 BNB and is continuously consolidating its position as a market leader in Web 3.0 infrastructure and product solution providers. (Globenewswi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21777</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institution has accumulated and staked 365,000 SOL tokens over the past 3 months, with unrealized gains of $7.3 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21775</link>
      <description>On July 25th, according to Ashes Monitoring, a whale or institution that has been continuously adding SOL through FalconX since the end of April continued to accumulate 73,500 SOL (valued at approximately $13.83 million) in a single day recently.So far, it has accumulated and staked up to 365,000 SOL ($59.3 million) in three months via FalconX, with an average price of $162.4. Currently, the unrealized profit is $7.3 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21775</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windtree Therapeutics has signed a $520 million new financing agreement, which will be used to purchase BNB.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21774</link>
      <description>On July 25th, the Nasdaq-listed biotechnology company Windtree Therapeutics (WINT) announced that it has reached a share purchase agreement with a potential value of up to $500 million to set up an Equity Line of Credit (ELOC). Furthermore, the company has also signed an additional stock purchase agreement worth $20 million with Build and Build Corp.The total funding amount for this round reaches up to $520 million, and 99% of the funds will be used to purchase BNB. The company intends to officially commence using the funds after obtaining shareholder approval to increase the number of authorized common shares.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21774</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>