<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:53:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Whale Trader AiRev Closed All Their PUMP Long Positions, Earning a $1.5 Million Profit in the Last Month</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24086</link>
      <description>On August 11th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the whale trader AiRev (@ParallelAiRev) has just liquidated all of his PUMP long positions and realized profits at the peak. During the past month, his total profit has exceeded $1.5 million, making him the top-earning PUMP trader on the Hyperliquid 30-day leaderboard.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24086</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Crypto Stocks Surge, BMNR Soars 30%, SBET Up Over 15%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24085</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to rockflow data, US crypto stocks witnessed a general upward trend. These included:Coinbase (COIN) increasing by 5.84%.Circle (CRCL) rising by 3.66%.MicroStrategy (MSTR) going up by 3.12%.Bitmine (BMNR) rising by 30.04%.BTCS (BTCS) increasing by 4.20%.Bit Digital (BTBT) going up by 7.19%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) rising by 15.72%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24085</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trends Teams Up with Bitget Wallet to Kickstart a New Era of Convenient Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24084</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Trends made an announcement about entering into a strategic partnership with Bitget Wallet. Users will be able to log in to Trends via Bitget Wallet and directly conduct trades of the Trends token on Bitget DEX. This supports both Curve LP and Automated Market Maker (AMM) modes. Additionally, they can explore the latest projects through Memescan. The Trends TPS Season 1 has commenced, and more partnerships are expected to follow shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24084</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pendle Weekly Update: Boros Fund Limit Significantly Increased, Ecosystem TVL Surpasses $8 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24083</link>
      <description>August 11th: The funding cap of Pendle&apos;s fund rate trading platform, Boros, continues to rise. The open position limit has increased from $15 million to $28.55 million. The treasury limits for BTC and ETH have respectively gone up from $60,000 and $80,000 to $100,000 and $125,000, suggesting a trend of expanding fund size.In terms of the ecosystem, as of August 9th, Pendle&apos;s Total Value Locked (TVL) has seen an increase from $7 billion five days ago to $8 billion, reaching a new all-time high. Regarding cross-chain deployment, Pendle has achieved a TVL of over $300 million on the HyperEVM network within less than two weeks and entered the top ten on DefiLlama&apos;s ranking. This indicates that cross-chain functionality is gradually gaining user acceptance, and the ecosystem development is progressing steadily.Regarding market performance, according to Block Media, Pendle has performed well on the Upbit exchange and become one of the top three gainers among crypto assets. Alongside Prov</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24083</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale investor @ParallelAiRev just closed all his $PUMP longs, taking profits at highs.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24082</link>
      <description>Whale investor @ParallelAiRev just closed all his $PUMP longs, taking profits at highs. Over the past month, he has made a total profit of over $1.5M, becoming the most profitable $PUMP trader on Hyperliquid&apos;s 30-day leaderboard.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24082</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thumzup is planning a $50 million initial public offering (IPO), with the net proceeds intended to accumulate cryptocurrency and mining equipment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24081</link>
      <description>August 11th. Thumzup Media Corporation (Nasdaq: TZUP) announced today the pricing of its covertly marketed common stock public offering. Alongside this, there is a common stock alternative for certain investors - pre-funded warrants to subscribe for its common stock, with a public offering price set at $10 per share.The company anticipates receiving gross proceeds of $46.5 million from this offering, prior to deducting underwriting discounts and other offering expenses. The offering is expected to close around August 12th, 2025, contingent upon the usual closing conditions. The company intends to utilize the net proceeds from this offering for the exploration of cryptocurrency and the accumulation of mining equipment, as well as for working capital and general corporate purposes.BlockBeats Note: In July 2025, Donald Trump Jr., the son of the former president, disclosed that he had purchased 350,000 shares of Thumzup, which was worth approximately $3.3 million to $4.3 million based on</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24081</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berenstein: Coinbase Will Be the Biggest Beneficiary of ETH&apos;s Rise, Altseason Has Begun</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24080</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Bernstein analysts declared that as ETH rose and the altcoin season arrived, Coinbase would become the greatest beneficiary.Led by Gautam Chhugani, the analysts pointed out in a report to clients on Monday that since the remarkable IPO of the stablecoin issuer Circle on June 5th, ETH has increased by 80%. With the awareness that most stablecoins are issued on the Ethereum network, investor interest in the Ethereum ecosystem is expanding.Chhugani stated: &quot;In cryptocurrency terms, this market structure is referred to as an &apos;altcoin season rally,&apos; where digital assets other than Bitcoin exhibit a stronger rebound compared to Bitcoin. We believe that the altcoin rebound has already commenced (the recent outstanding performance of ETH has already reflected this), and Coinbase will be the biggest beneficiary as it has listed more than 250 tokens and integrated Base Layer 1 tokens into the Coinbase App.&quot;The analysts pointed out that Base Layer 1 processes more than 9 millio</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSR Partners with DigiFT to Launch RWA Token OTC Secondary Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24079</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to Coindesk, the cryptocurrency market maker GSR has formed a partnership with the regulated tokenized asset trading platform DigiFT to initiate over-the-counter (OTC) secondary trading of tokenized real-world assets (RWA). This service is targeted at eligible institutional investors and is available seven days a week during Asian market hours. Qualified institutions can trade tokenized units of funds such as the Invesco US Senior Loan ETF (iSNR), the UBS Dollar Money Market Fund (uMINT), and the Wellington Ultra Short Duration Government Chain Fund (ULTRA). GSR will offer systematic bid-ask spreads, while DigiFT&apos;s platform enables settlement under regulation in Singapore and Hong Kong.According to DeFiLlama data, the RWA sector has grown to a total asset size of over $13.4 billion, with a substantial portion coming from tokenized government bond funds and gold-backed cryptocurrencies.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24079</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contract Trading Whale AguilaTrades Liquidates Short Position with a &quot;Lightspeed&quot; Exit, Losing $1.866 Million in 12 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24078</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), after the US stock market opened and Ethereum surged to $4300, a short order of 26187 ETH from the contract trading whale AguilaTrades was triggered. Subsequently, a &quot;lightning-speed&quot; liquidation occurred 12 minutes later, resulting in a loss of $1.866 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24078</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Surges Above $4300, US Stocks Up 2.84% After Market Open</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24077</link>
      <description>On August 11th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum experienced a rebound and broke through $4300. It was initially priced at $4301 and rose by 2.84% after the U.S. stock market opened.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24077</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>