<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin drops below $116,000, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach 1.041 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24862</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin drops below $116,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will amount to $1.041 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin surges above $119,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity of mainstream CEXs will reach $1.014 billion.**BlockBeats Note**: The liquidation chart does not precisely display the number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the relative significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows the extent to which the underlying price will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. Higher &quot;liquidation bars&quot; indicate that the price will undergo a more intense reaction due to a surge in liquidity.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24862</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Global Q2 Stake in Circle, Acquires 125,000 Class A Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24863</link>
      <description>August 16th. As per the disclosure by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Tiger Global Management submitted its second-quarter holdings report (13F) as of June 30, 2025. The figures indicate that Tiger Global&apos;s total holdings in the second quarter amounted to $34.1 billion, which is higher than the $26.6 billion in the previous quarter, representing a quarter-on-quarter growth of 28.2%.In the second quarter of 2025, Tiger Global newly purchased 125,000 shares of Class A stock of the stablecoin issuer Circle (CRCL.US). When Circle&apos;s stock went public in June, it performed well, and since then, its market value has almost increased by a factor of five from the initial public offering price.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24863</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Ukrainian President to Visit Oval Office on Monday Afternoon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24861</link>
      <description>On August 16th, President Trump of the US stated that President Zelensky of Ukraine will pay a visit to the Oval Office on Monday afternoon.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24861</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crypto Fear and Greed Index has dropped to 56, indicating that the market is still experiencing &quot;greed&quot; sentiment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24860</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on alternative data, today&apos;s Crypto Fear and Greed Index has decreased to 56 (yesterday it was 60), with the average of last week being 67, suggesting that the market is still in a &quot;Greed&quot; sentiment.Note: The Fear and Greed Index ranges from 0 to 100 and encompasses the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Hype (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance Ratio (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24860</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: All parties believe that Russia and Ukraine should reach a peace agreement directly, rather than a ceasefire agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24859</link>
      <description>August 16th, The latest social media post by U.S. President Trump: &quot;Had an extremely successful day in Alaska! The meeting with Russian President Putin proceeded very smoothly. And the late-night calls with Ukrainian President Zelensky and several respected European leaders, including the NATO Secretary General, were also highly productive.&quot;It is widely believed that the most effective way to end the tragic war between Russia and Ukraine is to directly reach a peace agreement to bring the war to a complete end rather than just a ceasefire agreement. Ceasefires often do not last long.President Zelensky is scheduled to travel to Washington, D.C. on Monday afternoon to visit the Oval Office. If all goes well, we will then make arrangements for a meeting with President Putin. This has the potential to save millions of lives. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24859</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Withdrawal Trend Continues, with CEX Net Outflow of 148,700 ETH in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24858</link>
      <description>On August 16th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, the total net outflow of Ethereum on CEX was 148,700 ETH. The top three exchanges with outflows are as follows:· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 127,600 ETH;· Binance, with an outflow of 73,700 ETH;· Bybit, with an outflow of 8,748.98 ETH.In addition, Kraken witnessed an inflow of 45,400 ETH and ranked first on the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24858</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address withdrew 9006 ETH from Kraken today.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24857</link>
      <description>On August 16th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a new address withdrew 9006 ETH from Kraken today. The value of this withdrawal is approximately $40.16 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24857</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Launches MiL.k (MLK), Users Holding at Least 200 Points Can Claim 245 MLK Airdrop</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24856</link>
      <description>On August 16th, according to official channels, Binance Alpha has launched MiL.k (MLK). Users who hold at least 200 Alpha Points are eligible to claim an airdrop of 245 MLK tokens. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Story Co-founder Jason Zhao has resigned from his full-time role within the project and transitioned to a Strategic Advisor position.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24855</link>
      <description>On August 16th, Jason Zhao, a co-founder of Story, announced on his personal Twitter that he would resign from his full-time position in the project and transition to a strategic advisor.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24855</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Swiftly Achieving Peace Agreement Better Than Ceasefire, Putin Hopes for Comprehensive Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24854</link>
      <description>On August 16th, Trump stated in a phone call that in his opinion, achieving a peace agreement promptly is more favorable than a ceasefire. Putin is not inclined towards a ceasefire; instead, he desires to reach a comprehensive agreement in order to bring an end to the war. (AXIOS)</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 07:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24854</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>