<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Treasury Department Calls for Public Comment on Cryptocurrency Illegal Activity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25089</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the U.S. Treasury is soliciting public comments in order to understand how financial institutions should combat illegal activities related to cryptocurrency. This comes after last month&apos;s landmark stablecoin legislation was enacted into law.On Monday, the U.S. Treasury issued a request for comments on &quot;innovative approaches to detecting illicit activities involving digital assets.&quot; The notice stated that this new law, known as the &quot;Guidance and Examination of the United States Stablecoin National Innovation in Use of Strategic Plans Act&quot; (GENIUS), directs the Treasury to inquire about issues such as application programming interfaces (APIs), artificial intelligence, digital identity verification, and the use of blockchain technology.U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen said on Monday, &quot;Stablecoins will expand global USD channels by tens of billions of dollars, and the demand for U.S. Treasury bonds supporting stablecoins will surge. This is a triple win situation for all</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25089</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Expects a solution today, resolution may include security measures</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25088</link>
      <description>On August 19th, President Trump of the US stated that Russia has agreed to accept security assurances, and we will consider who is responsible for what. I am optimistic that we will reach an agreement together to prevent aggression against Ukraine. We also need to discuss possible territorial exchange matters.Only Zelensky and Ukraine have the power to make decisions. As we strive to achieve lasting peace, we all prefer an immediate ceasefire. So far, this has not occurred. A final peace agreement is achievable and can be reached soon. It is believed that a solution will be reached today, and the resolution may include security measures.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Will attempt to reach a US-Ukraine-Russia trilateral agreement, with no requirement for a ceasefire agreement between Russia and Ukraine.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25087</link>
      <description>On August 19, President Trump of the United States declared that he will make an attempt to reach a trilateral agreement involving the United States, Ukraine, and Russia.During a meeting with Ukrainian President Zelensky at the White House, Trump stated that he &quot;does not believe there is a need for a ceasefire agreement.&quot; He said, &quot;A ceasefire may seem pleasant as it can immediately halt the killing. However, strategically, some countries might not desire a ceasefire because it would provide the enemy with an opportunity to regroup.&quot; Trump further said, &quot;It is also possible to engage in fighting while conducting negotiations simultaneously.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25087</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC Delays Decision on Multiple Cryptocurrency ETFs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25086</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) postponed the approval decision regarding the Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF applications submitted by Trump Media &amp; Technology Group&apos;s social media platform, Truth Social.According to a filing made on Monday, the SEC has extended the deadline for the approval of the Truth Social ETF to October 8th. This is part of its standard procedure for reviewing dozens of cryptocurrency ETF proposals.Also postponed on the same day are the approval decisions for the CoinShares Litecoin ETF, CoinShares Ripple ETF, and 21Shares Ripple ETF, with the decision deadlines all being pushed back to late October. The SEC stated in the filing: &quot;The Commission deems it appropriate to set a longer period within which to issue an order approving or disapproving the proposed rule change in order to have sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25086</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S.-based Bitcoin mining firm TeraWulf is planning to raise $400 million to expand its data center business.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25083</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the U.S.-listed Bitcoin mining firm TeraWulf (with the stock code: WULF) declared its intention to raise $400 million through a private placement of convertible senior notes. This fundraising move took place as its AI cloud service customer, Fluidstack, decided to increase its leasing of 160 megawatts of power capacity at the Lake Mariner campus in New York State.According to a statement issued on Monday, these convertible notes encompass a $60 million over-allotment option granted to the initial buyers, and the funds will be utilized for covered call options trading and the expansion of the non-mining data center business. The notes are unsecured senior notes and will accrue interest semi-annually starting from March 1, 2026, and mature on September 1, 2031. Upon obtaining shareholder approval, TeraWulf has the option to settle conversions in cash, stock, or a combination thereof. This financing represents TeraWulf&apos;s accelerated entry into the high-performance comput</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25083</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loom Capital&apos;s associated address has deposited 13,000 ETH into Binance in the past 3 days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25085</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, an address linked to Longling Capital transferred 5,000 ETH (approximately $21.73 million) to Binance for sale.During the past 3 days, this wallet has made a total deposit of 13,000 ETH (approximately $53.38 million) into Binance.Currently, the wallet still retains 74,090 ETH (approximately $322.6 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25085</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Within the last 24 hours, the entire network has seen a total of $587 million in liquidations, with the majority coming from long positions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25080</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on Coinglass data, the total value that was liquidated across the entire network within the past 24 hours reached $587 million. A total of 133,228 individuals were liquidated globally. The amount of long liquidations was $504 million, and the amount of short liquidations was $82.32 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase International Launches MNT, RSR, SUPER Perpetual Contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25084</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to official information, Coinbase Pro has declared the listing of MNT, RSR, and SUPER perpetual contracts on its international platform. Trading is set to commence at 9:30 AM on August 21st, 2025 in UTC time.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25084</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Acquires High-Performance Consensus Engine Malachite to Support its Arc Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25082</link>
      <description>August 18th. Today, Informal Systems made an announcement that its high-performance consensus engine, Malachite, has been acquired by the global financial technology company Circle Internet Group (CRCL). This acquisition is intended to support the launch of the Layer-1 blockchain network Arc, which is specifically designed for stablecoin finance.Circle&apos;s integration of Malachite will boost the performance, reliability, and security of stablecoin payments. It will also contribute to the realization of a low-cost, borderless, and trusted financial infrastructure. The Malachite codebase will remain under the Apache 2.0 open-source license to ensure continuous industry innovation.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25082</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Surges Above $116,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25081</link>
      <description>On August 18th, based on HTX market data, Bitcoin experienced a rebound and broke through $116,000. It is now trading at $116,176.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25081</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>