<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 09:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>「Silent 14.5-Year Holder of 3963 BTC Ancient Whale」 transferred an additional 50 BTC half an hour ago</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22453</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to the on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the &quot;ancient whale that had been holding 3,963 BTC in silence for 14.5 years&quot; transferred an additional 50 BTC ($5.91 million) to the address bc1q8...kxayr half an hour ago. The current ownership of the receiving address remains unknown.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22453</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has launched perpetual contract trading for A2Z and UNITE.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22452</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to official channels, Gate has initiated A2Z perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT), with support for 1-20x leverage; and it will launch UNITE perpetual contract spot trading (settled in USDT) at 18:10 on July 30th (UTC+8), also providing support for 1-20x leverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22452</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutional Ethereum Whale Holdings Change in the Last 30 Days: BMNR Holds 625,000 ETH Ranking First</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22451</link>
      <description>On July 30th, based on strategicethreserve data, the following treasury companies and institutions witnessed significant changes in their Ethereum holdings over the past 30 days:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) took the lead, currently holding 625,000 ETH, which is approximately worth $23.8 billion, with a 283.1% increase in holdings during the past 30 days;SharpLink Gaming (SBET) ranked second, currently holding 438,200 ETH, approximately worth $16.7 billion, and experiencing a 132.49% increase in holdings over the past 30 days;The Ethereum Foundation ranked third, holding 238,500 ETH, approximately worth $8.977 billion, with a 6.69% decrease in holdings over the past 30 days;Bit Digital (BTBT) ranked seventh, holding 120,300 ETH, approximately worth $4.585 billion, and showing a 335.53% increase in holdings over the past 30 days;BTCS Inc (BTCS) ranked tenth, holding 70,000 ETH, approximately worth $2.669 billion, with a 379.64% increase in holdings over the past 30 days.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22451</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU project team&apos;s associated address has once again transferred 150 million PENGU to Binance, equivalent to approximately $5.64 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22450</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), the team behind the PENGU project&apos;s affiliated address 8hQvQ...zund8 has once more deposited 150 million PENGU tokens into Binance, with a value of $5.64 million.This address previously received 1.35 billion PENGU tokens from the deployment address in December 2024. Since July, it has transferred a total of 485 million tokens to exchanges. The total value of these transfers is $17.67 million, and the average price per token is $0.03642.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22450</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Market Quietly Awaits FOMC Meeting Statement, BTC Holds Steady in Support Range, Short-Term Pressure Still Focuses on the 120,000 Level</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22449</link>
      <description>July 30th: After 30 years, a rare divergence in interest rate policy has emerged within the Federal Reserve. Board members Waller and Bowman inclined towards an immediate 25-basis-point rate cut, highlighting the risks to the labor market and the short-term inflationary impact of tariffs. However, the majority of the board still favored maintaining the current interest rates. Several institutions pointed out that this divergence would be a key observation point for the future direction of policy in the coming months.In the crypto market, BTC has recently been stable within the range of 116,000 to 119,000. There is support below 117,000, and selling pressure is concentrated in the 119,000 to 120,000 region, posing resistance to upward movement. Price fluctuations are being influenced by market expectations regarding the Fed&apos;s policy shift.Bitunix analyst recommendation: The policy divergence has intensified short-term market uncertainty. It is expected that BTC will continue to fluc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22449</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental is set to carry out a $200 million private placement to kickstart its Ethereum Treasury strategy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22448</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Nasdaq-listed company Fundamental Global Inc. declared the sale of 40 million common shares at a price of $5 per share, with an expected total amount of proceeds being $200 million. The proceeds will be utilized to initiate the company&apos;s Ethereum Treasury strategy. The participants comprise Galaxy Digital, Kraken, Hivemind Capital, Syncracy Capital, Digital Currency Group (DCG), and Kenetic.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix is launching TREE spot and futures trading, participate to win 10,000 TREE</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22447</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Bitunix now offers Treehouse (TREE) spot trading and USDT perpetual contract trading, presenting users with multiple trading choices. Meanwhile, the platform has concurrently launched a time-limited Token Splash event, during which participants have the chance to divide a total of 10,000 TREE tokens as rewards.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22447</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Binance Alpha Launches GAIA</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22446</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Binance Alpha makes Gaia (GAIA) available for listing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22446</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperwhale Watch: Three whale addresses have increased their BTC and ETH short positions again, currently holding unrealized losses of $11.52M, $23.10M, and $19.75M respectively</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22444</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as per the monitoring of HyperInsight, within the past 1 hour, a whale whose address begins with 0x20c2d9 enhanced its ETH short position by 849,750.04, currently having an unrealized loss of approximately 23.1 million USD, and the current liquidation price is 5,028.484 USD;A whale with an address starting with 0x5d2f44 increased its BTC short position by roughly 806,412 USD in the past hour. It is currently holding an unrealized loss of about 11.525 million USD, and the current liquidation price is 125,243.797 USD;A whale with an address starting with 0x880ac4 increased its ETH short position by around 1,027,988 USD. Currently, it is holding an unrealized loss of about 19.754 million USD, and the current liquidation price is 4,817.769 USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22444</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Fear &amp; Greed Index Rises to 74, Market Still in &quot;Greed&quot; State</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22445</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to alternative data, today&apos;s cryptocurrency Fear and Greed Index stands at 74 (yesterday it was 73), suggesting a slight rise in the market&apos;s &quot;greed&quot; sentiment.Note: The Fear and Greed Index has a threshold ranging from 0 to 100 and encompasses the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Sentiment (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin Dominance (10%) + Google Trends (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22445</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>