<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:20:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong has already seen a state-owned investment fund actively planning a Coin-Stock Linkage project.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28078</link>
      <description>September 8th: According to DeepChain of Tencent News, an article titled &quot;Alibaba&apos;s Jack Ma&apos;s Holding Company Buys $310 Million Worth of Ethereum: Hong Kong-listed Companies Showing Interest in Cryptocurrency&quot; pointed out that a fund in Hong Kong, which has received investment from a state-owned enterprise, has been actively planning a coin-stock linkage project during this period. A financial professional in Hong Kong stated that since state-owned funds cannot directly invest in cryptocurrency industry-related funds, they can purchase stocks, and &quot;there is currently no restriction on investing in and holding the stocks of listed companies holding Bitcoin.&quot;It is reported that among the 49 member units of the Hong Kong Digital Asset Listing Association, there are a total of 38 Hong Kong-listed companies. Most of them have ideas to hold coins or plans to increase their coin holdings. The total market value of the member units is approximately $20 billion, but specific coin holding plan</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28078</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAl-supported animated movie Critterz is set to premiere next year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28079</link>
      <description>On September 8th, OpenAI has now enabled the production of an AI-generated animated feature film. Several companies have announced that the animated movie Critterz, which is supported by OpenAI, is expected to have its premiere next year and is set for a global release.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28079</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Labs Joins Hyperliquid for USDH Stablecoin Issuance Rights Competition</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28077</link>
      <description>September 8th: The issuer of the third-largest USD stablecoin, USDe, which is Ethena Labs. Ethena Labs hinted at its intention to join the competition for the stablecoin issuance rights under Hyperliquid&apos;s USDH. This morning, Ethena Labs stated, &quot;Dear Jeff (Hyperliquid Co-Founder), I sent you a letter, but you have not responded yet. I submitted two USDH proposals last fall. You definitely did not receive them. It might be a problem with Discord or something else. Sometimes I write the deployment address too carelessly.&quot;On September 5th, Hyperliquid announced that it would release the USDH token symbol for stablecoin issuance and requested all institutions to submit proposals by September 10th (Wednesday), with voting scheduled for September 14th (Sunday).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 01:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28077</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale switched from longing ETH to shorting it after losing over $35 million, then lost an additional $614,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28076</link>
      <description>On September 8th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, the whale address 0xa523 switched from a long position to a short position on ETH after incurring a loss of more than $35 million. Additionally, it suffered a loss of $614,000. Currently, the whale holds a short position of 1,351 BTC, with a value of $150 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28076</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Week&apos;s Unlocking Data Overview: S, IO, APT, and others will see a large one-time token unlock.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28075</link>
      <description>On September 8th, according to Token Unlock data, there will be a one-time large token unlock this week for S, IO, APT, etc. The details are as follows:The Sonic (S) will unlock approximately 150 million tokens at 8 a.m. on September 9th, which accounts for 5.02% of the current circulating supply and is worth about $45.4 million.The Movement (MOVE) will unlock approximately 50 million tokens at 8 p.m. on September 9th, representing 1.89% of the current circulating supply and worth about $5.9 million.The BounceBit (BB) will unlock approximately 42.89 million tokens at 8 a.m. on September 10th, making up 6.31% of the current circulating supply and worth about $6.4 million.The Aptos (APT) will unlock approximately 11.31 million tokens at 6 p.m. on September 11th, which is 2.20% of the current circulating supply and worth about $48 million.The io.net (IO) will unlock approximately 13.29 million tokens at 8 p.m. on September 11th, representing 6.24% of the current circulating supply an</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28075</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIC Securities: The Federal Reserve will cut interest rates by 25bps in September, and will cut rates by another 25bps in October and December respectively</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28074</link>
      <description>On September 8th, a research report by Citic Securities stated that the U.S. August non-farm payroll data weakened once again. The July unemployment rate rose to 4.248% when rounded to three decimal places, and the August unemployment rate rose to 4.324% when rounded to three decimal places. The one-decimal-place unemployment rate was recorded at 4.3%, which was in line with market expectations. The August non-farm payroll increase was significantly below expectations, with both the government and private sectors showing weakness. In addition, U.S. employment data such as ADP and PMI employment sub-indexes all weakened this week, confirming previous views: the U.S. labor market is not as healthy as the data superficially indicates. The U.S. labor market continues to cool, and the economy continues to weaken but is not immediately heading into a recession. For the Federal Reserve, labor market risks will rise again. Citic continues its previous view and expects the Fed to cut interest r</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28074</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The U.S. long-term unemployment rate is rapidly surging, surpassing all economic recessions outside of 2020 and 2008.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28073</link>
      <description>September 8th. The data analysis released by TheKobeissiLetter shows that the long-term unemployment rate in the US is rising at an astonishingly fast pace. In August, the number of long-term unemployed people in the US surged to 1.94 million, reaching the highest level since November 2021. Since December 2022, the number of Americans who have been unemployed for 27 weeks or more has more than doubled. The proportion of individuals unemployed for more than 27 weeks has risen to 26.3%, the highest level since February 2022. In just 20 months, the number of long-term unemployed in the US has increased by nearly 10 percentage points. This rate is now higher than in all previous economic recessions except in 2020 and 2008, undoubtedly indicating a deterioration in the US job market.Over the past four months, excluding the healthcare sector, the US has lost 142,200 jobs, the highest number since 2020. US non-farm employment excluding healthcare decreased by -53,000 in May, -71,800 in June</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28073</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle has announced that native USDC and CCTP V2 will be deployed on Hyperliquid.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28072</link>
      <description>On September 8th, as per an official announcement by Circle, native USDC and CCTP V2 will be deployed on Hyperliquid. This will facilitate the usage of USDC on HyperCore and HyperEVM. Users can make institutional-grade deposits and withdrawals using Circle Mint. Meanwhile, developers can utilize CCTP V2 to enable secure cross-chain transfers of USDC between Hyperliquid and other supported blockchains. USDC will act as the core stablecoin for Hyperliquid&apos;s DeFi applications and transactions.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 10.25 million WLFI and 5.67 million BLOCK from a CEX.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28071</link>
      <description>Update, September 8: Based on the monitoring of OnchainLens, a whale has withdrawn 10.25 million WLFI tokens, which are worth $2.34 million, and 5.67 million BLOCK tokens, which are worth $528,000, from a CEX.The whale currently possesses 72.83 million WLFI tokens with a value of $16.39 million and 17.23 million BLOCK tokens with a value of $1.2 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28071</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump family&apos;s wealth surged by $1.3 billion last week, with WLFI contributing $670 million to the increase.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28070</link>
      <description>On September 8th, the Trump family witnessed a notable increase in their wealth during the past week. This was attributed to the listing of the crypto mining firm American Bitcoin (ABTC) and the gains generated by World Liberty Financial (WLFI). Their total wealth rose by $1.3 billion. WLFI added $670 million to the Trump family&apos;s net worth. Eric Trump, as a co-founder of ABTC, saw his stake in ABTC valued at over $500 million after the company&apos;s public listing last Wednesday. At that time, ABTC&apos;s stock price soared to $14 and then plummeted by more than 50% to a low of $6.24.However, this $1.3 billion does not yet encompass the approximately $4 billion worth of WLFI tokens held by the Trump family, which are currently under a lock-up period. Excluding the $4 billion WLFI tokens, the Trump family&apos;s combined net worth has now exceeded $7.7 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/28070</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>