<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:12:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Wenzhou Court in China successfully disposed of the involved virtual currency through a licensed trading platform.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23717</link>
      <description>August 8th. As per the Wenzhou Evening News, starting from December 2022, the defendant Liu employed a counterfeit digital wallet app to unlawfully obtain 544 virtual coin addresses and keys, transferring tens of thousands of virtual coins that were stolen from victims like Yang. This led to substantial financial losses.In order to find a reliable professional organization for disposal, Wang Zitai shuttled back and forth between various relevant departments for several days and finally got in touch with the Third Research Institute of the Public Security Department through the Lucheng Public Security Sub-bureau, entrusting them to select a mature professional disposal organization. When signing the entrusted agreement, he carefully examined each clause and clearly stipulated the rights and responsibilities such as detection, sale, and transfer. Eventually, with the support of a licensed exchange, the realization process was completed successfully. After completing the relevant proced</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23717</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market Trading: Block Soars Over 9%, Reveals Total BTC Holdings Reached 8,692 Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23716</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on the market data from RockFlow, during pre-market trading, Jack Dorsey, the co-founder of Twitter, saw his payment platform Block Inc (XYZ) surge by more than 9%, with the stock price currently at $83.86.According to the latest quarterly earnings report released on Thursday, Block achieved a gross profit of $2.54 billion in the second quarter, representing a 14% year-on-year increase. Block increased its holdings of Bitcoin by 108 coins, bringing the total holdings to 8692 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23716</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Trump Signs Executive Order, $12.5 Trillion Expected to Enter Market, Bitcoin Ethereum See Price Spike</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23715</link>
      <description>August 8th. On Thursday, Trump signed an executive order mandating the U.S. Department of Labor to reassess the investment eligibility of industries like private equity, real estate, and cryptocurrency, enabling their inclusion in 401(k) retirement plan investments. This action might not only infuse a substantial amount of funds into the market but also trigger a robust rally in cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH).According to reports, this executive order also instructs the Department of Labor to cooperate with the Department of the Treasury, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and other relevant agencies to study how to adjust supporting regulations to permit more types of investments into 401(k) pension plans. It is anticipated that this change will bring approximately $12.5 trillion of pension funds into the market, undoubtedly offering strong backing for cryptocurrencies and related assets.In the past, due to legal uncertainties, the majority</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23715</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIO Protocol: Staking Feature Now Locks Over 100 Million BIO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23714</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the DeSci protocol BIO Protocol declared that since the launch of the BIO token and staking feature on the Ethereum mainnet, more than 100 million BIO has been locked up till now.According to HTX market data, BIO briefly exceeded $0.1 today. It is currently trading at $0.087, with a 24-hour increase of 13.38%. On July 31st, Coinbase added support for Bio Protocol (BIO) on the Ethereum network.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Rush Investment: Holding 527.2048 Ethereum, with an average cost of approximately $3,714.91</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23713</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the Hong Kong-listed company Golden Fountain Investment (01328.HK) announced that as of the announcement date, the group holds 527.2048 Ethereum. The total cost is approximately $1.9585 million, and the average cost per Ethereum is approximately $3,714.91.According to the market data of RockFlow, Golden Fountain Investment (01328.HK) rose by 13.18% today with a trading volume of 21.5 million Hong Kong dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23713</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana-based Meme Coin BOSS Surges Over 93% in 24 Hours, Market Cap Briefly Exceeds $40 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23712</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on GMGN data, the Solana-based Meme coin BOSS witnessed a surge of over 93% within the past 24 hours. Its market value briefly exceeded $40 million and is currently around $35 million. The 24-hour trading volume reached $50.7 million.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins generally lack practical use cases and are highly volatile in price. Therefore, investment in them should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN Technology: In July, Bitcoin production was 89 coins, bringing the total Bitcoin holdings to 1511 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23711</link>
      <description>August 8th: The Nasdaq-listed company Canaan Technology announced that in July, it produced 89 Bitcoin. By the end of the month, the total number of Bitcoin it held reached 1,511 coins. The company had completed the withdrawal from its mining business in Kazakhstan. At the end of July, Canaan Technology deployed a hash rate of 7.95 EH/s, with an operational hash rate of 6.24 EH/s, and an average electricity cost of $0.042 per kWh.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23711</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackQuest is excited to announce a partnership with 0G to launch the 0G Learning Track.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23710</link>
      <description>August 8th. HackQuest announced today that it has entered into a partnership with the decentralized AI public chain 0G (Zero Gravity) and officially launched the 0G Learning Track. 0G is the world&apos;s first decentralized L1 blockchain designed specifically for AI workloads, capable of supporting the unified scheduling of storage, computing power, data, and models to achieve large-scale AI inference and deployment.This course will center around 0G&apos;s core architecture and cover modules such as the sharded data availability layer, the zero-cost storage mechanism, the SDK compatible with mainstream AI frameworks, the decentralized GPU market, the ZK verification mechanism, and cross-chain interoperability. Upon the successful completion of the course, learners will receive an official certification jointly issued by HackQuest and 0G.In addition, HackQuest will concurrently launch a Chinese technical documentation library, facilitate the localization translation of whitepapers, SDK docume</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23710</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: BTC May Undergo Chip Redistribution in the $112K-$117K Range, Breaking Above $117K to Test New High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23709</link>
      <description>August 8th. The on-chain data analyst Murphy released a market analysis, stating that BTC&apos;s breakthrough above $117,000 the previous day was significantly influenced by the favorable event of &quot;Trump signing an executive order to include cryptocurrency in the 104K.&quot; However, it was merely a short-term emotional stimulus and had not yet substantially attracted a large amount of funds. The active index of short-term investors has been continuously declining after reaching a peak in July, and there is no clear sign of an upward turning point (forming a higher high). The panic low points witnessed during the recent price corrections are also not as severe as those on December 24 and February 25, indicating that up to this point in the current market cycle, investor sentiment is generally more neutral, neither leaning towards extreme panic nor excessive optimism.According to URPD data, BTC is once again testing a key resistance level. $117,000 is the highest candle in the current entire ch</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23709</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The confirmation process of CFTC Chairman Brian Quintenz, nominated by Trump, has been stalled</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23708</link>
      <description>August 8th. According to cryptocurrency journalist Eleanor Terrett, the process of nominating Brian Quintenz, the CFTC chairman nominated by Trump, has come to a standstill. Internal emails obtained through the Freedom of Information Act showed that Quintenz might have had access to confidential CFTC information during his tenure as a director at Kalshi, a prediction market regulated by the agency. A detailed email blog post about this matter is spreading on Capitol Hill, giving rise to questions. The White House has requested the Senate Agriculture Committee to postpone the scheduled confirmation vote.Meanwhile, at the end of last month, the White House once again expressed its support for Trump&apos;s nomination of Brian Quintenz as the chairman of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). On July 31st, the White House made it clear that Quintenz still is the top candidate for the position and is expected to be confirmed promptly.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23708</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>