<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:36:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale in the cryptocurrency community has offloaded 1550 WETH, realizing a profit of $3.211 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25130</link>
      <description>On August 19th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the 2018 ETH swing trader whale 0xF89...8AEfe has completely liquidated 1550 WETH that was purchased on June 23rd at an average price of $2285, realizing a profit of $3.211 million.Over the past four years, he has carried out a total of 4 ETH swing trades and accumulated a profit of $3.739 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25130</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The blockchain game Pirate Nation will temporarily suspend full on-chain operations, and some content will be preserved through Abstract&apos;s Proof of Play Arcade.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25128</link>
      <description>On August 19th, the blockchain game Pirate Nation announced via Twitter that it will suspend full on-chain operations within the earliest 30 days. &quot;We will freeze the full on-chain operations of the Pirate Nation game, as well as the Apex and Boss chains, within the earliest 30 days starting from today. From an economic standpoint, operating two chains simultaneously is no longer viable. The exciting aspects of the game will continue to exist on the Proof of Play platform on Abstract. The platform&apos;s format enables us to gradually port different parts of the game to other chains over time and potentially even to other chains in the future. Regarding Founder&apos;s Pirates, we will conduct the final PIRATE token distribution, after which they will transition to community identity NFTs and will no longer be eligible for token claims.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Passes Two Cryptocurrency Regulation Bills Covering Exchanges and Crypto ATMs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25129</link>
      <description>August 19th. JB Pritzker, the governor of Illinois, has signed the &quot;Digital Asset and Consumer Protection Act&quot; (SB 1797) and the &quot;Digital Asset ATM Act&quot; (SB 2319). The former empowers the state&apos;s Department of Financial and Professional Regulation to regulate digital asset exchanges and related businesses, mandating that they maintain sufficient financial resources and implement cybersecurity measures. The latter centers on cryptocurrency ATMs, requiring operators to register, offer full refunds to fraud victims, cap transaction fees at 18%, and restrict daily transactions for new users to $2500.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25129</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longling Capital has once again sold 5,000 ETH today</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25127</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Longling Capital once more sold 5,000 ETH today, with a value of $21.56 million. They focus on swing trading ETH, buying at low prices and selling at high prices.Over the past two years, they have withdrawn 123,405 ETH ($290 million) from Binance at an average price of $2,349. Subsequently, they deposited 70,800 ETH ($248 million) at an average price of $3,502, making a profit of $184 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25127</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: Has Been Buying the Dip on Ethereum for Three Consecutive Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25126</link>
      <description>On August 19th, Wang Feng, the founder of Blueport Interactive, tweeted, &quot;I have been purchasing Ethereum at a lower price for three consecutive days.&quot;Previously reported, Wang Feng stated that he was bullish on Tesla last year. Now, he recommends buying Ethereum. Trump&apos;s new encryption policy and the release of liquidity, Bitcoin being regarded as digital gold, traditional funds embracing the programmability of cryptographic assets, and in the &quot;first to reach consensus&quot; track, only Ethereum has an advantage. This is also why many players are competing for the first place.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25126</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized Exchange Holdings of ETH Drop to a 9-Year Low, Tom Lee Says ETH Rose from $30 to $1500 After Last Similar Low</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25125</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as reported by Cointelegraph, the balance of ETH on centralized exchanges reaches a 9-year low. Tom Lee, the new chairman of BitMine&apos;s board, stated that the last time the ETH balance was this low, ETH was priced at $30 and then rose to $1,500.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25125</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Whales Received 510 BTC from FalconX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25124</link>
      <description>August 19th. According to the monitoring of Onchain Lens, two whales purchased 510 BTC from FalconX.The bc1qgf Whale: bought 300 BTC, with a value of $34.71 million. In the past month, this whale has accumulated 1,521 BTC (worth $176.27 million).The bc1qgz Whale: acquired 210 BTC, valued at $24.30 million. During the last 10 days, this whale has accumulated 466.66 BTC (worth $54.07 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25124</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet has deposited 1,997,000 USDC into HyperLiquid and taken a 10x leveraged short position on BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25123</link>
      <description>On August 19th, as monitored by Onchain Lens, a new wallet deposited 1.997 million USDC into HyperLiquid and initiated a 10x leveraged short position on BTC. The position value reached $19.95 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25123</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Over 90% of OKB Migration to Ethereum L1 Completed</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25122</link>
      <description>On August 19th, based on official sources and on-chain data, more than 90% of OKB on Ethereum L1 has completed the cross-chain swap. This OKB cross-chain swap is a part of OKEx&apos;s implementation of the &quot;Native Gas Token - OKB Economic Model Upgrade&quot; announced on August 13th. Subsequently, OKB will exist in a new cross-chain mode across multiple chains and serve as the X Layer&apos;s native Gas token. The X Layer Layer 2 network is reported to be a highly flexible, global on-chain ecosystem that bridges the Euro-DeFi and Ethereum communities, with the vision of bringing everything on-chain.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25122</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD.AI is pleased to announce its official launch. Points earned from deposits will be used for future airdrops and public offering quotas.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25121</link>
      <description>On August 19th, USD.AI, a stablecoin protocol that provides credit to AI, announced its official launch. Users are able to deposit USDC on the Arbitrum network in order to exchange it for USDai. Subsequently, they can further pledge to obtain sUSDai. Depositors will receive points, which will be utilized for future airdrops and public sale quotas.Earlier reports indicated that USD.AI completed a Series A financing round worth $13.4 million, with Framework Ventures taking the lead and Bullish, Dragonfly, Arbitrum, and others participating.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25121</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>