<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:48:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Four.Meme&apos;s New Presale USD1 Deposit Volume Surpasses $100 Million, Setting a New Fundraising Record on the BNB Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26907</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as the leading token launchpad within the BNB Chain, Four.Meme announced that the total subscription amount in US dollars for the presale project Creditlink (CDL) on its platform has exceeded 100 million dollars, thereby setting a new record for fundraising on the BNB Chain.During this presale project, two types of tokens were accepted for investment: USD1 and FORM. As of the writing time, USD1 has received investments amounting to 100,154,369 dollars. This significant milestone not only underscores the rapid growth of USD1 in on-chain fundraising but also showcases that the community, memes, and builders are jointly driving the adoption and innovation of the ecosystem.This historical breakthrough further solidifies Four.Meme&apos;s core position within the BNB Chain as a community-driven fundraising new standard and lays a solid foundation for the incubation and growth of more high-quality projects in the future.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26907</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin falls below $107,000, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach $1.127 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26906</link>
      <description>On August 29th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin drops beneath $107,000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.127 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin surpasses $110,000, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEXs will merely be $186 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not disclose the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of the liquidated contracts. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to the adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the price of the underlying asset will be influenced when it attains a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price, once reached, will experience a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26906</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US stock market continues to decline, with the Nasdaq falling by 1.00%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26905</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the U.S. stock market maintained its downward trend, with the Nasdaq declining by 1.00%.Joanne Hsu, the director of the University of Michigan Consumer Survey, said that the final value of the U.S. Consumer Confidence Index was in line with the preliminary value, showing a decrease of approximately 6% from July. Although the current index is about 11% higher than the levels in April and May, it is still at least 10% lower than it was six and twelve months ago. The decline this month was widespread among different age groups, income levels, and stock wealth groups, and the public&apos;s views on various aspects of the economy have become worse. Due to the increased concern about high prices, the purchasing conditions for durables have dropped to the lowest point in a year, and the current personal financial conditions have decreased by 7%. Expectations for business conditions and the labor market also contracted in August.However, although it is relatively calm compared to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26905</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Falls Below $4300</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26904</link>
      <description>Update: On August 29th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum fell below $4300, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 6.51%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The final value of the one-year inflation rate expectation in the U.S. in August was 4.8%, with an expected value of 5%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26903</link>
      <description>August 29th: The one-year US inflation expectation&apos;s final value in August was 4.8%. The forecast was 5%, and the previous value was 4.90%. (Xinhua Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26903</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. August University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment Index final value is 58.2, expected 58.6</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26902</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the final value of the August University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment Index in the United States was 58.2. The expected value was 58.6, and the previous value was also 58.6. (CAIXIN)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26902</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Short-Term Price Drops Below $109,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26901</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin briefly fell below $109,000, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 3.19%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26901</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market is currently focusing on the Fed&apos;s independence, while the US Dollar Index continues its upward trend.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26900</link>
      <description>August 29th: In the United States, the July PCE inflation data met expectations, which led to the continuous strengthening of the US dollar. Meanwhile, the market is closely observing President Trump&apos;s attempt to pressure the Federal Reserve to lower interest rates.Federal Reserve Governor Waller once again expressed a dovish stance. Marc Chandler, the Managing Director of Bannockburn Global Forex, stated that in the face of a deteriorating labor market, he is in favor of a September rate cut by the Federal Reserve and advocates ignoring price pressures related to tariffs. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26900</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. August Chicago PMI is 41.5, expected 46</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26899</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the August Chicago PMI in the United States was made public as 41.5. The expected value was 46, and the previous value was 47.1. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26899</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum drops below $4200, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach $1.103 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26898</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to Coinglass data, if Ethereum drops below $4200, the total liquidation strength of the long positions on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.103 billion.Conversely, if Ethereum breaks through $4450, the total liquidation strength of the short positions on mainstream CEXs will reach $680 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not provide a precise display of the number of contracts awaiting liquidation or the exact value of the contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to nearby liquidation clusters, that is, the strength. Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the price of the underlying asset will be impacted when it reaches a certain level. Higher &quot;liquidation bars&quot; indicate that when the price is reached, it will experience a stronger reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26898</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>