<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered: The stablecoin industry is expected to grow by about 8 times by the end of 2028, with stablecoins currently representing 40% of all blockchain transaction fees.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24434</link>
      <description>On August 13th, Standard Chartered Bank declared that currently stablecoins make up 40% of all blockchain transaction fees. The Ethereum network accounts for more than half of all stablecoins. It is anticipated that by the end of 2028, the stablecoin industry will expand by approximately 8 times. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24434</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has partially realized gains from Ethereum accumulated last November, making a profit of $7.6 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24432</link>
      <description>On August 13th, based on EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, the Whale address 0xe42...08A accumulated 6,918 ETH when the price was $3,613 on November 30th of the previous year. After holding it for 9 months, he took partial profits half an hour ago by transferring 2,501 ETH ($11.71 million) to Binance.His profit on ETH reached $7.6 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitdeer&apos;s self-mined Bitcoin production in July reached 282 BTC, representing a month-on-month growth of approximately 39%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24433</link>
      <description>On August 13th, the mining firm Bitdeer Technologies Group reported that the self-mined Bitcoin production in July came to 282 coins, showing a month-on-month growth of approximately 39%. This was mainly due to the deployment of SEALMINER miners, which led to a 35% increase in the self-mining hash rate to 22.3 EH/s.Furthermore, the company completed the 100 MW water-cooled conversion in Rockdale, Texas, USA, and added 159 MW of power in Bhutan and Norway. The SEALMINER A3 miner is anticipated to be mass-produced in September, with the next-generation SEAL04 chip aiming for an energy efficiency of 5 J/TH. Bitdeer&apos;s global power capacity has reached 1257 MW, and it is expected to expand further by the end of the year.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24433</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Launches Annual Award 2025, Celebrating Fifth Anniversary and Recognizing Ecosystem Builders</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24431</link>
      <description>August 13th, BNB Chain announced the commencement of the &quot;BNB Chain Annual Awards 2025&quot; as a special initiative to mark its fifth anniversary. The purpose of this awards program is to recognize outstanding projects and builders in the Web3 field who are driving innovation, promoting adoption, and fostering active communities.The event is divided into two stages. The nomination stage runs from August 13th at 12:00 UTC to August 20th at 12:00 UTC. The community voting stage is from August 27th at 12:00 UTC to September 3rd at 12:00 UTC. The final list of winners will be announced on September 5th at 12:00 UTC, and the date of the award ceremony will be determined later.This edition features 5 award categories, namely Rising Star, AI Pioneer, Trading Titan, New Horizon, and Most Engaging Product. During the voting period, each valid wallet can cast 3 votes per day per award category, and it requires a balance of no less than 0.01 BNB (snapshot taken on September 3rd).BNB Chain state</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24431</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameSquare will publicly purchase up to $2.5 million worth of Animecoin to expand its cryptocurrency treasury</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24429</link>
      <description>On August 13th, GameSquare Holdings, Inc. (traded on Nasdaq as GAME) announced a new strategic partnership today with the Animecoin Foundation. The Animecoin Foundation is a non-commercial entity that backs the Animecoin ecosystem. This cooperation will enhance GameSquare&apos;s standing in the Web3 space by adding high-potential digital assets to the company&apos;s balance sheet and positioning the company within the rapidly expanding global market.In conjunction with the Animecoin Foundation and its early contributors, such as Azuki (an anime company based in Los Angeles operating Anime.com and developing original intellectual property), GameSquare will purchase up to $2.5 million worth of Animecoin on the open market, thereby expanding its crypto-native treasury with another digital asset that holds significant cultural value and has high promise.Under the terms of the one-year agreement, GameSquare will serve as the official agent of the Animecoin Foundation and will receive $2.5 million</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24429</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Institutional Trading Volume on Coinbase Reaches 75%, Strong Institutional Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24430</link>
      <description>On August 13th, Charles Edwards, the founder of the crypto quant digital asset fund Capriole Investments, stated that Coinbase has witnessed a significant outflow of institutional funds. With US inflation cooling and the market anticipating a rate cut next month, Bitcoin has once again become the target of institutional investors. Capriole data indicates that this Tuesday, 75% of the volume on Coinbase originated from institutional investors. &quot;Each reading above 75% has led to a higher price one week later.&quot;Capriole estimates that this week, institutional &quot;excess demand&quot; is approximately 600% of the daily output, while the current daily Bitcoin production is around 450 coins. Just on Tuesday, Bitcoin corporate treasuries added 810 BTC, and the accumulation on Monday was even greater, close to 3,000 BTC. These actions took place against the backdrop of July&apos;s US Consumer Price Index (CPI) data coming in lower than expected and Bitcoin&apos;s price making a push towards its all-time high.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24430</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: High Likelihood of Fed Lowering Interest Rates by 50 Basis Points</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24428</link>
      <description>On August 13th, US Treasury Secretary Yellen stated in an interview that the Fed&apos;s interest rates should be 150 to 175 basis points lower than the current level. If the data is accurate, the Fed may start cutting rates earlier. Yellen believes that there is a possibility of a 50-basis-point rate cut by the Fed, and a series of rate cuts may commence with a 50-basis-point cut in September.When it comes to the selection of the Fed chair, she mentioned that they will conduct a review involving 10 to 11 people. She also stated that she had proposed the establishment of a &quot;Shadow Fed Chair,&quot; but now believes it is unnecessary. Additionally, Yellen believes that the Fed does not need to reintroduce large-scale asset purchases (QE).Regarding the employment report, she expressed that she does not support halting the release of the employment report but emphasized the need for reliable data. Some analysts have stated that the probability of a 50-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24428</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Adds Three Fed Chair Candidates, Including Former Fed Governor Larry Lindsey</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24427</link>
      <description>On August 13th, as per CNBC: Two government officials disclosed that the Trump administration is giving thought to 11 candidates to succeed Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell when his term comes to an end in May. The list encompasses three individuals who have never been publicly put forward before. The new candidates comprise JPMorgan&apos;s Chief Market Strategist David Zervos, the former Fed Governor Larry Lindsey, and BlackRock&apos;s Chief Investment Officer of Global Fixed Income Rick Rieder.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24427</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tron address recently withdrew a total of $1,172,000 worth of BGB from Bitget.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24426</link>
      <description>On August 13th, as monitored by lookonchain, multiple addresses have been accumulating BGB recently:· The address 0x8900 withdrew 192,668 BGB from Bitget within the past 2 months (approximately $936,000).· The address 0x171D withdrew 30,607 BGB from Bitget 2 days ago (approximately $134,000).· The address 0x7C9C withdrew 20,980 BGB from Bitget in the past 3 months (approximately $102,000).It is worth noting that Bitget has burned a total of 860 million BGB in the past 8 months (approximately $5.25 billion), reducing the total supply by 43%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24426</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company LIXTE Biotechnology will allocate up to 25% of the company&apos;s financial reserves to cryptocurrency, pending approval.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24425</link>
      <description>August 13th. The clinical-stage pharmaceutical company LIXTE Biotechnology Holdings, Inc. (with Nasdaq codes: LIXT and LIXTW) announced today that its board of directors has given the green light to a strategic capital allocation plan. This plan will involve integrating cryptocurrency into the company&apos;s financial reserves. The board has authorized allocating up to 25% of the company&apos;s financial reserves to cryptocurrency, such as Bitcoin and other digital assets, on a case-by-case basis.The timing and extent of such transactions will be contingent upon market conditions at the time and other strategic factors. LIXTE will continuously keep a close eye on the developments in the digital asset space and maintain the flexibility to adjust its holdings. The company intends to have all cryptocurrency assets held by fully regulated and compliant custodians. All future transactions will strictly comply with relevant financial, legal, and auditing regulations to ensure transparency, security,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24425</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>