<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:31:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A Bitcoin OG Whale Keeps Reallocating to ETH, Ethereum&apos;s Total Holdings Valued at $1.06 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25985</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as monitored by OnchainLens, within the past 3 hours, a certain Bitcoin OG whale once more carried out a swap where 1,276 BTC were exchanged for ETH. This transaction was valued at $1.4709 billion. Currently, the OG whale holds 221,600 ETH, with a value of $1.06 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25985</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Coinbase User Funds Theft Hacker」 Buys 38,126 SOL at an average price of $208.7</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25984</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, within the past hour, the &quot;hacker who stole funds from Coinbase users&quot; swapped 7.957 million DAI for USDC and conducted a cross-chain transfer to Solana, purchasing 38,126 SOL at a purchase price of $208.7.The hacker:In May, sold 26,347 ETH and received 68.18 million DAI, with an average selling price of $2,588.In July, spent 14.865 million DAI to repurchase 5,513 ETH at a price of $2,696.Today, used 7.957 million DAI to buy 38,126 SOL at a price of $208.7.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: The bull market cycle is coming to an end, and my own ETH trading journey has effectively concluded</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25983</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Trader Eugene Ng Ah Sio shared in his personal channel that it appears we have reached the climax of the bull market cycle that began in January 2023. I expect this phase to last no more than a few months. Every global marginal buyer is to some extent turning towards and investing in cryptocurrency. Both Bitcoin and Ethereum have reached new all-time highs. The high target I set for myself of an Ethereum/Bitcoin exchange rate of 0.04 has also been accomplished, indicating to me that the trading of ETH has effectively come to an end.I will no longer adopt an aggressive approach - no more large-scale Martingale momentum trades. The strategy focus is shifting from capital accumulation to capital preservation. I may miss out on any subsequent market frenzy, but that&apos;s fine because these fluctuations no longer match my trading system. This does not mean I have exited all positions and gone short (on the contrary, I am still holding long positions), but the net position siz</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 04:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25983</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea: Status Network will first offer LINEA token yield farming</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25982</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Linea&apos;s official blog announced that Status Network, which combines native ETH rewards, stablecoin rewards, and native application fee commissions, will be the first to provide LINEA token staking. Users are able to deposit LINEA and SNT tokens to obtain increased LINEA token rewards.BlockBeats previously reported that on August 20, 2024, Status was collaborating with Linea, supported by Consensys, to launch a Layer 2 rollup solution. The two parties are jointly developing a Layer 2 network that will operate in parallel with Linea&apos;s zkEVM chain, named Status Network. Status contributors will interact with Linea&apos;s open-source code and actively participate in managing its codebase to maintain a parallel version.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25982</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Major &quot;Bankruptcy&quot; Contract Whales Current Positions Overview, AguilaTrade 40x Long on Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25981</link>
      <description>On August 24th, based on the monitoring of HyperInsight, the current positions of the three major contract trading whales who had previously gone through a &quot;bankruptcy&quot; event (losing tens of millions of dollars on the books and ending up with zero), namely James Wynn, AguilaTrades, and the &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio, are as follows:James Wynn has liquidated his 25x long position in ETH and currently holds approximately $240,000 worth of DOGE with a 10x long position. The entry price was $0.23963, and he has incurred a net loss of $226,000 in the past 30 days.AguilaTrades has closed the 25x short position he opened at the all-time high of ETH. Currently, he holds around $2.82 million worth of BTC with a 40x long position. The entry price was $115,077, and the liquidation price was $113,640. He has suffered a net loss of $6.69 million in the past 30 days.The &quot;insider trader&quot; @qwatio has closed his 3x short position in XPL and is</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25981</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Launches WLFI Perpetual Contract Pre-market Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25980</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to official information, Gate has now initiated the pre-market trading of WLFI perpetual contracts (settled in USDT), with support for leverage ranging from 1 to 10 times.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25980</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odin.fun Developers Release Smart Contract Public Audit Report</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25979</link>
      <description>On August 24th, Bob Bodily, the developer of the Bitcoin ecosystem trading platform Odin.fun, presented the public audit report of Odin.fun&apos;s smart contract. He declared that following the receipt of the preliminary report from an external auditor, the platform had resolved all critical, high-priority, and medium-priority issues.BlockBeats had previously reported that on August 13th, the Bitcoin ecosystem trading platform Odin.fun announced the suspension of trading to investigate recent platform withdrawal activities and would keep users updated on the investigation progress. It seemed that the Odin.fun platform had a vulnerability, with approximately 60 BTC being transferred abnormally.On April 14th, Bob Bodily, the developer of Odin.fun, cleared out all assets on the Odin platform, which were suspected to have been stolen. Trading and withdrawals were stopped on that day to assess the extent of the hack.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25979</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Aave to Receive 7% of WLFI Total Token Supply」 Sparks Ongoing Dispute, Both Sides Stick to Their Guns with No Resolution</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25978</link>
      <description>August 24th witnessed a disagreement between the Aave official and the WLFI team regarding &quot;Aave will receive 7% of the WLFI total token supply,&quot; which triggered a significant price fluctuation of the AAVE token. The timeline of this event is as follows:On December 6th, 2024, the WLFI team proposed &quot;Launching Aave V3 Instance on the Ethereum Mainnet,&quot; and it was passed on December 13th. According to the proposal, as a lending ecosystem partner of WLFI, Aave will adopt the same reserve factor mechanism in this Aave v3 instance as the main Aave instance. AaveDAO will receive 20% of the protocol fees generated by the WLFI Aave v3 instance and will receive approximately 7% of the total WLFI token supply for participating in future WLFI governance processes, liquidity mining, and driving the decentralization of the WLFI platform.Last evening at 8:30 PM, Aave founder Stani.eth responded to doubts about &quot;Is the WLFI partnership with AAVE still valid? Are they really building on Aave? Ther</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25978</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Bought 24,959 ETH 9 Years Ago, Has Earned a Whopping $102 Million Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25977</link>
      <description>On August 24th, as monitored by Onchainlens, a whale deposited 1,400 ETH ($6.63 million) into Kraken. This led to them earning a substantial profit of $102 million on their ETH holdings.Nine years ago, this whale spent a total of $258,000 to purchase 24,959 ETH from Kraken and ShapeShift. Currently, they still hold 13,477 ETH, which is worth $64.52 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25977</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROMPT Surges Above $0.31, Marking a 114% Increase in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25976</link>
      <description>On August 24th, according to HTX market data, PROMPT (Wayfinder) witnessed a significant surge and broke through $0.31. It is currently priced at $0.311, with a 24-hour increase of 114% and a market capitalization of $290 million.Yesterday, Wayfinder released its Open Alpha, enabling users to access its encrypted AI agent and engage in cross-chain transactions, deployment, and exploration.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 02:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>