<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:21:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: The current Bitcoin sell-off is led by short-term holders, with over 85% of on-chain volume coming from new buyers</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22819</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Glassnode announced that within the past 24 hours, the majority of Bitcoin (BTC) on-chain spending originated from Short-Term Holders (STH). The on-chain spending by Short-Term Holders (STH) was $18.24 billion (85.5%), while for Long-Term Holders (LTH) it was $3.1 billion (14.5%), with a total spending amount of $21.34 billion.This shows that this round of selling was mainly driven by recent buyers rather than long-term investors.Note: Spending refers to the total amount of Bitcoin that was moved or utilized on the blockchain during a specific period and is not merely &quot;selling&quot; or &quot;transaction volume.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22819</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX DAO Achieves First Community Listing Recommendation Vote with Over 1.2 Trillion HTX Tokens, HTX Monthly Growth Reaches 44.3%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22817</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on an announcement on the official social media of HTX DAO, since June 30th when HTX DAO launched its listing recommendation governance mechanism, the total voting amount has reached 1.1916 trillion HTX. The on-chain total voting amount has neared 3 million USDT. Driven by the successful implementation of this mechanism, HTX has achieved remarkable growth. There was a monthly maximum increase of 44.3%, the TVL has increased by more than 42 million USDT, and there are over 12,000 new HTX holding users.HTX DAO stated that the final listing results and voting rewards of the recent listing recommendation vote will be announced and distributed soon.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22817</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget and Fibonacci Capital Deepen Cooperation to Strengthen Liquidity Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22818</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Bitget announced an even more extensive deepening of its partnership with the high-frequency trading and market-making institution Fibonacci Capital. As part of this collaboration, Fibonacci will offer institutional-level liquidity support to projects listed on the Bitget platform and assist potential Web3 projects in obtaining early-stage resources to improve their market performance. This partnership is intended to optimize the Bitget trading ecosystem, create a more efficient market environment for traders, and enhance liquidity and price transparency.Furthermore, Fibonacci Capital&apos;s self-developed InfoFi platform is an AI-driven market analysis system that enables real-time monitoring of token liquidity, order flow, market impact, and other aspects. This platform will provide institutional-level data dashboards and execution strategy support for projects listed on Bitget.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22818</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the first day of the Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation Ordinance coming into effect, some OTC stores have temporarily closed due to unclear regulations.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22816</link>
      <description>August 1st. According to a report by Techub, on the very first day when the Hong Kong stablecoin regulations came into official effect, some Hong Kong cryptocurrency over-the-counter (OTC) offline stores, such as One Satoshi, closed temporarily out of concerns about violating regulatory requirements. Nevertheless, some OTC offline stores decided to keep operating. The operators of certain stores that chose to remain open hold the view that OTC activities involving non-Hong Kong legal tender issued overseas (like USDT) are not within the regulatory purview of the regulations.Based on the essence of Hong Kong&apos;s common law, if there is no explicit precedent determining stablecoin OTC activities as illegal, OTC businesses may still be able to carry on their operations.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Bitcoin Pullback Initiates August Market, Selling Pressure Unresolved, Direction Uncertain, Near-Term Facing Key Inflection Point</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22815</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to the analysts of BiyaPay, at the start of August, the cryptocurrency market experienced an initial pullback. Currently, BTC/USDT is priced at $115,547.97, with a 24-hour decline of -2.4%. In the short term, it is still fluctuating within the range of $114,000 to $118,000. The moving average system is closely stuck together, and the market is facing a directional decision.It is worth noting that early last weekend, a large holder sold more than 80,000 BTC (approximately $9.6 billion) through Galaxy Digital OTC transactions, which exerted significant selling pressure on the market. However, BTC quickly stabilized near $119,000, demonstrating the strong liquidity absorption capacity of the market.BiyaPay Analyst Insights:- Currently, BTC is still in a consolidation phase since the end of June, with $115,000 as a key support level.- The resistance above is in the range of $118,200 to $120,000, and a breakthrough is expected to challenge the previous high.-</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22815</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: FDIC Still Trying to Block Public Crypto Banking Charter Application</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22814</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Paul Grewal, the Chief Legal Officer of Coinbase, disclosed that a motion has been submitted to a federal court, accusing the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) of systematically impeding the disclosure of documents related to &quot;Operation Chokepoint 2.0.&quot; The court documents indicate that despite being ordered to cooperate four times, the FDIC still refused to fully disclose the &quot;suspension letters&quot; that requested banks to suspend cryptocurrency-related transactions between 2020 and 2024. Internal policy documents confirm that the FDIC instructed its staff to &quot;withhold in full&quot; documents covered by the exemption clause of the Freedom of Information Act without differentiating between factual and analytical materials. Coinbase alleges that the agency has adopted an &quot;extremely narrow interpretation&quot; and only searched for documents submitted to the Inspector General&apos;s office, resulting in the omission of numerous key records. During a January hearing, the FDIC admi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22814</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Securities Raises Target Stock Price for Kakao Pay and Others, Citing Potential of Korean Won Stablecoin to Drive Benefits for Fintech Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22813</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Samsung Securities has designated Kakao Pay and NHN KCP as the preferred targets in the Korean Won Stablecoin sector and has raised their target stock prices by 23.4% and 24.8% respectively. Samsung Securities pointed out that if South Korea allows non-bank fintech companies to issue stablecoins in the future, large platforms like Kakao Pay will have a significant first-mover advantage and it is optimistic about their potential to generate income through stablecoin circulation. (Fnnews)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22813</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The whale address that previously bought ETH for SharpLink withdrew 14,520 ETH from a CEX nearly 9 hours ago.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22812</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, Whale 0xF436 is engaged in the purchase of ETH. It has withdrawn 14,520 ETH (amounting to 53 million USD) from a CEX within the past 9 hours.Just 5 days prior to this, this whale made a purchase of 38,606 ETH (valued at 148.44 million USD) for SharpLink.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22812</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Powell Is Too Stubborn, Fed Board Should Take Over His Duties</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22811</link>
      <description>On August 1st, President Trump said on the Truth platform, &quot;Powell, a stubborn and foolish person, must immediately make a significant cut in interest rates. If he continues to refuse, the board should take over and take the action that is widely known to be necessary.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22811</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: $105,000 Key Support Area for Next</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22810</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on Sentora (formerly IntoTheBlock) data, currently only around 7.9% of Bitcoin&apos;s circulating supply is in a loss state. This indicates that the current price range up to $121,000 is a region with a high concentration of underwater positions.If the price continues to retrace, the area around $105,000 may become a crucial support zone. This is because this range has witnessed historical buying activities of approximately 900,000 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22810</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>