<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Plasma Fixed Savings Quota of 250 million USDT Sold Out, More Quotas May Be Opened Soon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25380</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Binance&apos;s Launchpool launched the earn-as-you-go coin Plasma USDT fixed-term product (with limited time and quantity) at 20:00 (GMT+8) tonight. Within approximately 50 minutes, the $250 million USDT quota was sold out. Binance announced that more quota may be opened soon, and participating users can receive daily USDT rewards and XPL rewards (after TGE).</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25380</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USDC Treasury has burned approximately 74.4 million USDC on the Solana network.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25378</link>
      <description>On August 20th, as monitored by Whale Alert, the USDC Treasury has incinerated 74,406,039 USDC on the Solana network, with an approximate value of $74.4 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25378</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X Layer&apos;s on-chain transaction volume in the last 24 hours reached $19.2 million, with a total of 12.51 thousand transactions.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25379</link>
      <description>On August 20th, based on geckoterminal data, the on-chain transaction volume of X Layer in the past 24 hours reached $19.2 million, experiencing a 47.73% decrease compared to the previous period and having a total of 12,510 transactions.The on-chain Meme coin OKAY of X Layer is currently valued at $6 million, with a 73% price increase in the last 24 hours and a trading volume of $3.74 million. The on-chain Meme coin XDOG of X Layer is currently valued at $6.74 million and has a 24-hour trading volume of $2.56 million.According to l2beat data, the Total Value Locked (TVL) of X Layer Network is currently at $39 million, which is significantly lower than the recent high of $88 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25379</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito AI Announces H1 Roadmap Update, New Unlocking, and Growth Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25377</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Kaito AI presented the Kaito Roadmap H1 update, a new unlock, and a growth plan. In the next 12 months, the emphasis will be on strengthening on-chain and social integration, optimizing the leaderboard and Kaito Earn to enhance matching efficiency and investment returns. Additionally, the development of a multi-platform distribution network will be advanced. Kaito also announced the launch of Kaito Venture, which will invest in and expedite crypto applications capable of leveraging its distribution advantage, further strengthening the value loop of the ecosystem.Founder Yu Hu stated that Kaito is at a critical innovation juncture and will, based on the vision of &quot;financializing information,&quot; drive industry development through core functions such as sovereign data ownership, market-driven signals, and an open information market. Kaito plans to use a strategically reserved 6 million KAITO tokens to incentivize creators and ecosystem development while also exploring long</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25377</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Federal Reserve Board Member Powell Must Resign Immediately</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25376</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Trump issued a statement on Truth Social, stating, &quot;The Federal Reserve Board Member Powell must resign without delay!!!&quot;President Trump&apos;s unwavering ally and the Director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency, Bill Pulte, sent a letter to DOJ official Ed Martin on August 15th. This letter insinuated that the Federal Reserve Board Member Powell might have committed criminal acts. According to a copy of the letter made public by Bloomberg, the letter alleges that Powell &quot;forged bank documents and financial records in order to obtain more favorable loan terms, potentially violating criminal law amounting to mortgage fraud.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Launches Season 11 of MVB (Most Valuable Builder), a Ten-Week Global Residency Program Supporting Web3 Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25375</link>
      <description>On August 20th, BNB Chain, in conjunction with YZi Labs and CMC Labs, announced the commencement of the 11th season of the &quot;Most Valuable Builder&quot; (MVB) program. This program has been upgraded from a four-week incubation to a ten-week global offline residency support program. The projects selected in this season will have the chance to receive up to $500,000 in investment, receive top-notch mentorship, present their progress at the Dubai Binance Blockchain Week roadshow, and have the opportunity to connect offline with global hubs in Dubai, San Francisco, Singapore, and New York.In the previous season, MVB10, it attracted over 500 applications, and 15 projects were incubated, covering areas such as AI, DeFi, DePIN, DeSci, payments, and RWA. The selected teams participated in a two-day intensive incubation event last week in New York and showcased their project progress at the New York Stock Exchange Demo Day.The deadline for the 11th season of MVB is September 6, 2025, and the offl</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25375</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI CFO: Will Consider Going Public at Some Point in the Future</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25374</link>
      <description>On August 20th, Sarah Friar, the CFO of OpenAI, stated that they will consider going public at some point in the future. (Jinse)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25374</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s latest DGC airdrop single-claim profit is approximately $27.5</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25373</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to market data, DecentralGPT (DGC) has been listed on Binance Alpha. Currently, its market capitalization is $8.6 million. Each eligible user is able to receive an airdrop of 500,000 DGC tokens. The estimated single bonus income for this airdrop activity is approximately $27.5 based on the current price.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25373</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list SAPIEN perpetual contract trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25372</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to an official announcement, Gate will list the trading of SAPIEN perpetual contracts (settled in USDT) on August 21st at 01:10 (UTC+8) and support leverage ranging from 1 to 20x.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25372</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto startup Legion raises $5 million in funding, with VanEck and Brevan Howard Digital as lead investors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25371</link>
      <description>On August 20th, according to a report in Fortune, the cryptocurrency startup Legion has successfully completed a financing round of $5 million. The round was led by VanEck and Brevan Howard Digital, with participation from Kraken, as well as the venture capital arms of Coinbase and Crypto.com. Legion declined to disclose valuation details. This funding round will be used for equity and token warrants.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25371</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>