<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:42:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Faraday Future launches the first C10 Treasury Program on the US Stock Market and introduces the C10 Index</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24905</link>
      <description>August 17th. According to official channels, Faraday Future has put forward and launched the &quot;EAI+Crypto&quot; Dual Flywheel &amp; Dual Bridging Eco Strategy. The company intends to bring the EAI EV asset onto the blockchain, establishing an ecosystem encompassing EAI Mobility + Web3 + Blockchain Technology + Crypto Asset Applications.In addition, Faraday Future has officially initiated the C10 Index, which is the first market crypto asset basket index launched by a US-listed company (excluding stablecoins).Faraday Future has also concurrently released the C10 Treasury, a treasury product based on the &quot;C10 Index.&quot; In the first phase, it aims to purchase a total of $5 to $10 billion worth of crypto assets after obtaining the necessary funds. The initial allocation amount is $30 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24905</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Trading Volume Continues to Shrink: ETH, XRP, ADA Currently in Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24904</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on CoinGecko data, in the past 24 hours, Upbit&apos;s trading volume has decreased to $14.68 billion. Among them, the ETH/KRW trading pair accounted for 15.14% of the volume and ranked first in the Korean won trading market. The other top five in terms of volume are: XRP, ADA, BTC, PROVE.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shanghai court in China has concluded a digital collectible fraud case, and the main culprit has been sentenced to eight and a half years in prison.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24903</link>
      <description>August 17th. According to the official WeChat account of the First Intermediate People&apos;s Court of Shanghai (Shanghai No. 1 Court), the court has recently concluded a second-instance criminal case related to digital collectibles. The defendants, Wang and Liu, under the pretext of operating a digital collectibles platform, issued digital collectibles whose underlying electronic images were generated by AI. They falsely promoted the appreciation prospects of these digital collectibles and promised a &quot;50% off&quot; guaranteed return of principal. The court ruled that Wang and Liu were guilty of fundraising fraud and sentenced them to eight years and six months and seven years and two months of imprisonment respectively.In October to December 2023, Wang and Liu registered a technology company in Shanghai and focused on a digital collectibles platform. During this period, Wang and Liu used the platform and WeChat groups to publicly promote the sale of digital collectibles to the general public.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24903</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has abandoned the queuing process to withdraw their staked assets, opting to sell 4242.4 stETH in exchange for 4231 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24902</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale directly conducted a transaction where 4242.4 stETH was exchanged for 4231 ETH (valued at $18.74 million), and this ETH was deposited into Kraken for sale. During this direct exchange, a loss of 11.4 ETH (approximately $50,500) was incurred.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 04:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24902</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary CEO: Bitcoin Expected to Reach $150,000 This Year, Ethereum&apos;s Ability to Sustain Its Growth Trajectory Remains Uncertain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24901</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per Decrypt, Steven McClurg, the CEO of Canary Capital, stated that Bitcoin might rise to $150,000 by the end of this year; however, it will encounter a new bear market in 2026. Meanwhile, he is doubtful about whether the recent rise of Ethereum can be maintained.This Bitcoin prediction arrives as the cryptocurrency market is approaching its all-time high and institutional investors are pouring into Bitcoin ETFs.He attributes this current rise to the growth of ETF demand and the expansion of the institutional buyer base, which includes sovereign wealth funds, pension funds, and corporate treasuries.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 03:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24901</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Base Layer Token Definitive (EDGE) Market Cap Briefly Surpasses $150 Million, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24900</link>
      <description>On August 17th, based on GMGN market data, the on-chain transaction execution platform Definitive&apos;s token EDGE briefly reached a market capitalization of over $1.5 billion. Currently, it stands at $1.46 billion and has hit a new all-time high with a 24-hour increase of 24.58%.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 03:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24900</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 wallet addresses will collectively swap 4806 ETH for LINK, approximately $21.23 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24896</link>
      <description>On August 17th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, 5 wallet addresses that are likely to belong to the same entity carried out a swap. They exchanged 4806 ETH for 938,489 LINK, with an approximate value of $21.23 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Suspends Monero Deposits Due to 51% Attack</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24899</link>
      <description>August 17th, according to an official communication, Kraken has declared that as a security measure, it has temporarily ceased Monero (XMR) deposits because it detected that a single mining pool was controlling more than 50% of the network&apos;s total hashrate. Such a concentration of hashrate may pose a potential threat to network integrity.Kraken is closely observing the situation and will resume deposits once security is verified. XMR trading and withdrawals are still operating normally.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24899</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand Introduces Cryptocurrency Exchange Program for Foreign Tourists to Boost the Tourism Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24898</link>
      <description>On August 17th, according to the report in &quot;crowdfund insider&quot;, Thailand is scheduled to launch a new measure on Monday. This measure enables foreign tourists to convert cryptocurrency into Thai Baht for making payments. The aim is to rejuvenate the tourism industry after a decrease in the number of tourists.This initiative, named &quot;TouristDigiPay&quot;, will be announced at a press conference presided over by the Thai Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Pichai Chunhavajira. Officials from the Ministry of Finance, the Securities and Exchange Commission, the Anti-Money Laundering Office, and the Ministry of Tourism and Sports will be in attendance.The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission has completed a public consultation on using digital assets to support economic and tourism growth. The feedback period ended on August 13th.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24898</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump, Son of Former President Trump: Buy Bitcoin and Ethereum on Dips</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24897</link>
      <description>On August 17th, Eric Trump, the son of former President Donald Trump, responded on his social media platform to the news that &quot;a certain WLFI linked address spent $18.6 million to purchase 1911 ETH and 84.5 WBTC,&quot; and he said, &quot;Buy the dips.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24897</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>