<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:08:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Kamino is about to launch a new High-Yield Treasury for USDC and USDG</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26528</link>
      <description>On August 27th, in Kamino (a liquidity protocol within the Solana ecosystem), it was announced that two new high-yield USDC and USDG pools were about to be launched, which were based on Steakhouse custody.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland transferred 25,200 ETH to Coinbase, worth approximately $116 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26527</link>
      <description>On August 27th, as monitored by Whale Alert, Cumberland transferred 25,200 ETH to Coinbase Institutional approximately 5 minutes prior. The value of this transfer is around $116 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26527</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by Buyback News, OM Surges Over 7% in the Short Term, Breaking $0.25</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26526</link>
      <description>On August 27th, based on HTX market information, due to the &quot;MANTRA Officially Announces Repurchase of $25 Million Worth of OM Tokens&quot;, OM witnessed a short-term surge of more than 7% and broke through $0.25. The market capitalization of OM is currently reported to be $2.46 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26526</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio Protocol&apos;s first BioAgent Launch project, Aubrai, has now been launched on the Base network.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26525</link>
      <description>On August 27th, the first BioAgent Launch project of Bio Protocol, Aubrai, was launched on the Base network and currently has a market capitalization of $7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26525</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANTRA Announces $25 Million OM Token Buyback, Representing Approximately 10% of Circulating Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26524</link>
      <description>August 27th. MANTRA officially made an announcement regarding a $25 million OM token buyback. This was supported by major investors and stakeholders. In addition, Inveniam&apos;s previous investment of $20 million brought the total committed funds to $45 million.The buyback plan will be carried out by MANTRA AG. It will be executed over several months through multiple centralized exchanges at a price that is close to the market price. The repurchased OM tokens will be withdrawn from the exchanges in the form of ERC20 tokens and then transferred to the MANTRA mainnet and staked to validator nodes. Based on the current price, the buyback plan involves approximately 110 million OM tokens, which accounts for around 10% of the circulating supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26524</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market prices for XPL and WLFI on Hyperliquid have dropped, with the premium over other major platforms narrowing.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26522</link>
      <description>On August 27th at 8:00 PM this evening, Hyperliquid officially announced that the marked price of the contract would adopt the regular marked price formula. After integrating with the price of perpetual contracts from external listings (if available), both the prices of XPL and WLFI in the pre-market contract market showed a decline. XPL is currently trading at $0.63 on Hyperliquid, and WLFI is trading at $0.28. The premium compared to other mainstream trading platforms has become narrower.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26522</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reuters: Despite Nvidia&apos;s Better-Than-Expected Earnings, Stock Price Could Still Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26521</link>
      <description>August 27th. Analyst Ipek Ozkardeskaya from Swissquote Bank stated that although Nvidia (NVDA.O) reported earnings that exceeded expectations after the close on Wednesday, the company&apos;s stock price could still decline. She said, &quot;Investors may seize the opportunity of positive earnings to take profits, which could lead to an accelerated price pullback.&quot; Ozkardeskaya suggested that investors might consider diversifying away from expensive US tech stocks and looking into other regions such as Europe and the UK, or moving into more defensive sectors. She believed that gold, US treasuries, and investment-grade bonds are also good choices as these assets may benefit from future rate cuts. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26521</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary Calls for Federal Reserve Internal Review, Calls Out Cook Mortgage Fraud Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26523</link>
      <description>On August 27th, U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson once again called on Wednesday for Federal Reserve Chairman Powell to carry out an internal review of the Federal Reserve and include the mortgage fraud allegations against Fed Governor Cook in the review. Benson said in an interview with the Fox Business Channel: &quot;I encourage Chairman Powell to conduct an internal review prior to conducting an external review as this is an issue that needs to be addressed.&quot; He was referring to the incident involving Fed Governor Cook. Benson stated: &quot;We have not heard her say that she did not do it. She just kept saying that the President cannot fire her. If a Federal Reserve official commits mortgage fraud, they should not hold a position at one of the main financial regulatory agencies in the United States. The Fed is an irresponsible institution, and its relationship with the American people depends on high trust, and events like this undermine that trust.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26523</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Enterprise increased its holdings by acquiring 120 Bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 1008 coins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26520</link>
      <description>On August 27th, according to Businesswire, the US-listed DDC Enterprise increased its stake in 120 bitcoins, and currently the total bitcoin holdings have reached 1008 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Ethereum Hits New High as Momentum Shifts, Surging Market Leverage Raises Tail Risk</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26519</link>
      <description>On August 27th, Vetle Lunde, the research director of K33, stated that a long-term holder exchanged 22,400 BTC for ETH. This action propelled Ethereum to a new all-time high last week, demonstrating a shift in market momentum. However, Bitcoin&apos;s recent price weakness may not have ended yet. The surge in leverage and significant fund rotation to Ethereum continue to put pressure on Bitcoin in the short term. Bitcoin&apos;s perpetual futures nominal open interest (OI) has soared to a two-year high, exceeding 310,000 BTC (approximately $34 billion). It has increased by 41,607 BTC in the past two months and had a spike of 13,472 BTC over the weekend, indicating a potential turning point. Bitcoin&apos;s annualized funding rate has jumped from 3% to nearly 11%, showing increasing aggressiveness in taking long positions during a period of relative price stagnation.Lunde stated that the current situation is similar to the leverage accumulation in the summers of 2023 and 2024. Both events triggered vio</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26519</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>