<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:54:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid is planning to automatically refund users affected by API issues</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22510</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to market information, Hyperliquid intends to automatically refund users who were affected by API issues.BlockBeats reported earlier today that Hyperliquid announced on Discord that from 22:10 to 22:47 (UTC+8) last night, the API server encountered problems, resulting in delays when orders were sent to the node. This was due to a surge in traffic. There was no hacking or exploitation involved. The issue has been resolved, and further improvements are planned for the future. In addition, various levels of the technical stack will also implement additional protection measures to detect API server issues and prevent users from encountering unexpected problems.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22510</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to strong data-driven momentum, the US Dollar is poised to achieve its longest winning streak since February.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22509</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the latest data indicates that the U.S. economy is robust, and the dollar is moving towards its longest consecutive upward trend since February. The Bloomberg Dollar Spot Index increased by 0.3%, reaching its highest level since June 23rd, with the index rising for five consecutive trading days.The U.S. economic growth and inflation data released on Wednesday were both higher than expected, which supported the Federal Reserve&apos;s hawkish stance. In the second quarter, U.S. economic activity rebounded as consumer spending picked up slightly, and the Fed&apos;s preferred inflation indicator, core PCE, rose by 2.5% year-on-year.Meanwhile, ADP private sector employment data shows that the labor market remains strong. Valentin Marinov, the head of G10 currency strategy at Credit Agricole CIB, said, &quot;The market may view this data as suggesting that the Fed&apos;s future rate cuts will be slower and more postponed. If Federal Reserve Chair Powell continues to maintain his current relative</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22509</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 Capital is currently exploring issuing USD loans backed by Bitcoin as collateral.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22508</link>
      <description>On Wednesday, July 30th, according to Bloomberg, sources familiar with the matter stated that Twenty One Capital is in the process of exploring a strategic plan to offer dollar loans with Bitcoin serving as collateral. Twenty One Capital, which is backed by Cantor Fitzgerald, has currently increased its Bitcoin holdings to at least 43,500 BTC, which is about 1,500 BTC more than was originally anticipated.The company recently acquired approximately 5,800 BTC from the stablecoin issuer Tether. With the current prices, the total value of its holdings is now approximately $5.13 billion. Established in April of this year, the company aims to build one of the largest Bitcoin reserves in the world. Its backers include Tether, Bitfinex, and SoftBank. The merger plan with the SPAC company Cantor Equity Partners is progressing smoothly and is expected to go public in the near future.As digital assets are increasingly being incorporated into corporate balance sheets, public companies and fund</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22508</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Ethereum Reserve Concept Stocks Soar, with BMNR Up by 3.67%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22507</link>
      <description>On July 30th, according to Rockflow market data, the US Ethereum reserves concept stocks witnessed a general increase. These include:· SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) increased by 0.72%;· Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) rose by 3.67%;· GameSquare (GAME.US) went up by 3.58%;· Bit Digital (BTBT.US) gained by 0.99%;· Coinbase (COIN.US) rose by 2.07%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22507</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three major U.S. stock indices opened higher, with Coinbase up 2.9%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22506</link>
      <description>On July 30, when the U.S. stock market opened, the Dow increased by 8 points. The S&amp;P 500 went up by 0.12%, and the Nasdaq rose by 0.19%. Coinbase (COIN.O) rose by 2.9%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22506</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canaan Inc: Bitcoin Designated as Company&apos;s Primary Long-Term Reserve Asset</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22505</link>
      <description>On July 30th, Canaan Inc. (CAN.O) announced that Bitcoin has been designated as the company&apos;s principal long-term reserve asset.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22505</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Issues 750 Million USDC on the Solana Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22503</link>
      <description>On July 30th, as monitored by Whale Alert, Circle issued a total of 750 million USDC in three distinct transactions on the Solana network.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22503</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Cryptocurrency Report to Embrace DeFi, But Lacks Progress on Government Reserve Bitcoin or Other Digital Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22504</link>
      <description>July 30th. According to DoinDesk, based on a highly anticipated report preview that is set to be released by the White House today, the Trump administration&apos;s friendly stance towards cryptocurrency indicates that the United States is on the brink of a &quot;Crypto Golden Age&quot; - the federal level will promptly initiate digital asset trading and actively embrace DeFi.In a brief summary document by the President&apos;s Working Group on Financial Markets, many of the points emphasized have been progressing in the comprehensive legislative agenda for cryptocurrency formulated by the Trump administration, such as the GENIUS Act (aimed at regulating stablecoins) and the Clarity Act (focused on regulating the crypto market).One aspect that is not yet included - at least not mentioned in the report preview - is specific details regarding the progress and plans of the federal government regarding holding Bitcoin or other digital assets in reserves. However, for crypto practitioners who have endured mo</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Crypto Asset Group Releases Digital Finance Promotion Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22502</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the Digital Asset Market Policy Working Group established by President Trump of the United States released a report on Wednesday. It called on federal regulatory agencies to utilize existing authorities to establish clearer rules for digital asset trading and to streamline the process of introducing new financial products.The White House stated in the briefing: &quot;By implementing these recommendations, policymakers can ensure that the United States takes the lead in the blockchain revolution and ushers in the crypto golden age.&quot; The working group was established in accordance with an executive order signed by Trump in January of this year. The report covers various issues in the digital asset space, including calling on Congress to pass the &quot;Digital Asset Market Clarity Act&quot; to address regulatory gaps, authorizing the Commodity Futures Trading Commission to regulate the &quot;spot market for non-securities digital assets,&quot; and supporting the development of decentralized financi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22502</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken&apos;s Q2 Revenue Increases 18% Year-over-Year to $412 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22501</link>
      <description>On July 30th, the cryptocurrency exchange platform Kraken announced that its second-quarter revenue has seen an increase. However, with a growing market share, the adjusted earnings have slightly declined.The company stated that its second-quarter revenue rose by 18% compared to the same period last year, reaching $4.12 billion. Due to the company&apos;s investment in new products and geographical expansion, the adjusted pre-tax profit reached $79.7 million, which is a decrease of about 7% from $85.5 million.Kraken&apos;s total trading volume for this quarter reached $186.8 billion, with a year-on-year growth of 19%. The number of Kraken&apos;s funded accounts increased by 37% to reach 4.4 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22501</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>