<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:48:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The ETH Queued for Exiting the Ethereum PoS Network Rises to 914,000, While Over 620,000 ETH is Waiting to Join</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26273</link>
      <description>On August 26th, based on the data from the Validator Queue tracking website &quot;validatorqueue&quot;, the current exit queue on the Ethereum PoS network has risen to 914,690 ETH, which is approximately worth $40.3 billion. The withdrawal delay has been extended to 15 days and 21 hours.At the same time, the ETH waiting to join the network is about 623,750 ETH, approximately worth $27.5 billion. It is also showing an upward trend, and the current waiting time in the admission queue is 10 days and 20 hours.Previously reported, this situation reflects the existence of two opposing forces in the market. On the one hand, some stakers may choose to cash out significantly after the sharp rise of Ethereum since the April low, resulting in a surge in the exit queue. On the other hand, new inflows of funds driven by regulatory optimism and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue. Listed companies such as SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion have increased their ETH holdings and are</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26273</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale sold 886,000 HYPE tokens and 1,630,000 Fartcoin tokens, and went long on 51,691 ETH with 15x leverage.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26272</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as monitored by LookOnChain, in the past 12 hours, Whale 0xa523 sold 886,287 HYPE tokens ($39.66 million) and 1.63 million Fartcoin tokens ($1.27 million), resulting in a loss of $1.14 million and went long on ETH. He took a 15x leveraged long position on 51,691 ETH ($2.267 billion). Currently, he is facing an unrealized loss of more than $13 million, with a liquidation price of $4,075.7.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 4 years of silence, a whale withdrew 6,334 ETH from Kraken.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26271</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as monitored by LookOnChain, Whale 0x4097, which had been dormant for 4 years, withdrew 6,334 ETH (equivalent to 28.08 million USD) from Kraken 50 minutes ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26271</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve&apos;s September interest rate cut probability is 84.6%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26270</link>
      <description>August 26: Based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch Tool&quot;, there is a 15.4% probability that the Fed will maintain interest rates in September. Meanwhile, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is 84.6%.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26270</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUI Treasury Management Company Mill City Ventures III has today officially rebranded as SUI Group Holdings (SUIG).</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26269</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the SUI Treasury Management Company Mill City Ventures III announced its rebranding to Sui Group Holdings. It will commence trading on Nasdaq under the new ticker symbol SUIG starting from August 26, 2025.SUI Group indicated that the renaming is aimed at strengthening its treasury strategy positioning within the Sui ecosystem and better aligning with SuiFoundation. As the sole publicly listed company with an official association with the Sui Foundation, the group will focus on promoting the development and adoption of the Sui Network while providing long-term value to shareholders.The company stressed that existing shareholders do not need to take any actions regarding this renaming and ticker symbol change. The stock will continue to be listed on the Nasdaq Capital Market and will remain eligible for options trading on Cboe Global Markets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26269</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins will be launching a Soulbound Token called Early to the Party</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26268</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the NFT series Pudgy Penguins is going to launch a Soulbound Token named Early to the Party. Users are required to pre-download Pudgy Party and go through the registration process. Once the game is launched, the tokens will be distributed to eligible wallets.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26268</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Governor Powell: Trump Does Not Have the Authority to Fire Me, Will Continue to Fulfill Duties</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26267</link>
      <description>August 26th: Federal Reserve Governor Powell declared that the U.S. President Trump does not possess the authority to dismiss me and that I will persist in fulfilling my responsibilities. (Xinhua News Agency)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26267</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Schiff: Bitcoin Could Fall to $75,000, Slightly Below Average Strategy Holding Cost</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26266</link>
      <description>On August 26th, the economist and cryptocurrency critic Peter Schiff tweeted, &quot;Bitcoin has dropped beneath $109,000, with a 13% decline from its peak which was less than two weeks ago. Considering the recent over-hype and institutional purchasing, this weakness is a matter of concern. At the very least, Bitcoin may fall to around $75,000, slightly lower than MicroStrategy&apos;s (MSTR) average holding cost. Sell at present and buy back at the lower level.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26266</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn, the &quot;Insider Trader,&quot; AguilaTrades, and the &quot;ETH Long Rollover&quot; Whale, the four whales, made a combined profit of nearly $200 million, but have since lost all their gains and even part ...</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26265</link>
      <description>On August 26th, as per on-chain analyst Embermonitor, four whales - James Wynn, the &quot;Insider Trader&quot; @qwatio, AguilaTrades, and the &quot;ATH Longing ETH&quot; whale - reached a peak profit of $197.7 million. At present, all of them have repatriated their profits and even lost their initial capital.Similar Style: All of them employed the aggressive approach of taking profits through leverage.Similar Process: All of them achieved substantial profits through the act of taking profits.Similar Outcome: All of them transitioned from significant profits to currently repatriating all profits or even incurring losses on their initial capital.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26265</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Enterprise made its fourth Bitcoin purchase in August, doubling its holdings this month.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26264</link>
      <description>On August 26th, DDC Enterprise Limited (&quot;DDC&quot; or the &quot;Company&quot;) announced today that it has completed its fourth Bitcoin purchase in August and further acquired 200 BTC. With this acquisition, the company&apos;s total holdings have reached 888 BTC, more than doubling from the 368 BTC it held at the beginning of the month.Key Points of the Purchase:- Reserve Growth: Added 200 BTC to the Bitcoin reserve with an average cost of $107,447 per BTC.- Holding Milestone: Achieved more than a 2x growth since August 1st.- Return Increase: Compared to the first purchase in May, the return on investment has increased by 1572%.- Shareholder Value: The latest holdings are equivalent to 0.106853 BTC per 1,000 shares of DDC.Norma Chu, the Founder, Chairwoman, and CEO of DDC, said: &quot;This month&apos;s purchase not only demonstrates our execution capabilities and speed but also reflects our discipline and conviction. In the context of Bitcoin market volatility, doubling our holdings in just a few weeks trul</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 03:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>