<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:42:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Xiao Feng: Crypto ETF is good, but Digital Asset Treasury is better</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26673</link>
      <description>August 28th. Xiao Feng, the Chairman and CEO of HashKey Group, declared today during Bitcoin Asia 2025 that the Digital Asset Treasury (DAT) might be the optimal approach for crypto assets to move off-chain.Xiao Feng expounded on the four core merits of DAT in contrast to ETF:Firstly, superior liquidity. The ETF creation and redemption processes consume more time, while DAT facilitates the transfer of assets more conveniently and efficiently for investors.Secondly, higher price elasticity. DAT has a greater market value fluctuation and risk isolation feature, providing more arbitrage tools for institutions.Thirdly, a more reasonable leverage design. DAT companies offer leveraged financing structures, which, compared to the price growth of cryptocurrencies themselves, can bring higher premiums to investors.Fourthly, DAT has a built-in price protection mechanism. When the stock price drops by more than the net asset value held by the company, investors have the opportunity to p</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26673</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: BTC Struggles to Break Through the Mega Whale Accumulation Zone of $93k to $118k, the Lower Support Gap Has Been Filled</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26672</link>
      <description>On August 28th, on-chain data analyst Murphy released a market chip structure analysis. One month ago, due to the rapid surge of BTC, there was almost no trading volume in the price range of $112,000 to $114,000, resulting in a gap in the chip structure (URPD). According to common experience, all &quot;gaps&quot; on URPD will be filled.One month later, as of August 27th, the gap between $112,000 and $114,000 has been completely filled, connecting the original high and low chip accumulation zones to form a large chip accumulation zone ranging from $93,000 to $118,000. Within this range, 5.59 million BTC have been accumulated. This means that from November 20, 2024, to the present, in a short period of 9 months, more than 5 million BTC have been bought in this price range, accounting for 28% of the total circulation. If we exclude chips that are lost or held in long-term &quot;HODL&quot; like Satoshi Nakamoto&apos;s holdings, this proportion is even higher.If there are no sudden &quot;black swan&quot; events, it will</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB Executive Board Member Lane Warns: Federal Reserve Independence Being Eroded, Market Trust May Be Affected</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26671</link>
      <description>August 28: The Executive Board member of the European Central Bank and the Governor of the Bank of Finland, Rehn, warned on Thursday in a speech that for the first time in decades, the independence of the Federal Reserve is facing a &quot;major&quot; challenge, posing &quot;significant&quot; risks to the market and the economy. Rehn said: &quot;Since the containment of double-digit inflation in the 1980s, the independence of the Federal Reserve has been regarded as an inviolable principle - but now this principle is being eroded. When the central bank is trusted, the public, businesses, and financial markets all believe that it will uphold price stability. This trust anchors inflation expectations.&quot; Rehn stated that the credibility brought by independence has enhanced the effectiveness of monetary policy, meaning that the central bank does not need to make &quot;drastic&quot; responses to temporary economic fluctuations. (CNBC)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26671</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWF Labs: Willing to provide 10 to 20% of the funding for the project to facilitate publicly traded companies in establishing a token treasury</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26670</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Andrei Grachev, the managing partner of DWF Labs, posted that if you can persuade a Nasdaq-listed company to set up a crypto treasury reserve for the token of your project, DWF Labs is ready to invest 10% to 20% of the targeted funding amount.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26670</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gryphon Digital surged over 20% in pre-market trading, American Bitcoin Plans to Go Public through a SPAC Merger</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26669</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on market data, during pre-market trading, the U.S. stock Gryphon Digital Mining (GRYP), which is a crypto mining company, once surged by more than 20% and is currently up by more than 12%. The Bitcoin mining company backed by the Trump family, American Bitcoin, is planning to go public through a SPAC merger and aims to be listed on Nasdaq in September under the stock symbol ABTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26669</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sony&apos;s Layer2 network Soneium has launched an on-chain loyalty point system and has kicked off its first-season event.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26668</link>
      <description>On August 28th, Sony&apos;s Layer2 network Soneium launched the on-chain rewards system &quot;Soneium Score&quot; to monitor and reward users&apos; genuine on-chain participation. This system will allocate points to users according to their asset transactions, staking, NFT transactions, and other operations. It will evaluate them based on four aspects: daily activity, liquidity provision, NFT holdings, and interaction with featured projects. The first-season activities have already been launched in cooperation with multiple ecosystem partners. Users with a score exceeding 80 points will receive the SBT badge.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26668</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four.Meme: Creditlink (CDL) Presale Hype</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26667</link>
      <description>On August 28th, according to official information, the decentralized identity and credit project Creditlink (CDL) has now commenced its presale on the Four.Meme platform. It has raised approximately 40.16 million USD1 and 620,000 FORM tokens within just 1 hour. Creditlink aims to establish an AI-driven on-chain identity verification and credit scoring system, facilitating the development of Web3 finance towards collateral-free and inclusive directions.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26667</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed Hong Kong Company, Suntech Holdings, Plans to Include BTC, ETH, BNB, FIL, and Stablecoins in Its Cryptocurrency Investment Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26666</link>
      <description>August 28th. As per the announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, the Hong Kong-listed company Sunlot Holdings Group Limited has issued a supplementary announcement. It is planning to incorporate BTC, ETH, BNB, FIL, and stablecoins (such as USDT and USDC) into its cryptocurrency investment portfolio. It intends to allocate approximately 70 million Hong Kong dollars from its internal financial resources for cryptocurrency trading. Some of the funds have already been used to purchase FIL tokens. Currently, Sunlot Holdings has bought several FIL tokens at a trading price ranging from $2.1 to $2.3 per unit. In addition, Sunlot Holdings has also announced that it will consider using cryptocurrency for payment settlements and disclosed that the proportion of stablecoins in the company&apos;s investment portfolio will not be less than 5%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26666</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Institutional Holdings Overview: 13 Entities Establish SOL Treasury Reserve, Totaling 8.277 Million Tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26665</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on Strategic SOL Reserve data, there are currently 13 entities that have set up SOL Treasury Reserves. These entities hold a total of 8.277 million SOL, which accounts for 1.44% of SOL&apos;s current total supply. Among them, approximately 585,000 SOL are staked, with a value of $1.041 billion. The average staking yield is 6.86%, accounting for 0.102% of the total supply. The top entities in terms of holdings are as follows:Sharps Technology (STSS) ranks first. It currently holds 2.14 million SOL, with a value of approximately $460 million. There has been no change in holdings in the past 30 days.Upexi (UPXI) ranks second. It currently holds 2 million SOL, with a value of approximately $400 million. There has been a 15.3% increase in holdings in the past 30 days.DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) ranks third. It currently holds 1.42 million SOL, with a value of approximately $305 million. There has been a 5.2% increase in holdings in the past 30 days.Mercurity Fintec</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26665</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIA Launches Base on BSC Cross-Chain, Price Surges 22.4% in 24 Hours After Initiating Treasury Buyback Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26664</link>
      <description>On August 28th, based on Coingecko data, the AI concept token MIA has witnessed a 22.4% increase in the past 24 hours. It is currently trading at $0.06 and has a market capitalization of approximately $33.25 million. Recently, MIA simultaneously launched cross-chains on Base and BSC. It also announced the commencement of a treasury buyback plan, which has driven the token price upward.According to official information, the MIA treasury has utilized ETH to complete the buyback of more than 818,200 MIA tokens on the secondary market. Currently, it holds more than 300 ETH, which will continue to be used for buybacks and to support the development of the Smart Body Economy and AgentFi ecosystem. The relevant buyback and treasury addresses have been disclosed, and users can query them on-chain.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 08:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>