<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:32:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Matador Technologies has secured a $100 million funding round to acquire more Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21544</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the publicly traded Canadian company Matador Technologies managed to secure a $100 million funding commitment for the purpose of purchasing more Bitcoin.BlockBeats had previously reported that the board of directors of the Canadian publicly traded company Matador Technologies Inc. gave the green light to a long-term Bitcoin acquisition strategy in an effort to expand Matador&apos;s Bitcoin reserves, thereby making the company a significant corporate holder of BTC. Matador has submitted a preliminary short form base shelf prospectus, which will offer financing flexibility over the next 25 months, with the aim of accumulating up to 6,000 bitcoins by 2027 or even earlier.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie: Not in a hurry to choose Powell&apos;s successor</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21543</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. Treasury Secretary Yellen declared that the current administration is &quot;not in a hurry&quot; to decide on the successor to Fed Chair Powell, and the potential candidate could come from current Board members or regional bank presidents. Yellen stated on a TV program on Wednesday: &quot;There are numerous strong candidates, including several key Board members and perhaps regional bank presidents.&quot; She did not disclose any specific names.Reports have suggested that Yellen herself, White House National Economic Council Director Hassett, former Fed Governor Kevin Warsh, and current Fed Governor Wall are among the candidates put forward by Trump for the chairmanship. Yellen said: &quot;There is an extremely long, extremely long list.&quot; She further stated: &quot;I will not be discussing this process. However, we are advancing with this process. Obviously, it will be President Trump&apos;s decision, and we are not in a rush.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21543</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Powell Refusing Interest Rate Cut, American Families Are Being Hurt</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21542</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. President Trump posted on his personal social platform and said, &quot;Our country&apos;s housing issue is falling behind due to &apos;Mr. Too Late&apos; Powell&apos;s refusal to reduce interest rates. Families are suffering because the interest rates are too high. Even our country itself is paying more interest than it should - all because of this &apos;Mr. Too Late.&apos; &quot;Our interest rates should be three percentage points lower than they are currently, which would save the country one trillion dollars a year. This obstinate person just doesn&apos;t understand - didn&apos;t understand before and won&apos;t understand in the future. The Federal Reserve Board should take action, but they don&apos;t have the courage to do it!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21542</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Commerce Secretary: Trump Has Decided to Allow China to Purchase H20 Chips in a &apos;Balanced Manner&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21541</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. Commerce Secretary Raimondo declared that Trump has made a decision to enable China to acquire NVIDIA H20 chips in a &quot;balanced&quot; manner.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Commerce Secretary: Trump Wants EU to &apos;Fully&apos; Open Its Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21540</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. Commerce Secretary Raimondo declared that if the EU were to accept U.S. products and standards, it would &quot;promptly&quot; lead to a response from Trump. Trump desires that the EU will &quot;completely&quot; open its market.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21539</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $118,000, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 1.20%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Stock Options have commenced trading on the New York Stock Exchange.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21538</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the cryptocurrency mining company BitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE AMERICAN: BMNR; hereinafter referred to as &quot;BitMine&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) announced today that the common stock of the company is now open for options trading on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE).BitMine Immersion Technologies is a company specializing in cryptocurrency mining, and its treasury strategy aims to acquire 5% of the global Ethereum (ETH) supply.The stock options of BitMine officially began trading on July 23, 2025, with the trading symbol &quot;BMNR&quot;, covering a range of standard expiration dates and exercise prices. The introduction of options is expected to expand investors&apos; participation channels, increase the liquidity of the company&apos;s stock, and provide investors with more flexible means to manage risks, leverage positions, or express views on the company&apos;s stock price movement.The BitMine stock options will be cleared through the Options Clearing Corporation (OCC) and are subject to t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The massive ETH queue for unbonding may be related to the sudden drop in Ethereum supply on Aave, and if it worsens, it could lead to stETH becoming untethered.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21537</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the cryptocurrency Key Opinion Leader (KOL) darkpools posted an analysis on social media, stating that the recent reason for the 620,000 ETH queued for unstaking might be as follows: A whale withdrew ETH deposits from Aave (reducing the supply of ETH), resulting in the ETH utilization rate on Aave soaring, leading to a sharp increase in the borrowing rate of ETH; Users using stETH for looping faced unprofitability due to high costs, prompting them to reduce leverage; A large amount of de-leveraged stETH entered the staking withdrawal queue; Some users chose to directly sell stETH to avoid the withdrawal queue, causing stETH to deviate by 30 basis points (0.3%).Due to the fact that the oracle price of stETH is based on the redemption value rather than the market price, lenders are currently stuck in their positions and may need to wait for up to about 18 days, which is the current ETH unstaking queue time. If the situation continues to deteriorate, stETH may face liquida</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature&apos;s Miracle Market Cap currently stands at $7.09 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21536</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc., a vertical agriculture technology company listed on the US OTC trading market (OTCQB: NMHI), currently has a market value of $7.09 million. Its stock price rose by more than 10% on the previous trading day.Today, Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc. announced a $20 million XRP Treasury Reserve Plan. This plan will be supported by equity financing from GHS Investments based on the company&apos;s previously effective S-1 registration statement declared by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The purpose is to purchase XRP and meet operational funding needs.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Network&apos;s Stablecoin Supply Surpasses $140 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21535</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on on-chain data, the supply of stablecoins on the Ethereum network has exceeded $140 billion and reached a new record high. Compared to the level in January 2024, the supply has nearly doubled.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>