<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:55:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey to Include JitoSOL in its Solana Staking ETF Investment Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21705</link>
      <description>On July 24th, REX-Osprey announced the official inclusion of the staking token JitoSOL of the Solana ecosystem in the REX-Osprey Solana + Staking ETF (SSK) portfolio. This upgrade allows the ETF to maintain liquidity, transparency, and the convenience of traditional brokerage trading while receiving the native staking rewards of Solana.Since its listing on July 2nd, the assets under management (AUM) of the SSK have exceeded $100 million, reflecting the increasing demand from investors to allocate crypto assets through traditional accounts.Greg King, CEO of REX Financial and Osprey Funds, stated: &quot;SSK is the first product to bring crypto staking rewards into a U.S. ETF. By now integrating JitoSOL for liquid staking, we have further enhanced liquidity while continuously delivering Solana&apos;s native yield within the ETF structure.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21705</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance now supports using USYC and cUSDO as off-chain collateral</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21704</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per official information, Binance has now officially extended its institutional over-the-counter settlement service and added support for two tokenized real-world assets (RWA) as collateral, namely USYC and cUSDO. Institutional users are now able to utilize these yield-bearing tokenized stable assets as collateral through Banking Triparty custody and MirrorRSV. They can maintain off-platform custody and optimize capital efficiency while conducting secure trading on the Binance platform.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affected by Musk&apos;s announcement to relaunch Vine in AI form, the meme coin VINE experienced a short-term price surge of over 102%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21703</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to the market information of GMGN, due to Musk&apos;s announcement of relaunching Vine as an AI, the Solana-based meme coin VINE has surged and exceeded a market capitalization of $80 million. It is now at $81.02 million, with a 24-hour increase of more than 102%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21703</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the week ending on July 19, initial jobless claims in the United States were 217,000, compared to the expected 226,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21702</link>
      <description>July 24th: In the United States, for the week ending July 19th, the initial jobless claims were 217,000. This was in contrast to the expected value of 226,000 and the previous value of 221,000. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21702</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: Will Relaunch Vine in AI Form</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21701</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Musk tweeted, &quot;We are going to relaunch Vine in an AI form.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21701</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Holds Interest Rate Steady, Monitors Progress of US-EU Trade Negotiations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21700</link>
      <description>July 24th - On Thursday, the European Central Bank (ECB) maintained its key interest rate at 2%. It was waiting for clearer indications regarding the direction of EU-US trade relations. Current inflation has dropped back to the 2% target level, and the rate has been reduced from 4% to 2% since June of last year. The policy pressure on the ECB has significantly eased. The ECB stated that it would continue to adhere to a &quot;meeting-by-meeting&quot; policy without predefined interest rate paths, with all decisions based on the latest data.The statement suggested that the latest information generally aligns with previous judgments on the inflation outlook. Domestic price pressures are continuing to ease, and wage growth is slowing down. The market is still anticipating at least one more rate cut later this year. Market focus has shifted to President Lagarde&apos;s subsequent press conference, where she is likely to face intense questioning about whether to continue cutting rates in the future, the s</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21700</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy CEO: Ethereum Poised to Outperform Bitcoin in Next 3 to 6 Months</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21699</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Michael Novogratz, the CEO of Galaxy Digital, stated in an interview with Squawk Box that Ethereum has the potential to outperform Bitcoin within the next 3 to 6 months. (CNBC)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21699</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Keeps Interest Rates Unchanged</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21698</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the European Central Bank maintained the deposit facility rate at -2% without any change, which was in line with market expectations. After seven consecutive rate cuts in previous meetings, the main refinancing rate and the marginal lending rate remained unchanged at 0.00% and 0.25% respectively. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21698</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will accept Circle&apos;s stablecoin USYC as collateral from institutional clients</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21697</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to the report in Fortune, Circle announced that Binance will commence accepting USYC (a stablecoin that distributes yields to investors) as collateral from institutional clients. Although many institutional traders using platforms like Binance will use Bitcoin or other crypto assets as collateral, some traditional institutions still hesitate to do so.Catherine Chen, Binance VIP and Head of Institutional Business, stated that one of the reasons is the recent collapse of FTX, which has made many people wary of providing collateral on exchanges. Binance is trying to address this issue through a service called &quot;Banking Triparty&quot;. This service involves Binance partnering with traditional banks to act as custodians and using the assets held by the banks as collateral for cryptocurrency trading. She added that many partners are working with Binance to integrate USYC, which will provide faster settlement times. Binance also announced that it will integrate anot</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21697</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semler Scientific has increased its holdings by 175 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 5021 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21696</link>
      <description>On July 24th, the US-listed company Semler Scientific increased its holdings of BTC by 175 coins, raising its total holdings to 5021 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>