<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:01:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Macro Outlook: CPI and PPI Data Incoming, &apos;Crypto-Friendly&apos; Fed Governor to Take Office</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23852</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the key macroeconomic data and events to be announced in the next week are as follows:Tuesday:US July CPI data;2027 FOMC voter and Richmond Fed President Barkin&apos;s speech.Thursday:Chicago Fed President Evans&apos; speech on monetary policy;Atlanta Fed President Bostic&apos;s speech on the US economic outlook;US initial jobless claims for the week ending August 9th and August PPI data.Friday:US July retail sales m/m and July import price index m/m;US August 1-year inflation rate expectations preliminary and the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment Index preliminary.Additionally, Trump has announced the nomination of the &quot;pro-crypto&quot; official Stephen Miran as a Federal Reserve Board Member, with a term ending on January 31, 2026. According to public information, during his tenure as the Chair of the White House Economic Advisory Committee, he explicitly supported the Trump administration&apos;s crypto-friendly policies. He believes that cryptocurrency has the potential</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23852</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDe&apos;s market capitalization has surpassed $10 billion for the first time, while at the same time ENA has surged over 186%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23851</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on official data, the current market capitalization of USDe has reached a new all-time high for the first time, exceeding 10 billion US dollars. It has increased by 46.9 billion US dollars compared to July 4th (5.31 billion US dollars), with a growth rate of 88.3%. Meanwhile, during the same period, ENA has seen a 186% increase.As of the time of writing, USDe is currently trading at $1.001; ENA is trading at $0.7449, with a 24-hour increase of 20.77%, and its market capitalization has risen to 4.911 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23851</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Company LM Funding America Mined 5.9 BTC in July</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23850</link>
      <description>On August 9th, as per Globenewswire, the U.S.-listed Bitcoin mining company LM Funding America issued an unaudited update report on Bitcoin mining and operations as of July 31st. During July, they mined 5.9 BTC and sold 11 BTC. The Bitcoin holdings at the end of July decreased to approximately 150.4 BTC, with a total value of around $17.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23850</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharplink: Ethereum Roadmap on Network Upgrade, Focused on Decentralization, Smartness, and Integrity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23849</link>
      <description>On August 9th, &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; Sharplink Gaming stated in a post that the Ethereum roadmap is by no means solely focused on expanding the financial scale. Instead, it is about rebuilding the network, with decentralization, intelligence, and integrity at its core. AI agents, physical infrastructure, data flows, and reputation layers all require programmable trust, and this is what Ethereum provides.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23849</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutional Ethereum Holdings Overview: BMNR Holds 833.1K ETH, Ranking First</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23848</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on strategicethreserve data, the following treasury companies and institutions with significant changes in Ethereum holdings over the past 30 days are as follows:Bitmine Immersion Tech (BMNR) takes the first place. It is currently holding 833,100 ETH, with a value of approximately $35.1 billion and a 30-day holding increase of 41.068%.SharpLink Gaming (SBET) ranks second. It is currently holding 521,900 ETH, with a value of approximately $22 billion and a 30-day holding increase of 153.83%.The Ether Machine (DYNX) ranks third. It is currently holding 345,400 ETH, with a value of approximately $14.6 billion and a 30-day holding increase of 8.01%.Ethereum Foundation ranks fourth, holding 232,600 ETH, with a value of approximately $9.8 billion and a 30-day holding decrease of 4.47%.Bit Digital (BTBT) ranks seventh, holding 120,300 ETH, with a value of approximately $5.07 billion and a 30-day holding increase of 19.58%.BTCS Inc (BTCS) ranks tenth, holding 7</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetix Founder Releases sUSD Deprovisioning Update: Mainnet Preload Event Will Ultimately Reanchor it</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23847</link>
      <description>On August 9th, Kain, the founder of Synthetix, released the latest update regarding the sUSD de-pegging issue. The current price of sUSD is $0.990619 and is about to re-anchor. Although it has been a difficult period, with the launch of the mainnet pre-staking activities, sUSD will ultimately return to normal.Previously, on April 18th, the Synthetix stablecoin sUSD experienced a further deterioration of its de-pegging issue to $0.7. Synthetix then announced an emergency solution, where the USD 420 Pool would be launched with incentives. SNX stakers in the 420 Pool could deposit sUSD to receive a share of the 5 million SNX rewards over a period of 12 months. The deposited sUSD will be locked for one year and can be fully withdrawn after the event ends. Synthetix founder Kain commented on this emergency solution, stating, &quot;This is one of the worst instant solutions ever used to generate demand for sUSD from the user base.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:09:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23847</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades will take profit in multiple steps on the BTC and ETH long positions, aiming for a total profit of approximately $11.4 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23845</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to the monitoring of EmberCN, whale contract trader AguilaTrades. After going through several situations where floating profits turned into losses, it learned a costly lesson and began to take profits. Currently, AguilaTrades is closing positions on Hyperliquid. It has made a profit of approximately $11.4 million from going long on BTC and ETH.AguilaTrades opened long positions on BTC and ETH the day before yesterday. Two hours later, due to Trump&apos;s executive order signing, the cryptocurrency market surged. AguilaTrades took profits and rolled over the positions when the market was in profit. Yesterday, it added to the position to a notional value of $250 million. After ETH&apos;s sharp rise today, AguilaTrades started to take profits and close positions.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insight: Stablecoin Issuers are Digesting US Treasuries, with Tether Holding Over $100 Billion in US Treasury Bonds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23846</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to the report in Fortune, stablecoin issuers like Circle and Tether are purchasing a greater amount of U.S. Treasuries than most countries, which has the potential to reshape the U.S. economy. Tether disclosed the latest data indicating holdings of more than $100 billion in U.S. Treasury bonds, exceeding countries such as the UAE and Germany. Cryptocurrency proponents think that stablecoins will contribute to consolidating the U.S. dollar&apos;s dominant position globally. However, critics caution that even if stablecoins only make up a small portion of the overall market, it could still give rise to banking and financial instability, potentially draining funds from bank deposits and reducing bank liquidity.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23846</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes ironically jokes about his &quot;buy low, sell high ETH&quot; strategy: vows never to profit again</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23844</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the co-founder of BitMEX, Arthur Hayes, posted a self-mocking message about &quot;selling low and buying high ETH&quot; and said, &quot;I must buy it all back. Can you forgive me @Thomas Lee? I swear I will never take profits again.&quot;A week ago, Arthur Hayes sold 2,373 ETH when the price was approximately $3,507. And he bought back ETH at a higher price four hours ago.Thomas Lee, the chairman of BitMine (BMNR), which is Ethereum&apos;s largest institutional holder, has been actively promoting ETH in the crypto community recently. His statements are as follows: &quot;Ethereum is currently at a crucial moment similar to Bitcoin in 2017. Some people will regret not betting on it at this time. As Wall Street&apos;s attention to cryptocurrency gradually increases, Ethereum is becoming the core platform in the financial market&apos;s &apos;tokenization&apos; process. This is one of the biggest macro trading events in the next decade. Based on the ETH/BTC exchange rate during the 2021 peak, ETH could rise to $16,000.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23844</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem Token GEN Market Cap Surpasses $45 Million, 24-hour Growth Rate 35%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23843</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on GMGN data, the ecological AI concept token GEN of Solana briefly surged to $0.045. It currently has a market value of $45 million and a 24-hour increase of 35%.It is reported that GEN is the native token of the General Impressions (GI) project. GI is building the core infrastructure of the Agentic AI era. It is a Rust-driven intelligent agent network that provides underlying support for the trusted execution of autonomous AI, low-cost reusability, and multi-agent collaboration. As a key driver of the emergence of the Agentic Paradigm, GI is gradually becoming a key algorithm protocol for decentralized intelligent systems.BlockBeats reminds users that token prices are highly volatile, so investment should be made with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23843</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>