<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:48:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected SharpLink Associated Address withdrew 17,655 ETH from a CEX in the last 18 hours, worth approximately $72.7 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23867</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to the monitoring of LookOnChain, the suspected SharpLink Gaming-related address withdrew 17,655 ETH from the exchange platform again within the past 18 hours. The value of this withdrawal is approximately $72.7 million.Moreover, the whale address 0x3684 spent $34 million to purchase 8,109 ETH at a price of $4,193 per ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23867</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Bitcoin Advocate Erik Voorhees Sells 6,581 ETH Today, Worth $27.38 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23866</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on LookOnChain&apos;s monitoring, the early Bitcoin evangelist and ShapeShift founder, Erik Voorhees, sold 6,581 ETH today at a price of $4,161, with a value of $27.38 million.Nine years ago, he acquired 14,945 ETH from ShapeShift (valued at $11,560 at that time and now worth $62.68 million), when the price of ETH was only $7.74. His last ETH sale was on December 6, 2024, when he sold 7,807 ETH at a price of $4,005 each ($31.27 million). He still holds 556.68 ETH ($2.33 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23866</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitalik&apos;s on-chain assets surpass $1 billion, including 240,000 ETH</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23865</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on Arkham data, the on-chain assets of Vitalik Buterin, a co-founder of Ethereum, have exceeded $1 billion and currently amount to $1.02 billion. His main holdings consist of 240,000 ETH, 2906 AETHWETH, 300 billion MOODENG tokens, etc.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23865</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block to Launch New Bitcoin Mining Chip Next Week</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23864</link>
      <description>On August 9th, it was reported that during an interview, the Chief Financial Officer of Block Inc (XYZ), which is a payment platform owned by Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey, stated that the company will introduce a new Bitcoin mining chip next week. This chip is intended to enhance the decentralized Bitcoin mining ecosystem. A few months ago, Block disclosed that it had completed the development of a 3-nanometer Bitcoin mining chip.In addition, Jack Dorsey posted on the X platform with the caption &quot;Next Week&quot; along with an image of mining tools, suggesting that a new product will be launched on August 14th.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Total US Debt Surpasses $37 Trillion for the First Time, Debt Crisis Growing More Severe</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23863</link>
      <description>September 8th. As per The Kobeissi Letter, on this day, the cumulative U.S. debt has for the first time ever officially exceeded $37 trillion. From July 4th, when Trump signed the &quot;Beautiful Act&quot; and raised the debt ceiling, the U.S. debt has seen an additional increase of $780 billion, which is equivalent to an average daily increment of $220 billion.Just in the previous week, the U.S. government carried out 10 bond sales with a total value of $724 billion, intensifying the U.S. debt crisis to an unprecedented level.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23863</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades has closed a long position, realizing a profit of $11.3 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23860</link>
      <description>August 9th. Based on EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, the whale contract trader AguilaTrades closed his long positions on BTC and ETH just 10 minutes ago, completing a trade that lasted only 2 days. During this long position, he expanded his initial $4.6 million capital to $15.9 million, thereby achieving a $11.3 million profit.Previously, AguilaTrades had witnessed substantial unrealized gains after opening positions, but each time he decided to compound those gains, which led to higher leverage. Minor retracements ate away at the gains, and eventually, he lost his initial capital. After this $11.3 million profit, AguilaTrades&apos; total losses have been reduced from $40 million to $28.7 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23860</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Shorts ENA and Other Ethereum Ecosystem Tokens, Accumulating a Unrealized Loss of $2.84 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23859</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), starting from the end of July this year, the address that took a 5x leveraged short position on ENA is now facing an unrealized loss of $3.288 million. The initial short position in ENA was opened at $0.5236 (current price $0.7328).In addition, this address has also shorted a basket of Ethereum ecosystem tokens including ETH, LDO, MKR, and CRV, accumulating a total unrealized loss of $2.84 million. In order to avoid liquidation, they have supplemented 1.6 million USDC as collateral to Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23859</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Ecosystem DEX Jupiter has released its weekly update and will announce the Jup Mobile update next week.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23862</link>
      <description>August 9th: The weekly recap of the Solana ecosystem DEX Jupiter was released. It included the launch of Lend Beta, the launch of the Jupiter Plugin, the addition of tokenized pre-IPO stocks, new APIs and upgrades, improvements in the Verify v4 process, studio upgrades, and vanity addresses.In addition, Jupiter announced that Jup Mobile will disclose a secret update next week.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23862</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Dominance Drops Below 60%, Altseason May Be on the Horizon</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23861</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on market data, the Bitcoin Dominance (BTC.D) has fallen below 60%, experiencing a 3.1% decrease over the past week and currently standing at 59.98%.The total cryptocurrency market capitalization has increased by 6.9% in the past week. The total market capitalization excluding Bitcoin (TOTAL 2) has risen by 11.94%, and the total market capitalization excluding Bitcoin and Ethereum (TOTAL 3) has increased by 8.58%.The market view generally holds that the continuous decline in Bitcoin dominance indicates the potential onset of Altseason.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23861</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: Ethereum&apos;s Rise Is Not Isolated in the Market, Cryptocurrency Autumn Is Expected to Begin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23858</link>
      <description>August 9th: Wang Feng, the founder of Blueport Interactive, mentioned in a post that the market sentiment of Bitcoin and Ethereum should not be regarded in isolation. Currently, Bitcoin is trading sideways around $120,000 with little volatility and no significant sell-off by institutions. This situation offers ample space for Ethereum to maintain its uptrend after breaking through $4,000, and it is forecasted to rise to at least around $5,000. Similarly, Ethereum and the entire crypto market have always been interrelated. The cryptocurrency autumn is expected to commence, with DeFi, RWA, and star meme coins entering a stage of takeoff.On July 16th, Blueport Interactive established the LK Crypto Division to be responsible for the management of the company&apos;s mainstream crypto assets and expedite its Web3 and RWA strategies.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23858</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>