<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:32:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: US Stablecoins Still Treated as Property for Tax Purposes, &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; Does Not Change Taxation Rules</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21669</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per Forbes, despite the recent passage of the GENIUS Act in the United States, the Internal Revenue Service still regards digital assets as property and maintains the key tax rules unchanged for traders and investors.The GENIUS Act imposes strict reserve, auditing, and disclosure requirements on U.S. stablecoin issuers, such as 1:1 asset backing and monthly financial audits; however, the act did not reclassify stablecoins for tax purposes.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21669</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Industry Calls on Trump to Block JPMorgan&apos;s 「Punitive Tax」 on Data Access</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21668</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per the report by CoinDesk, ten financial technology and cryptocurrency trade associations such as the Blockchain Association and the Crypto Council for Innovation have implored President Trump to prevent big banks from imposing fees that might impede innovation and competition. These organizations have cautioned that JPMorgan&apos;s plan to charge for accessing consumer banking data could result in millions of Americans losing their bank accounts and potentially hamper the adoption of stablecoins (USDC, USDT) and self-hosted wallets.The CFPB&apos;s open banking rule enables consumers to freely obtain bank data, but this rule is now in jeopardy as banks have filed lawsuits to block it, and the CFPB has requested to revoke the rule. At the core of this dispute lies how Americans fund digital wallets and exchanges. Aggregators like Plaid and MX enable consumers to transfer funds from bank accounts to platforms like Coinbase or Kraken. These connections rely on direct access to u</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21668</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Stock Crypto Concept Stocks See Mixed Pre-market Movement, Tron Up 5.77%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21667</link>
      <description>On July 24th, in the pre-market trading of US stock cryptocurrency concept stocks, the results were mixed. They included:· Tron increased by 5.77%;· Sharplink Gaming decreased by 0.97%;· Circle declined by 1.54%;· Strategy rose by 0.24%;· Coinbase went up by 0.25%;· HOOD rose by 1.20%;· BMNR increased by 1.80%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21667</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elympics Airdrop Lookup is now live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21666</link>
      <description>On July 24th, Elympics, a multi-chain entertainment infrastructure, announced that the airdrop query is now available. The scope of airdrop eligibility includes:· The top 1600 Respect recipients.· The top 500 Cookie DAO Snapshot #1 users.· Cookie stakers in Elympics&apos; multi-airdrop incentive event.BlockBeats previously reported that on July 23rd, Gate will launch Elympics (ELP) spot trading for the first time at 20:00 on July 24th, 2025 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21666</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republic of Ghana Plans to Issue License to Cryptocurrency Platforms</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21665</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to Bloomberg, the Republic of Ghana is making plans to issue licenses to cryptocurrency platforms. The authorities&apos; goal is to regulate the asset class that is used by millions in this West African country while also generating revenue.The governor of the Bank of Ghana stated that the central bank is finalizing a regulatory framework that is intended to be submitted to Parliament for review in September. The proposed legislation would allow the country to fully utilize cryptocurrency, facilitate cross-border trade, attract strategic investments, and collect financial data.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21665</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky DeFi continues to utilize Staking Rewards to buy back SKY tokens</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21664</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to the monitoring of @EmberCN, Rune, a co-founder of Sky (formerly MakerDAO), is continuously using the staking rewards of SKY to repurchase SKY.He claimed the SKY staking rewards half an hour ago: 1.9 million USDS + 10.378 million SPK (approximately $1.3 million), and then transferred it to his buyback address. Currently, he is selling SPK to repurchase SKY.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU has approved a $930 billion counter-tariff plan against the US, which will be implemented on August 7 if negotiations with the US fail.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21663</link>
      <description>July 24th: The member states of the EU voted to give approval to a measure for imposing retaliatory tariffs on US products amounting to 93 billion euros. The day prior to this, a spokesperson for the European Commission stated on July 23rd that the EU plans to merge two lists of retaliatory tariffs targeting US export goods into a single unified list with a total of 93 billion euros. This list mainly encompasses high-value industrial products such as aircraft, automobiles, and electrical equipment. The comprehensive retaliatory list formed by the combination of the two lists totals 93 billion euros.European Commission spokesperson Olaf Gill stated on July 23rd that in the event that (negotiations with the US) fail, the retaliatory measures will come into effect on August 7th. (Jinse Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21663</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWT Surges Over 60% in 24 Hours, Market Cap Reaches $129 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21661</link>
      <description>On July 24th, according to HTX market data, NEWT has seen a surge of more than 60% in the past 24 hours. It is currently trading at $0.6082, and its market capitalization has risen to $129 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21661</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s new airdrop ASP has an initial claim threshold of 225 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21662</link>
      <description>July 24th witnessed Binance becoming the inaugural platform to list Aspecta (ASP). Trading is scheduled to commence on July 24, 2025, at 10:00 (UTC). Qualified users have the opportunity to partake in an airdrop of 125 ASP tokens by leveraging Binance Alpha points on the Alpha Event page within 24 hours following the start of trading.The Binance Alpha airdrop will be dispensed in two phases:Phase 1 (First 18 hours): Users possessing at least 225 Binance Alpha points can claim the airdrop.Phase 2 (Last 6 hours): Users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha points can participate in the airdrop on a first-come, first-served basis.In the event that the rewards are not completely distributed, the point thresholds will automatically decrease by 10 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21662</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address then withdrew 2759 ETH from Kraken, increasing the total holdings to 15,100 ETH.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21660</link>
      <description>On July 24th, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, a newly established wallet address once more withdrew 2759 ETH from Kraken, with a value of $9.84 million. Currently, the wallet holds 15,100 ETH, which is worth $54 million. The address is 0x6A955C288B7b355c1EAe2F1ED1aD8a2a0f48eb1E.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21660</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>