<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:52:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The Japanese Financial Services Agency is planning to establish a new Cryptocurrency and Innovation Department</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26896</link>
      <description>August 29th. According to CoinPost, on this day, the Japanese Financial Services Agency announced the budget and personnel structure plan for the year 2026, revealing a significant restructuring of the regulatory framework. The specific measures involve the reorganization of the Integrated Policy Bureau, the establishment of the &quot;Asset Management and Insurance Regulatory Bureau (tentative name)&quot;, and the creation of dedicated departments to handle cryptocurrency assets and cashless payments - the &quot;Cryptocurrency Asset and Innovation Office&quot; and the &quot;Fund Settlement Monitoring Office&quot;.In the realm of cryptocurrency assets, the functions of the existing &quot;Cryptocurrency Asset and Innovation Advisory Office&quot;, &quot;Fund Settlement Monitoring Office&quot;, and &quot;Settlement and Digital Financial Group Monitoring Office&quot; will be integrated into the new department. This new department will be responsible for market monitoring, fulfilling disclosure obligations during sales solicitations, implementing a</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA’s Decline Widens to 3%, Cryptocurrency Market Continues to Fall</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26897</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Nvidia&apos;s stock price experienced a further 3% decline, and the cryptocurrency market remained in a downward trend. Bitcoin dipped below $110,000. Ethereum dropped below $4,350. And SOL briefly fell below $210.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26897</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Reserve Asset Concept Stocks Experience General Downtrend, SBET Drops by 2.00%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26895</link>
      <description>On August 29th, the US stock Ethereum reserve concept stocks witnessed a general decline. The stocks included:· SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US), which dropped by 2.00%;· Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US), with a decrease of 1.05%;· ETHZilla (ETHZ.US), down by 2.26%;· BTCS (BTCS.US), declining by 0.14%;· Bit Digital (BTBT.US), which fell by 2.68%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26895</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX is launching Wallet and DEX services in Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26894</link>
      <description>On August 29th, as per official channels, OKX Wallet and DEX services have become operational in Europe. This has brought users a self-custody experience encompassing over 140 blockchains. It also offers the best price aggregation from more than 500 DEXs, providing extremely swift swaps and seamless access to a variety of dApps and more. Consequently, a more convenient and enhanced Web3 usage scenario is being created.OKX CEO Star mentioned that Europe is embarking on a new chapter in Web3 development. With the implementation of the MiCA regulatory license, OKX will offer secure, regulated, and seamless on-chain financial services to millions of users within the EU.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26894</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three major U.S. stock indexes opened lower together, and stocks related to cryptocurrency concepts experienced a general decline.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26893</link>
      <description>On August 29, at the start of the US stock market session, the Dow experienced a decline of 0.15%, the S&amp;P 500 dropped by 0.18%, and the Nasdaq fell by 0.36%.Regarding cryptocurrency-related stocks, MSTR saw a decrease of 1.24%, COIN dropped by 0.87%, CRCL fell by 0.05%, HOOD declined by 0.55%, and BLSH saw a decrease of 2.22%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26893</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Withdrawal Trend Reversal, 24-hour Net Outflow of 17,940.48 BTC from CEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26892</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to Coinglass data, during the past 24 hours, the total net outflow of BTC from CEXs was 17,940.48 BTC. The top three CEXs with the largest outflow amounts are as follows:· Kraken, with an outflow of 16,859.07 BTC;· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 1,914.07 BTC;· Binance, with an outflow of 551.76 BTC.In addition, Bitfinex had an inflow of 884.28 BTC, ranking first in the inflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26892</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US PCE Continues to Exceed Target, Fed Faces Challenges Ahead of September Rate Cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26891</link>
      <description>On August 29th, Market analyst Matt Grossman stated that the inflation gauge that the Federal Reserve favors did not approach the 2% target level in July, emphasizing the policy challenge that the Fed is facing as it prepares for a possible rate cut in September. Data from the US Commerce Department&apos;s Bureau of Economic Analysis showed that the US PCE Price Index increased by 2.6% year-on-year in July, remaining the same as the previous month.The core PCE Price Index rose by 2.9% year-on-year in July, which is higher than June&apos;s 2.8%. This reading was widely anticipated as economists could very accurately predict PCE inflation using other official data released earlier this month. While some price increases driven by tariffs continue to exceed the target level, Fed Chairman Powell previously hinted that considering the cooling labor market, the Fed is considering implementing the first rate cut of the year in September. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26891</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins is entering the mobile gaming space with the launch of a new battle royale party game called Pudgy Party.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26890</link>
      <description>August 29th — It was announced on Friday by the well-known NFT brand Pudgy Penguins about the global launch of the Web3 mobile game Pudgy Party in collaboration with the developer of FIFA Rivals, Mythical Games. Pudgy Party is a light-hearted party battle royale game set in a fast-paced mini-game world where all the in-game characters are made up of the iconic Pudgy Penguins imagery. Each character has unique features, abilities, and personalities. Every match is designed to be fresh and unpredictable, with rotating challenges and unexpected twists to ensure that no two parties are the same.Players can customize their penguin characters by using outfits, emotes, and collectibles. Some of these are non-tradable, while others are limited edition and can be traded on Mythical&apos;s marketplace. Players can also mint, upgrade, and fuse rare items on Mythical&apos;s EVM-compatible Polkadot parallel chain, Mythos Chain, and turn them into NFTs.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26890</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Falls Below $4400</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26889</link>
      <description>On August 29th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum fell below $4400, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 4.34%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26889</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Updates Old Blockchain Transition Plan: Will Not Freeze Smart Contracts on the Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26888</link>
      <description>August 29th. Stablecoin issuer Tether declared today an update regarding its transition plan for five legacy blockchains, namely Omni Layer, Bitcoin Cash SLP, Kusama, EOS, and Algorand. More than a year ago, Tether announced its intention to halt the redemption and freezing of USDT tokens on these legacy blockchains starting from September 1, 2025, with a gradual phasing out of support.In response to feedback from the discontinued blockchain communities, Tether has adjusted this approach and will not freeze smart contracts on these networks. Although users can still transfer tokens between wallets, Tether will discontinue the direct issuance and redemption of tokens on these blockchains. This indicates that these tokens will no longer receive official support like other Tether tokens. Tether remains dedicated to a smooth transition and will continue to cooperate with the community to ensure transparency and clarity throughout the entire process.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 12:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>