<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:48:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: Grok humanoid companions Valentine and Ani have completed a series of upgrades</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23722</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Musk stated on the X platform that the Grok humanoid companions Valentine and Ani have undergone a series of upgrades.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23722</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source: InsiderThe company&apos;s stock may go public before the circulation of WLFI tokens, with USD1 credits eligible for WLFI token airdrop.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23721</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Insider @0xDylan_ disclosed on the X platform, &quot;We will shortly witness the news of WLFI Company&apos;s listing on the US stock market. (The company&apos;s going public) might even occur prior to the circulation of the WLFI token.&quot;@0xDylan_ also stated that USD1 credits may be eligible to receive a WLFI token airdrop.Insider @0xDylan_ accurately forecasted the USD1 points event earlier this week.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23721</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Partners with Spain&apos;s Major Bank BBVA to Provide Offline Custody Service for Users</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23720</link>
      <description>On August 8th, according to the Financial Times, Binance is collaborating with Spain&apos;s third-largest bank, BBVA, to offer offline custody services to users. Customer assets will be held by BBVA in the form of US Treasuries, and Binance will accept these assets as collateral.Sources with knowledge of the matter stated that this structure is intended to &quot;prevent another FTX-like incident.&quot; Neither party has made any comments regarding the cooperation.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Allocating only 2% of a 401(k) to Bitcoin and Ethereum would surpass 1.5 times the total ETF inflows to date</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23719</link>
      <description>August 8th. Concerning Trump&apos;s signing of an executive order enabling 401(k) retirement funds to invest in cryptocurrency, Jake Ostrovskis, an OTC trader at Wintermute, stated that the impact of this action should not be underestimated. &quot;Simply a 2% allocation to Bitcoin and Ethereum is equivalent to 1.5 times the cumulative inflows of ETFs up to now. Meanwhile, a 3% allocation would more than double the overall market&apos;s inflow. The crucial point is that these buyers are largely insensitive to prices and focus on meeting their allocation targets rather than engaging in tactical trading.&quot; (CoinDesk)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23719</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Ecosystem AI Data Solution Platform Tagger (TAG) Hits All-Time High Market Cap, Surging 32% in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23718</link>
      <description>August 8th. Based on market data, the market capitalization of the BNB ecosystem AI data solution platform Tagger (TAG) has reached a new all-time high. The currently circulating market capitalization is $1.058 billion, with a 24-hour growth rate of 32.9% and a trading volume of more than $3.4 million.On July 19th, WLFI announced an increase of $40,000 in its holdings of TAG tokens.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23718</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wenzhou Court in China successfully disposed of the involved virtual currency through a licensed trading platform.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23717</link>
      <description>August 8th. As per the Wenzhou Evening News, starting from December 2022, the defendant Liu employed a counterfeit digital wallet app to unlawfully obtain 544 virtual coin addresses and keys, transferring tens of thousands of virtual coins that were stolen from victims like Yang. This led to substantial financial losses.In order to find a reliable professional organization for disposal, Wang Zitai shuttled back and forth between various relevant departments for several days and finally got in touch with the Third Research Institute of the Public Security Department through the Lucheng Public Security Sub-bureau, entrusting them to select a mature professional disposal organization. When signing the entrusted agreement, he carefully examined each clause and clearly stipulated the rights and responsibilities such as detection, sale, and transfer. Eventually, with the support of a licensed exchange, the realization process was completed successfully. After completing the relevant proced</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23717</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-market Trading: Block Soars Over 9%, Reveals Total BTC Holdings Reached 8,692 Coins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23716</link>
      <description>On August 8th, based on the market data from RockFlow, during pre-market trading, Jack Dorsey, the co-founder of Twitter, saw his payment platform Block Inc (XYZ) surge by more than 9%, with the stock price currently at $83.86.According to the latest quarterly earnings report released on Thursday, Block achieved a gross profit of $2.54 billion in the second quarter, representing a 14% year-on-year increase. Block increased its holdings of Bitcoin by 108 coins, bringing the total holdings to 8692 coins.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23716</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiyaPay Analyst: Trump Signs Executive Order, $12.5 Trillion Expected to Enter Market, Bitcoin Ethereum See Price Spike</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23715</link>
      <description>August 8th. On Thursday, Trump signed an executive order mandating the U.S. Department of Labor to reassess the investment eligibility of industries like private equity, real estate, and cryptocurrency, enabling their inclusion in 401(k) retirement plan investments. This action might not only infuse a substantial amount of funds into the market but also trigger a robust rally in cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH).According to reports, this executive order also instructs the Department of Labor to cooperate with the Department of the Treasury, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and other relevant agencies to study how to adjust supporting regulations to permit more types of investments into 401(k) pension plans. It is anticipated that this change will bring approximately $12.5 trillion of pension funds into the market, undoubtedly offering strong backing for cryptocurrencies and related assets.In the past, due to legal uncertainties, the majority</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23715</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIO Protocol: Staking Feature Now Locks Over 100 Million BIO</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23714</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the DeSci protocol BIO Protocol declared that since the launch of the BIO token and staking feature on the Ethereum mainnet, more than 100 million BIO has been locked up till now.According to HTX market data, BIO briefly exceeded $0.1 today. It is currently trading at $0.087, with a 24-hour increase of 13.38%. On July 31st, Coinbase added support for Bio Protocol (BIO) on the Ethereum network.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Rush Investment: Holding 527.2048 Ethereum, with an average cost of approximately $3,714.91</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23713</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the Hong Kong-listed company Golden Fountain Investment (01328.HK) announced that as of the announcement date, the group holds 527.2048 Ethereum. The total cost is approximately $1.9585 million, and the average cost per Ethereum is approximately $3,714.91.According to the market data of RockFlow, Golden Fountain Investment (01328.HK) rose by 13.18% today with a trading volume of 21.5 million Hong Kong dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 10:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23713</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>