<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Kashkari: Inflation Still Too High, But Labor Market Showing Signs of Cooling</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27595</link>
      <description>September 4th: Kashkari of the Federal Reserve stated that the Fed has not yet accomplished its work of bringing inflation back to 2%. Inflation remains at a high level, yet the labor market is demonstrating signs of cooling. The Fed is confronted with a tricky situation related to its mandate.Data shows that the economy is decelerating and moving towards a soft landing. Tariffs have resulted in an increase in commodity inflation. The Fed relies heavily on government-published economic data. (Fx678 News)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27595</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US 5-Year Treasury Yield Falls Below 3.68%, Hitting a New Low Since April</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27594</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the yield of the US 5-year Treasury fell below 3.68%, reaching a new low since April. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27594</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin breaks $114,000, the mainstream CEX&apos;s total short liquidation volume will reach $1.289 billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27593</link>
      <description>On September 4th, based on Coinglass data, if Bitcoin manages to break through $114,000, the cumulative short liquidation intensity on mainstream CEX will reach $1.289 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin drops below $111,000, the cumulative long liquidation intensity on mainstream CEX will reach $1.231 billion.**BlockBeats Note**: The liquidation chart does not provide the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of liquidated contracts. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to the adjacent cluster, that is, the intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the underlying asset price will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will undergo a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade once it reaches that level.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27593</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aria, an IP Tokenization Platform, Completes Two Rounds of $15 Million Financing at a $50 Million Valuation, With Participation from Polychain</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27591</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the Aria Protocol Labs and the Aria Foundation—the team behind the story-driven Intellectual Property (IP) tokenization platform Aria—recently raised a total of $15 million in a seed round and a strategic round of financing. Both rounds of financing were completed in the previous month following negotiations that started in March. The seed round was led by Polychain Capital and Neoclassic Capital, while the strategic round received support from the Story Protocol Foundation and other unnamed investors in the cryptocurrency, intellectual property, and entertainment sectors.This financing employed a combination of equity and tokenized subscription rights, resulting in a $50 million valuation for Aria&apos;s equity. The project also intends to launch a native token in the future.Aria is constructed on Story, a Layer 1 blockchain designed specifically for IP tokenization. Currently, Aria is mainly focused on the tokenization of music IP, transforming music royalties into t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27591</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Suggests Future Tariffs Could Replace Income Tax, Potentially Altering Tax Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27592</link>
      <description>September 4th: U.S. President Trump insinuated that future tariffs might replace income tax, which could potentially lead to a transformation of tax policies.He asserted that tariffs are &quot;of great significance&quot; to America&apos;s prosperity. If we lose the tariff case, our nation might once again descend into an unimaginable state of poverty. The Supreme Court is set to hear the international tariff case. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Coinbase will list Awe (AWE)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27590</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Coinbase will make Awe (AWE) available for listing and support on the Base network. It is important to note that you should not send this asset through other networks, as there is a risk of losing your funds.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27590</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Withdrawal Recovery, 24-hour CEX Net Outflow of 898.13 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27589</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, according to Coinglass data, in the past 24 hours, a total net outflow of 898.13 BTC has been observed on CEX. The top three CEX with the largest outflow amounts are as follows:· Binance, with an outflow of 1,194.49 BTC;· Coinbase Pro, with an outflow of 674.44 BTC;· Bithumb, with an outflow of 304.17 BTC.In addition, Bitstamp saw an inflow of 335.46 BTC, ranking first in the list of inflows.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27589</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha&apos;s new airdrop BOOST will go live on September 5th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27588</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Binance Alpha will take the lead in listing Boost (BOOST) on September 5th. After trading begins, eligible users can use Binance Alpha Points to claim the airdrop on the Alpha event page. More details will be made public shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27588</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve will host a &quot;Payment Innovation&quot; conference next month to discuss stablecoins, artificial intelligence, and tokenization</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27587</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Federal Reserve will hold a &quot;Payment Innovation&quot; conference on October 21st. The conference topics will encompass: stablecoins, artificial intelligence, and tokenization.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27587</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Global Site Increases Perpetual Contract Leverage Limit to a maximum of 50x</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27586</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Coinbase International made an announcement regarding the adjustment of the perpetual contract leverage limit. It now allows for a leverage of up to 50x. This feature is accessible to Coinbase Advanced retail and institutional users via the Coinbase International Exchange. Perpetual contracts can only be used in compliant jurisdictions outside the United States.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27586</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>