<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A user fell victim to a fraudulent Uniswap phishing transaction, resulting in the loss of approximately $1 million in tokens and NFTs.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25723</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as monitored by ScamSniffer, a user lost around 1 million dollars&apos; worth of tokens and NFTs after signing a phishing batch trade request that was disguised as a Uniswap swap transaction.The attacker employed a fake Uniswap trading interface to deceive the user into signing a transaction. Malicious code or authorization was embedded within this transaction. Unaware of the situation, the user signed the transaction, which led to the theft of their assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25723</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwanese Prosecutors in China Bust &quot;CoinWish&quot; Tech Company for Fraud, Uncovering Money Laundering Totaling NT$2.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25722</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to the United News Network, the prosecutor&apos;s office in Taiwan, China, took action against the virtual currency physical store trading platform &quot;Coinwish&quot; Technology Company for being involved in a fraud case. The money laundering amount reached 2.3 billion New Taiwan Dollars, and there were over a thousand victims. Since April, the prosecutor&apos;s office has carried out search operations and successively detained 15 people, including the person in charge Shi Qiren. They seized 60.49 million New Taiwan Dollars in cash, 640,000 USDT, and other virtual assets. Today, the Shilin District Prosecutor&apos;s Office filed charges against these 15 individuals for fraud, money laundering, and organization crimes and applied for the confiscation of criminal proceeds totaling 1.275 billion New Taiwan Dollars.The prosecutor&apos;s office pointed out that Shi Qiren and others illegally provided virtual asset services to the public through the unapproved and incomplete anti-money launderi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25722</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Powell&apos;s speech tonight may not necessarily signal a policy shift, but it could open the door to a 25 basis point rate cut</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25721</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, Christoph Rieger, who is the Head of Rate and Credit Research at a German bank, stated in a report that the Fed Chair has in the past used the Jackson Hole Symposium to convey important policy guidance changes. However, it is not likely to occur this year. Rieger said, &quot;Although we anticipate that, when compared to previous guidance, that is, the Fed is waiting for more data, Powell&apos;s statement this time will not experience a significant change. Leaving the door open for a 25 basis point rate cut in September would be a reasonable action.&quot; (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25721</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two new wallets withdrew approximately 80,000 SOL from Binance and used it for staking.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25720</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per the monitoring of OnchainLens, within the past 2 hours, two new wallets have withdrawn 80,003 SOL from Binance. The value of this withdrawal is $14.7 million, and these funds have been staked.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale held 2216.79 ETH on Ethereum throughout the bullish trend for three months, achieving an impressive 73% return on investment.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25718</link>
      <description>August 22nd. According to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), on June X, the address 0x7C1...36FA7 withdrew 2216.79 ETH from Binance at a price of $2484 per ETH. The holdings remained idle for three months until all were transferred back to Binance three hours ago. If sold, the rate of return would be 73%, and a profit of $4 million was earned over the three-month period.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25718</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Stock Exchange Listed Company Timely Resources Plans to Issue Tokenized Silver Digital Currency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25719</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, as per an announcement from the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, the Hong Kong-listed company Timing Resources (08028.HK) declared that it would cooperate with Edelweiss Securities Futures to issue a digital token supported by physical silver assets (Silver Token), thus propelling Hong Kong&apos;s first Silver Tokenization of Real World Assets (RWA) project. Edelweiss Securities Futures&apos; parent company, Edelweiss Financial, will aid the issuer in obtaining all the requisite approvals from the relevant regulatory authority (if any) prior to the launch of the Silver Token.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25719</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIO briefly touched $0.21, surging over 37% in the past 24 hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25717</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, according to HTX market data, BIO briefly reached $0.21 and is currently trading at $0.2035, with a more than 37% increase in the past 24 hours.The DeSci protocol Bio Protocol recently launched a token launch platform. The first project is Aubrai. Users can obtain an issuance allocation by pledging BioXP. By investing in BIO, they can receive tokens. The final allocation depends on the BioXP staking share. The first BioAgent Launch project Aubrai sale will last for 24 hours, and the exact opening time will be announced separately. The AUBRAI token will be listed immediately after the sale.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25717</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump&apos;s son Eric Trump will attend the Metaplanet shareholder meeting on September 1st.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25716</link>
      <description>August 22nd: The son of former U.S. President Donald Trump, Eric Trump, is scheduled to attend the shareholders&apos; meeting of Japan&apos;s Bitcoin financial company Metaplanet Inc. on September 1st.Metaplanet, a hotel operator, shifted to a Bitcoin treasury strategy in early 2024 and has up to now accumulated 18,888 BTC with a value of over $2.1 billion. In March, Eric Trump was appointed as a strategic advisor. Meanwhile, at the meeting on September 1st, Metaplanet shareholders will vote on a new financing method. Metaplanet CEO Simon Gerovich previously stated that the goal for this year to increase the BTC holdings to 30,000 coins remains unchanged.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25716</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroBit Bitcoin and Ethereum Spot ETF Listed on HKEX</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25715</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the two virtual asset spot ETFs of Hong Kong asset management company MicroBit Asset Management were officially listed on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange. They are the MicroBit Bitcoin Spot ETF (HKD counter stock code: 3430.HK, USD counter stock code: 9430.HK) and the MicroBit Ethereum Spot ETF (HKD counter stock code: 3425.HK, USD counter stock code: 9425.HK). The management fee for both ETFs is 0.5%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25715</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss asset management company Tyr Capital has launched a new cryptocurrency market-neutral hedge fund.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25714</link>
      <description>On August 22nd, the Swiss digital asset management company Tyr Capital announced the establishment of a new cryptocurrency market-neutral hedge fund. The fund is designed to generate returns for investors by employing market-neutral and arbitrage strategies. It aims to maintain independence from market trends through a meta-strategy portfolio.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 06:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25714</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>