<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:18:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority: Stablecoin License &quot;Invitation-Only&quot; Unofficial Term, Institutions Can Proactively Engage in Licensing Matters</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22755</link>
      <description>August 1st. An official from the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) pointed out that the term &quot;license by invitation&quot; for stablecoins is not an official designation but rather a market perception. This term does not completely represent the licensing process of the HKMA. Institutions that have the intention and interest to apply can actively communicate with the HKMA regarding licensing matters.A week ago, Eddie Yue, the chief of the HKMA, disclosed that although it was clearly stated that only a few stablecoin licenses would be issued in the initial stage, dozens of institutions have already taken the initiative to approach the HKMA team. The HKMA announcement on July 29th also indicated that institutions interested in applying for the license should contact the HKMA by August 31, 2025, so that the HKMA can communicate regulatory expectations and provide corresponding feedback. The licensing process will continue. If individual institutions feel fully prepared and wish to be consid</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22755</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jie Zhuang Ng: The Stablecoin Regulation Will Surely Drive Hong Kong to Become a Global Web3 Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22756</link>
      <description>August 1st. Hong Kong Legislative Councilor Wu Jiezhuang posted on social media, stating that the official enforcement of the Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation took place today. He is glad to witness that many institutions from around the world are visiting Hong Kong to gain an understanding or express their intention to apply for a stablecoin license. This will undoubtedly contribute to the development of Hong Kong as a global Web3 hub. Meanwhile, it is necessary to remind industry practitioners and relevant institutions: after the law comes into effect, any business related to stablecoins must strictly comply with regulations. Recently, many industry insiders have inquired whether offline &quot;cryptocurrency exchange shops&quot; can continue to exchange and sell so-called &quot;stablecoins.&quot; It is recommended that everyone pay close attention to:Thoroughly studying the specific provisions of Article 6 and Article 9 of the Stablecoin Regulation;Urging users in Hong Kong who are interested in part</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22756</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Binance Retail Bitcoin Sell-off Surges, Whale Contrarian Accumulates $900 Million Worth of Ethereum</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22754</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Cryptoquant analyst Amr Taha issued a market analysis stating that the 7-day moving average of Bitcoin inflows to Binance by Short-Term Holders (STHs) has witnessed a significant spike. It rose from approximately 10,000 BTC to more than 36,000 BTC by the end of July. This sharp increase indicates abnormal activities among retail investors, which may be driven by profit-taking. A surge in exchange inflows usually implies that short-term investors are preparing to sell, especially when the price reaches a new high. This is in line with Bitcoin&apos;s recent record-breaking surge, further supporting the assumption that retail investors are reducing their BTC exposure.In sharp contrast to retail selling behavior, on July 31st, a whale wallet transferred over $9 billion worth of ETH from a centralized exchange (CEX) to an off-exchange wallet. Large-scale exchange outflows are usually related to accumulation strategies. When whales move assets to cold storage wallets, it indicate</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22754</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid Whale 24-Hour Intensive Withdrawal: Total USDC outflow exceeding 22 million, exacerbating downward market pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22753</link>
      <description>Update, August 1st: Based on HyperInsight&apos;s monitoring, a whale has withdrawn nearly 16.1 million USDC within the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x540545 withdrew approximately 7 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x9Cb4F2 withdrew approximately 1.85 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0xc68E69 withdrew approximately 1.2 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x2ac1fA3 withdrew approximately 2 million USDC in the past 2 hours. The whale at address 0x29862 withdrew approximately 4.05 million USDC in the past 2 hours. Meanwhile, the whale at address 0x3077fA made a deposit of approximately 1.85 million USDC in the past 1 hour.Earlier today, before 10 a.m., several whales had already withdrawn more than 6.4 million USDC, bringing the total withdrawal amount to over 22 million USDC so far. Additionally, due to the bearish market conditions, some whale ETH and BTC short positions are still under pressure.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22753</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridgewater Associates Founder Ray Dalio Sells Remaining Stake, to Step Down from Board of Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22752</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as reported by Reuters, in a letter addressed to investors, Ray Dalio, the founder of Bridgewater Associates, has sold his remaining stake in the fund. Dalio established the Bridgewater hedge fund 50 years ago, and this transaction signals the conclusion of a multi-year transition for the world&apos;s largest hedge fund with $92.1 billion in assets under management. Ray Dalio, who is 76 years old, stepped down as the CEO in 2017 and is scheduled to transfer the control of the Bridgewater hedge fund to a new generation of investors in 2022. A source disclosed that Ray Dalio will also resign from the board.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink: The per-mil &quot;ETH concentration&quot; has increased from around 2 to around 3.4, a 70% increase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22751</link>
      <description>August 1st, The &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; SharpLink Gaming declared that our mission is to maximize shareholder value while holding as much Ethereum as possible. To ensure full transparency, we not only report the issued number of shares or the amount of ETH held but also monitor the ETH amount within every 1000 shares of ownership. We refer to it as &quot;ETH Concentration&quot;, which indicates how much Ethereum is supporting every 1,000 shares of SBET stock. Since the implementation of the ETH Treasury strategy, the &quot;ETH Concentration&quot; has risen from approximately 2.00 to about 3.40, representing a 70% increase.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22751</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riot Blockchain&apos;s Net Revenue Reaches $219.5 Million in Q2, Mining Cost Doubles Year Over Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22750</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as per TheBlock, the Bitcoin mining firm Riot Platforms attained a net revenue of $219.5 million during the second quarter of 2025. This reversed a net loss of nearly $300 million in the first quarter. As of this year, Riot Platforms has accumulated a net loss of $76.9 million. Owing to the global average network hash rate increase, the cost of mining one Bitcoin has gone up by 93% compared to the same period last year. In the second quarter, Riot Platforms mined 1,426 Bitcoins, raising their total holdings to 19,273 Bitcoins and ranking fourth among publicly traded global companies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22750</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Ethereum Spot ETF has seen net inflows for 20 consecutive trading days, with yesterday&apos;s inflow reaching $17 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22748</link>
      <description>Update: On August 1st, based on the information from Farside Investors, the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF was $17 million the previous day, indicating that it has seen net inflows for 20 consecutive days.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22748</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In July, the U.S. Ethereum Spot ETF saw a precise net inflow of $54.309 billion, setting a new monthly record for inflows</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22749</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as monitored by Farside Investors, the precise data indicates that the net inflow of the US Ethereum spot ETF in July reached $5.4309 billion, setting a record for the highest monthly inflow. Ethereum&apos;s monthly low began at $2485.47 and closed at $3698.39, representing a roughly 48.8% increase. This marks the highest monthly gain since August 2022. During this period, it reached a 2025-year-to-date high of $3941.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22749</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hong Kong &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; has officially come into effect today, opening the first round of stablecoin issuer license applications.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22747</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the &quot;Stablecoin Regulation&quot; in Hong Kong officially came into effect today. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority has opened the application for stablecoin issuance licenses, marking a new stage in the development of stablecoins in the Hong Kong region. Over the past year, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority has promoted sandbox testing of stablecoin application scenarios, gradually clarifying regulatory guidelines and application processes. Now, participating institutions will transition from testing to the formal issuance and circulation under the regulatory framework. According to incomplete statistics, dozens of institutions have indicated that they will apply for a stablecoin license, including JD Coin Chain Technology (Hong Kong) Limited, RoundCoin Innovation Technology Limited, Standard Chartered Bank (Hong Kong) Limited, Onchain Group Limited, Hong Kong Telecommunications (HKT) Limited, and others. Meanwhile, more local banks, tech companies, and Web3 teams are making fu</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22747</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>