<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:17:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Korean Prosecutors Seek to Sentence South Korean Actress Hwang Jung-eum to 3 Years in Prison for Embezzling 4.2 Billion KRW in Public Funds to Invest in Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25630</link>
      <description>August 22nd. As per Yonhap News Agency, the South Korean prosecutor sought a 3-year prison term for actor Hwang Jung-eum, who is facing accusations of embezzling 4.3 billion South Korean Won (approximately $3.07 million) of company funds and investing in cryptocurrency.On the 21st, during the closing argument in a public trial at the Jeju District Prosecutor&apos;s Office, it requested the Jeju District Court Criminal Division 2 (Presiding Judge Im Namin) to sentence actor Hwang Jung-eum to 3 years in prison on charges of violating the &quot;Specific Economic Crimes Aggravation Act Punishment and other relevant laws&quot; (embezzlement).Previously reported on June 17th, South Korean actress Hwang Jung-eum was accused of embezzling around 4.2 billion South Korean Won (about $3.07 million) of company funds to invest in cryptocurrency. Her agency, Y1 Entertainment, stated on June 17th that Hwang Jung-eum had repaid the full amount in two installments on May 30th and June 5th. Earlier, Hwang Jung-eum</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25630</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encryption security company Kerberus has announced the acquisition of Refract.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25629</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as reported by The Block, the cryptocurrency security firm Kerberus declared the acquisition of the wallet anti-fraud browser extension Pocket Universe from its developer Refract for a sum in the seven-figure range.According to the announcement, Kerberus will incorporate Pocket Universe into its native Sentinel3 security extension, thereby expanding antivirus protection to all EVM chains and Solana. The company also intends to keep Pocket&apos;s user experience &quot;unaltered.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25629</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant Analyst: Bitcoin Whales are Buying the Dip, Accumulating Over 16,000 BTC in the Past 7 Days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25628</link>
      <description>On August 21st, CryptoQuant analyst Cauê Oliveira stated, &quot;During the past seven days, Bitcoin whale wallets have accumulated more than 16,000 BTC, suggesting that whales are purchasing on dips when the Bitcoin price declines.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25628</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaoBank becomes the first third-party custodian to launch services on the J.P. Morgan Digital Asset Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25627</link>
      <description>On August 21st, State Street became the first third-party custodian to initiate services on JPMorgan&apos;s digital debt servicing platform, thereby offering institutional clients blockchain-based debt security custody services. (Sohu Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25627</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total OKB 24h Contract Trading Volume across the Network: $398 million, a 726.98% increase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25626</link>
      <description>On August 21st, based on Coinglass data, the current total open interest of OKB futures is $22.0646 million, with a 24-hour increase of 244.74%. The futures trading volume is $398 million, with a 24-hour increase of 726.98%. The 24-hour aggregated long/short ratio is 1.0412.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25626</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Research Director: Predicts Stablecoin Market Size Could Reach $1.2 Trillion by 2028</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25625</link>
      <description>On August 21st, David Duong, the Research Director of Coinbase, wrote that Coinbase Research employed a random model and the Monte Carlo simulation method to predict that the stablecoin market could reach $1.2 trillion by 2028. Future growth projections generally rely on assumptions regarding the share of the global money supply that stablecoins could ultimately hold. The model captures the potential growth range of the market through an autoregressive model AR(1), commencing from the most recent observed level and month-on-month growth, and simulates 20,000 Monte Carlo paths on a monthly basis in accordance with a simple AR(1) process. The predicted outcomes indicate that by December 2028, the stablecoin market could reach $1.2 trillion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25625</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The trading volume on Polymarket for betting on LeBron James to be elected President of the United States in 2028 has exceeded the combined total for Musk and others.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25624</link>
      <description>On August 21st, the trading volume on Polymarket for placing bets on NBA star LeBron James being elected President of the United States in 2028 has reached $1.9 million. This has exceeded the total amounts for US Vice President Harris, California Governor Gavin Newsom, and US Congresswoman Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.However, according to Polymarket data, James&apos; current election probability is merely 0.3%. The $1.9 million trading volume may be due to some users engaging in wash trading in the hope of potentially receiving future airdrops.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Justice Department Official Urges Powell to Replace Director Cook</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25623</link>
      <description>On August 21, officials from the US Department of Justice urged Chair Powell of the Fed to replace Governor Quarles. (Xinhua News)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25623</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verb Technology Reveals Holdings of $7.13 Billion in TON and $67 Million in Cash</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25622</link>
      <description>On August 21st, Verb Technology Company, Inc. (listed on NASDAQ as VERB and to be renamed Ton Strategy Company) announced today that the company&apos;s treasury assets have exceeded $780 million. This includes $713 million in Toncoin (TON) and $67 million in cash.Previously, on August 8th, Verb Technology completed a $558 million private placement. It was participated in by over 110 institutional and crypto-native investors. The company will use most of the funds raised in this private placement to purchase TON as its primary treasury reserve asset. The aim is to accumulate more than 5% of TON&apos;s circulating supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25622</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institution has sold 2,070 BTC in the past 24 hours and bought 30,367 ETH, opening long positions for 78,000 ETH in contracts.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25621</link>
      <description>On August 21st, as monitored by on-chain analyst Wu Ji, a whale/institution that had been holding 10,606 BTC for 7 years achieved a profit of $1.12 billion. In the past 24 hours, it sold 2,070 BTC ($235 million).A portion of the proceeds from the BTC sale was used to purchase 30,367 ETH ($131 million) in the spot market; part of it was used to open a long position of 78,000 ETH through contracts (with a position value of $336 million). It still holds 8,437 BTC ($960 million) and may continue to shift to ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/25621</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>