<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:14:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Commerce Secretary: Trump Has Decided to Allow China to Purchase H20 Chips in a &apos;Balanced Manner&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21541</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. Commerce Secretary Raimondo declared that Trump has made a decision to enable China to acquire NVIDIA H20 chips in a &quot;balanced&quot; manner.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Commerce Secretary: Trump Wants EU to &apos;Fully&apos; Open Its Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21540</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, U.S. Commerce Secretary Raimondo declared that if the EU were to accept U.S. products and standards, it would &quot;promptly&quot; lead to a response from Trump. Trump desires that the EU will &quot;completely&quot; open its market.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $118,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21539</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $118,000, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 1.20%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Stock Options have commenced trading on the New York Stock Exchange.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21538</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the cryptocurrency mining company BitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE AMERICAN: BMNR; hereinafter referred to as &quot;BitMine&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) announced today that the common stock of the company is now open for options trading on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE).BitMine Immersion Technologies is a company specializing in cryptocurrency mining, and its treasury strategy aims to acquire 5% of the global Ethereum (ETH) supply.The stock options of BitMine officially began trading on July 23, 2025, with the trading symbol &quot;BMNR&quot;, covering a range of standard expiration dates and exercise prices. The introduction of options is expected to expand investors&apos; participation channels, increase the liquidity of the company&apos;s stock, and provide investors with more flexible means to manage risks, leverage positions, or express views on the company&apos;s stock price movement.The BitMine stock options will be cleared through the Options Clearing Corporation (OCC) and are subject to t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The massive ETH queue for unbonding may be related to the sudden drop in Ethereum supply on Aave, and if it worsens, it could lead to stETH becoming untethered.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21537</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the cryptocurrency Key Opinion Leader (KOL) darkpools posted an analysis on social media, stating that the recent reason for the 620,000 ETH queued for unstaking might be as follows: A whale withdrew ETH deposits from Aave (reducing the supply of ETH), resulting in the ETH utilization rate on Aave soaring, leading to a sharp increase in the borrowing rate of ETH; Users using stETH for looping faced unprofitability due to high costs, prompting them to reduce leverage; A large amount of de-leveraged stETH entered the staking withdrawal queue; Some users chose to directly sell stETH to avoid the withdrawal queue, causing stETH to deviate by 30 basis points (0.3%).Due to the fact that the oracle price of stETH is based on the redemption value rather than the market price, lenders are currently stuck in their positions and may need to wait for up to about 18 days, which is the current ETH unstaking queue time. If the situation continues to deteriorate, stETH may face liquida</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature&apos;s Miracle Market Cap currently stands at $7.09 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21536</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc., a vertical agriculture technology company listed on the US OTC trading market (OTCQB: NMHI), currently has a market value of $7.09 million. Its stock price rose by more than 10% on the previous trading day.Today, Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc. announced a $20 million XRP Treasury Reserve Plan. This plan will be supported by equity financing from GHS Investments based on the company&apos;s previously effective S-1 registration statement declared by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The purpose is to purchase XRP and meet operational funding needs.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature&apos;s Miracle has announced a $20 million XRP Treasury Reserve Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21534</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, the vertical farming technology company Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc. (OTCQB: NMHI) (hereinafter referred to as &quot;Nature&apos;s Miracle&quot; or the &quot;Company&quot;) announced today that the Company will establish a corporate-level XRP treasury plan with a maximum amount of $20 million. This plan will be supported by equity financing from GHS Investments based on the previously effective S-1 registration statement announced by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and will be used to purchase XRP and meet operational funding requirements.This strategic move makes Nature&apos;s Miracle one of the first listed companies to adopt XRP as a core treasury strategy. The plan will focus on the following directions:- Long-term strategic XRP reserves;- Deployment of staking mechanisms to earn rewards;- Deep involvement in the Ripple ecosystem.To support this plan, Nature&apos;s Miracle will initially use a portion of the equity financing funds that may be obtained through the S-1 registra</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21534</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Network&apos;s Stablecoin Supply Surpasses $140 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21535</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, based on on-chain data, the supply of stablecoins on the Ethereum network has exceeded $140 billion and reached a new record high. Compared to the level in January 2024, the supply has nearly doubled.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink Gaming generated a yield of 567 ETH through Ethereum staking.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21533</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, SharpLink Gaming made an official announcement that it possesses 360,807 Ethereum and has obtained 567 ETH in revenue through staking.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21533</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinUp.io&apos;s public blockchain CPChain is officially live</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21532</link>
      <description>On July 23rd, CoinUp.io made an announcement that its underlying public chain, CPChain, has officially been launched. This not only signifies a new chapter within the CoinUp ecosystem but also takes a firm stride towards a decentralized future.CPChain will offer a fast, secure, and low-cost on-chain experience to global users, enabling countless innovative scenarios and applications. As the core asset of the platform, the CP token will serve as a key driving force for the cross-chain ecosystem, unlocking more rights and value.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/21532</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>