<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:45:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Market&apos;s Three Major Indexes Turn Lower, S&amp;P 500 Index Erases Opening Gains</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27741</link>
      <description>September 4th: The three major U.S. stock indexes witnessed a downward trend. The Dow decreased by 0.06%. The S&amp;P 500 wiped out its opening gains. And the Nasdaq dropped by 0.1%. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27741</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In August, CEX Platform Ethereum Spot Trading Volume Surpasses Bitcoin for the First Time in Seven Years</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27740</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to The Block. Based on The Block&apos;s data, the August and weekly spot trading volume of centralized exchanges (CEX) Ethereum exceeded that of Bitcoin (BTC) for the first time in at least seven years.Throughout August, Ethereum consistently outperformed Bitcoin in the seven-day cumulative spot trading volume of centralized exchanges, bringing an end to Bitcoin&apos;s long-term dominance in global spot trading volume. The total Ethereum trading volume on CEX platforms reached approximately $480 billion, while Bitcoin was around $401 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27740</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $110,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27739</link>
      <description>On September 4th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $110,000, with a 24-hour decline of 1.66%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27739</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buidlpad: Initiated BARD Public Sale Settlement and Refund, Token Claiming to Open at TGE</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27738</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as per an official announcement by Buidlpad, the settlement and refund procedure for the Bitcoin DeFi protocol Lombard&apos;s token BARD public sale has officially commenced. In order to ensure the security of all user funds, withdrawals will be opened in a phased manner. Token claiming can be carried out at Lombard&apos;s TGE.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27738</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list OpenLedger (OPEN) on September 8th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27737</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Binance Alpha is scheduled to list OpenLedger (OPEN) on September 8th. Eligible users will be able to use Alpha Points to claim the airdrop on the Alpha Activity page once trading commences. Further details will be disclosed shortly.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27737</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk&apos;s X Money Plan Thwarted by Regulation and Employee Attrition</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27736</link>
      <description>September 4th: Musk&apos;s X Money plan faced setbacks due to regulatory issues and employee attrition. It is reported that one of Musk&apos;s primary ambitions is to utilize technology to disrupt and replace traditional banks and payment processors. Meanwhile, one of his management ideologies is to encourage employees to develop products in a quick and cost-effective manner. Within X, these two ideologies are beginning to clash. Musk desires that X can promptly launch a nationwide payment service, which has led to regulatory hurdles and triggered a wave of senior employee departures.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Department of Justice has launched a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Governor Lisa Cook and has issued a subpoena.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27735</link>
      <description>On September 4th, as reported by The Wall Street Journal, the U.S. Department of Justice has initiated a criminal investigation into Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard and has issued a subpoena to conduct an investigation into whether she provided false information in a mortgage loan application. (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27735</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. August Services PMI Final Slightly Below Preliminary Reading, Future Economic Growth Still Faces Downside Risks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27734</link>
      <description>On September 4th, Chris Williamson, the Chief Business Economist at S&amp;P Global Market Intelligence, stated that although the final value of the US services PMI was lower than the initial value and below the July level, the August service sector data still ranked as the second strongest so far this year. Coupled with the excellent performance of the manufacturing PMI, these survey results suggest that the US economy is expected to achieve a 2.4% annualized growth rate in the third quarter.At the same time, the orders more evidently reflect the increase in summer customer demand, which has led an increasing number of service providers to recruit new employees. Moreover, the manufacturing industry has also resumed hiring. However, the current positive news regarding growth and hiring has been overshadowed by concerns about the outlook for future development and inflation. Survey data indicate some downside risks to economic growth in the upcoming months. Additionally, there are upside r</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27734</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The stablecoin FRNT issued by the state of Wyoming is about to go live on Hedera</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27733</link>
      <description>On September 4th, the Wyoming Stablecoin Committee announced during a committee meeting that the first state government-issued stablecoin in the United States, the Frontier Stable Token (FRNT), is scheduled to be launched on Hedera. In the committee&apos;s second-quarter assessment, Hedera was selected as the sole candidate blockchain for FRNT because of its strict standards in terms of speed, reliability, and compliance.FRNT is the first stablecoin created under the &quot;2023 Wyoming Stablecoin Act.&quot; This is the first stablecoin issued by a U.S. state government. The token is fully backed by the U.S. dollar and short-term government bonds, with an additional 2% reserve to ensure stability. The design of FRNT aims to demonstrate how digital assets can enhance public finance by enabling faster, more transparent, and more efficient payments.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27733</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle announces that native USDC and CCTP V2 will soon be available on Plume</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27732</link>
      <description>According to official sources on September 4th, Circle announced that native USDC and CCTP V2 will soon become available on Plume.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27732</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>