<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:48:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Point Rule Adjustment, Doubling of New Coin Trading Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27541</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as per an official announcement, Binance Alpha has made an adjustment to its points rules and entered a new coin exclusive reward season. The trading volume points bonus rule will be updated as follows:Tokens that are airdropped or from a TGE via Binance Alpha will be eligible for a 30-day Binance Alpha platform incentive. Users who purchase the token within 30 days of the airdrop or TGE will receive the following trading volume points bonus:For BSC chain token purchases, you will receive 4 times the Alpha trading volume;For purchases of tokens from other chains, you will receive 2 times the Alpha trading volume;For tokens that are airdropped or from a TGE by BinanceAlpha and exceed 30 days or tokens that do not have any Binance Alpha airdrop or TGE activities, they will not be subject to any trading volume points bonus rules. The Binance Wallet Alpha Leaderboard has now added a &quot;Points+&quot; ranking, enabling users to easily participate in the new coin exclusive r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27541</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital has tokenized stocks on Solana, taking a key step in RWA [Real World Asset] integration.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27540</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Nasdaq-listed crypto company Galaxy Digital launched a plan to &quot;tokenize its SEC-registered stock and deploy it on a mainstream blockchain.&quot; Beginning today, shareholders can tokenize GLXY stock through Superstate&apos;s Opening Bell platform.The announcement indicated that Galaxy&apos;s tokenized stock and future listings on Opening Bell may offer broader liquidity and utility through automated market makers (AMMs) and other DeFi platforms. Galaxy&apos;s tokenized stock will only be accessible to KYC-verified accredited investors, who can hold and transfer these tokens within their own crypto wallets.In May of this year, Superstate launched Opening Bell with the aim of bringing SEC-registered stocks onto the blockchain, starting with Solana. While several projects have attempted to integrate publicly traded stocks with blockchain infrastructure, Opening Bell claims to be the first platform to provide direct issuance and on-chain trading of SEC-registered public stocks, rath</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27540</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Reserve Concept Stock Surges Pre-market, BMNR Up by 3.55%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27539</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, based on market data, Ethereum reserve concept stocks in the US stock market showed an overall increase in pre-market trading. These included:· SharpLink Gaming (SBET.US) with a rise of 1.71%;· Bitmine Immersion Technologies (BMNR.US) up by 3.55%;· ETHZilla (ETHZ.US) increasing by 1.50%;· BTCS (BTCS.US) with a gain of 0.98%;· COIN (Coinbase.US) up 0.66%;· Bit Digital (BTBT.US) rising by 1.15%.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27539</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whale Has Accumulated Over 167,000 AAVE in the Past Week, Valued at Around $53.65 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27538</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as monitored by lookonchain, the whale address 0xF436 withdrew an additional 25,097 AAVE (approximately $7.9 million) from the exchange platform 2 hours ago. During the past week, this whale has already withdrawn a total of 167,451 AAVE (approximately $53.65 million) from the exchange platform.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27538</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Bitcoin company Treasury has completed a $147 million financing round, acquiring over 1000 BTC</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27537</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as reported by Cointelegraph, the European Bitcoin company Treasury has successfully completed a fundraising round amounting to $147 million. This round was led by Winklevoss Capital and Nakamoto Holdings. Additionally, Treasury has acquired more than 1000 BTC.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27537</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State Bank of Pakistan to Withdraw its Warning on Cryptocurrency Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27536</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, the Pakistani Ministry of Finance made an announcement. It stated that the State Bank of Pakistan will withdraw its warning regarding cryptocurrency trading. At the same time, the State Bank of Pakistan is in the process of working to launch a digital currency.Previously reported by BlockBeats, on July 27th, the Pakistani Minister of State for Cryptocurrency and Blockchain, Bilal Bin Saqib, pointed out that the country&apos;s demographic structure would drive the adoption of Bitcoin and achieve &quot;leapfrog development&quot;, surpassing developed countries in this regard. Bilal Bin Saqib emphasized that Pakistan has 40 million crypto wallets, making it one of the top five countries globally in terms of the cryptocurrency adoption rate. The country has a median age of 20 years, a total population of 250 million, with 70% of the population being under 30 years old. &quot;Emerging markets will achieve leapfrog development in the adoption of these new technologies, and smaller countries</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top L2 Network Linea Finally Launches Mainnet after Three Years of Development, Set to Go Live on September 10th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27535</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, Linea, the premier Ethereum Layer 2 network developed by Consensys, has finally launched its native token after a three-year development period. Currently, the airdrop query is officially available, and the TGE will occur on September 10th.Linea&apos;s team stated that the relationship between LINEA and ETH is similar to that of silver and gold. They will empower the Ethereum ecosystem through a native asset income mechanism, a dual-token burn model (ETH + LINEA), value flowing back to the Layer 1 network, and sustainable funding for open-source software. Their goal is to build the most ETH-centric Layer 2 network, with scaling and strengthening Ethereum being inseparable dual goals.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27535</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KuCoin Launches Innovative Cloud Mining Platform KuMining, Product to Be Available for Purchase Starting September 16th</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27534</link>
      <description>September 3rd. According to official information, KuCoin declared the launch of the innovative cloud mining platform KuMining. This will enable individual investors to obtain hashing power at a competitive price.It is reported that the platform supports Bitcoin (BTC) and Dogecoin (DOGE), including Litecoin (LTC) merged mining. It relies on a 300-megawatt to 2-gigawatt infrastructure (provided by elphapex) and an initial 10 EH/s BTC hashing power. Through cooperation with professional manufacturers and energy experts, decentralized hashing power is achieved. Thousands of liquid-cooled machines will be added monthly to ensure capacity expansion and real-time transparent monitoring of operations. The product will be available for purchase starting from September 16th.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27534</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CanGu Group produced 663.7 Bitcoins in August, bringing their total holdings to 5197 Bitcoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27533</link>
      <description>September 3rd: Canaan Inc. (&quot;Canaan&quot; or &quot;the Company&quot;) provided its August 2025 Bitcoin production and operational update on September 2nd. The figures indicate that the company mined 663.7 bitcoins in August, increasing its total holdings to 5,193.4 bitcoins. The company intends to hold Bitcoin for the long term and currently has no plans to sell.Canaan&apos;s CEO and Director, Paul Yu, offered the following comments: &quot;Since attaining full production of the additional 50 EH/s of mining power in July, the company&apos;s average monthly operational hash rate has witnessed a 6.9% growth. This month&apos;s production of 663.7 bitcoins has enabled the company to surpass the 5,000 bitcoins milestone, a notable achievement that firmly validates our strategic orientation and lays a solid foundation for sustainable development.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27533</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase is planning to launch the first U.S. stock and cryptocurrency blended index futures, with the index composition including seven giants, COIN, and two BlackRock spot ETFs.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27532</link>
      <description>On September 3rd, as per official channels, Coinbase declared that its derivative trading platform is constantly expanding its product range and is planning to launch the innovative Mag7+ Cryptocurrency Stock Index Futures, which is the first derivative futures contract in the US to simultaneously cover both stocks and cryptocurrencies. The composition of the index includes:· US Stocks &quot;Big Seven&quot;: Apple (AAPL), Microsoft (MSFT), Google (GOOGL), Amazon (AMZN), Nvidia (NVDA), Meta (META), Tesla (TSLA)· Coinbase Stock (COIN)· Cryptocurrency ETFs: Bletchley Bitcoin Trust (IBIT), Ethereum Trust (ETHA)The index adopts an equally weighted calculation method, with each of the 10 components holding a 10% weight, and undergoes quarterly rebalancing to reflect market fluctuations. MarketVector acts as the official index provider. The contracts utilize a monthly cash settlement model, with each contract representing 1 times the index value, and it is expected that trading of this product</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27532</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>