<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:51:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ORDER surged above $0.20 yesterday, with a 25%+ gain in the past 7 days</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26111</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on HTX market data, Orderly (ORDER) witnessed a significant increase yesterday. It briefly exceeded $0.2 and is now in a retracement to $0.1770. It has witnessed a 3.38% increase in the past 24 hours and a surge of more than 25% in the past 7 days. The current market capitalization is $50.16 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26111</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Deposit Trend Continues, with CEX Net Inflow of 7,316.90 BTC in the Last 24 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26110</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on Coinglass data, within the past 24 hours, the total net inflow of BTC on CEX was 7,316.90 BTC. The top three CEX exchanges in terms of inflow volume are as follows:- Binance had a net inflow of 4,072.23 BTC.- Coinbase Pro had a net inflow of 2,111.21 BTC.- Bitfinex had a net inflow of 896.61 BTC.In addition, OKX had a net outflow of 872.60 BTC and ranked first on the outflow list.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26110</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Big Bro Buddy」 went long 25x with 15,600 ETH and 40x with 175 BTC.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26109</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on on-chain data, &quot;Brother Ma Ji&quot; Huang Licheng took a long position of 25 times on 15,600 ETH and 40 times on 175 BTC on the Hyperliquid platform, with a total position value of 93 million US dollars.The liquidation price for the Ethereum long position was $4696.96, and the liquidation price was $2075.7.The liquidation price for the Bitcoin long position was $113,714.4.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 05:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26109</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: Food Industry Seeks Tariff Exemption, Inflation and Rate Cut Tug-of-War Market Expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26108</link>
      <description>August 25th: The U.S. food industry, which is highly reliant on imports, is striving for a tariff exemption in order to avoid price hikes that could lead to an increase in inflation. At this moment, Trump&apos;s substantial tariff hikes are further highlighting the industry&apos;s vulnerability. The market is also concentrating on the September Federal Reserve meeting. During this meeting, Chairman Powell hinted that weak employment might justify a rate cut. Generally, investors expect a 25-basis-point cut. History indicates that rate cuts after a prolonged period of stagnation are beneficial to the stock market. However, the inflationary pressure caused by tariffs may offset some of the easing effects.On the crypto market front, ETH has achieved a new high in a bullish sentiment. The liquidation heat map shows strong support in the range of 4,600 - 4,650, and the liquidity is concentrated in the range of 4,850 - 4,880 above.Bitunix Analyst Recommendation: The U.S. is entering a stage of po</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 04:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26108</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Bitcoin Drops Below $113,000</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26107</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to HTX market data, Bitcoin dropped below $113,000, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 2.08%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 04:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26107</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin&apos;s Near-Term Outlook May Depend on US Economic Data</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26106</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Linh Tran, a market analyst at XS.com, stated that the recent outlook for Bitcoin will mainly depend on the upcoming U.S. economic data, such as preliminary GDP and core personal consumption expenditures inflation. If the data continues to indicate a slowing U.S. economy and easing inflation, the Federal Reserve will have more grounds to initiate a rate-cutting cycle.Tran said, &quot;This situation will create a liquidity-rich environment that is conducive to Bitcoin&apos;s recovery.&quot; However, Tran also added that if the data unexpectedly turns out to be &quot;hot,&quot; investors may adopt a defensive stance and extend the short-term pullback. (FX678)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 04:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26106</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit Makes Solana Debut in Global Trading Competition, Onchain Wave Event Prize Pool Surpasses $1 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26104</link>
      <description>August 25th. Bybit declared that its annual event WSOT 2025 is going to make its debut on the Solana blockchain for the very first time. It is going to launch the on-chain special event &quot;Onchain Wave&quot; with a total prize pool exceeding $1 million and will run until September 15th. This event is co-hosted by Bybit Web3 and Byreal platforms, enabling CEX and DEX users to compete on the leaderboard together. The awards comprise:- Weekly Leaderboard Rewards: The top 200 traders each week will jointly share up to 250 BBSOL tokens.- Overall Leaderboard Rewards: The top 1000 traders will share 1650 BBSOL tokens.- Warrior Award: Users with a trading volume exceeding $10,000 but not making it to the leaderboard will share 900 BBSOL tokens.- Byreal Exclusive Award: LPs will daily share a prize pool of 650,000 USDC.In addition, a sixth-anniversary special award will be presented to the 6th-ranked users on both the weekly and overall leaderboards.It is reported that the event&apos;s partners inclu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DONKEY Meme Coin Market Cap Briefly Surpasses $77 Million, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26103</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to the market data of GMGN, the market capitalization of the BSC ecosystem Meme coin DONKEY briefly exceeded 77 million USD, reaching a historical high. It has now dropped to 60.9 million USD, with a 24-hour increase of 81%.The 24-hour trading volume reached 19.2 million USD, and the number of hodlers reached 34,360.BlockBeats Note: Meme coins are highly volatile and mostly lack practical use cases. Please be cautious about asset protection and avoid the fear of missing out (FOMO).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26103</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin Balaji&apos;s Market Cap Surges Above $20M Briefly, with a 123% 24-Hour Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26105</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to GMGN market data, the market capitalization of the Base ecosystem&apos;s Meme coin balajis briefly reached over $20 million and is now back at $19.48 million, with a 24-hour increase of 123%.A screenshot was posted by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong on the X platform yesterday at 6:01, showing his purchase of 4,964,005 balajis, which is currently worth about $99,000. Brian Armstrong also retweeted a tweet from Jesse Pollak, the head of the Base ecosystem, stating that users can now directly purchase any Zora creator token in the Coinbase app.balajis is created through the Zora platform and is a Meme concept coin named after former Coinbase CTO and angel investor Balaji Srinivasan.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26105</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris Bank expects the Federal Reserve to cut interest rates by 25 basis points in September and December.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26102</link>
      <description>On August 25th, BNP Paribas anticipates that the Federal Reserve will reduce interest rates by 25 basis points in September and December (formerly predicted that there would be no rate cut until 2025).Previously, Barclays expected that the Federal Reserve would cut interest rates by 25 basis points in both September and December of this year (formerly predicted to cut rates only once in December). (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 03:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26102</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>