<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:33:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>An address holding 306 BTC has just been activated after 12.4 years of dormancy</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22854</link>
      <description>On August 1st, as monitored by Whale Alert, an address that was holding 306 BTC (approximately $35.16 million) was just made active after having been dormant for 12.4 years.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22854</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary: Actively Exploring the Potential of Decentralized Computing and Digital Payments to Unleash the Power of Blockchain Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22853</link>
      <description>On August 1st, U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson made a post on social media, saying, &quot;The United States has stepped into the golden era of cryptocurrency. We are delving into new possibilities regarding decentralized computing and digital payments, with the goal of tapping the potential of blockchain technology. Thus, establish a company here, launch a protocol, and hire employees.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22853</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Farm Payroll Data Validates Powell and Bowman&apos;s Justification for Rate Cut: Labor Market Shows Signs of Weakness</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22852</link>
      <description>August 1st: On August 1st, the U.S. labor data provided support for calls for monetary easing. As a result, U.S. Treasury yields and the U.S. dollar declined. Meanwhile, previous data was revised significantly downward: the May nonfarm payroll number was revised from 144,000 to 19,000, and the June nonfarm payroll number was revised from 147,000 to 14,000.Before the release of the employment report, Federal Reserve Board members Waller and Bowman, who held different views, indicated signs of weakness in the labor market. The market experienced a sharp decline immediately after the release of the employment data. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22852</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gryphon shareholders will vote on the proposed merger with Bitcoin mining firm American Bitcoin on August 27.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22851</link>
      <description>August 1st: As per The Miner Mag, American Bitcoin Corp (ABC), a Bitcoin mining firm with the backing of the Trump family, is scheduled to finalize a covert merger with Gryphon Digital Mining and get listed on Nasdaq.On July 31st, Gryphon submitted a proxy statement in connection with the merger to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and officially set a shareholder vote for August 27th. Meanwhile, the SEC has declared the effectiveness of the S-4 registration statement for the transaction, indicating that regulatory approval has been obtained and clearing the way for the merger.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22851</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Fed: Still Expects One Rate Cut This Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22850</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the Boston Fed stated that although employment data is significant, revisions are even more crucial. The job market is showing a slowdown from a strong position. The inflation risk is far greater than the employment risk. It still anticipates cutting interest rates once this year. (Xinhua)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22850</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARK Innovation ETF (ARKK) Receives Record Single-Day Inflow</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22849</link>
      <description>On August 1st, Bloomberg ETF Senior Analyst Eric Balchunas posted on social media that ARKK attracted $800 million within just one day, establishing a new all-time record for daily fund inflows. This is probably because the fund has seen a 50% surge in the past 3 months, which is double the gains of SPY, QQQ, and IBIT. ARKK attracted $150 million in inflows, and the total daily fund inflows for the entire ARK series reached nearly $1 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22849</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin protocol Resupply has announced that it has fully repaid a $10 million bad debt.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22848</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to official channels, the stablecoin protocol Resupply declared that the $10 million in bad debts has now been completely repaid. Specifically, the $8.8 million in bad debts associated with the recent security vulnerability was repaid first.The remaining $1.13 million in bad debts is covered by a loan obtained from yearn and will be gradually repaid through the RSUP pledged in Convex and Yearn Finance within the protocol. Thus, all bad debts have officially been wiped out.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain insider whale increased their ETH short position to a notional value of $40.25 million, realizing a floating profit of over $3.24 million.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22846</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a particular &quot;insider whale&quot; continued to increase their short position in ETH and raised it to 11,111.11 coins (with a nominal value of $40.25 million). Currently, their short positions in both BTC and ETH are worth more than $168 million, and they have an unrealized gain of more than $3.24 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22846</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The total nonfarm payroll employment for May and June in the United States has been revised downward by 258,000 people.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22847</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the US Bureau of Labor Statistics announced that the non-farm payroll figures for May were adjusted from 144,000 to 19,000; and the non-farm payroll figures for June were revised from 147,000 to 14,000.After the revisions, the combined total number of new jobs added in May and June was 258,000 lower than the revised figures. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22847</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. publicly traded company DevvStream has initiated a Crypto Treasury strategy, with the initial purchase of BTC and SOL.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22845</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to businesswire, DevvStream Corp., a publicly traded carbon management company (Nasdaq: DEVS), announced the formal launch of its cryptocurrency treasury strategy today. The first batch has purchased Bitcoin (BTC) and Solana (SOL). This purchase was backed by the first $10 million portion of funding from a $300 million senior secured convertible note financing agreement with Helena Global Investment Opportunities 1 Ltd.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22845</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>