<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:34:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Completes GUNZ (GUN) Integration on the Solana Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23688</link>
      <description>August 8, according to an official communication, Binance has accomplished the integration of GUNZ (GUN) on the Solana network and has currently initiated the deposit and withdrawal services.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A &quot;Alpha Attack Speed Build&quot; whale address recently spent $90,000 sniping the PROVE listing, making a $6,517 profit</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23687</link>
      <description>August 8th. According to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), a particular &quot;Alpha Raid Speed&quot; smart money address has been constantly implementing the &quot;sniper opening and buy low, sell high&quot; strategy. In a recent transaction, they used $90,000 to snipe the opening price of PROVE and achieved a profit of $6,517.According to statistics, Binance Alpha has recently shifted some newly listed tokens from the &quot;opening price drop&quot; mode to the &quot;stable&quot; or even &quot;opening low and rising high&quot; mode. Among the latest 5 listed tokens, four have not witnessed a price drop within the first 24 hours. The token listed the day before yesterday, IN, has seen a 65% price increase in the past 24 hours, making it the best-performing Alpha new coin recently.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23687</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Enterprise is pleased to announce a partnership with Galaxy Digital.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23686</link>
      <description>On August 8th, DDC Enterprise Limited (with the New York Stock Exchange symbol: DDC) declared a partnership with Galaxy Digital in order to enhance its corporate Bitcoin treasury management. Galaxy&apos;s institutional trading services and infrastructure will be incorporated into DDC&apos;s operations, offering deeper liquidity, secure execution, and regulated custody for DDC&apos;s digital asset reserves.Previously on July 1st, DDC Enterprise (NYSE: DDC) announced the accomplishment of a $528 million financing plan. The investors consist of Anson Funds, Animoca Brands, Kenetic Capital, QCP Capital, and others. The raised funds will be utilized to expand its Bitcoin reserves.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23686</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit Web3 has been newly revamped and launched, making on-chain transactions more convenient.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23685</link>
      <description>August 8th. Bybit announced the official launch of the new version of Web3. It enables users to directly trade on-chain assets on the Bybit main site through a Unified Trading Account (UTA). There is no need to connect a wallet, create a Web3 wallet, or recharge Gas tokens. Bybit Web3 serves as a bridge between CEX and DEX, providing users with a more convenient, secure, and seamless on-chain asset exploration and trading experience.Currently, Bybit Web3 supports popular tokens such as TUNA, PUMP, FRAG, Fartcoin, JLP, RAY, MOODENG, LetsBONK, TSLAx, MSTRx, SPYx, CRCLx, and NVDAx.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23685</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Market Interest Rate Viewpoint Seriously Deviates from Fed&apos;s Position, Mispricing or Brewing</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23684</link>
      <description>On August 8th, Dhaval Joshi, an analyst at BCA Research, wrote that the current market pricing of U.S. interest rates is showing a significant divergence from the stance of the Federal Reserve, suggesting a mispricing or a potential brewing of troubles. Trump has demanded a 3% rate cut from the Fed, considering that the July jobs report indicated a significant slowdown in the U.S. labor market. It seems that Trump has the upper hand in this &quot;battle&quot; with Powell. However, attention should be paid to the true reasons behind the slowdown in the labor market.Joshi stated that the weakness in the labor market generally does stem from a reduction in labor demand; however, this is not the case currently. The reason is that the new employment is not mainly driven by the demand for workers but by the number of workers available for employment (labor supply). Moreover, a rate cut will intensify the imbalance between labor demand and supply, potentially reigniting inflation without promoting jo</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23684</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AILiquid&apos;s trading volume exceeded $500 million in its first week of launch, with registered users surpassing 12,000.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23681</link>
      <description>On August 8th, the AI-driven on-chain derivative protocol AILiquid announced the data of the first week online. The number of new registered users exceeded tens of thousands. The contract trading volume reached 5.92 billion US dollars. The platform token CCC entered the top ten of the Binance ecosystem, and the market activity continued to rise.It is reported that AILiquid&apos;s perpetual contract supports a leverage of up to 1000 times. The highest trading mining returns 105% of the fees (75% USDT + 30% CCC), which enhances trading activity and user retention. AILiquid recently upgraded its website to the globally unified domain AILiquid.com and launched a global KOL agent recruitment. The official trading mining activity will continue until August 31st.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23681</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Holdings Denies Submitting Cryptocurrency-Related ETF Application</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23683</link>
      <description>August 8th. Japanese financial services company SBI Holdings made it clear that the company has not yet submitted any ETF applications related to cryptocurrency assets. The relevant plans are still in the preliminary stage. The application will be filed after the Japanese financial regulatory agency completes the legal amendments.Previously on August 6th, it was reported that Japanese financial services company SBI Holdings had submitted applications for two cryptocurrency-related Exchange-Traded Funds (ETFs). The first fund is a cryptocurrency ETF that will directly invest in XRP and Bitcoin. The second fund is a digital gold ETF that will combine gold-backed securities and digital assets, with more than 50% of the funds allocated to gold ETFs.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23683</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhongnong Rural Credit and Ed Finance have reached a cooperation agreement to promote Agricultural Real World Assets (RWA) and initiate a Hong Kong listing.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23682</link>
      <description>August 8th, Zhongnong Rongxin and Ed Financial have reached a formal comprehensive strategic cooperation agreement to jointly engage in various capital market activities. Zhongnong Rongxin will appoint Ed Securities and Futures, a subsidiary of Ed Financial, as its exclusive advisor in the capital market, compliance consulting, and related technical services. It will provide full sponsorship and underwriting support for Zhongnong Rongxin&apos;s real-world asset tokenization (RWA), capital market advisory, corporate financing, merger and acquisition restructuring, and Hong Kong initial public offering (IPO) projects.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 08:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23682</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSTR Holdings has announced that it has raised $65 million and will launch a Bitcoin Treasury after its merger listing.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23679</link>
      <description>August 8th. BSTR Holdings Inc. (BSTR) made an announcement that it has managed to secure an extra $65 million, which is roughly equivalent to 555 bitcoins at the prevailing Bitcoin price. This infusion of funds will become accessible to BSTR upon the successful completion of the merger with CEPO.On July 17th, BSTR Holdings Inc. disclosed that it had reached a definitive business merger agreement with Cantor Equity Partners I, Inc. (NASDAQ: CEPO). CEPO is a special purpose acquisition company (SPAC) that is sponsored by an affiliate of Cantor Fitzgerald, a prominent global financial and real estate services holding company. Following the merger, the resulting combined company will be listed under the stock symbol &quot;BSTR&quot;. BSTR will commence with a balance sheet comprising 30,021 bitcoins and is anticipated to emerge as the fourth-largest publicly traded Bitcoin treasury globally. In addition, it intends to obtain up to $1.5 billion in PIPE (Private Investment in Public Equity) financin</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23679</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyStonks has successfully completed a Security Token Offering (STO) filing in the United States</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23680</link>
      <description>August 8th, MyStonks announced that it has successfully completed the filing for a U.S. Security Token Offering (STO), and has obtained regulatory approval to issue security tokens to qualified U.S. investors. This significant milestone indicates that the platform has fully complied with strict regulatory standards in core areas such as product architecture, information disclosure, investor suitability, and asset custody, laying a solid legal and trustworthy foundation for digital securities products.As one of the few platforms worldwide to achieve this certification, MyStonks, by relying on leading technological innovation and a deep commitment to compliance, has laid a solid foundation for its future strategic layout in global digital securities issuance, asset custody, and trading, driving the security token industry towards large-scale applications. This filing not only enhances market investment security and transparency but also showcases MyStonks&apos; leading position in digital a</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>