<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:17:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase has included MAMO in its listing roadmap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23143</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per official information, Coinbase has incorporated MAMO into its listing plan.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23143</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Acquires Solana-Based Meme Coin Trading Platform Solsniper</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23142</link>
      <description>August 5th. As per official channels, the cryptocurrency wallet Phantom declared the acquisition of the Solana-based Meme coin trading platform Solsniper. The specific sum remains undisclosed. Solsniper, with precision and swiftness as its essence, assists traders in monitoring tokens, tracking wallets, and responding promptly.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23142</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. CFTC Explores Allowing Registered Futures Platforms to Offer Cryptocurrency Spot Contracts Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23141</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per Bloomberg, the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) is examining ways to enable leveraged digital assets like Bitcoin and Ethereum to be listed on registered futures trading platforms.CFTC Acting Chairman Caroline Pham stated, &quot;The CFTC can now adopt a clear and straightforward approach.&quot; She referred to a column she published in March of this year, in which she proposed that the agency could utilize its exemption authority to allow certain entities to operate beyond current regulatory limitations - limitations that currently only permit futures trading platforms to list derivative products.The CFTC has now solicited public feedback on trading spot contracts of crypto assets listed on registered futures trading platforms, with a deadline of August 18th.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 22:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23141</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve&apos;s Daly: Rate Cut Timing Is Near, More Likely to Cut Rates Over Twice This Year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23140</link>
      <description>On August 5th, San Francisco Fed President Daly stated that with the growing evidence of a weak job market and the absence of signs of tariff-driven inflation persisting, the moment for a rate cut is getting closer. When discussing the Fed&apos;s decision from last week, Daly said, &quot;I&apos;m willing to wait for another cycle, but I can&apos;t wait indefinitely.&quot;Although this does not mean that a rate cut in September is a certainty, she said, &quot;I would be inclined to the view that each meeting moving forward is a possible meeting for a policy adjustment.&quot; Daly stated that two 25-basis-point rate cuts this year still seem to be an appropriate recalibration. The key lies in whether to cut in both September and December rather than whether the cut will occur.Daly said, &quot;If inflation picks up and spreads, or if the labor market heats up, of course, we could have fewer than two cuts. But more likely, we would need to cut more than twice. If the labor market appears to be moving into a soft phase and we</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 20:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23140</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Daly: Two Interest Rate Cuts This Year Still Appropriate Adjustment Level, No Sign of Prolonged Tariff Impact on Inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23139</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Federal Reserve&apos;s Daly indicated that it remains appropriate to make two rate cuts this year. She was content with the Fed&apos;s July decision but less so with making the same decision again.There remains a great deal of uncertainty regarding whether a rate cut will occur in September. &quot;Regarding the July decision, I would be willing to wait for another cycle, but we cannot wait indefinitely. The labor market is not significantly weak, but it is showing signs of softening, and further softening would be undesirable.&quot;No signs have been detected of tariffs having a persistent impact on inflation. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 20:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23139</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Expects the Fed to Cut Interest Rates by 25 Basis Points for Three Consecutive Meetings Starting in September</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23138</link>
      <description>On August 5th, Goldman Sachs declared, &quot;We anticipate that the Fed will commence a series of three interest rate cuts in September, with each cut amounting to 25 basis points. In the event that the next report indicates a further rise in the unemployment rate, they might implement a cut of 50 basis points.&quot; (FX168)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 20:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23138</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Breaks $3700</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23137</link>
      <description>On August 5th, according to HTX market data, Ethereum has breached $3,700 and is currently trading at $3,710, with a 24-hour increase of 6.25%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23137</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CZ: The Cryptocurrency Global Race is expected to arrive soon. Countries that delay adoption will be forced to buy in at a higher price.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23136</link>
      <description>On August 5th, CZ said in an interview: &quot;The world&apos;s largest economy is establishing a crypto reserve. This implies that for any country that is not currently doing so, when they do start, they will be at a considerable disadvantage. Since the wealthiest countries have already aggressively purchased Bitcoin, the next country that buys them will only be able to do so at a higher price. As a result, they will be able to buy less with the same amount of money. I believe we will witness a competition among countries in adopting Bitcoin and mainstream cryptocurrencies.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPO Looms, Grayscale Founder Barry Silbert Returns as Chairman of the Board</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23135</link>
      <description>On August 5th, as per The Block, following the submission of a confidential IPO application, Grayscale Investments announced the appointment of four executives and welcomed back founder Barry Silbert as the Chairman of the Board. The newly appointed executives are: Chief Operating Officer Diana Zhang, Chief Marketing Officer Ramona Boston, Chief Communications Officer Andrea Williams, and Chief Human Resources Officer Maxwell Rosenthal. All four executives will report to Grayscale CEO Peter Mintzberg and are from traditional financial giants such as Bridgewater Associates, Apollo Global Management, Goldman Sachs, and Castle Investment.Barry Silbert founded Grayscale in 2013 and stepped down as the Chairman of the Board at the end of 2023. He will now succeed Mark Shifke as the Chairman of the Board, with Shifke continuing to serve on the board. The board has now expanded to five members. The company has indicated that it is considering adding independent directors.Barry Silbert sta</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23135</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes: The next few months will usher in the Crypto Stock IPO Season, with funds expected to flow into native crypto projects rather than suffocating the season of copycats</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23134</link>
      <description>On August 4th, Forbes reported that the success of the Circle IPO will inspire those who are still on the sidelines. Since publicly traded crypto stocks present a highly attractive prospect for investors, especially for crypto newcomers, buying stock in a listed company is much easier than participating in a Curve Finance liquidity pool or trying to predict which memecoin will multiply by 100 in the future. Listed stocks can be purchased through traditional brokerage accounts or platforms like Robinhood, thus eliminating the barriers to entering the cryptocurrency ecosystem. Investors can enjoy the benefits of crypto with much less risk.Forbes stated that, similar to any free market, demand is expected to drive supply as well. This is good news for projects built in the crypto ecosystem. The launch of new projects indicates that capital is flowing into the digital asset economy. Undoubtedly, this capital is flowing into infrastructure projects, developer tools, Layer 1, and Layer 2 b</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23134</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>