<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Wang Feng: Ethereum&apos;s Rise Is Not Isolated in the Market, Cryptocurrency Autumn Is Expected to Begin</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23858</link>
      <description>August 9th: Wang Feng, the founder of Blueport Interactive, mentioned in a post that the market sentiment of Bitcoin and Ethereum should not be regarded in isolation. Currently, Bitcoin is trading sideways around $120,000 with little volatility and no significant sell-off by institutions. This situation offers ample space for Ethereum to maintain its uptrend after breaking through $4,000, and it is forecasted to rise to at least around $5,000. Similarly, Ethereum and the entire crypto market have always been interrelated. The cryptocurrency autumn is expected to commence, with DeFi, RWA, and star meme coins entering a stage of takeoff.On July 16th, Blueport Interactive established the LK Crypto Division to be responsible for the management of the company&apos;s mainstream crypto assets and expedite its Web3 and RWA strategies.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23858</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Ultimate wish is to bring peace and stability to the world</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23856</link>
      <description>On August 9th, today, President Trump held a meeting with Azerbaijani President Ilham Aliyev and Armenian Prime Minister Nikol Pashinyan at the White House, which facilitated the signing of a peace and economic agreement between the two countries. Trump posted on Truth Social, expressing that &quot;As the President of the United States, my greatest aspiration is to bring peace and stability to the world.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Co-Founder Jeffrey Wilcke Deposits 9840.36 ETH into Kraken, Worth Approximately $41.33 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23857</link>
      <description>August 9th. As per on-chain analyst Ai Ma (@ai_9684xtpa), following a period of three months, Ethereum co-founder Jeffrey Wilcke once more deposited 9840.36 ETH into Kraken, approximately amounting to $41.33 million.In May of this year, after depositing 105,737 ETH into Kraken, he distributed it to 8 new addresses. In the past hour, one of those addresses began to transfer ETH back to the exchange platform once again, suggesting a possible intention to sell at a peak. The 105,737 ETH deposited in May was valued at $262 million, and three months later, this portion of tokens has increased to $442 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23857</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pendle TVL Surges by $1.2 Billion in 5 Days, Reaching $8.2 Billion to Hit Another All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23855</link>
      <description>On August 9th, TN Lee, a co-founder of Pendle, posted on X, indicating that 5 days prior, Pendle&apos;s Total Value Locked (TVL) reached a first-time milestone of exceeding $7 billion. And as of today, Pendle&apos;s TVL has achieved a new high of $8.2 billion, reaching $8 billion for the first time. Pendle is now on its way towards even loftier goals.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23855</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana On-Chain Meme Token SPARK Surpasses $18 Million Market Cap, with a 24-hour Growth of 437%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23854</link>
      <description>On August 9th, according to data from GMGN, the on-chain AI virtual creature concept Meme token SPARK on Solana has achieved a market capitalization of more than $18 million, reaching a new all-time high. The 24-hour trading volume is $16.6 million, and the 24-hour price increase is 437%.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins usually lack practical use cases and experience significant price fluctuations. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23854</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strobe Ventures transferred 7 million ENA to Binance and still holds 113.9 million ENA</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23853</link>
      <description>On August 9th, as per EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, the crypto venture capital firm Strobe Ventures transferred 7 million ENA to Binance within the past half hour, with a value of $5.15 million.Strobe Ventures, which spun off from BlockTower Capital, the institutional investor of Ethena, received a distribution of 142.9 million ENA through investment a year ago. Currently, the address still holds 113.9 million ENA, with a value of $83.94 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23853</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Week Macro Outlook: CPI and PPI Data Incoming, &apos;Crypto-Friendly&apos; Fed Governor to Take Office</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23852</link>
      <description>On August 9th, the key macroeconomic data and events to be announced in the next week are as follows:Tuesday:US July CPI data;2027 FOMC voter and Richmond Fed President Barkin&apos;s speech.Thursday:Chicago Fed President Evans&apos; speech on monetary policy;Atlanta Fed President Bostic&apos;s speech on the US economic outlook;US initial jobless claims for the week ending August 9th and August PPI data.Friday:US July retail sales m/m and July import price index m/m;US August 1-year inflation rate expectations preliminary and the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment Index preliminary.Additionally, Trump has announced the nomination of the &quot;pro-crypto&quot; official Stephen Miran as a Federal Reserve Board Member, with a term ending on January 31, 2026. According to public information, during his tenure as the Chair of the White House Economic Advisory Committee, he explicitly supported the Trump administration&apos;s crypto-friendly policies. He believes that cryptocurrency has the potential</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23852</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDe&apos;s market capitalization has surpassed $10 billion for the first time, while at the same time ENA has surged over 186%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23851</link>
      <description>On August 9th, based on official data, the current market capitalization of USDe has reached a new all-time high for the first time, exceeding 10 billion US dollars. It has increased by 46.9 billion US dollars compared to July 4th (5.31 billion US dollars), with a growth rate of 88.3%. Meanwhile, during the same period, ENA has seen a 186% increase.As of the time of writing, USDe is currently trading at $1.001; ENA is trading at $0.7449, with a 24-hour increase of 20.77%, and its market capitalization has risen to 4.911 billion US dollars.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23851</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Company LM Funding America Mined 5.9 BTC in July</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23850</link>
      <description>On August 9th, as per Globenewswire, the U.S.-listed Bitcoin mining company LM Funding America issued an unaudited update report on Bitcoin mining and operations as of July 31st. During July, they mined 5.9 BTC and sold 11 BTC. The Bitcoin holdings at the end of July decreased to approximately 150.4 BTC, with a total value of around $17.8 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23850</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharplink: Ethereum Roadmap on Network Upgrade, Focused on Decentralization, Smartness, and Integrity</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23849</link>
      <description>On August 9th, &quot;ETH Version MicroStrategy&quot; Sharplink Gaming stated in a post that the Ethereum roadmap is by no means solely focused on expanding the financial scale. Instead, it is about rebuilding the network, with decentralization, intelligence, and integrity at its core. AI agents, physical infrastructure, data flows, and reputation layers all require programmable trust, and this is what Ethereum provides.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23849</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>