<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:43:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha and Futures will list Bitlayer (BTR)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26086</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per official channels, Binance Alpha is set to launch and commence trading for Bitlayer (BTR) on August 27th, 2025, at 18:00 (UTC+8). Furthermore, the Binance Futures platform will initiate the BTRUSDT perpetual contract on August 27th, 2025, at 18:30 (UTC+8), with a maximum leverage of up to 50x.Binance is the inaugural platform to announce the opening of Bitlayer (BTR) contract trading and to present the Bitlayer token on Binance Alpha.All eligible users will be entitled to an exclusive token airdrop. Eligible users are required to utilize Binance Alpha Points to claim the airdrop on the Binance Alpha event page from August 27th, 2025, 18:00 (UTC+8), to August 28th, 2025, 18:00 (UTC+8).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26086</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain Bitcoin ancient whale has sold 19,663 BTC to switch to 455,672 ETH, and has staked 279,000 ETH from it.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26085</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, the Unit team announced that a Bitcoin ancient whale has sold 19,663 BTC (approximately $2.22 billion) by means of two entities and exchanged it for 455,672 ETH. Among them, 279,000 ETH (approximately $1.13 billion) has been staked.The Bitcoin ancient whale still possesses BTC on HyperLiquid and intends to sell it in exchange for ETH while holding 176,616 ETH on the blockchain (approximately $832 million).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26085</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: HYPE Expected to Have 126x Potential Upside</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26084</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Arthur Hayes stated during his speech at the WebX Summit that it is expected that the Hyperliquid token (HYPE) will have a 126x potential upside. The project aims to increase its annualized transaction fees to $258 billion by 2028 through a stablecoin expansion strategy.He also predicted that by 2028, the supply of stablecoins would reach $10 trillion, with Hyperliquid accounting for a 26.4% market share. The Average Daily Volume (ADV) is projected to reach $2.636 trillion, which is a significant increase from the current $119 billion. Based on a 0.03% net transaction fee rate, the projected annual income is expected to reach $258 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26084</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Story Foundation will launch an $82 million IP buyback program on the open market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26083</link>
      <description>On August 25th, Story tweeted that Heritage Distilling (CASK), a Nasdaq-listed company, officially completed a PIPE financing on August 15th and established a treasury strategy centered around IP.As promised, the Story Foundation will launch an $82 million IP repurchase program in the open market. The repurchase will be carried out from August 15th to November 16th, which is a total of 90 days. Subsequent progress will be regularly updated to the community.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26083</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「$125,000 Leveraged Long Position on ETH Liquidated」 Whale Liquidates 2000 ETH, Liquidation Price Adjusted to $4658</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26082</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Yu Jin, during the recent rapid price drop, the &quot;125,000 USD liquidation long position on ETH&quot; whale grew anxious as the price neared its liquidation price of 4,668 USD. Consequently, they closed 2,000 ETH just a few dollars above the liquidation price. This action led to a decrease in the liquidation price by 10 USD, from 4,668 USD to 4,658 USD.Currently, with a margin of 740,000 USD, their position still holds 23,100 ETH, which is valued at 108 million USD. They have an unrealized profit of 2.63 million USD.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26082</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Securities: It is expected that the Federal Reserve will cut interest rates three times this year</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26081</link>
      <description>August 25th. Based on a research report by CITIC Securities, Powell&apos;s speech at the Jackson Hole central bank summit was in line with our prior expectations. It emphasized the downside risks to the labor market. This has continued the view from the July interest rate meeting that &quot;tariff inflation is temporary,&quot; laying the groundwork for a rate cut in September. We maintain our previous view that the Fed is expected to cut rates three times this year, with each cut being 25 basis points. Regarding the adjustment of the monetary policy framework, the Fed has given up the average inflation targeting regime and returned to a flexible inflation targeting regime. It has also modified its language to emphasize the focus on the &quot;two-way&quot; risks in the labor market. (FXStreet)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26081</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s 10x DOGE Long Position Partially Liquidated</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26080</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, during the period of market volatility, James Wynn&apos;s DOGE 10x leverage long position was partially liquidated. He still retains a long position of DOGE worth $143,000.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Unknown Hacker Who Received Funds on March 28」 Sells 5001 ETH Bought 4 Days Ago, Profits $2.04 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26079</link>
      <description>On August 25th, as monitored by on-chain analyst Wu Ji, the &quot;unknown hacker who received funds on March 28th&quot; sold the 5,001 ETH that he purchased 4 days ago, realizing a profit of $2.04 million.· 4 days ago, he utilized 21.76 million DAI to buy 5,001 ETH at a price of $4,352.· As of today, 4 hours ago, all 5,001 ETH were sold back for 23.8 million DAI at a price of $4,760.· This swing trade led to a $2.04 million profit.· Currently, this hacker holds 46.13 million U (36.54 million DAI + 9.59 million sUSD).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26079</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>profit</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raydium has spent a total of $196.3 million to repurchase 71 million RAY tokens, accounting for 26.4% of the circulating supply.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26078</link>
      <description>On August 25th, based on the data disclosed by Infura, Raydium has expended a total of $196.3 million to repurchase 71 million RAY tokens, which accounts for 26.4% of the circulating supply.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26078</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum drops below $4600, the mainstream CEX long liquidation pressure will reach $726 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26077</link>
      <description>On August 25th, according to Coinglass data, if Ethereum falls below $4600, the cumulative strength of long liquidation in mainstream CEXs will reach 726 million.Conversely, if Ethereum breaks through $4800, the cumulative strength of short liquidation in mainstream CEXs will reach 924 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the relative significance of each liquidation cluster to the adjacent liquidation cluster, that is, strength. Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the target price will be influenced when it reaches a certain position. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will have a more intense response due to a liquidity avalanche when it reaches that level.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/26077</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>