<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:45:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance now supports users to directly activate the Staking feature through their spot wallet account.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22801</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to an official announcement, Binance has initiated a Spot Account Soft Staking feature. This enables users to effortlessly activate soft staking directly through their spot accounts without the need to lock their funds in order to receive staking rewards. Currently, supported tokens comprise BNB, SOL, ADA, SUSHI, TON, NEAR, POLY, ALGO, SAND, AXS, and others. The staking rewards will be distributed to the spot account on a daily basis.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22801</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Whale Who Bought $20.8 Million Worth of ETH on Chain at a High Slippage Is Now Facing a $1.645 Million Unrealized Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22802</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa), on July 28th, he purchased 5,073.16 ETH at a price that was higher than on CEX. The cost per ETH was $37, but he bought at $3,958 per ETH, almost at the short-term high. He is currently in an unrealized loss of $1.645 million and has not yet sold or transferred.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22802</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Surpasses South Korea as the 18th Largest Holder of US Treasury Bonds</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22800</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to Messari data, Tether has overtaken South Korea and become the 18th largest holder of U.S. Treasury bonds.Yesterday, Tether released its second-quarter financial report indicating that its holdings of U.S. bonds exceed $127 billion.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Websea burned 2.16 million WBS in August, with a total of over 63.7 million WBS burned to date.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22799</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the Websea platform accomplished the 34th round of platform token WBS burning. The data indicates that a total of 2,165,156.28 WBS were burned this time, which is an increase of 80,190.97 WBS compared to last month, setting a new record for the buyback burning mechanism. As of the time of writing, the price of WBS is $1.18, and the value of this burning exceeds $2.55 million.After this burning, the total accumulated amount of WBS burned has reached 63,714,740.08, completing 31.86% of the planned 200 million WBS burning. It is reported that the platform will continue to use 10% of the monthly fee revenue for buyback burning until the total supply of WBS is reduced to 100 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22799</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesia&apos;s Cryptocurrency Annual Tax Revenue Reaches $364 Million, User Base Exceeds 20 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22797</link>
      <description>August 1st. According to the Tax Office of Indonesia, since this year, the annual cryptocurrency tax revenue in Indonesia ranges from 500 billion to 600 billion Indonesian Rupiah (approximately 31.25 million to 36.40 million US dollars). Specifically, the tax revenue in the first year of 2022 was 24.6 billion Rupiah, decreased to 22 billion Rupiah in 2023, surged to 62 billion Rupiah in 2024, and as of now in 2025, 11.5 billion Rupiah has been collected.The Indonesian government has recently updated its cryptocurrency regulatory policy. The tax rate for overseas platforms has been increased to 1%, and the tax rate for domestic platforms has been adjusted to 0.21%. In addition, the value-added tax for buyers has been canceled, and cryptocurrencies have been reclassified as financial assets and are under the supervision of the Financial Services Authority.Currently, there are more than 20 million cryptocurrency users in Indonesia, surpassing the number of local stock market investors</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22797</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>glassnode: The current downturn experienced a relatively low liquidation volume, indicating that it was primarily driven by the spot market.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22798</link>
      <description>On August 1st, based on the data from the analysis platform glassnode, although Bitcoin dropped by 3.2% and Ethereum by 6%, the market liquidation scale remained at a low level, amounting to only $110 million and $132 million respectively. The slight withdrawal of open interest suggests that this round of correction is mainly driven by the spot market rather than the derivatives market.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22798</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has launched Toshi (TOSHI), with an airdrop claiming threshold of 200 points.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22796</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to official channels, Binance Alpha has now listed Toshi (TOSHI).Users who hold at least 200 Alpha points are eligible to claim an airdrop of 69,349 TOSHI tokens. The first come, first served principle applies. If the event is not yet completed, the points threshold will automatically decrease by 15 points every hour.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22796</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The9 Limited, the mainland Chinese operator of World of Warcraft, has launched the Web3 game platform the9bit through its Hong Kong subsidiary.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22795</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the Nasdaq-listed company The9 Limited announced that its wholly-owned Hong Kong subsidiary, Vast Ocean International Limited, has launched the Web3 gaming platform the9bit. The9bit has formed a strategic partnership with the blockchain gaming guild Yield Guild Games (YGG). It is reported that the9bit will be integrated into YGG&apos;s official onboarding channel and blockchain gaming guild activities.It is reported that from 2005 to 2009, The9 Limited was the exclusive operator of World of Warcraft in mainland China.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22795</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Sees Ongoing Negative Premium on Coinbase, First Time Since April</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22794</link>
      <description>On August 1st, according to the crypto data platform Kiyotaka, there has been a persistent discount of Ethereum on Coinbase. This marks the first time since April of this year. During this period, Ethereum has surged by more than 150%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22794</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly traded company Cemtrex purchases $1 million worth of SOL, planning to establish a $10 million cryptocurrency reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22793</link>
      <description>On August 1st, the Nasdaq-listed company Cemtrex (stock code: CETX) announced that it had acquired $1 million worth of SOL as the initial step in its digital asset reserve strategy. The company purchased 5500 SOL at an average price of $181 per coin and intends to gradually expand the size of its cryptocurrency reserves to $10 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22793</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>