<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:53:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun: WLFI Token Unjustly Frozen, Calls for Unlock</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27820</link>
      <description>September 5th, Justin Sun made a post on the X platform, saying: &quot;As one of the early significant investors in WLFI, I have not only provided funds but also placed my trust and support in the future development of this project. My aim has always been to grow together with the team and community and jointly build a robust and healthy WLFI ecosystem.&quot;However, during the operation process, my tokens were frozen unreasonably. As an early investor, I joined along with others. We made purchases in the same way, and we should all have the same rights.I appeal to the team to respect these principles, unlock my tokens, and let us move forward together towards the success of WLFI.I believe that a truly excellent financial brand must be established on the basis of fairness, transparency, and trust, rather than through one-sided actions to freeze investor assets. Such measures not only violate the legitimate rights of investors but may also undermine people&apos;s overall confidence in World Libe</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27820</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of Non-Farm Payrolls Data, the probability of a Fed rate cut on the CME has risen to 99.3%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27818</link>
      <description>September 5th: The US August non-farm payroll data is set to be released this evening. Prior to that, based on CME&apos;s &quot;FedWatch&quot; data, the likelihood of a 25-basis-point rate cut by the Fed in September stands at 99.3%, with the probability of keeping rates unchanged at 0.7%.On Polymarket, the probability of a 25-basis-point rate cut is relatively more cautious and currently stands at 88%.Moreover, derivative contracts employed to wager on the Fed&apos;s policy direction indicate that by the end of next year, the Fed will have implemented five rate cuts (each of 25 basis points), reducing the federal funds rate from the current range of 4.25%-4.5% to approximately 3%.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27818</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun retweeted a tweet from Nansen CEO supporting himself, with the comment &quot;I am innocent.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27819</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Justin Sun retweeted a tweet by Nansen CEO Alex Svanevik regarding the &quot;Justin Sun WLFI Token Address Activity Analysis&quot; and claimed, &quot;I am innocent.&quot;In the tweet, Alex Svanevik said, &quot;After verifying with the agent: Justin Sun did not lead to the WLFI price decline.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27819</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WLFI TOP1 Holder Starts Transferring Distributed Value of $14.69M WLFI, May Sell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27817</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the top 1 WLFI holder has begun to transfer decentralized WLFI.In the past 18 hours, he has dispersed 79.54 million WLFI to 9 addresses (approximately $14.69 million). One address, moonmanifestphilanthropy.eth, had a small sell-off operation 3 days ago. Currently, the receiving addresses have no sell-off activities.The TOP1 holder, moonmanifest.eth, owns a total of 1% of WLFI tokens. With 2 billion tokens unlocked at TGE, this address is suspected to belong to TechnoRevenant, a key participant in the XPL sniper rug pull incident.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27817</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>
      <category>transfer</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due to the Bithumb listing announcement, Euler experienced a short-term surge of over 30% before retracting.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27816</link>
      <description>On September 5th, based on HTX market data, Euler (EUL) saw a brief surge of more than 30% and then pulled back. It is now trading at $11.4.Earlier news had reported that Bithumb added Euler (EUL) to its Korean won trading market.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Economist: Regardless of how tonight&apos;s non-farm payroll report turns out, subsequent revisions may promptly push the figures higher.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27815</link>
      <description>On September 5th, Bloomberg economist Anna Wong predicted for tonight&apos;s non-farm payroll report, saying, &quot;Regardless of the employment data, it is likely to be revised upward promptly. The reason is that in August, due to various reasons such as people being on vacation, the initial response rate tends to be lower. Historically, the next two revisions are likely to be upward.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27815</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb Adds Euler (EUL) KRW Market</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27814</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to an official announcement, Bithumb has incorporated the Euler (EUL) KRW trading market. Trading is set to commence on Friday, September 5th at 5:00 PM in the local time.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27814</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will suspend AIO trading on September 8th to support contract swap</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27813</link>
      <description>On September 5th, as per an official announcement, Binance Alpha will offer support for the OLAXBT (AIO) BEP20 contract swap.Starting from 1:00 PM on September 8, 2025, Binance will halt AIO trading in order to facilitate the contract swap.It is anticipated that trading of OLAXBT (AIO) via BEP20 will resume at 8:00 AM UTC on the same day.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27813</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean Financial Regulatory Authority Introduces Virtual Asset Loan Service Guidelines, Prohibits Over-Leveraging</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27812</link>
      <description>On September 5th, according to the report of Newsprime, South Korea&apos;s financial regulatory authorities have introduced the first virtual asset loan service guide. Due to the intensified exchange competition resulting in increased investor risks, the regulators have completely prohibited leverage and cash loans. They have established individual limits and fee caps and prevented similar short-selling behaviors. On the 5th, the Financial Services Commission of South Korea announced that it will implement a self-regulatory &quot;Virtual Asset Loan Service Guide&quot; developed by the Financial Supervisory Service and DAXA. The new guide focuses on three core aspects: service scope restriction, user protection, and market stability. The guide clearly prohibits over-leveraging and Korean won cash loans. It requires exchanges to use their own assets to provide services and prohibits third-party trusteeship or indirect lending models.Regarding the enhancement of user protection measures, first-time us</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 03:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27812</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fenghuang Finance: In the future, there are also plans to include BTC, SOL, and other assets in the company&apos;s strategic reserves</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27811</link>
      <description>September 5th - Sequoia Capital China has amassed 10,000 ETH in the open market. Sequoia Capital China declared that the acquired ETH will be categorized as investment assets within the financial statements. In the forthcoming period, the company intends to continuously augment its allocation to digital assets. Apart from Ethereum, it also has the plan to explore diversifying its strategic reserve assets to encompass mainstream digital assets like BTC and SOL. (Caixin)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/27811</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>