<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Gallup Survey: 14% of U.S. Adults Own Cryptocurrency, 60% of Surveyed Individuals Unlikely to Purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22014</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on a new survey carried out by Gallup from June 2nd to 15th, approximately 14% of American adults state that they own cryptocurrency. However, the majority claim that they have no interest in purchasing it. Despite a slight rise in digital asset ownership since 2021, the majority of Americans still view digital assets as a speculative investment.The survey indicates that the phenomenon of men under 50 owning cryptocurrency is more prevalent. 25% of men declare that they own Bitcoin or other digital currencies.Furthermore, college graduates (19%), high-income adults (19%), and political conservatives (18%) have a higher rate of cryptocurrency ownership. In contrast, only 7% of adults aged 65 and above state that they own some form of cryptocurrency.17% of Americans mention that they are interested in cryptocurrency but do not plan to invest in the near future. Only 4% say that they may purchase cryptocurrency soon. 60% of people state that they have no intentio</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22014</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director of the U.S. Office of Management and Budget: Trump Clearly States No Intention to Fire Powell</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22013</link>
      <description>On July 27th, the Director of the US Office of Management and Budget, Vought, stated that Trump has clearly demonstrated no intention of dismissing Powell. (FX678 News)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22013</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Secretary of Commerce: August 1 Tariff Increase Deadline Will Not Be Further Extended</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22012</link>
      <description>On July 27th, U.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick announced that the deadline for the tariff increase set for August 1st will not be extended any further. Europe expresses a need and a willingness to reach a trade agreement with the United States. The key question now is whether the agreement proposed by the EU is sufficient to persuade Trump to abandon the 30% tariff threat.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22012</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain smart money opened a 2x long position on Ethereum in less than 1 hour, with an entry price of $3,837.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22011</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on on-chain information, a large holder recently held a 2x leveraged long position in Ethereum for nearly 1 hour. Currently, it is holding a long position in $12.977 million worth of Ethereum at an entry price of $3,837.In addition, the same address holds the largest long position with a 3x leveraged long position in XRP, and the position value is $16.26 million.This address has accumulated a profit of $1.447 million on Hyperliquid.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22011</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point of View: The GENIUS Act is Driving Stablecoins Towards Payment Applications, Potentially Spawning a Wave of &quot;Killer Apps&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22010</link>
      <description>On July 27th, Fabian Dori, the Chief Investment Officer of Sygnum, stated that the GENIUS Act will bring about a transformation in the stablecoin landscape. This will prompt issuers to shift from a yield-oriented model to a payment use case. The revised bill makes a clear distinction between interest-bearing stablecoins and payment-use stablecoins, bringing the U.S. framework closer to the EU&apos;s MiCA regulation and laying the foundation for a &quot;global consensus.&quot; Dori believes that regulatory clarity will stimulate institutions to develop innovative &quot;killer applications,&quot; thereby generating a whole new demand for payment services. (Cointelegraph)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22010</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director of the Office of Management and Budget: Trump&apos;s only requirement for the Fed is rate cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22009</link>
      <description>July 27th: Vought, the acting director of the United States Office of Management and Budget, stated that Trump&apos;s sole requirement for the Fed is to lower interest rates, and Trump is seeking a Fed chair who does not fall behind the economy. (Hibor)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22009</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letsbonk&apos;s leading edge continues to expand, with the tokenomics of the last 24 hours showing an almost 8x increase in the graduation token count for pump.fun.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22008</link>
      <description>On July 27th, based on the Jupiter Data Dashboard, within the past 24 hours, Letsbonk, a Solana-based token launchpad, has achieved a market share of 81%, outpacing pump.fun with 12.7% and further widening its lead.Moreover, according to Dune Analytics, in the past 24 hours, the Letsbonk platform has launched 163 graduation tokens, which is 7.76 times the number of graduation tokens on the pump.fun platform (21 tokens).</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitalik retweeted the &quot;Ethereum 10 Years of Zero Downtime, Zero Maintenance&quot; tweet.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22007</link>
      <description>On July 27th, Vitalik Buterin retweeted on the X platform: &quot;Ethereum has been continuously online for ten years with zero downtime and zero maintenance. In contrast, Facebook was down for 14 hours. Cloudflare abandoned 19 data centers. Other Layer 1 networks have encountered multiple issues. Ethereum will never cease. Whether it&apos;s a fork, a crash, a bubble, a lawsuit, a hack, or any other dramatic event that the internet may bring about, despite bank failures and the need for server patches, Ethereum continues to operate.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22007</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Believe Founder: Full details of the Ecosystem Flywheel Mechanism to be Announced Tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22006</link>
      <description>On July 27th, Ben Pasternak, the founder of the token issuance platform Believe, stated on the X platform, &quot;For a currency to achieve long-term success, it requires a flywheel. Believe allows any creator to effortlessly integrate it into their token.&quot; &quot;Full details will be disclosed tomorrow.&quot; Perhaps due to this news, LAUNCHCOIN rebounded by more than 18% today, and its market value is now $95.45 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22006</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor has released Bitcoin Tracker information, hinting at a potential BTC accumulation strategy.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22005</link>
      <description>On July 27th, the founder of Strategy, Michael Saylor, once again released information related to the Bitcoin Tracker and stated, &quot;It all started with a quarter billion in bitcoin.&quot;Following the typical pattern, Strategy always discloses information about its additional Bitcoin purchases on the day following the release of relevant news.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22005</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>