<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 05:07:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 05:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>British Former Chancellor: UK is Behind in the Cryptocurrency Space</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23046</link>
      <description>August 4th. As per the Financial Times, the former UK Chancellor George Osborne launched a vehement assault on the Labour government&apos;s stance towards cryptocurrency. He cautioned that the UK might miss out on a &quot;financial revolution analogous to that of the 1980s&quot; and lag behind the trend.Osborne is currently a member of the Global Advisory Board of the US cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase. He stated that Chancellor Rishi Sunak and Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey are placing the UK on the slower track. Osborne said, &quot;Rachel Reeves is correct. We have all become overly risk-averse. We became the world&apos;s financial center because we were not afraid of change. The harsh truth is that, just like many other aspects, we are completely behind in cryptocurrency and stablecoins. It is time to catch up.&quot;Osborne asserted that blaming regulators for being overly cautious is an &quot;unsustainable excuse.&quot; Reeves should take the lead from the US Congress and establish a legal framework for cryp</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23046</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet will upgrade its Web端自动确认 functionality on August 4th, with the update expected to be completed within this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23045</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to official information, OKX announced that the OKX Wallet will upgrade its Web automatic confirmation feature on August 4, 2025, and it is anticipated to be completed within this week. During the upgrade period, the automatic confirmation feature will be temporarily unavailable; however, manual transaction signing will not be impacted.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23045</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDe Circulation Surpasses 9.3 Billion, Reaching an All-Time High</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23044</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on the data from the official website, the supply of the stablecoin USDe issued by Ethena Labs has surpassed 9.3 billion. Currently, it is around 9,310,382,206 USDe, reaching a new record high. This indicates a substantial increase of more than 75% compared to the issuance of 5.31 billion USDe a month ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23044</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance BNSOL Super Staking Launches SIGN (SIGN)</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23043</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per an official announcement, Binance has declared that the BNSOL Super Staking will incorporate the twelfth project - SIGN (SIGN), a multi-chain authentication protocol that offers digital public infrastructure for governments and serves as the foundational layer for decentralized applications by validating identity, ownership proof, and contracts.From August 5, 2025, at 08:00 to September 6, 2025, at 07:59 (UTC+8), users who complete the following actions will be eligible to receive a SIGN APR Boost airdrop reward:1. Binance Account - Possessing BNSOL or staking SOL to BNSOL; or2. Binance Wallet - Holding BNSOL, sBNSOL, or bzSOL.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23043</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit Trading Volume Continues to Decline: XRP, ETH, BTC Remain Top Three</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23042</link>
      <description>On August 4th, based on CoinGecko data, in the past 24 hours, Upbit&apos;s trading volume decreased to $16.34 billion. The XRP/KRW trading pair accounted for 29.08% of the volume, taking the lead in the Korean won market. The rest of the top five in trading volume are: ETH, BTC, ENA, and TON.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23042</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letsbonk&apos;s Solana Launchpad market share in the last 24 hours has risen to 65.2%, while pump.fun has fallen to 23.1%.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23041</link>
      <description>On August 4th, according to the Jupiter Data Dashboard, in the Solana issuance platform market share ranking within the past 24 hours, Letsbonk took the first place with 65.2%, pump.fun came in second with 23.1%, and BAGS ranked third with 4.41%.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23041</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitunix Analyst: VINE Rebounds by 12.2% but Faces Continued Pressure, Short-term Focus on 0.082 and 0.094, Beware of Whale Sell Pressure and Speculative Fund Withdrawal Risk</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23039</link>
      <description>August 4th: The meme coin VINE has witnessed a 12.2% increase in the past 24 hours and is currently trading at $0.07446. The trading volume has surged to 214 million, representing an increase of over 80%. The liquidation heat map indicates that the price received strong support in the range of 0.059 to 0.062 and experienced short liquidation, which triggered a technical rebound. However, significant liquidation pressure is evident in the range of 0.082 to 0.094, presenting an opportunity for short-term profit-taking.Since Elon Musk&apos;s tweet on July 24th promoting the AI revival Vine, VINE briefly soared to $0.172. However, without substantial follow-up news, profit-taking pressure ensued, and the price broke below the 30-day moving average. According to on-chain data, the top ten wallets still hold 40% of the supply, leaving the market liquidity risk unresolved. Additionally, the outflow of funds from the Solana network has further dampened the basic confidence.Bitunix Analyst Sugge</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23039</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lido lays off 15% of its staff due to cost pressures</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23040</link>
      <description>On August 4th, the co-founder of Lido, Vasiliy Shapovalov, announced in a post that, considering cost factors, Lido Labs, the Lido Ecosystem, and the Lido Alliance have made the tough decision to reduce their workforce by approximately 15%. This adjustment was not a result of performance problems. The affected individuals were all key members who had been actively involved in protocol and community development.Shapovalov stated that although the market is currently in an upward trend, this decision reflects a commitment to long-term resilience and sustainable growth. It is intended to focus on operational priorities, optimize resource allocation, and be in line with the interests of LDO token holders.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardano&apos;s parent company, Input Output, has announced that the community has voted to approve the &quot;IO Global Roadmap&quot; proposal.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23038</link>
      <description>On August 4th, as per official channels, Input Output, the parent company of Cardano, announced that the Cardano community has cast votes and approved the &quot;IOHK Project Catalyst Fund 4&quot; proposal, with a support rate reaching 73.93%. The proposal involves allocating approximately 96,817,080 ADA (approximately $71.4 million) from the treasury funds to provide support for core protocol development. The approved budget will facilitate significant enhancements in terms of scalability, developer experience, and interoperability.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23038</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Leveraged Tokens will Delist Some Trading Pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23037</link>
      <description>August 4th. According to an official announcement, Binance Margin will remove the following leverage trading pairs on August 8, 2025, at 14:00 (UTC+8). The isolated margin trading pairs are DOGS/FDUSD, MOVE/FDUSD, MANTA/FDUSD, PEOPLE/FDUSD. And the cross margin trading pairs are also DOGS/FDUSD and PEOPLE/FDUSD.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23037</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>