<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:51:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to List ZRC and ESPORTS Perpetual Futures Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22267</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per an official announcement, Binance is set to commence ZRC and ESPORTS perpetual contract trading.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22267</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new address withdrew 20 million EDU from Binance, worth approximately $2.82 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22266</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the monitoring of Onchain Lens, a newly established wallet withdrew 20 million EDU from Binance, which was approximately worth $2.82 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22266</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares is launching a zero management fee SEI ETP in Europe, offering a 2% staking reward.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22265</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per the report by CoinDesk, the cryptocurrency asset management firm CoinShares has introduced a new Exchange-Traded Product (ETP). This ETP enables investors to invest in SEI with zero management fees and offers a staking yield of 2%. The product, bearing the trading symbol CSEI, will be listed and available for trading on the SIX Swiss Exchange. It is the first investment instrument that provides investors with direct access to SEI in a regulated manner.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22265</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hang Seng Electronic Response to Ant Group Collaboration Rumors: Unable to Confirm Company&apos;s Collaboration with Ant Group</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22264</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to 21 Finance, Hongsen Electronics, a leading financial IT company that was prominent during the bull markets in 2015 and 2020, witnessed a significant price surge. The market anomaly might be related to a &quot;brief text.&quot;A stock recommendation seemingly from a securities research analyst stated that they got to know that Hongyun Technology, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Hongsen Electronics, has reached a strategic cooperation agreement with Ant Group&apos;s AntChain. The cooperation focuses on the operation and system development of virtual assets/stablecoins, with an emphasis on the Hong Kong and international markets. They also planned to hold a stablecoin summit in September, claiming that &quot;the cooperation will break through Hongsen&apos;s growth ceiling.&quot;In response, an investor relations staff member of Hongsen Electronics said that the company is aware of the market rumors and today&apos;s price surge may be related to the rumor. However, the investor relations departme</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion: Bitcoin May Enter Consolidation Phase as Trading Volume Stabilizes, Suggesting the Arrival of a &quot;Summer Lull&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22263</link>
      <description>July 29th - Matrixport disclosed today&apos;s market analysis, suggesting that investors might be observing the early indications of &quot;summer fatigue.&quot; The trading volume has begun to stabilize. Although the current market activity remains at a relatively high level, the absence of clear catalysts in August may lead to a significant deceleration in the market—especially since retail participants tend to reduce their participation during holidays.Each of the three major volume surges in the past 18 months has triggered a strong market rally but occurred sporadically. This once more emphasizes the significance for investors to closely monitor market signals.Historically, a reduction in trading volume usually indicates that Bitcoin is entering a consolidation phase. As August approaches, the market may currently be entering a similar stage.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22263</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale is currently engaged in a long ETH position, having collateralized a total of 16,448.13 ETH to borrow $46.21 million in stablecoins.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22262</link>
      <description>On July 29th, as per on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), VIP user AndreIsBack on DeBank is currently employing the Fluid strategy to leverage ETH. He has initiated a total of 6 positions, pledged 16,448.13 ETH as collateral, and borrowed stablecoin assets worth $46.21 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22262</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>《Ming Pao》: JD.com has registered &quot;JCOIN&quot; and &quot;JOYCOIN,&quot; expected to be the names of its stablecoins</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22261</link>
      <description>July 29th. According to Ming Pao, the Hong Kong Stablecoin Regulation is set to come into effect in August. Local media referred to a registration document suggesting that JD.com&apos;s JD Coin Chain has registered &quot;JCOIN&quot; and &quot;JOYCOIN&quot;, with some noting that these names are likely the designations of its stablecoins.As per the registration document mentioned in the report, the services associated with &quot;JCOIN&quot; and &quot;JOYCOIN&quot; involve providing electronic fund transfers and cryptocurrency financial transactions via blockchain technology.JD Coin Chain is one of the Stablecoin Issuers participating in the sandbox of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority. In July of the previous year, it collaborated with Stardust Bank, a local virtual bank supported by companies such as Xiaomi and Futu, to explore a novel enterprise cross-border payment solution based on stablecoins within the sandbox.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22261</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX DeepThink: Policy Maneuvering Meets Earnings Season, Crypto Market&apos;s Short-Term Direction May Soon Become Clear</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22260</link>
      <description>On July 29th, the HTX Researcher Chloe pointed out in the latest edition of HTX DeepThink that during this week&apos;s Bank of Japan interest rate decision, the core PCE data closely watched by the Federal Reserve, and the earnings reports of multiple US tech giants will jointly influence the short-term direction of global risk assets.Currently, Japanese inflation is stabilizing, and the market is observing whether it will adjust its interest rate hike path. If the policy coordination between the US and Japan strengthens, it may stabilize the Asian foreign exchange market structure and indirectly boost the liquidity in the East Asian cryptocurrency market. The activity of users on the platforms in Hong Kong and South Korea is worthy of attention. The US non-farm payroll data (NFP) released on Friday is regarded as the &quot;key macroeconomic indicator.&quot; If employment growth slows in line with wage growth, it will provide support for the Fed&apos;s future shift to a rate cut.At the same time, the</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22260</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list IKA and TREE perpetual contract trading.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22259</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to official sources, Gate is scheduled to list IKA perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT) at 18:10 (UTC+8), with support for 1-20x leverage. Additionally, it will list TREE perpetual contract trading (settled in USDT) at 22:10 (UTC+8), also providing support for 1-20x leverage.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22259</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Bitcoin surpasses $120,000, the mainstream CEX&apos;s total short liquidation volume will reach 1.04 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22258</link>
      <description>On July 29th, according to data from Coinglass, if Bitcoin breaks through $120,000, the cumulative intensity of short liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $1.04 billion.Conversely, if Bitcoin falls below $117,000, the cumulative intensity of long liquidation on mainstream CEXs will reach $784 million.BlockBeats Notes: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the exact value of contracts being liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to adjacent liquidation clusters, that is, intensity.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the asset price will be affected when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that once the price reaches that level, it will experience a more intense reaction due to a liquidity cascade.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 06:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/22258</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>