<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:05:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: BTC On-Chain Structure Returns to $117k Support Range, First Rebound Target is $125k</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23990</link>
      <description>August 11th. On-chain data analyst Murphy posted that BTC has reverted to $120,000. Although it can&apos;t be regarded as a successful hold for the time being, it can be confirmed that on the chip structure side, BTC has once again returned to the price range supported by $117,000, transforming the turnover zone from $112,000 to $116,000 into a &quot;safe zone,&quot; which is almost in line with the price trajectory deduced based on the &quot;double-anchor structure.&quot;Looking at the &quot;MVRV Extreme Deviation Pricing Range,&quot; BTC is currently still operating between the channel formed by the orange and yellow lines. It may find support at the lower rail and encounter resistance at the upper rail. The current upper rail position of the operating channel is $125,000, which is also the first target of the rebound within the channel. If it successfully breaks through and does not fall back below on a pullback, it is most likely to move up another range to the second target of $137,000. If it meets resistance, it</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23990</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has deposited 6 million USDC into Hyperliquid to avoid BTC short liquidation.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23989</link>
      <description>On August 11th, based on the monitoring of LookOnChain, a whale deposited 6 million USDC as collateral to Hyperliquid in order to avoid liquidation.The address currently holds a short position of 1266.84 BTC, which is worth about $154 million. The liquidation price is $127,780, resulting in a loss of approximately $12.5 million.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23989</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US convenience store chain Sheetz has announced that it will accept Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies as payment</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23988</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to Deepnewz, the U.S. convenience store chain brand Sheetz announced that it will commence accepting Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies as a form of payment. Additionally, it will provide a 50% discount to customers who make purchases using cryptocurrency on a daily basis. Sheetz is a chain brand with a valuation of $6.2 billion and has 700 stores spread across the United States.Previously, on May 16th, the chain fast-food brand Steak &apos;n Shake started accepting Bitcoin payments at all its U.S. stores. Its Chief Operating Officer stated that after implementing Bitcoin payments, same-store sales in the second quarter witnessed an increase of 10.7%, and Bitcoin has become a &quot;game changer.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23988</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Coin SPARK&apos;s Market Cap Briefly Surpasses $40 Million, With a 24-hour Gain of 80.2%</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23987</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to GMGN data, the on-chain AI virtual creature concept Meme token SPARK on Solana momentarily exceeded a market cap of $40 million and reached a historical high. It had a 24-hour price increase of 80.2% and a 24-hour trading volume of $24.4 million.BlockBeats reminds users that Meme coins usually lack practical use cases and experience significant price volatility. Therefore, investment should be approached with caution.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23987</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital Founder Andy Li: To launch the unified Liquid Capital brand series name, heralding the dawn of a new era in global on-chain finance</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23986</link>
      <description>On August 11th, Li Xiaohua, the founder of LD Capital, stated in a post that when looking back at the past few months, being bullish on ETH and the resulting bull market, the market performed as expected or even more quickly. He is looking forward to the next major opportunity. With the deep involvement of Wall Street in the crypto market, it is expected that there may not be a major bottoming opportunity. The new financial era with 6 billion people worldwide going on-chain is approaching.LD Capital will use a new brand name - the full name of LD Capital is Liquid Capital, as well as Liquid Ventures (financial information first-level investment) and Liquid Digital, Liquid Group, Liquid Crypto, Liquid Labs, and other unified brand businesses. They will hold on to spot positions and set off again, not disappointing in this brand new era.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23986</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crypto Market Remains in a &quot;Greed&quot; State, with Sentiment Shifting from &quot;Neutral&quot; to Strongly Positive Since the Beginning of the Month</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23985</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to alternative data, the current Crypto Fear and Greed Index is 70. This compares to 69 from yesterday (with last week&apos;s average being 64), suggesting that the market sentiment is in a &quot;Greed&quot; state.The crypto market sentiment had previously dropped to 53 at the beginning of the month and entered &quot;Neutral&quot; territory for the first time since July. It has now fully recovered.Note: The Fear Index threshold ranges from 0 to 100 and incorporates the following indicators: Volatility (25%) + Market Volume (25%) + Social Media Sentiment (15%) + Market Surveys (15%) + Bitcoin&apos;s Dominance in the Market (10%) + Google Trends Analysis (10%).</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23985</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stock Exchange plans to list a cryptocurrency perpetual futures contract by the end of the year, catering to institutional demand.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23984</link>
      <description>August 11th, the President of the Singapore Exchange stated that the Singapore Exchange might list cryptocurrency perpetual futures contracts by the end of the year. Cryptocurrency trading is not appropriate for retail investors, and cryptocurrency products will be launched to meet the demands of institutions. (Golden Finance)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT project Nakamigos saw its floor price reach a peak of 0.34 ETH yesterday, with a growth of over 25% in the past 7 days.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23983</link>
      <description>On August 11th, based on Blur market data, the floor price of the NFT project Nakamigos once exceeded 0.34 ETH, representing a more than 88% increase. Currently, it is trading at 0.19 ETH and has increased by more than 25% in the past 7 days, with a 7-day trading volume of 998.44 ETH.NFT project Crypto Fish&apos;s floor price once exceeded 0.4 ETH and is currently trading at 0.3 ETH. Its 7-day trading volume is 998.44 ETH.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23983</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This year’s cryptocurrency project funding has reached $20.6 billion, surpassing the total for the entire previous year.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23982</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to CryptoRank data, by July 31, 2025, the fundraising of cryptocurrency projects this year has reached $20.6 billion, exceeding the full year of the previous year and breaking the previous funding records.Coinbase Ventures completed 44 transactions and ranked first among investment institutions. Animoca Brands and Amber Group ranked second and third respectively, with 31 and 25 transactions. Selini Capital and a16z CSX each completed 22 transactions and tied for fourth place.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23982</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale/institution has once again increased its holdings by 8745 ETH, accumulating a total of 68000 ETH since June 22nd.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23981</link>
      <description>On August 11th, according to on-chain analyst Ai Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa), the whale/institutional address &quot;0x395...45500&quot; has been accumulating a total of 68,000 ETH since June 22nd. The average price during this period was $2,597, resulting in an unrealized gain of $115 million. This address has been steadily accumulating ETH from $2,284 all the way up to the current $4,302. Additionally, it just withdrew 8,745 ETH from Binance in the past 5 minutes.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/23981</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>