<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - LookOnChain</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from LookOnChain</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:58:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/lookonchain.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Inflation has dropped to the perfect level, almost no inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24650</link>
      <description>On August 15th, US President Trump declared that inflation has decreased to a perfect level and there is almost no inflation. (Xinhua News)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24650</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abu Dhabi sovereign wealth fund Mubadala has disclosed holding $534 million worth of the BlackRock Bitcoin Futures ETF as of June 30th.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24649</link>
      <description>On August 15th, as per a filing made public by the U.S. SEC today, Abu Dhabi&apos;s sovereign wealth fund Mubadala held 8,726,972 shares of IBIT as of June 30th, and the market value was approximately $534 million. This holding has remained the same since the previous filing in May.Furthermore, in a new filing, Al Warda Investments disclosed that it held 2,411,034 shares of IBIT as of June 30th, with a market value of approximately $147.5 million. The manager of this position is indicated in the filing as the Abu Dhabi Investment Council, which is a sovereign wealth fund under Mubadala.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24649</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>btc</category>
      <category>bitcoin</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan: Ethereum Ecosystem Stablecoin Scale Continues to Grow, Driving Continued ETH Upside</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24648</link>
      <description>On Thursday, August 15th, JPMorgan Chase pointed out in a report that as Wall Street starts to issue a large number of stablecoins within the Ethereum ecosystem, the recent outperformance of ETH may continue.According to the bank&apos;s analysts, a series of USD-pegged tokens - following last month&apos;s &quot;GENIUS Act&quot; which provided a regulatory framework for stablecoins - are expected to have an impact on the price of Ethereum. Although these assets are issued on layer-two networks rather than directly on the Ethereum main chain.The analysts stated: &quot;We believe that Ethereum is emerging as the pathway to directly access the high-growth opportunity of stablecoins. As the Ethereum network hosts most of these stablecoin assets, whether as L1 directly hosted or via L2 partially hosted.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks.Live: Option Market Indicates Optimistic Market Sentiment, Bull Market Likely to Continue</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24647</link>
      <description>On August 15th, the Greek.Live analyst Adam posted on social media, saying, &quot;While BTC hit a new all-time high again and ETH was about to reach its all-time high, the market experienced a somewhat unanticipated pullback. The main trigger was the higher-than-expected PPI. There weren&apos;t many changes in the options market. The IVs of major expiries showed no significant fluctuations, and the fluctuation of Skew was relatively small.&quot;However, the trading volume indicates the market&apos;s enthusiasm. Today, Deribit traded $10.9 billion in options, setting a new single-day record with a volume of over $10 billion for the first time. The high trading activity indicates that the market remains confident about the future, and the bull market is likely to continue.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24647</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>「Big Brother Whale」 Huang Licheng&apos;s ETH long position has increased to 22,000 ETH, with an unrealized loss of $2.4 million</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24646</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to the monitoring of HyperInsight accessible through https://app.hyperliquid.xyz/join/NTOD, the &quot;Big Brother Ma Ji&quot; Huang Licheng&apos;s long position in ETH has risen to 22,000 ETH (equivalent to 100 million US dollars), and there is an unrealized loss of 2.4 million US dollars. The opening price was $4,664.57, and the liquidation price was $2,889.27.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24646</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>whale</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Ethereum drops below $4400, the total Long Liquidation on major CEXs will reach $1.191 billion.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24645</link>
      <description>On August 15th, according to Coinglass data, if Ethereum drops below $4400, the total liquidation strength of mainstream CEXs in terms of long positions will reach $1.191 billion.Conversely, if Ethereum surges above $4700, the total liquidation strength of mainstream CEXs in terms of short positions will reach $928 million.BlockBeats Note: The liquidation chart does not display the exact number of contracts to be liquidated or the precise value of the contracts to be liquidated. The bars on the liquidation chart actually represent the significance of each liquidation cluster in relation to neighboring liquidation clusters, that is, the strength.Therefore, the liquidation chart shows to what extent the target price will be influenced when it reaches a certain level. A higher &quot;liquidation bar&quot; indicates that the price will have a more intense reaction due to a surge in liquidity when it reaches that level.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24645</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Banking Industry Calls for Amendment to the GENIUS Act Signed by Trump, Warning of Potential Financial Risks</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24644</link>
      <description>August 14th. According to The Block, the largest banking association in the US is advising senators to fill what it deems as loopholes in the stablecoin legislation signed by President Trump last month. It is stated that these loopholes may pose a threat to the broader financial system.This week, the American Bankers Association (ABA) along with 52 other banking organizations sent a letter to the leadership of the Senate Banking Committee, suggesting revisions to the American Stablecoin Guidance and Establishment of a National Innovation in U.S. Act (GENIUS). The letter highlighted concerns in aspects such as interest payments, state-level regulations, and the issuance of stablecoins by non-financial companies.The dispute centers around the prohibition in the GENIUS Act on stablecoin issuers paying interest to holders, which is regarded as being too lenient. While these groups support the restrictive measures, they contend that the new legislation can be easily bypassed by e</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24644</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dinari will launch the L1 blockchain Dinari Financial Network</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24643</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per CoinDesk, Dinari, a startup that offers blockchain-based U.S. stock trading services, is set to launch the L1 blockchain called Dinari Financial Network. The network is designed to serve as a coordination and settlement layer for securities issued on other networks such as Arbitrum and is custom-built using the Avalanche (AVAX) technology stack. The testnet is currently in operation, with the plan to go live publicly in the upcoming weeks.In June of this year, Dinari obtained a broker-dealer registration from the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA) in the United States, enabling it to tokenize securities under the U.S. National Market System (NMS) and providing a compliant solution for issuing tokenized versions of U.S. publicly traded stocks.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24643</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookOnChain: Ethereum Drops Below $4600</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24642</link>
      <description>On August 14th, based on HTX market data, Ethereum fell below $4600, experiencing a 24-hour decline of 1.15%.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24642</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>
      <category>high-value</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lido&apos;s market share in the Ethereum staking market has dropped to 24.4%, hitting an all-time low.</title>
      <link>https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24641</link>
      <description>On August 14th, as per Coindesk, Lido&apos;s market share within the Ethereum staking market has plummeted to 24.4%, reaching a record low. During the past month, Figment has witnessed the most significant increase in staked ETH, adding approximately 344,000 ETH and currently accounting for 4.5% of all staked ETH. Lido has experienced the largest exodus of stakers, totaling around 285,000 ETH.With the growing competition and the opening up of new avenues in the industry through infrastructure tailored for institutional financing, there has been a shift in the previously dominant platforms, indicating that the staking ecosystem is maturing.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>LookOnChain</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.lookonchain.com/feeds/24641</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>lookonchain</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>on-chain</category>
      <category>whale-watching</category>
      <category>initial-load</category>
      <category>eth</category>
      <category>ethereum</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>