<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:27:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Boom in RWA tokenization expected after passing of GENIUS Act — Aptos exec</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947767951902134272</link>
      <description>21:15Boom in RWA tokenization expected after passing of GENIUS Act — Aptos exec</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947767951902134272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla’s futuristic diner is here, serving fries and popcorn—but where’s the Dogecoin?Elon Musk’s Tesla diner is now serving up burgers and futurism in Hollywood. However, patrons noticed the absence of Dogecoin payments, despite his earlier endorsement, turning what could’ve been a crypto milestone into a missed opportunity. The grand opening of Tesla’s long-hyped “retro-futuristic” diner in Hollywood unfolded Monday afternoon with all the usual Musk theatrics: a 4:20 p.m. unlock time, robots behind popcorn machines, and Cybertruck-shaped trays. Tesla Diner &amp; Supercharger in Hollywood, LA Open 24/7, starting now  pic.twitter.com/nISRNoV89Y The crowd, which had gathered at the Santa Monica Boulevard diner hours before opening, cheered as Tesla’s chief designer, Franz von Holzhausen, unlocked the doors.  For Dogecoin ( DOGE ) loyalists, the fanfare rang hollow. Despite Musk’s 2022 tweet insisting DOGE payments were coming, the only currency accepted was the old-fashioned kind. When one patron approached a touch screen and placed his order, he followed up with a question: “Can I pay in Dogecoin?” “Not today,” the diner employee responded. See below. 🚨DOGE FAM MUST SEE THIS🚨 I actually went to Tesla Diner first day to ask them if they accept DOGECOIN! 👇  pic.twitter.com/3b7zeDhhsA Musk’s influence on Dogecoin’s valuation is well-documented; a single tweet from him has sent the memecoin soaring or cratering for years. His latest pivot away from crypto integration, especially at a high-profile venture blending tech and commerce, raises questions about how seriously Tesla takes digital assets. The diner’s omission of DOGE isn’t just a snub to crypto enthusiasts; it’s a missed chance to normalize cryptocurrency in everyday transactions, something Musk once championed. The Tesla diner, nestled at the intersection of electric vehicles, entertainment, and lifestyle, could have become a high-visibility proving ground for real-world crypto payments. Killing it, man! “Not today” paying with  $Doge . Not the answer we where hoping for but better then a flat out no Instead, the absence of Dogecoin underscores a widening gap between Musk’s rhetoric and implementation, particularly at a time when the digital assets sector is seeking tangible, everyday use cases. Whether this was a delay or a quiet reversal remains unclear, but in the current climate, silence on crypto can speak volumes. Meanwhile, Musk has already floated plans to expand the diner concept to major cities and Supercharger stops, contingent on its initial success. Whether he’ll keep his word and eventually accept DOGE as a payment remains to be seen.  “‘Not today’ paying with $Doge. Not the answer we where hoping for but better then a flat out no,” another observer noted on X [sic].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947767458576486400</link>
      <description>11 minutes agocrypto.newsTesla’s futuristic diner is here, serving fries and popcorn—but where’s the Dogecoin?Elon Musk’s Tesla diner is now serving up burgers and futurism in Hollywood. However, patrons noticed the absence of Dogecoin payments, despite his earlier endorsement, turning what could’ve</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947767458576486400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily: JPMorgan explores crypto loans, Musk&apos;s SpaceX moves bitcoin, Senate pushes policy, and moreThe following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter,The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.
Never miss a beat with The Block&apos;sdaily digestof the most influential events happening across the digital assetecosystem.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947762440301465600</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoThe BlockThe Daily: JPMorgan explores crypto loans, Musk&apos;s SpaceX moves bitcoin, Senate pushes policy, and moreThe following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter,The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.
Never miss a beat with The Block&apos;sdaily digestof the most influe</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947762440301465600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US seeks to recover $7.1 million in crypto tied to oil and gas fraud schemeU.S. prosecutors are seeking $7.1 million worth of cryptocurrency tied to an oil and gas investment scam.

The U.S. Attorney&apos;s Office for the Western District of Washington filed a civil action on Tuesday to get those funds.

“The co-schemers in this fraud moved their ill-gotten gain through various cryptocurrency accounts to try to launder the money stolen from victims,” said acting U.S. Attorney Miller in the statement. “Federal investigators and prosecutors in our office moved as quickly as possible to trace and seize the cryptocurrency so that some of the losses can be returned to victims.”

Geoffrey K. Auyeung, 47, who was allegedly behind the scheme, was indicted in 2024 on a slew of money laundering charges. Prosecutors say he and others persuaded victims to send money to &quot;what was represented as escrow accounts to purchase oil tank storage in either Rotterdam, Netherlands, or Houston,&quot; promising profits through renting out the oil tank storage.

Instead, prosecutors said the money was moved to 81 different accounts, taken offshore or moved to 19 crypto accounts where Bitcoin, USDT, USDC, ETH, and other assets were bought.

About $2.3 million were seized from Auyeung&apos;s bank accounts when he was arrested, prosecutors said.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947756692041388032</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoThe BlockUS seeks to recover $7.1 million in crypto tied to oil and gas fraud schemeU.S. prosecutors are seeking $7.1 million worth of cryptocurrency tied to an oil and gas investment scam.

The U.S. Attorney&apos;s Office for the Western District of Washington filed a civil action on Tuesd</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947756692041388032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU Could Rally 38% if One Key Price Resistance BreaksAfter a strong 26% gain over the past week, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) is now hovering just below a crucial resistance level. While much of the altcoin market cools down, PENGU price looks poised to break out. Only if it can push past one key wall. A deeper look at bullish strength, liquidations, and price charts shows the token might still have room to run. PENGU Bulls Are In Complete Control Even though PENGU dropped around 2% in the past 24 hours, the bulls still seem to be holding the reins. The Bull-Bear Power (BBP) index, which compares recent highs and lows to measure market strength, is currently flashing green, at around 0.0148. This level suggests buyers still have the upper hand, despite a short-term dip. For token TA and market updates : Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here . In simple terms, when BBP is positive, bulls are stronger than bears. And Pengu’s BBP has remained above zero since late June, even as prices hovered below key resistance. That steady strength could be a sign that any dip is just part of a cooldown before another leg up. If BBP stays positive while price climbs past resistance, it might confirm that PENGU still has momentum. But if BBP flips negative, it could warn of a deeper pullback ahead. 7-Day Liquidation Map Shows Short-Biased Setup PENGU is currently trading around $0.036. The 7-day liquidation map shows cumulative short liquidation leverage building up to $10.46 million versus $10.18 million for longs; a slight bias toward short positions. Do note that there isn’t much to choose between Longs and  Shorts , and a price push in either direction can decide the next leg for PENGU.  However, as bulls are in power and that too by a sizable margin, as established by the BBP index, the price action could impact the short positions more than the long. If the price crosses $0.039, led by bulls breaking key resistance level, and even nears $0.042, a major liquidation cluster of shorts gets triggered. That would reduce downward pressure and potentially propel the  PENGU price  to the next key price level. The liquidation map shows a build-up of short positions; if PENGU’s price moves up fast, those betting against it may be forced to buy back, pushing the price even higher. PENGU Price Action Hints at a 38% Upside Technically, the  PENGU price  has tested the 0.382 Fibonacci level near $0.039 twice and failed to break above cleanly. It now trades just under that resistance. Do note that besides the Fib extension resistance, a key resistance of $0.037 also exists. The chart uses the Trend-based Fibonacci extension tool. It connects the swing low of $0.0077 to the last swing high of $0.035 and then to the immediately retraced price level of $0.028. This tool helps chart the next price targets for a coin/token in an uptrend.  If PENGU price manages a clean breakout above $0.037, $0.039, and then $0.042 (the 0.5 Fib zone), it opens the path to $0.045 first, a 25% surge. If that breaks, the next key resistance point, or rather target, would be $0.050, the 0.786 Fibonacci level. That would be a 38% rally from current prices around $0.036. Validation for this move comes from declining bear power, building short positions, and strong chart structure. The bullish trend would get invalidated if PENGU breaks the $0.035 resistance-turned-support. Or if it continues to drop to touch the retracement zone of the Fibonacci extension: the $0.028 mark.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947763664618803200</link>
      <description>56 minutes agobeincryptoPENGU Could Rally 38% if One Key Price Resistance BreaksAfter a strong 26% gain over the past week, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) is now hovering just below a crucial resistance level. While much of the altcoin market cools down, PENGU price looks poised to break out. Only if it can</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947763664618803200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Tapiero sees crypto ecosystem reaching $50 trillion as he launches new $500.0 million fund under 50T rebrand10T Holdings (10T) and 1RoundTable Partners (1RT), two crypto growth equity funds founded by veteran macro investor Dan Tapiero, have consolidated under a new brand, 50T, and launched a new $500.0 million fund.

The rebrand comes alongside a revised market outlook from Tapiero, who now sees the digital asset ecosystem reaching $50.0 trillion in value over the next decade — up from his original $10.0 trillion projection in 2020.

Asked whether this referred to the global crypto market alone, Tapiero told The Block that it also includes the valuation of all public and private companies in the space.

&quot;We originally named our fund 10T because we projected the digital asset ecosystem could reach $10.0 trillion in value over the next decade. This ecosystem encompasses Bitcoin, Ethereum, all cryptocurrencies, and equity in the space. Remarkably, we&apos;ve already reached $5.0 trillion today. Looking ahead to the next decade, especially considering the recent significant changes in Washington DC, we believe there&apos;s a realistic path from today&apos;s $5.0 trillion to $50.0 trillion,&quot; Tapiero said.

The new vehicle, called 50T Fund V, is a 10-year closed-end fund focused on growth equity investments in blockchain, crypto, and web3 infrastructure. The first close is planned for the fourth quarter of this year.

The rebrand and new fund follow a string of notable exits from the firm’s portfolio, including Deribit’s recent $2.9 billion acquisition by Coinbase and the public listings of Circle and eToro. Earlier this year, 1RT Acquisition Corp. — a special purpose acquisition company (SPAC) affiliated with the firm — raised $172.5 million in an oversubscribed IPO on Nasdaq. The SPAC focuses on digital assets and technology-enabled businesses, particularly in the cryptocurrency, blockchain, and fintech sectors.

With additional portfolio companies preparing for public listings, the firm says it is positioned to continue benefiting from what it sees as the next wave of growth in the digital asset ecosystem.

Under the combined brand, 50T currently manages $2.0 billion in assets and maintains board representation across its portfolio. The firm says its &quot;picks and shovels&quot; concentrated approach emphasizes structured downside protection and active governance.

The Funding newsletter:Stay on top of the latest crypto funding and M&amp;A deals, news, and trends with my free bi-monthly newsletter, The Funding. Sign uphere! [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947756169439498240</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoThe BlockDan Tapiero sees crypto ecosystem reaching $50 trillion as he launches new $500.0 million fund under 50T rebrand10T Holdings (10T) and 1RoundTable Partners (1RT), two crypto growth equity funds founded by veteran macro investor Dan Tapiero, have consolidated under a new brand,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947756169439498240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orphanage in Uganda That Runs on Bitcoin Celebrated Bitcoin Pizza Day with a Road TripOn May 22, 2025, children from the Orphans of Uganda Children’s Center, an orphanage in eastern Uganda that’s part of the Bitcoin Kampala community, took a road trip to the zoo thanks in part to bitcoin donations from around the world. The team that helps fund and run the the orphanage chose to take the trip on Bitcoin Pizza Day to show the orphans, many of whom had never left the village in which the orphanage is located, that anything is possible, much like Laszlo Hanyecz showed the world that paying for goods and services in bitcoin is possible when he paid 10,000 bitcoin for two pizzas on May 22, 2010. 22•05•2025 – Orphanage Bitcoin Pizza Day 😇 We dreamt to leave our district on a bus to the zoo at the end of last year, you all made it happen…. Special Thanks to @blinkbtc , @studentofbtc , @travelwbitcoin who sponsored us for the day And our forever patrons @Bitcoinbeach ,… pic.twitter.com/Ol6XC52bcv “We organized this trip to give the children hope and to open their minds to what’s possible,” Brindon Mwiine, founder of Bitcoin Kampala, told Bitcoin Magazine. “Last year, we started teaching them to write down their dreams in notebooks we gave them, and when we asked what they wished for at Christmas, their answers were simple: visit the capital, see animals, and travel,” he added. “Bitcoin Pizza Day at the Entebbe Zoo became the perfect way to bring those dreams to life while teaching them about Bitcoin.” Mwiine also noted that this was the first time the children had taken an extended bus ride, crossed the Nile, traveled through the capital city of Kampala, explored a zoo — and tasted pizza. “It was a day of firsts,” said Mwiine, who added that it was all the more special because he, the support staff and the children “experienced it all together as a family.” Edith Mpumwire, a member of Blink Wallet’s marketing team and someone who works with the Bitcoin Kampala team, seconded what Mwiine said. “This trip is the first of its kind [for these children],” said Mpumwire in the video embedded in the X post above. “Most of these children are from eastern Uganda [and] they stay in a small house located in Bugiri. They have never left Bugiri, so, for them, today is the first day to not only visit the zoo, but to leave their enclosure,” she added. Mpumwire also noted how the international Bitcoin community is partially to thank for enabling the orphans to take this trip. “The global [Bitcoin] community contributes to their livelihood [and] here we are taking them on a road trip [where] they get to see a mini national park, Lake Victoria and very many animals.” You can contribute to the Orphans of Uganda Children’s Center via the project’s Geyser page.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947764719289126912</link>
      <description>1 hour agobitcoinmagazineOrphanage in Uganda That Runs on Bitcoin Celebrated Bitcoin Pizza Day with a Road TripOn May 22, 2025, children from the Orphans of Uganda Children’s Center, an orphanage in eastern Uganda that’s part of the Bitcoin Kampala community, took a road trip to the zoo thanks in pa</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947764719289126912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citadel calls on SEC to strictly regulate tokenized stocks, opposes exemptive treatmentThis week, market-making giant Citadel Securities sent a letter to the U.S. SEC&apos;s Crypto Assets Working Group, opposing granting exemptive treatment to tokenized equities, saying that doing so could cause liquidity to flow out of traditional markets and cause investors to be confused about asset issuers. Citadel said that tokenized equities should follow the same regulatory rules as traditional securities, and that the SEC should advance relevant policies through roundtables and formal rulemaking, rather than circumventing existing regulations through &quot;innovation exceptions.&quot; [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947765365081919488</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Citadel calls on SEC to strictly regulate tokenized stocks, opposes exemptive treatmentThis week, market-making giant Citadel Securities sent a letter to the U.S. SEC&apos;s Crypto Assets Working Group, opposing granting exemptive treatment to tokenized equities, saying that doing so could ca</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947765365081919488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KindlyMD and Nakamoto Holdings File with SEC, Merger Expected to Close August 11Today, KindlyMD (NASDAQ: NAKA) and Bitcoin-native firm Nakamoto Holdings announced that it has officially filed their definitive information statement with the SEC in connection with the proposed merger with Nakamoto, moving forward with a planned merger expected to close around August 11, 2025. BREAKING: 🇺🇸 $763.00 million #Bitcoin treasury company Nakamoto files with SEC to merge with publicly traded KindlyMD. Expects to complete the merge in 20 days. pic.twitter.com/ejjMaoqI6k “Filing the definitive information statement is a critical milestone for this merger and accelerates our mission of acquiring one million Bitcoin,” stated the Founder and CEO of Nakamoto David Bailey. “I’m very proud of the teams’ collaboration at Nakamoto and KindlyMD to get us one step closer to closing the merger. Our shared enthusiasm for Bitcoin paired with our expertise in structuring this opportunity for public markets has created a strong foundation for the combined company’s future.” The merger is a key step in advancing Nakamoto’s strategy, which will use Bitcoin not only as a reserve asset but as the foundation of a new capital framework. Nakamoto will treat Bitcoin as the base and combine it with public stocks to grow and invest more effectively. This model supports smaller companies that hold Bitcoin in regions where direct access to it is limited. Firms like Metaplanet, Smarter Web Company, and The Blockchain Group have already shown strong results. Performance is measured by Bitcoin per share, with gains reinvested into more Bitcoin or new ventures. Nakamoto manages the 40 percent securities limit under the Investment Company Act by using Bitcoin-denominated convertible notes, giving it more flexibility and control. With over 750 million dollars raised, the merger with KindlyMD supports its goal of expanding a Bitcoin based financial model globally. “We are proud to reach this important milestone alongside Nakamoto,” said the Founder and CEO of KindlyMD Tim Pickett. “Our shareholders now have the opportunity to be part of a groundbreaking shift in how public companies approach treasury management, with Bitcoin at the center.” Disclosure: Nakamoto is in partnership with Bitcoin Magazine’s parent company BTC Inc to build the first global network of Bitcoin treasury companies, where BTC Inc provides certain marketing services to Nakamoto. More information on this can be found here.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947754372343812096</link>
      <description>2 hours agobitcoinmagazineKindlyMD and Nakamoto Holdings File with SEC, Merger Expected to Close August 11Today, KindlyMD (NASDAQ: NAKA) and Bitcoin-native firm Nakamoto Holdings announced that it has officially filed their definitive information statement with the SEC in connection with the propose</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947754372343812096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $120,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.68% in the past 1H, up 2.29% in the last 24H. Now at $120,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947732176492519424</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $120,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.68% in the past 1H, up 2.29% in the last 24H. Now at $120,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947732176492519424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiNFT index 24hr gain of 10.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has risen by 10.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU +21.28%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947731920098910208</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSSI Price BotssiNFT index 24hr gain of 10.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has risen by 10.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU +21.28%.$PENGUShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947731920098910208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Senate Republicans release draft bill for crypto market structureRepublican leaders on the Senate Banking Committee said the legislation “built on” the CLARITY Act passed in the House of Representatives last week.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947724867109670912</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsUS Senate Republicans release draft bill for crypto market structureRepublican leaders on the Senate Banking Committee said the legislation “built on” the CLARITY Act passed in the House of Representatives last week.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947724867109670912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram launches non-custodial crypto app in USMessaging app Telegram has launched a new non-custodial crypto wallet in the United States through a partnership with MoonPay. The new feature will enable millions of users to send and manage crypto directly within the app.

Telegram previously launched a crypto wallet globally that was activated by more than 100 million users. Tuesday’s launch will enable users in the U.S. to send, receive, and manage cryptocurrency directly inside the app.

The wallet is built on The Open Platform, a.k.a. TOP, which is built on the TON blockchain. The feature allows users to transact with crypto as easily as sending a message. Telegram said that the wallet will be instantly installed and will not require a download.

The Open Platform recently raised a $28.5 million Series A at a $1 billion valuation.

Telegram infamously fought the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission in court after launching its TON token in 2019. After a protracted legal battle, Telegram agreed to return $1.2 billion to investors and pay an $18.5 million penalty to settle with the SEC.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947722467271528448</link>
      <description>3 hours agoThe BlockTelegram launches non-custodial crypto app in USMessaging app Telegram has launched a new non-custodial crypto wallet in the United States through a partnership with MoonPay. The new feature will enable millions of users to send and manage crypto directly within the app.

Telegra</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947722467271528448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevvStream pivots, anchors crypto treasury to BTC and SOLNasdaq-listed carbon management firm DevvStream unveiled Tuesday the initial composition of its digital asset treasury, naming Bitcoin, Solana and its own DevvE token as core holdings. The company also appointed BitGo as its qualified custodian and brought in FRNT Financial as a digital asset advisor, signaling a deliberate move to pair ESG mandates with programmable finance. DevvStream CEO Sunny Trinh said the company’s crypto treasury strategy is less about speculative upside and more about institutional-grade liquidity, ecosystem alignment, and real-world asset integration. “Our treasury model isn’t just about holding crypto. It’s about aligning capital with our mission,” Trinh said. “Our mix of assets is designed to deliver institutional-grade efficiency and income, while bridging to sustainability tokenization and real-world asset integration. Together, they position DevvStream at the intersection of liquidity, innovation, and impact.” Bitcoin (BTC), described by the company as the “foundational asset of the digital economy,” serves as the bedrock of its treasury, offering deep liquidity and institutional credibility. Unlike firms that treat BTC purely as a hedge, DevvStream appears to view it as an on-ramp for broader blockchain integration, ensuring stability while it experiments with more dynamic assets. Solana’s (SOL) inclusion is equally deliberate. The company cited SOL’s transaction speed and ecosystem depth as key factors, suggesting an intent to generate yield through staking or DeFi participation. This is a departure from passive Bitcoin holdings, aligning with a growing trend of corporations leveraging proof-of-stake networks for treasury management, where idle assets can earn returns without traditional market risks. But the most unconventional pick is DevvE, the company’s proprietary token. Unlike BTC and SOL, DevvE isn’t just a store of value or yield vehicle; it’s designed to facilitate what the firm calls “impact-layer tokenization,” linking digital finance directly to carbon offset projects and other sustainability initiatives. The company hasn’t disclosed exact allocation percentages.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947721623717302272</link>
      <description>3 hours agocrypto.newsDevvStream pivots, anchors crypto treasury to BTC and SOLNasdaq-listed carbon management firm DevvStream unveiled Tuesday the initial composition of its digital asset treasury, naming Bitcoin, Solana and its own DevvE token as core holdings. The company also appointed BitGo as</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947721623717302272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street is Warming Up to Rate Cuts—Will Crypto Be the Biggest Winner?Wall Street is increasingly betting on US interest rate cuts before the end of 2025. At the same time, political pressure from Donald Trump has intensified, as he becomes more vocally aggressive toward Powell for rate cuts.  With inflation cooling and markets adjusting expectations, crypto could stand to gain the most from a looser monetary policy. Trump Wants Fed to Bring Interest Rate Down to 1% Earlier today, Trump renewed his attack on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. He called for a 3 percentage point rate cut and claimed it would save the US economy $1 trillion annually.  The US President also accused Powell of keeping rates high for “political reasons.” While the Fed has held rates steady at 4.25%–4.50% since June, speculation is rising. Goldman Sachs now expects the first cut to arrive in September.  Meanwhile, traders on prediction market Kalshi see a 40% chance of two cuts before year-end. This shift follows a steep drop in US inflation expectations . One-year consumer expectations fell to 4.4% in July, the lowest since February. That marks a 2.2 percentage point drop over just two months—one of the largest two-month declines in history. Longer-term inflation expectations are also easing. Five-year outlooks dropped 0.8 percentage points in the last quarter, now sitting at 3.6%.  Overall, these trends suggest the Fed has more room to ease without sparking fears of a price spiral. The crypto market is paying close attention. Bitcoin remains above $118,000 , while Ethereum holds near $3,700. Both assets have historically rallied after Fed rate cuts, benefiting from increased liquidity and investor risk appetite. Could a Major Crypto Bull Run Begin? Historically, rate cuts have kicked off strong crypto bull markets .  After the Fed slashed rates in March 2020 during the COVID-19 crisis, Bitcoin soared from under $10,000 to over $60,000 within a year. Ethereum followed, supported by DeFi and NFT growth. If a new rate cut cycle begins in September, it could bring similar conditions. Lower yields push investors toward risk-on assets, including crypto.  Capital could also rotate from bonds and cash into Bitcoin, Ethereum, and high-conviction altcoins. Additionally, falling inflation expectations and improving regulatory clarity—such as the GENIUS and CLARITY Acts —may reinforce investor confidence.  This convergence of macro and policy signals could extend the current cycle beyond previous all-time highs. However, timing matters. Crypto is already near record levels, so momentum may depend on how fast and deep the cuts are. A delayed or shallow response from the Fed could limit upside. Key Dates to Watch The next Federal Reserve policy meeting will take place on July 29–30 . While markets expect no change, Fed commentary will be closely parsed for signals about September. The next critical date is September 16–17 , when the FOMC reconvenes. This is widely seen as the first realistic window for a rate cut, especially if inflation continues to decline. Other key indicators to monitor: For crypto traders, these dates offer cues for potential market inflection points. A confirmed Fed pivot could trigger renewed buying pressure, particularly in Bitcoin, Ethereum, and high-liquidity altcoins.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947727172513058816</link>
      <description>3 hours agobeincryptoWall Street is Warming Up to Rate Cuts—Will Crypto Be the Biggest Winner?Wall Street is increasingly betting on US interest rate cuts before the end of 2025. At the same time, political pressure from Donald Trump has intensified, as he becomes more vocally aggressive toward Powe</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947727172513058816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF issuers file amendments for in-kind redemptions, signaling &apos;positive movement&apos; with SECSeveral ETF issuers filed amendments with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to permit in-kind creations and redemptions from their spot crypto funds, something one expert says indicates that there is positive momentum going on at the agency.

21Shares, Fidelity, Franklin Templeton, Galaxy, VanEck, and WisdomTree all submitted their amended proposals Tuesday morning seeking to make their spot Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds, as well as future crypto ETFs, more efficient.

&quot;More positive signs,&quot; Bloomberg Intelligence ETF analyst James Seyffart said in a post on X .&quot;This indicates to me that there is positive movement and likely fine tuning happening with the SEC.&quot;

These firms have been seeking in-kind redemptions for months, and SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce said last month that in-kind redemptions for crypto ETFs are &quot;on the horizon.&quot;

&quot;Those (forms) are going through the process now,&quot; Peirce said on June 25. &quot;So I think that&apos;s something that&apos;s certainly on the horizon at some point. I can&apos;t prejudge, but we hear that there&apos;s a lot of interest.&quot;

Seyffart clarified that this would only be for the &quot;authorized participants&quot; like major Wall Street firms and market makers — not retail traders — to trade in shares of their ETFs for the underlying asset.

&quot;[T]he vast majority of people won&apos;t even see a difference because the products on the market now already trade extremely efficiently,&quot; Seyffart said. &quot;This will treat crypto ETPs the same as other ETPs are treated.

Crypto ETF &quot;floodgates&quot; are poised to open as the SEC is also weighing a faster approval framework, The Block&apos;s Sarah Wynn previously reported. Following spot BTC ETFs (January 2024) and spot ETH ETFs (July 2024), there are now several dozen more crypto-related ETFs seeking approval. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710893240635392</link>
      <description>3 hours agoThe BlockBitcoin and Ethereum ETF issuers file amendments for in-kind redemptions, signaling &apos;positive movement&apos; with SECSeveral ETF issuers filed amendments with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to permit in-kind creations and redemptions from their spot crypto funds, somethin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710893240635392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle launches Circle Gateway, a new infrastructure for unified USDC cross-chain balancesAccording to official sources, Circle has released the Circle Gateway testnet, supporting Avalanche, Base, and the Ethereum mainnet, providing users with the ability to access USDC across chains in seconds. The mainnet version is coming soon and will continue to expand to more blockchains. Key highlights include: 1. &lt;500ms cross-chain access: No cross-chain bridge required, no pre-set assets required, quickly call unified USDC balance; 2. Efficient liquidity management: Meet multi-chain liquidity needs through a single integration, reducing capital occupation; 3. Non-custodial design: Users have complete control over USDC, funds can only be moved under signature authorization, and withdrawals do not require trusting a third party. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710508304191488</link>
      <description>4 hours agoOdailyCircle launches Circle Gateway, a new infrastructure for unified USDC cross-chain balancesAccording to official sources, Circle has released the Circle Gateway testnet, supporting Avalanche, Base, and the Ethereum mainnet, providing users with the ability to access USDC across chain</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710508304191488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — ReportThe investigation was reportedly not connected to Jesse Powell’s activities within the crypto industry.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947695662019923968</link>
      <description>4 hours agoPANewsFBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — ReportThe investigation was reportedly not connected to Jesse Powell’s activities within the crypto industry.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947695662019923968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun to Become Youngest Chinese Commercial Astronaut with Blue Origin’s New ShepardGeneva, Switzerland - July 22, 2025 - Justin Sun, founder of TRON and one of the most recognizable figures in crypto, is set to make history as the youngest Chinese-born commercial astronaut and the first Forbes-cover crypto entrepreneur to travel to space aboard Blue Origin’s New Shepard. This mission is the 14th human flight for the New Shepard program and the 34th in its history. The flight date will be announced soon. The live webcast on launch day will start 30 minutes before liftoff.

In 2021, Sun placed the winning bid for the first seat on New Shepard. The $28 million in proceeds were donated to Blue Origin’s foundation, Club for the Future, which selected 19 space-focused non-profits to each receive a $1 million grant to inspire future generations to pursue careers in STEAM (science, technology, engineering, arts, and math) for the benefit of Earth and help invent the future of life in space.

“We are witnessing the beginning of a new chapter in human exploration, where space is no longer reserved for governments or institutions but is becoming a frontier for innovators, dreamers, and builders from all walks of life,” said Sun. “Blue Origin’s commitment to expanding access to space, along with Club for the Future’s mission to inspire young people worldwide, reflects a powerful vision. I am proud to support this effort and help advance the belief that space is a place for everyone, not just a select few.”

Sun’s upcoming flight is more than a personal milestone. It highlights the growing international presence in commercial space travel and the increasing connection between blockchain and scientific innovation. As a leading voice in the digital economy and a strong advocate for decentralized technology, his journey reflects the broader potential for global collaboration and progress at the frontier of space exploration.

About TRON DAO

TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.

Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON blockchain has experienced significant growth since its MainNet launch in May 2018. TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin, exceeding $81 billion. As of July 2025, the TRON blockchain has recorded over 320 million in total user accounts, more than 10 billion in total transactions, and over $25 billion in total value locked (TVL), based on TRONSCAN.

TRONNetwork | TRONDAO | X | YouTube | Telegram | Discord | Reddit | GitHub | Medium | Forum

Media Contact

Yeweon Park

[email protected]

This post is commissioned by TRON and does not serve as a testimonial or endorsement by The Block. This post is for informational purposes only and should not be relied upon as a basis for investment, tax, legal or other advice. You should conduct your own research and consult independent counsel and advisors on the matters discussed within this post. Past performance of any asset is not indicative of future results. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947693515320610816</link>
      <description>5 hours agoThe BlockJustin Sun to Become Youngest Chinese Commercial Astronaut with Blue Origin’s New ShepardGeneva, Switzerland - July 22, 2025 - Justin Sun, founder of TRON and one of the most recognizable figures in crypto, is set to make history as the youngest Chinese-born commercial astronaut</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947693515320610816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance CEO Joins The Digital Chamber Advisory BoardAccording to the official announcement, Binance CEO Richard Teng has officially joined its advisory board. This move aims to assist the organization in promoting the collaborative development of the global digital asset industry in terms of compliance, transparency, and innovation. The Digital Chamber is the world&apos;s largest blockchain and digital asset industry association, and its advisory members also include executives from institutions such as Chainlink and Custodia Bank. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694544774778880</link>
      <description>5 hours agoOdailyBinance CEO Joins The Digital Chamber Advisory BoardAccording to the official announcement, Binance CEO Richard Teng has officially joined its advisory board. This move aims to assist the organization in promoting the collaborative development of the global digital asset industry in</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694544774778880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Zohran Mamdani’s Crypto Position Ahead of the New York Mayoral Election?New York’s viral mayoral candidate Zohran Mamdani has caused a social media storm with his ‘social democratic’ political ideology and engaging campaign approach. However, his crypto stance still remains in the grey. Meanwhile, Mamdani’s opposition is already turning to the crypto industry to swing public opinion. Zohran Mamdani’s Silence on Crypto New York City, a major cryptocurrency industry hub, is scheduled to hold a mayoral election on November 4, 2025. Current Mayor Eric Adams, elected as a Democrat, is seeking re-election as an independent candidate. Andrew Cuomo, the former governor of New York State, is also running. The two men, who formerly ran for offices on Democratic party tickets, are up against a rising newcomer in the NYC mayoral race. That would be 33-year-old New York assemblyman Zohran Mamdani, who is running as a Democrat, winning the party’s nomination over Cuomo, who now plans to run as an independent. Already, Mamdani is quite popular, even to those outside of New York’s five boroughs. On July 16, Mamdani was in Washington. He was meeting with leading Democrats such as Senator Bernie Sanders and Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, who both endorsed Mamdani in his party’s successful primary run against Cuomo. Sanders posted on Twitter/X on that day about Mamdami, saying he was “deeply impressed by the grassroots campaign he is running”. But Mamdani has never talked about crypto. BeInCrypto reached out to Mamdani, both his campaign and council office, for comments on the blockchain industry. There was no response as of press time. Though his following is largely a younger demographic, he hasn’t yet addressed policy regarding blockchain and cryptocurrency in a city well-known for the industry. Some in crypto might be concerned. Leading Democrats have been critical of cryptocurrency, mainly due to consumer protection issues. Will Mamdani’s Political Ideology Hamper New York’s Crypto Progress? The most outspoken Democrat member of the crypto opposition is Elizabeth Warren, who told CNBC on July 17 that Mamdani is “willing to try new ideas”. That might not be enough to convince cryptocurrency advocates Mamdani is the right person to push blockchain technology forward in NYC, where companies like Uniswap, OpenSea and ConsenSys are headquartered. “Not bullish,” said Brian Mahoney, based in NYC as vice president of business development for Thesis, a Bitcoin startup accelerator. Influential Democrats like Warren have been outspoken critics of the cryptocurrency industry. And Mamdani’s position as a “socialist” Democrat may not align with the free market ideals of blockchain and cryptocurrency. It’s hard to tell when Mamdani’s positioning is not yet clear. It may take some time before that positioning crystallizes ahead of the election in November. Many cryptocurrency companies that would rather have less regulation, especially in light of New York State’s onerous BitLicense requirements, could be concerned if Mamdani starts to criticize the industry. Yet the majority of crypto companies concerned about tougher regulations in New York may have some fear of a very left-leaning mayoral candidate like Mamdani. This is largely because Mamdani plans to make busing in NYC free and freeze rents for citizens. Already, opponent and incumbent Eric Adams is busy courting cryptocurrency, seeing it as an opportunity for fundraising. Empower NYC, a super PAC, is raising up to $10 million for Adams, largely from the crypto and banking industry. It will be interesting to see what Mamdani’s views and positioning will be about crypto. To him, is it a world-changing good for the people? Or does he view it as harmful for the people of New York City, despite it being an industry epicenter? Only time and Mamdani’s positioning will truly tell. [BeInCrypto]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947696231220531200</link>
      <description>5 hours agobeincryptoWhat is Zohran Mamdani’s Crypto Position Ahead of the New York Mayoral Election?New York’s viral mayoral candidate Zohran Mamdani has caused a social media storm with his ‘social democratic’ political ideology and engaging campaign approach. However, his crypto stance still rema</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947696231220531200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 21:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>