<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Building crypto vaults with Veda co-founder Sun RaghupathiEpisode 35 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and Veda co-founder and CEO Sun Raghupathi.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or wherever you listen to podcasts. Please send feedback and revision requests to[emailprotected]

Tim and Sun discussed how DeFi vaults are simplifying complex finance systems and looking to drive mainstream and institutional adoption. Sun explained on Veda&apos;s Vault architecture, the importance of security, and the evolving competitive landscape in the DeFi space.

OUTLINE
00:00 – Introduction 
00:25 – What is Veda? 
03:31 – Potential Contagion Risks 
04:30 – GMX Hack 
05:39 – DeFi Hacks 
08:16 – Challenges of Building Vaults 
09:48 – DeFi&apos;s Evolution 
15:23 – Institutional Involvement 
16:58 – Vault Uses in TradFi 
17:47 – Tokenized Stocks 
20:44 – Vaults vs. Staking 
22:48 – Types of Vault Strategies 
24:39 – AI in Vault Management 
25:47 – Veda’s Future Plans 
26:37 – Conclusion

The Block Newsletters
The Block&apos;s newsletters bring you the latest news and analysis of the fast-moving crypto and DeFi markets. To subscribe, visit theblock.co/newsletters

Guest links:
Sun - ⁠⁠https://x.com/sunandr_⁠ 
Veda - ⁠⁠⁠https://x.com/veda_labs⁠

Are you hiring in crypto?
Use Campus to quickly find your best candidates with our challenging Crypto Assessment Test.
Faster hiring, stronger teams.

Sign up for a trial today:theblock.co/campus

[The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336925928132608</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoThe BlockBuilding crypto vaults with Veda co-founder Sun RaghupathiEpisode 35 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and Veda co-founder and CEO Sun Raghupathi.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or wh</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336925928132608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Wallet launches BNB and XRP incentive activities to support the use of on-chain assetsOn July 24, according to an official announcement, Gate Wallet hit a new high around the price of BNB and officially launched two online incentive activities covering the two major assets of BNB and XRP.
During the event, new users who complete their first BNB transaction in their wallet (amount ≥ $100) can receive a maximum $10.00 airdrop, limited to the first 1,000 participants. All users who top up BNB can also share a $10,000.00 prize pool based on their top-up ratio, with a maximum single-person reward of $100.00.
In the XRP incentive activity, users who deposit no less than 10 XRP can participate in the $5,000.00 airdrop; those who complete XRP transactions (amount ≥ $50.00) can also participate in the $20,000.00 prize pool. The rewards are distributed according to the transaction ratio, and a single person can get up to $200.00. The activity ends on August 10.
Gate Wallet is the industry-leading multi-chain crypto wallet, connecting 100+ public chains, millions of assets and tens of thousands of DApps in one stop, opening up a professional-level Web3 experience and providing the best solution for every Web3 need. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336439938322432</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoPANewsGate Wallet launches BNB and XRP incentive activities to support the use of on-chain assetsOn July 24, according to an official announcement, Gate Wallet hit a new high around the price of BNB and officially launched two online incentive activities covering the two major assets of</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336439938322432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address holding 3,962 BTC that had been dormant for 14.5 years was activated, with a value of approximately $468.00M.According to Whale Alert monitoring, about 10 minutes ago, a dormant address containing 3,962 BTC (worth approximately $468.00M) was reactivated after being dormant for 14.5 years. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948335454021029888</link>
      <description>8 minutes ago吴说An address holding 3,962 BTC that had been dormant for 14.5 years was activated, with a value of approximately $468.00M.According to Whale Alert monitoring, about 10 minutes ago, a dormant address containing 3,962 BTC (worth approximately $468.00M) was reactivated after being dormant</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948335454021029888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-chain detective ZachXBT: Some projects are running Yaps campaigns to attract low-quality users and AI-generated content, which will only dilute brand value.On-chain detective ZachXBT posted on his personal channel, pointing out that some projects are currently attracting low-quality users and AI-generated content by running Yaps campaigns, which dilutes brand value and fails to bring long-term funds and real user growth. He called on the community to actively block related projects and question false data indicators in order to curb the &quot;proliferation of low-quality content&quot; in the ecosystem. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948335125921599488</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyOn-chain detective ZachXBT: Some projects are running Yaps campaigns to attract low-quality users and AI-generated content, which will only dilute brand value.On-chain detective ZachXBT posted on his personal channel, pointing out that some projects are currently attracting low-q</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948335125921599488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited the remaining 100 BTC into Binance, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale address starting with 1EGQSh deposited the remaining 100 BTC (worth approximately $11.88M) into Binance an hour ago, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M (+65%). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948334118823071744</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoForesightNewsA whale deposited the remaining 100 BTC into Binance, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale address starting with 1EGQSh deposited the remaining 100 BTC (worth approximately $11.88M) into Binance an hour ago, with a tot</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948334118823071744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nansen data: In the past 7 days, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea have both surged by over 100%.According to Nansen data, possibly influenced by the upcoming announcement related to the TGE this month, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea has surged by over 100% in the past 7 days. On July 21st, the number of active addresses reached 75,700.00, the highest in nearly four months; the number of transactions on the same day exceeded 200,000.00, the first time in nearly 5 months. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333306109562880</link>
      <description>16 minutes ago吴说Nansen data: In the past 7 days, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea have both surged by over 100%.According to Nansen data, possibly influenced by the upcoming announcement related to the TGE this month, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea h</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333306109562880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVNU Launches Starknet Paymaster, Enabling Developers to Sponsor User Gas Fees in 5 MinutesAVNU, a trading center on Starknet, has announced the launch of Starknet Paymaster, an open-source, production-ready, developer-first method for extracting Gas fees. It allows Starknet developers to sponsor or extract user fees in 5 minutes, accepting any token as a Gas fee. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331432258113536</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoForesightNewsAVNU Launches Starknet Paymaster, Enabling Developers to Sponsor User Gas Fees in 5 MinutesAVNU, a trading center on Starknet, has announced the launch of Starknet Paymaster, an open-source, production-ready, developer-first method for extracting Gas fees. It allows Starkn</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331432258113536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.49% in the past 1H, down 0.19% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331038785626112</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.49% in the past 1H, down 0.19% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331038785626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermBitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range, while the altcoin season index shows an upward trend, indicating that funds are rotating towards mainstream altcoins such as Ethereum, XRP, and Solana, with related assets rising by 20%-40% recently. Ryan Lee pointed out, &quot;The active performance of sectors such as AI, RWA, and Memecoin also shows the market&apos;s strong focus on specific narratives. However, the altcoin season index has not yet broken through the 75% confirmation threshold, and the current market is more likely a phase of rotation rather than a full-blown altcoin season. To drive the market to continue into the mid-to-late third quarter, the key lies in whether Bitcoin&apos;s market share can remain below 60%. At the same time, institutional fund inflows, regulatory benefits, and improved fundamentals in the Layer 1 and DeFi sectors are all important signals to confirm the start of the altcoin season.&quot; [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332610312278016</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyBitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermBitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range, while the altcoin season index shows a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332610312278016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotions from Aug. 1Starting Aug. 1, offering or advertising unlicensed stablecoins to retail investors in Hong Kong could land violators with a $50,000.00 Hong Kong dollars fine and six months in jail.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948330184045826048</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotions from Aug. 1Starting Aug. 1, offering or advertising unlicensed stablecoins to retail investors in Hong Kong could land violators with a $50,000.00 Hong Kong dollars fine and six months in jail.#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948330184045826048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana developers consider increasing block limit by 66% to 100 million compute units to further increase network capacitySolana developers are considering increasing the block limit from 60 million compute units to 100 million compute units via the SIMD-0286 proposal, which would achieve a 66% capacity increase, provided validators opt-in to the upgrade. The proposal aims to further increase Solana network capacity, allowing for more transactions per second to be processed. Compute units are the basic unit of measurement for transaction complexity and resource consumption in the Solana network, and increasing the block compute unit limit will directly enhance the network&apos;s transaction processing capabilities. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332618767994880</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoOdailySolana developers consider increasing block limit by 66% to 100 million compute units to further increase network capacitySolana developers are considering increasing the block limit from 60 million compute units to 100 million compute units via the SIMD-0286 proposal, which woul</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332618767994880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Using Kyrgyzstan Crypto Infrastructure to Evade Sanctions and Fund War in UkraineOn July 24, according to a report by TRM Labs cited by Cryptonews, Russian entities are using Kyrgyzstan&apos;s cryptocurrency infrastructure to bypass international sanctions and procure dual-use goods. The report shows that since Kyrgyzstan passed the Law on Virtual Assets in January 2022, the country has developed into a significant cryptocurrency hub. As of October 2024, the country has issued 126 Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) licenses, and transaction volume has surged from $59.00 million in 2022 to $4.20 billion in the first seven months of 2024. TRM Labs found that several exchanges registered in Kyrgyzstan are actually shell entities, reusing the same addresses and contact information, and have transactional ties to sanctioned Russian organizations, including the Rusich paramilitary group fighting alongside the Wagner Group. After the Russian exchange Garantex was targeted by law enforcement in March 2025, new entities registered in Kyrgyzstan, such as Grinex and Meer, exhibited similar trading patterns. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948329885751119872</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoTechFlowRussia Using Kyrgyzstan Crypto Infrastructure to Evade Sanctions and Fund War in UkraineOn July 24, according to a report by TRM Labs cited by Cryptonews, Russian entities are using Kyrgyzstan&apos;s cryptocurrency infrastructure to bypass international sanctions and procure dual-us</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948329885751119872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK-listed Satsuma Completes Over £100.00M Funding Round, Will Accelerate its Bitcoin Accumulation StrategyUK-listed Satsuma Technology PLC (Tao Alpha PLC) has announced the completion of its second round of convertible bond private placement, with the amount raised significantly exceeding the original minimum target of £100.00M. Satsuma stated that the financing will be used to expand its business and strengthen its Bitcoin adoption and decentralized AI strategy. The relevant convertible bond shares will be applied for listing on the London Main Board market after conversion. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328383770857472</link>
      <description>36 minutes ago吴说UK-listed Satsuma Completes Over £100.00M Funding Round, Will Accelerate its Bitcoin Accumulation StrategyUK-listed Satsuma Technology PLC (Tao Alpha PLC) has announced the completion of its second round of convertible bond private placement, with the amount raised significantly exce</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328383770857472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowMist CISO: Core Administrator of World&apos;s Largest Dark Web Crime Platform XSS.is Arrested23pds, Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at SlowMist, posted on the X platform that the core administrator of XSS.is, the world&apos;s largest dark web crime platform, has been arrested. This platform has been active for a long time and is one of the main trading places for Stealer tools (information stealers) in the cryptocurrency industry. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948327582923034624</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoOdailySlowMist CISO: Core Administrator of World&apos;s Largest Dark Web Crime Platform XSS.is Arrested23pds, Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at SlowMist, posted on the X platform that the core administrator of XSS.is, the world&apos;s largest dark web crime platform, has been arrested</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948327582923034624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bifrost Launches $3.00M Multi-Chain Liquidity Incentive to Drive Polkadot DeFi into a Multi-Chain EcosystemOn July 24th, to open up asset channels between Polkadot and the mainstream multi-chain ecosystem, vDOT/ETH and vDOT/BNB liquidity pools will be officially launched on Uniswap V4 on July 25th, and a 12-month liquidity incentive program with a total of 795,000 DOT incentives will be launched simultaneously. This integration provides DOT with a stable and sustainable liquidity entry point into the Ethereum ecosystem, expanding its actual usability in mainstream DeFi networks. As part of the DeFi Singularity program, the first round of incentives now covers Arbitrum, Base, BNB Chain, and the Ethereum mainnet, and liquidity rewards are simultaneously launched around the vDOT/ETH and DOT/ETH pools. Users can participate in liquidity provision through Uniswap V4 and receive incentives in real-time on the Merkl platform. vDOT is a DOT liquid staking token launched by Bifrost, and currently has a cumulative staked TVL of over $74,000,000.00, widely used in governance, lending, DEX and other scenarios. This round of incentives is seen as an important step in promoting vDOT to become a multi-chain yield-bearing asset, and also brings higher liquidity and DeFi integration potential to DOT. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325752528769024</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoTechFlowBifrost Launches $3.00M Multi-Chain Liquidity Incentive to Drive Polkadot DeFi into a Multi-Chain EcosystemOn July 24th, to open up asset channels between Polkadot and the mainstream multi-chain ecosystem, vDOT/ETH and vDOT/BNB liquidity pools will be officially launched on Uni</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325752528769024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto mining firm Bitzero announces completion of $25.00M fundingBitzero, a crypto mining company backed by renowned investor Kevin O&apos;Leary, has announced the completion of a $25.00M funding round, which it intends to use to expand its business footprint in North America and Europe. The company stated that it will initially use part of the funds to purchase 2,900 Bitmain S21 Pro miners, which are expected to be deployed within 4 to 6 months, increasing annual revenue by approximately $10.00M. Headquartered in Vancouver, Bitzero focuses on using low-carbon energy sources such as hydropower to support high-performance computing and blockchain tasks, and is currently advancing the construction of four new facilities in North Dakota, Norway, and Finland. [TheBlock]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325420419584000</link>
      <description>47 minutes ago吴说Crypto mining firm Bitzero announces completion of $25.00M fundingBitzero, a crypto mining company backed by renowned investor Kevin O&apos;Leary, has announced the completion of a $25.00M funding round, which it intends to use to expand its business footprint in North America and Europe.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325420419584000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK and India sign free trade agreementOn July 24, Bloomberg reported that the UK and India have officially signed a free trade agreement, eliminating tariffs on a number of products including cars and alcohol. The agreement was reached after three years of negotiations. It is the largest trade agreement since the UK&apos;s withdrawal from the EU and the most important trade agreement for India in a decade. According to the agreement, 90% of tariff items exported by the UK to India will be reduced, of which 85% will be completely duty-free within ten years; 99% of tariff items exported by India to the UK will also be reduced. The agreement is expected to increase the output of the UK economy by 4.8 billion pounds per year and bring long-term trade growth to the two countries. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324399509213184</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsUK and India sign free trade agreementOn July 24, Bloomberg reported that the UK and India have officially signed a free trade agreement, eliminating tariffs on a number of products including cars and alcohol. The agreement was reached after three years of negotiations. It is the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324399509213184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsSenseTime announced the placement of 1.667 billion new Class B shares, with expected total fundraising of approximately HKD 2.5 billion, subscribed by international long-term capital Infini Capital. The company announced that it intends to use approximately 20% of the net proceeds from the placement to explore the technological integration of AI and innovative vertical fields, including embodied intelligent robots, blockchain, Real World Assets (RWA), digital assets, and stablecoins, and will consider cooperating with strategic partners to carry out related businesses and obtain qualifications. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324449689866240</link>
      <description>51 minutes ago吴说SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsSenseTime announced the placement of 1.667 billion new Class B shares, with expected total fundraising of approximately HKD</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324449689866240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance alpha is now live with ASPOn July 24, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched ASP. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323539651727360</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoTechFlowBinance alpha is now live with ASPOn July 24, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched ASP. [深潮 TechFlow]$BNBShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323539651727360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treehouse Opens TREE Token Airdrop InquiryDecentralized fixed income layer Treehouse has announced the opening of airdrop queries and is about to launch its TGE. Users who accumulated more than 100 points in its GoNuts Season 1 campaign and passed the Sybil check can receive TREE tokens. In addition, as a reward to long-term users, Treehouse will also provide an additional 100% vault reward on top of the base share. At the same time, Treehose NFT holders will also receive a fixed amount of TREE airdrop rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323444252282880</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoForesightNewsTreehouse Opens TREE Token Airdrop InquiryDecentralized fixed income layer Treehouse has announced the opening of airdrop queries and is about to launch its TGE. Users who accumulated more than 100 points in its GoNuts Season 1 campaign and passed the Sybil check can recei</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323444252282880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>