<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:25:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Volcon Announces Increase of 2,903 BTC, Holding a Total of Approximately 3,183 BitcoinUS-listed electric vehicle company Volcon announced an increase of 2,903 BTC, holding a total of approximately 3,183 Bitcoin, with a total purchase amount of approximately $375.00M, and an average purchase price of $117,697.00. Volcon also sells short-term options to lock in future low-cost coin purchase opportunities and expand its stock repurchase program to $100.00M. Previously, Volcon completed a private placement of over $500.00M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948751105383350272</link>
      <description>3 minutes ago吴说Volcon Announces Increase of 2,903 BTC, Holding a Total of Approximately 3,183 BitcoinUS-listed electric vehicle company Volcon announced an increase of 2,903 BTC, holding a total of approximately 3,183 Bitcoin, with a total purchase amount of approximately $375.00M, and an average pu</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948751105383350272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold fell more than 1.00% during the day and is now trading at $3,334.20/ounceJuly 25, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold fell more than 1.00% during the day and is now trading at $3,334.20/ounce. [TechFlow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948750605623640064</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoTechFlowSpot gold fell more than 1.00% during the day and is now trading at $3,334.20/ounceJuly 25, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold fell more than 1.00% during the day and is now trading at $3,334.20/ounce. [TechFlow TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948750605623640064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury destroyed more than 54 million USDC on the Ethereum chainOn July 25, according to Whale Alert monitoring data, at 22:14 Beijing time, 54,466,955 USDC (equivalent to 54,454,591 USD) on the Ethereum chain were destroyed in the USDC Treasury. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948751109942558720</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsUSDC Treasury destroyed more than 54 million USDC on the Ethereum chainOn July 25, according to Whale Alert monitoring data, at 22:14 Beijing time, 54,466,955 USDC (equivalent to 54,454,591 USD) on the Ethereum chain were destroyed in the USDC Treasury. [PANews]#Layer1$USDC$ETH$MA</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948751109942558720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcon Expands Stock Buyback Authorization to $100.00M to Buy More BTCUS-listed company Volcon (NASDAQ: VLCN) has announced that it holds 3,183.37 Bitcoin (BTC), with a total purchase price of approximately $375.00M and an average purchase price of $117,697.00 per BTC. In addition, the company announced that its board of directors has approved an increase to its existing stock repurchase program. Volcon is now authorized to repurchase up to $100.00M of the company&apos;s outstanding common stock over the next 24 months, increasing its Bitcoin (BTC) holdings when the stock price is below net asset value. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948749864607563776</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoForesightNewsVolcon Expands Stock Buyback Authorization to $100.00M to Buy More BTCUS-listed company Volcon (NASDAQ: VLCN) has announced that it holds 3,183.37 Bitcoin (BTC), with a total purchase price of approximately $375.00M and an average purchase price of $117,697.00 per BTC. In a</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948749864607563776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogpay launches physical card service, $50 activation supports cash withdrawals in over 140 countries worldwideOn July 25, according to official sources, the crypto-financial ecosystem service Dogpay officially launched Visa/MasterCard physical card services, supporting multi-chain asset top-ups such as USDT, ETH, and BSC. Users can apply for just $50.00, supporting POS swipes and ATM withdrawals in over 140 countries worldwide. Dogpay focuses on connecting crypto with the real economy, with services covering Web3 consumer cards, CaaS APIs, merchant acquiring, and enterprise multi-currency accounts. The platform has legal card issuance qualifications, compliantly introducing KYC processes, and serves individual users, global developers, and cross-border merchants. The launch of the physical card service coincides with the start of an event where users can invite friends to waive the card opening fee. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948747601935745024</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoTechFlowDogpay launches physical card service, $50 activation supports cash withdrawals in over 140 countries worldwideOn July 25, according to official sources, the crypto-financial ecosystem service Dogpay officially launched Visa/MasterCard physical card services, supporting multi-c</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948747601935745024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain announces the shortlist for the 10th season of MVB, including 15 early Web3 projectsOn July 25, BNB Chain announced that the 10th season of the Most Valuable Builder (MVB) accelerator program has officially started, with a total of 15 early Web3 projects successfully selected. This season of MVB is jointly hosted by BNB Chain, YZi Labs and CMC Labs, aiming to provide all-round support for start-up projects from financing strategies, token economic design to team building, and promote BNB Chain&apos;s vision of &quot;popularizing one billion Web3 users&quot;. The 10th season of MVB will be launched online, and a two-day offline closing event will be held in New York. The outstanding projects finally selected will have the opportunity to receive investment support from YZi Labs. Demo Day will be held on August 15, and global audiences can watch online. Since its launch in 2021, the MVB program has incubated more than 200 projects, and 16 projects have been selected in the ninth season. Meet48 and Avalon Labs, which were recently invested by YZi Labs, are also from the MVB selected teams. The 15 selected Web3 projects cover tracks such as AI (RICE AI, Whitebridge Network), DeFi (AGNT.Hub, FlashX.ai, Opsin, Sigma Money), DePin (Bitring, ShareX), payment (AEON, Pepay), RWA (Asseto, AXC, DMZ Finance, R2) and decentralized social (dLife). The selected projects will participate in online incubation and offline closing, and the winners are expected to receive investment from YZi Labs. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948746068443676672</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsBNB Chain announces the shortlist for the 10th season of MVB, including 15 early Web3 projectsOn July 25, BNB Chain announced that the 10th season of the Most Valuable Builder (MVB) accelerator program has officially started, with a total of 15 early Web3 projects successfully se</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948746068443676672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Nearly 200 tariff letters will be sent out, with some letters specifying tariff rates of 10% or 15%.According to Jinshi, US President Trump said he will issue nearly 200 tariff letters. Some letters will specify tariff rates of 10% or 15%. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948745324726468608</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoForesightNewsTrump: Nearly 200 tariff letters will be sent out, with some letters specifying tariff rates of 10% or 15%.According to Jinshi, US President Trump said he will issue nearly 200 tariff letters. Some letters will specify tariff rates of 10% or 15%. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948745324726468608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin mining company Cango added 147 Bitcoins to its mining operations in the past week.Bitcoin mining company Cango added 147 Bitcoins in the past week, and the company&apos;s total Bitcoin holdings currently amount to 4,387.1 Bitcoins, equivalent to approximately $260.0 million, and continues to adhere to the &quot;zero sale&quot; policy. In addition, Cango is a key member of the EHS Club and has invested some funds in the EHS Club, an organization that aims to promote the development of decentralized Bitcoin mining. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948745132371492864</link>
      <description>25 minutes ago吴说Bitcoin mining company Cango added 147 Bitcoins to its mining operations in the past week.Bitcoin mining company Cango added 147 Bitcoins in the past week, and the company&apos;s total Bitcoin holdings currently amount to 4,387.1 Bitcoins, equivalent to approximately $260.0 million, and c</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948745132371492864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - Solana Foundation and Ecosystem Partners Release &quot;Internet Capital Markets&quot; Roadmap1. Solana Foundation and Ecosystem Partners Release &quot;Internet Capital Market&quot; Roadmap

Leaders from the Solana Foundation, Anza, Jito Labs, DoubleZero, Drift, and Multicoin Capital have co-authored a roadmap for the &quot;Internet Capital Market.&quot; It proposes a future evolution direction centered on Application-Controlled Execution (ACE), aiming to create the next generation of decentralized, high-performance financial infrastructure. The roadmap points out that the biggest challenge currently lies in market microstructure optimization, with ACE allowing smart contracts to control transaction sequencing with millisecond precision. In the long-term plan, Solana will implement an MCL (Multi-Leader Consensus) architecture to break through the &quot;single proposer bottleneck,&quot; enhance censorship resistance, and achieve synchronized reactions in the global market.

2. OSL Group Plans to Raise Over HK$2.3 Billion Through Share Placement for Strategic Acquisitions and Stablecoin Business Development

OSL Group announced on July 25th on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that it has signed a placement and subscription agreement, planning to raise a total of approximately HK$2.355 billion, with net proceeds of approximately HK$2.336 billion. The funds will be used as follows: 50% for strategic acquisitions, 30% for global and new business expansion (including payment and stablecoin plans), and 20% for general corporate purposes.

3. Matt Hougan: Crypto Four-Year Cycle is Dead, &quot;Sustained Steady Rise&quot; Expected in 2026

Bitwise CIO Matt Hougan stated in an article that &quot;the crypto four-year cycle is dead,&quot; as the traditional forces driving the cycle are weakening, such as the diminishing halving effect, the shift to a positive interest rate environment, and the gradual institutionalization of risk. He believes that longer-term forces such as ETF capital inflows, institutional participation, regulatory advancements, and Wall Street&apos;s entry are dominating the market rhythm. Although there will still be volatility, he is optimistic about the overall performance in 2026 and the years to come. This is more likely to be a &quot;sustained steady rise&quot; rather than a one-time super cycle.

4. Hubei &quot;Backdoor Currency Swap&quot; Fraud Case Sentenced: 103 People Defrauded of Over 77.00 Million Yuan in Virtual Currency

The Yunmeng County Court in Hubei recently issued a final verdict in a virtual currency fraud case. He Mou and 3 others manipulated the price of &quot;D coins&quot; by launching a virtual currency platform with a &quot;backdoor&quot; and illegally swapped and transferred users&apos; pledged assets, causing a total loss of approximately 77.76 million yuan to 103 investors within two months. The court sentenced He Mou and others to fixed-term imprisonment ranging from thirteen years to three years for fraud, and each was fined between 300,000 yuan and 20,000 yuan; the second instance ruling rejected the appeal and upheld the original judgment.

5. Strategy Issues Perpetual Preferred Stock, Raising Approximately $2.474 Billion to Purchase Bitcoin

Strategy announced that it has completed the pricing of 28.01 million shares of Series A Perpetual Preferred Stock (STRC) with variable interest rates, with an issue price of $90.00 per share. It is expected to be delivered on July 29th, raising net proceeds of approximately $2.474 billion. The company plans to use the funds for general corporate purposes, including further purchases of Bitcoin and supplementing working capital.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948744313437831168</link>
      <description>29 minutes ago吴说Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - Solana Foundation and Ecosystem Partners Release &quot;Internet Capital Markets&quot; Roadmap1. Solana Foundation and Ecosystem Partners Release &quot;Internet Capital Market&quot; Roadmap

Leaders from the Solana Foundation, Anza, Jito Labs, DoubleZero, Drif</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948744313437831168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Way to Play Tokenized Stocks: Bybit Launches xStocks with a 150,000.00 USDT Prize Pool EventOn July 25th, the cryptocurrency exchange Bybit launched the xStocks series tokens, sparking a new wave of stock tokenization. Today, they launched a one-month promotion where users can share a 150,000.00 USDT prize pool.

From now until August 15th at 10:00 AM UTC, eligible users can participate in:

1. Token Splash: Deposit and trade xStocks to share a 100,000.00 USDT prize pool.
2. Easy Earn: Stake xStocks to enjoy up to 200.00% APR and principal protection, with a total prize pool of 50,000.00 USDT.

About xStocks: xStocks are tokenized assets backed 1:1 by real stocks, providing users with genuine exposure to the stock market. Bybit currently offers 10 tokens covering technology, financial services, electric vehicles, and blockchain, including AAPLX, NVDAX, AMZNX, GOOGLX, COINX, TSLAX, and METAX.

Key advantages:

*   Fractional ownership lowers the barrier to entry
*   24/7 trading
*   Portfolio diversification
*   Combining stock exposure with DeFi opportunities

See the original link for activity terms and eligibility. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948743056849518592</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoTechFlowA New Way to Play Tokenized Stocks: Bybit Launches xStocks with a 150,000.00 USDT Prize Pool EventOn July 25th, the cryptocurrency exchange Bybit launched the xStocks series tokens, sparking a new wave of stock tokenization. Today, they launched a one-month promotion where user</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948743056849518592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam&apos;s NDA is pushing forward with the construction of a national-level blockchain platform, NDAChain.Vietnam&apos;s National Data Association (NDA) is advancing the construction of the national-level blockchain platform NDAChain to enhance digital security and transparency in key areas such as government affairs, finance, and healthcare. Operated by an agency under the National Data Center, the platform features decentralized identity (NDA DID), encryption, tamper-proof records, and compatibility with international standards (such as GS1 and EBSI Trace). [Saigon Liberation Newspaper]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948741301109669888</link>
      <description>41 minutes ago吴说Vietnam&apos;s NDA is pushing forward with the construction of a national-level blockchain platform, NDAChain.Vietnam&apos;s National Data Association (NDA) is advancing the construction of the national-level blockchain platform NDAChain to enhance digital security and transparency in key area</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948741301109669888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Reportedly Considers New Stimulus Checks: Will Crypto See Another 2020-Style Boom?President Donald Trump is considering a new round of stimulus checks targeting low-income Americans, according to unconfirmed reports. The unconfirmed reports say that the proposal is under review as part of broader economic support plans. Though still a rumor, the move might mirror pandemic-era relief policies that injected billions into American households. What Are Stimulus Checks? Stimulus checks are direct cash payments from the federal government to eligible citizens. They aim to boost spending and reduce financial stress during economic downturns or emergencies. In 2020, under the CARES Act, individuals received $1,200, while joint filers got $2,400. The government followed up with additional rounds in December 2020 and March 2021. Trump’s name was printed on the memo line of the first batch, drawing criticism for politicizing aid. However, the payments helped millions cover essentials—and many others turned to investing. Stimulus Checks and the 2020 Crypto Boom A significant portion of recipients used their stimulus checks to buy cryptocurrencies, especially Bitcoin . Data from Coinbase and Binance at the time showed a spike in $1,200 BTC purchases within days of the disbursements. Retail investors flooded into crypto markets, helping drive Bitcoin from around $7,000 in April 2020 to over $60,000 by April 2021. Altcoins like Ethereum, Dogecoin, and Uniswap also saw parabolic growth in the months that followed. Stimulus-fueled buying coincided with the rise of Robinhood traders, NFT speculation, and the first wave of DeFi expansion. It was a retail-driven phase that brought millions into digital assets. Potential Impact on Crypto in 2025 If a new round of checks is approved, crypto markets could see renewed retail activity. This comes as institutional flows into Bitcoin ETFs have slowed in recent weeks, leaving room for consumer sentiment to move prices. Unlike 2020, the crypto space in 2025 includes more onramps, tokenized assets, and mobile-first investing tools. So, this makes it easier for users to convert stimulus cash into digital assets, especially stablecoins and trending tokens.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948742371462496256</link>
      <description>42 minutes agobeincryptoTrump Reportedly Considers New Stimulus Checks: Will Crypto See Another 2020-Style Boom?President Donald Trump is considering a new round of stimulus checks targeting low-income Americans, according to unconfirmed reports. The unconfirmed reports say that the proposal is unde</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948742371462496256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimism Deploys Superchain Upgrade 16, Supporting Superchain InteroperabilityOptimism has announced the successful deployment of Superchain upgrade 16, which includes smart contract changes to support Superchain interoperability, increased decentralization and security to meet L2Beat&apos;s new standards for Phase 1 chains, and improvements to the OP Stack, including increasing the Gas limit per block to 500M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948740642687827968</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoForesightNewsOptimism Deploys Superchain Upgrade 16, Supporting Superchain InteroperabilityOptimism has announced the successful deployment of Superchain upgrade 16, which includes smart contract changes to support Superchain interoperability, increased decentralization and security to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948740642687827968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale transferred 5953 ETH to Coinbase, worth approximately $22.17M.According to The Data Nerd, Grayscale transferred 5,953 ETH, worth approximately $22.17M, to Coinbase 30 minutes ago. Currently, Grayscale still holds 1.779M ETH, worth approximately $6.63B. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948739733840871424</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoForesightNewsGrayscale transferred 5953 ETH to Coinbase, worth approximately $22.17M.According to The Data Nerd, Grayscale transferred 5,953 ETH, worth approximately $22.17M, to Coinbase 30 minutes ago. Currently, Grayscale still holds 1.779M ETH, worth approximately $6.63B. [Foresight</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948739733840871424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Lummis says US is ‘waking up’ on crypto after historic legislative weekFollowing the passage of key digital asset bills, Senator Lummis says “help is on the way” for crypto innovation in the US and urges developers not to lose faith.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948738518625173504</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsSenator Lummis says US is ‘waking up’ on crypto after historic legislative weekFollowing the passage of key digital asset bills, Senator Lummis says “help is on the way” for crypto innovation in the US and urges developers not to lose faith.#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948738518625173504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed company Mega Matrix completes $16.00 million in private equity financing and officially enters the stablecoin fieldOn July 25, according to PR Newswire, Mega Matrix Inc. (NYSE American: MPU) announced that it has completed a private placement of US$16.00 million, providing a solid capital foundation for its strategic entry into the stablecoin field. The investors in this private placement are mainly crypto funds and industry professionals, which shows the market&apos;s high recognition and confidence in the company&apos;s expansion strategy. The company plans to use the financing funds mainly to build a stablecoin asset allocation system and on-chain income mechanism, and will focus on developing corporate treasury strategies based on stablecoins and governance tokens. At present, Mega Matrix has negotiated with many of the world&apos;s leading stablecoin issuers, and will initiate the configuration of mainstream stablecoins and governance tokens. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948738518805528576</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoPANewsListed company Mega Matrix completes $16.00 million in private equity financing and officially enters the stablecoin fieldOn July 25, according to PR Newswire, Mega Matrix Inc. (NYSE American: MPU) announced that it has completed a private placement of US$16.00 million, providing</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948738518805528576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Guardians Network Completes $5 Million Pre-Seed FundingOn July 25, according to FinSMEs, the decentralized dataset platform Data Guardians Network (D-GN) recently completed a $5.00 million Pre-Seed round of financing. This round of financing was led by droppGroup, Saudi businessman Hamoud Al-Rumayyan and Hub Culture. The company plans to use the funds to expand contributor operations in the Middle East, North Africa, Latin America and Southeast Asia, expand multimodal cutting-edge datasets (including speech, lip synchronization and human emotion mapping), and deepen integration with open source and enterprise-level AI frameworks. D-GN provides compliant, traceable and human-centric AI training data to enterprises and model developers through stablecoin rewards, blockchain transparency and decentralized governance. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948736005536628736</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsData Guardians Network Completes $5 Million Pre-Seed FundingOn July 25, according to FinSMEs, the decentralized dataset platform Data Guardians Network (D-GN) recently completed a $5.00 million Pre-Seed round of financing. This round of financing was led by droppGroup, Saudi business</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948736005536628736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale accumulated 60,000 ETH through FalconX today, worth approximately $226.00MAccording to Ember Monitoring, a certain whale/institutional address accumulated 60,647 ETH through FalconX Global today, worth approximately $226.00 million, at an average price of $3,678.00. In July, many whale/institutional addresses accumulated a large amount of ETH. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948734702022443008</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsA whale accumulated 60,000 ETH through FalconX today, worth approximately $226.00MAccording to Ember Monitoring, a certain whale/institutional address accumulated 60,647 ETH through FalconX Global today, worth approximately $226.00 million, at an average price of $3,678.00. In</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948734702022443008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm case prosecution adjourns, defense begins witness testimonyOn July 25, according to Crypto In America, the criminal trial of Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm was adjourned on Thursday after eight days of witness testimony. The defense immediately began to present evidence, and the first witness was Ethereum developer Preston Van Loon. Van Loon said that Tornado Cash is a tool built to meet privacy needs, designed to protect user identity and transaction security, although some users use it for illegal purposes. In the next three days, the defense will continue to call multiple witnesses to refute the prosecution&apos;s allegations that Storm assisted and promoted money laundering. It is reported that if convicted, Storm faces up to 45 years in prison. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948730970241122304</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsTornado Cash founder Roman Storm case prosecution adjourns, defense begins witness testimonyOn July 25, according to Crypto In America, the criminal trial of Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm was adjourned on Thursday after eight days of witness testimony. The defense immediately bega</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948730970241122304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former BlackRock Head of Digital Asset Strategy Joseph Chalom Joins SharpLink as Co-CEOOn July 25, according to SharpLink’s announcement, Joseph Chalom, former head of digital asset strategy at BlackRock, officially joined SharpLink as co-CEO. Chalom has worked at BlackRock for 20 years and has led the launch of IBIT (managing over $87.00B in assets), ETHA (managing over $10.00B in assets) and BUIDL, the first tokenized treasury bond fund on Ethereum. SharpLink said that Chalom’s joining will help Ethereum become the core of global finance and promote the company to build the most trusted Ethereum vault. The asset is $ETH and the stock code is $SBET. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948728453339955200</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFormer BlackRock Head of Digital Asset Strategy Joseph Chalom Joins SharpLink as Co-CEOOn July 25, according to SharpLink’s announcement, Joseph Chalom, former head of digital asset strategy at BlackRock, officially joined SharpLink as co-CEO. Chalom has worked at BlackRock for 20 ye</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948728453339955200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>