<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:31:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>An institutional user transferred 540,000 SOL from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet.According to whale_alert monitoring, 540,000 SOL (approximately $103.00M) were transferred from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet address. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054322712576</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoForesightNewsAn institutional user transferred 540,000 SOL from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet.According to whale_alert monitoring, 540,000 SOL (approximately $103.00M) were transferred from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet address. [Foresight News]#Crypt</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054322712576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHENA announces $360 million &quot;StablecoinX&quot; PIPE transaction, and the Foundation initiates a $260 million buybackOn July 21, according to Aggr News, ETHENA announced a $360.00 million &quot;StablecoinX&quot; PIPE transaction, and its foundation has launched a $260.00 million open market repurchase plan. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947287152325054464</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsETHENA announces $360 million &quot;StablecoinX&quot; PIPE transaction, and the Foundation initiates a $260 million buybackOn July 21, according to Aggr News, ETHENA announced a $360.00 million &quot;StablecoinX&quot; PIPE transaction, and its foundation has launched a $260.00 million open market rep</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947287152325054464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena will establish StablecoinX and plans to purchase $260.0 million worth of Ena tokens on the open market.According to zoomer, Ethena plans to establish a company called StablecoinX and use $260.0 million to purchase Ena tokens on the open market. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054368849920</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsEthena will establish StablecoinX and plans to purchase $260.0 million worth of Ena tokens on the open market.According to zoomer, Ethena plans to establish a company called StablecoinX and use $260.0 million to purchase Ena tokens on the open market. [Foresight News]#Fundr</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054368849920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Foundation Acquires FAIR3 and BGSCThe BNB Chain Foundation wallet recently completed a new round of asset purchases, using a total of 50,000 USDT to purchase FAIR3 and BGSC tokens. The specific transactions are as follows: 25,000 USDT was used to exchange for 868,592.35 FAIR3, with a transaction price of approximately 0.02878 USDT, and 25,000 USDT was used to exchange for 3,723,999.37 BGSC, with a transaction price of approximately 0.00671 USDT. This operation is part of the BNB Chain&apos;s $100 million incentive plan, which aims to support high-quality projects and promote the continuous development of the ecosystem. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947286745192353792</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoForesightNewsBNB Chain Foundation Acquires FAIR3 and BGSCThe BNB Chain Foundation wallet recently completed a new round of asset purchases, using a total of 50,000 USDT to purchase FAIR3 and BGSC tokens. The specific transactions are as follows: 25,000 USDT was used to exchange for 868</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947286745192353792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched USDT-Margined TA Perpetual Contracts with leverage ranging from 1-50xAccording to the official announcement, Bitget has announced the launch of USDT-margined TA perpetual contracts, with a leverage range of 1-50x. Contract trading BOT will be launched simultaneously. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947285531553714176</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget has launched USDT-Margined TA Perpetual Contracts with leverage ranging from 1-50xAccording to the official announcement, Bitget has announced the launch of USDT-margined TA perpetual contracts, with a leverage range of 1-50x. Contract trading BOT will be launched s</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947285531553714176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitGo Crypto Custody Firm Files for U.S. IPOOn July 21, according to Aggr News, cryptocurrency company BitGo has secretly submitted an initial public offering (IPO) application to US regulators. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284170724364288</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsBitGo Crypto Custody Firm Files for U.S. IPOOn July 21, according to Aggr News, cryptocurrency company BitGo has secretly submitted an initial public offering (IPO) application to US regulators. [PANews]#FundraisingShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284170724364288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>599 Bitcoin transferred to Coinbase Institutional walletAccording to whale_alert data, an unknown wallet transferred 599 Bitcoin to the Coinbase Institutional wallet, worth approximately $70,824,959.00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284253759000576</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoForesightNews599 Bitcoin transferred to Coinbase Institutional walletAccording to whale_alert data, an unknown wallet transferred 599 Bitcoin to the Coinbase Institutional wallet, worth approximately $70,824,959.00. [Foresight News]#Crypto Stocks$MAG7.SSI$BTC$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284253759000576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registration is open for BUIDL_QUESTS 2025, hosted by Amber Group&apos;s accelerator amber.ac, offering over $10.00M in support.Web3 accelerator amber.ac has announced that registration for BUIDL_QUESTS 2025 is now open, offering over $10.00M in funding, liquidity, and ecosystem support. The program is aimed at founders, researchers, and developers, focusing on exploring the future development of AgentFi (a combination of crypto and intelligent agents). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284253800943616</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoForesightNewsRegistration is open for BUIDL_QUESTS 2025, hosted by Amber Group&apos;s accelerator amber.ac, offering over $10.00M in support.Web3 accelerator amber.ac has announced that registration for BUIDL_QUESTS 2025 is now open, offering over $10.00M in funding, liquidity, and ecosyste</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284253800943616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Up 7.45% PremarketMarket data shows that Trump Media &amp; Technology Group&apos;s stock rose 7.45% in pre-market trading and is now trading at $20.06. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283187113938944</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoOdailyTrump Media &amp; Technology Group Up 7.45% PremarketMarket data shows that Trump Media &amp; Technology Group&apos;s stock rose 7.45% in pre-market trading and is now trading at $20.06. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283187113938944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX has launched XTZ and TA perpetual contracts and launched the contract trading party.On July 21, according to the official announcement, Huobi HTX launched XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT perpetual contracts on July 21, with a maximum leverage of 20 times. At the same time, Huobi HTX launched the XTZ and TA contract trading party from 20:30 on July 21 to 20:30 on July 28 (UTC+8), with a total prize pool of up to $20,000.00.
During the event, users who complete the registration and participate in XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT contract transactions with a cumulative effective transaction amount of ≥10,000.00 USDT can share the prize pool based on the transaction amount ranking; new contract users who complete XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT contract transactions will also receive exclusive benefits. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947282575244677120</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoPANewsHuobi HTX has launched XTZ and TA perpetual contracts and launched the contract trading party.On July 21, according to the official announcement, Huobi HTX launched XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT perpetual contracts on July 21, with a maximum leverage of 20 times. At the same time, Huobi H</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947282575244677120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs Co-founder: All 1.866 million S tokens allocated for airdrop have been burned.Sonic Labs co-founder Andre Cronje posted on-chain data indicating that Sonic Labs has just burned all 1,866,256.59 S tokens allocated in the airdrop, worth $754,902.66. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283204008595456</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailySonic Labs Co-founder: All 1.866 million S tokens allocated for airdrop have been burned.Sonic Labs co-founder Andre Cronje posted on-chain data indicating that Sonic Labs has just burned all 1,866,256.59 S tokens allocated in the airdrop, worth $754,902.66. [Odaily]$SShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283204008595456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can PI Recover From Its Demand Drought as Volume Continues to Fall?Pi Network’s token has continued to underperform, trading sideways despite the crypto market’s bullish setup.  While the market rallied last week, with several assets reaching all-time highs and others climbing to multi-month peaks, PI remained in a range. With plunging interest in the altcoin, it shows little momentum to break out of its narrow range. Investor Interest Fades as PI Trades Sideways and On-Chain Activity Drops Currently trapped in a sideways trend, PI  faces stiff  resistance at $0.46 and a firm support level at $0.43. Unlike other assets riding the wave of renewed investor enthusiasm, PI continues to witness declining trading interest, as evidenced by a sharp drop in its on-chain trading volume.  According to Santiment, this has dropped by 21% in the past seven days, signaling waning demand and growing caution among investors.  A drop in trading volume means fewer investors are buying or selling the asset. It signals declining interest, lower liquidity, or  general indecision  in the market.  As with PI, when this happens during sideways price movement, it suggests a lack of strong conviction. Neither buyers nor sellers are dominating, creating a lull in momentum.  In addition, according to data from PiScan, the Pi Network is scheduled to unlock 95 million PI tokens over the next eight days, contributing to the bearish pressure on the token. With traders already wary amid persistent price stagnation and declining volume, the token unlock could strengthen PI’s price stagnation or even trigger a breakdown below support at $0.43. This is because a large influx of tokens like this increases selling pressure, particularly in bearish conditions where demand is too weak to absorb the added supply. PI’s Bearish Streak Deepens — All Eyes on $0.43 Support Level An assessment of PI’s Elder-Ray Index on the daily chart confirms the bearish tilt in market sentiment. The indicator, which gauges the strength of bulls and bears in the market, has posted a negative value since July 12, highlighting a strong  bearish presence.  If the current trend persists, a breakdown below the $0.43 support level appears increasingly likely, opening the door for a retest of PI’s all-time low at $0.40. However, a renewed wave of buying interest could shift momentum. Should demand rebound, PI token price may overcome resistance at $0.46 and potentially rally  toward the $0.50 mark. For token TA and market updates : Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here .</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284068492398592</link>
      <description>31 minutes agobeincryptoCan PI Recover From Its Demand Drought as Volume Continues to Fall?Pi Network’s token has continued to underperform, trading sideways despite the crypto market’s bullish setup.  While the market rallied last week, with several assets reaching all-time highs and others climbin</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284068492398592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOON Foundation has burned nearly 27.70 million SOON tokensSOON Foundation announces the successful burning of 27,695,265 SOON tokens, representing approximately 2.77% of the total token supply, nearing its initial commitment of a 3% burn target. This burn is part of the SOON Recovery Plan. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947280628680773632</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoForesightNewsSOON Foundation has burned nearly 27.70 million SOON tokensSOON Foundation announces the successful burning of 27,695,265 SOON tokens, representing approximately 2.77% of the total token supply, nearing its initial commitment of a 3% burn target. This burn is part of the S</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947280628680773632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed Bit Origin Announces Purchase of 40.54M DOGE at an Average Price of $0.2466Nasdaq-listed Bit Origin announced the purchase of 40.54M DOGE at an average price of approximately $0.2466 as the first operation of its crypto reserve strategy, with DOGE holdings accounting for approximately 0.691 per share. The strategy is supported by previously announced funding of up to $500M. (Globenewswire) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947280676722331648</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoOdailyUS-listed Bit Origin Announces Purchase of 40.54M DOGE at an Average Price of $0.2466Nasdaq-listed Bit Origin announced the purchase of 40.54M DOGE at an average price of approximately $0.2466 as the first operation of its crypto reserve strategy, with DOGE holdings accounting fo</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947280676722331648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soneium Head Meme PCAT Officially Launched on BNB ChainOn-chain data shows that Soneium&apos;s first Meme token, PACT, has been officially deployed to BNB Chain. The PACT token donation event ended yesterday, raising over $3.50M with over 26,000 on-chain addresses. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947278164862717952</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailySoneium Head Meme PCAT Officially Launched on BNB ChainOn-chain data shows that Soneium&apos;s first Meme token, PACT, has been officially deployed to BNB Chain. The PACT token donation event ended yesterday, raising over $3.50M with over 26,000 on-chain addresses. [Odaily Planet Dail</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947278164862717952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COINS Act model law offers blueprint for crypto regulation in IndiaHashed Emergent’s Vishal Achanta told Cointelegraph that COINS Act aims to turn India from a “regulatory minefield” to a destination of choice for the crypto community.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276110362595328</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoPANewsCOINS Act model law offers blueprint for crypto regulation in IndiaHashed Emergent’s Vishal Achanta told Cointelegraph that COINS Act aims to turn India from a “regulatory minefield” to a destination of choice for the crypto community.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276110362595328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yapper Leaderboard to Introduce Reputation Threshold MechanismKaito AI founder Yu Hu announced that the Yapper Leaderboard will launch a reputation threshold mechanism to reduce leaderboard manipulation and improve content quality. The mechanism draws on creator thresholds from platforms such as X, TikTok, and YouTube, and will be launched in the coming weeks. At the same time, Kaito will also introduce the community incentive mechanism gKAITO, allowing users with different levels of contribution to participate in platform revenue distribution. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677495410688</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoForesightNewsYapper Leaderboard to Introduce Reputation Threshold MechanismKaito AI founder Yu Hu announced that the Yapper Leaderboard will launch a reputation threshold mechanism to reduce leaderboard manipulation and improve content quality. The mechanism draws on creator thresholds</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677495410688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders to buy BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX can enjoy 4x trading volume counted towards Alpha pointsBinance has announced that starting from 08:00 on July 22, 2025, orders to purchase BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX will enjoy 4x trading volume counted towards Binance Alpha points. The end date of the promotion will be announced separately. Previously, Binance announced that purchasing BSC Alpha tokens or using the Alpha 2.0 limit order function to purchase other Alpha tokens would earn 2x trading volume Alpha points. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947275961783570432</link>
      <description>49 minutes ago吴说Orders to buy BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX can enjoy 4x trading volume counted towards Alpha pointsBinance has announced that starting from 08:00 on July 22, 2025, orders to purchase BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX will e</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947275961783570432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Announces Bitcoin Holdings Reach $2.00BTrump Media announced that its Bitcoin assets have reached approximately $2.00B, accounting for two-thirds of the company&apos;s approximately $3.00B in liquid assets. The strategy is supported by $3.00B in liquid funds, with an additional $300.00M used for Bitcoin-related options operations, which may be converted into spot Bitcoin in the future. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677700931584</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoForesightNewsTrump Media &amp; Technology Group Announces Bitcoin Holdings Reach $2.00BTrump Media announced that its Bitcoin assets have reached approximately $2.00B, accounting for two-thirds of the company&apos;s approximately $3.00B in liquid assets. The strategy is supported by $3.00B in l</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677700931584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks Profusa signs $100.00M equity credit agreement, launches Bitcoin treasury strategyCommercial-stage digital health company Profusa (Nasdaq: PFSA) announced today that it has entered into a securities purchase agreement (equity credit agreement) with Ascent Partners Fund LLC (&quot;Ascent&quot;) to raise up to $100 million through the issuance of common stock, and will use the net proceeds in full to purchase Bitcoin (which can be used for debt repayment), provided that the company&apos;s cash balance at the time of the equity sale is higher than $5.00 million. Under the terms of the agreement, Profusa has the right to sell common stock to Ascent at a price per share equal to 97% of the lowest volume-weighted average price (VWAP) within 5 trading days after each sale. The upper limit for a single sale is $5.00 million or 100% of the average daily trading volume for the 5 trading days prior to the sale date (whichever is lower). If the company&apos;s cash balance is less than $5.00 million, the net proceeds will be used to first replenish that amount, and the remaining funds will be used to allocate Bitcoin as a core reserve asset. (Business Insider) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947273130993274880</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUS stocks Profusa signs $100.00M equity credit agreement, launches Bitcoin treasury strategyCommercial-stage digital health company Profusa (Nasdaq: PFSA) announced today that it has entered into a securities purchase agreement (equity credit agreement) with Ascent Partners Fund LLC</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947273130993274880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>