<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:21:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Deputy Secretary: Demand for stablecoins will reach trillions of dollarsAccording to Cointelegraph, US Treasury Deputy Secretary Michael Faulkender said that the demand for stablecoins will reach trillions of dollars. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946786243621089280</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsUS Treasury Deputy Secretary: Demand for stablecoins will reach trillions of dollarsAccording to Cointelegraph, US Treasury Deputy Secretary Michael Faulkender said that the demand for stablecoins will reach trillions of dollars. [PANews]#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946786243621089280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers who previously stole over $300 million from Coinbase users purchased another 649.62 ETH, worth approximately $2.31 millionOn July 20, according to on-chain analysis platform Lookonchain (@lookonchain), the hacker who previously stole over $300 million from Coinbase users purchased 649.62 Ethereum (ETH) for $3,561 each, worth approximately $2.31 million, 9 hours ago. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946778610147192832</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoTechFlowHackers who previously stole over $300 million from Coinbase users purchased another 649.62 ETH, worth approximately $2.31 millionOn July 20, according to on-chain analysis platform Lookonchain (@lookonchain), the hacker who previously stole over $300 million from Coinbase user</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946778610147192832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent: The U.S. dollar is about to go on-chainOn July 20th, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent posted on the X platform, stating, &quot;Blockchain technology will power the next generation of payments, and the U.S. dollar is about to be on-chain. Thanks to Trump&apos;s leadership and Senator Bill Hagerty&apos;s important work in Congress, the GENIUS Act will help solidify the U.S. dollar&apos;s position as the global reserve currency for generations to come.&quot; [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946776282295889920</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoTechFlowU.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent: The U.S. dollar is about to go on-chainOn July 20th, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent posted on the X platform, stating, &quot;Blockchain technology will power the next generation of payments, and the U.S. dollar is about to be on-chain. Thanks to Tru</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946776282295889920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: USDT supply on the Aptos network has exceeded $1 billionAccording to DeFiLlama data, the USDT supply on the Aptos network has exceeded $1 billion, growing by 20.4% in the past month. The total market capitalization of stablecoins on the Aptos network is currently $1.41 billion, with a growth of $74.42 million in the past 7 days. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946775862794186752</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoForesightNewsData: USDT supply on the Aptos network has exceeded $1 billionAccording to DeFiLlama data, the USDT supply on the Aptos network has exceeded $1 billion, growing by 20.4% in the past month. The total market capitalization of stablecoins on the Aptos network is currently $1.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946775862794186752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</link>
      <description>Updated  52 minutes agoSoSo Daily Jul. 20 | $SOSO Is Officially Listed on Kraken00:00 / 08:48View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pump.fun Releases CTO Creator Fee Application GuidePumpfun has announced the launch of a Community Takeover (CTO) creator fee application process, allowing eligible projects to redirect fees to a new wallet address. This applies to tokens still bound to the curve or migrated to PumpSwap. Tokens migrated to Raydium before March 20, 2025, are not eligible. Applications must provide clear and undisputed evidence that the current project lacks a responsible party and the community cannot maintain itself. If there is a dispute, the fees will not be adjusted. False applications will be rejected, and Pumpfun will not intervene in subjective judgments. Applicants need to fill out a form, and the team will communicate further or inform them of the results via email. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946773164426457088</link>
      <description>57 minutes ago吴说Pump.fun Releases CTO Creator Fee Application GuidePumpfun has announced the launch of a Community Takeover (CTO) creator fee application process, allowing eligible projects to redirect fees to a new wallet address. This applies to tokens still bound to the curve or migrated to PumpS</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946773164426457088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: More than 29,000 BTC flowed into CEX platforms in the past 7 daysOn July 20, according to the latest data from Coinglass, about 29,671.03 Bitcoins flowed into the CEX platform in the past week. Coinbase Pro had an inflow of 24,971.17 Bitcoins in the past seven days, 10,516.36 Bitcoins flowed into the Binance exchange, and 9,305.23 Bitcoins flowed out of the Kraken exchange. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946771704208879616</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsData: More than 29,000 BTC flowed into CEX platforms in the past 7 daysOn July 20, according to the latest data from Coinglass, about 29,671.03 Bitcoins flowed into the CEX platform in the past week. Coinbase Pro had an inflow of 24,971.17 Bitcoins in the past seven days, 10,516.36 B</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946771704208879616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The address associated with the Pump.fun project deposited 2,000,000,000 PUMP to Binance, worth $12,750,000.00.According to @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, the Pumpfun project&apos;s associated address has deposited 2,000,000,000 PUMP into Binance. The address &quot;58WQi...gv33E&quot; previously received 125,000,000,000 PUMP from the project, of which 25,000,000,000 PUMP were suspected of being used for Wintermute market making, 8,000,000,000 PUMP were deposited into Bybit, and another 2,000,000,000 PUMP were deposited into Binance, worth $12,750,000. It is worth noting that Binance currently only supports PUMP in Alpha and contracts. According to Ai Yi&apos;s analysis, this deposit behavior may correspond to the following possibilities: PUMP will soon be airdropped or have other activities in Alpha; PUMP will soon be listed on the Binance main site spot market; this operation is only to confuse the public. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946768523210977280</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说The address associated with the Pump.fun project deposited 2,000,000,000 PUMP to Binance, worth $12,750,000.00.According to @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, the Pumpfun project&apos;s associated address has deposited 2,000,000,000 PUMP into Binance. The address &quot;58WQi...gv33E&quot; previously received 1</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946768523210977280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Bessent Urged Trump Not to Fire PowellU.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent recently privately advised Trump not to remove Federal Reserve Chairman Powell, citing reasons including: a good economy, the possibility of the Federal Reserve cutting interest rates this year, and the risk of political and legal risks from the removal. Bessent pointed out that Powell&apos;s term expires in May next year, at which time a replacement can be made. His moderate stance contrasts with the more radical attitudes of some officials. Trump called Bessent &quot;reassuring.&quot; [Wall Street Journal]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946765452829454336</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说WSJ: Bessent Urged Trump Not to Fire PowellU.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent recently privately advised Trump not to remove Federal Reserve Chairman Powell, citing reasons including: a good economy, the possibility of the Federal Reserve cutting interest rates this year, and the risk of po</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946765452829454336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 20On this day in 2016, the DAO contract was attacked, and Ethereum underwent a hard fork. The original chain after the fork was renamed Ethereum Classic.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946751981769388032</link>
      <description>2 hours agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 20On this day in 2016, the DAO contract was attacked, and Ethereum underwent a hard fork. The original chain after the fork was renamed Ethereum Classic.#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 02:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946751981769388032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Daily News1. Data: If the funds used to buy a new iPhone each time were used to purchase Bitcoin, the current profit would be $242.00 million;
2. The UK Treasury plans to sell over £5.00 billion in Bitcoin assets to alleviate the fiscal deficit;
3. IMF report states that El Salvador has not made any new Bitcoin purchases since February;
4. Mastercard executive: GENIUS Act brings a &quot;turning point&quot; for stablecoin adoption;
5. WLFI: No tokens from any co-founders, team, or advisors will be unlocked at launch, and there will be no new round of pre-sales;
6. Indian cryptocurrency exchange CoinDCX was robbed of $44.20 million 17 hours ago;
7. CoinDCX: User assets are not affected, and trading activities are operating normally;
8. Analysis: Ethereum is about to usher in a record short squeeze and will soon rise to $4,000.00;
9. Strategy: Bitcoin holdings market cap ranks ninth among S&amp;P 500 companies;
10. Trump: Has asked the Justice Department to release all of Epstein&apos;s jury testimony, only needing court approval.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946744645810057216</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyPlanet Daily News1. Data: If the funds used to buy a new iPhone each time were used to purchase Bitcoin, the current profit would be $242.00 million;
2. The UK Treasury plans to sell over £5.00 billion in Bitcoin assets to alleviate the fiscal deficit;
3. IMF report states that El S</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 02:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946744645810057216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Congressman warns against GENIUS Act, calling it a CBDC Trojan HorseOn July 20, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. Congresswoman Marjorie Taylor Greene said that the GENIUS Stablecoin Act opened a &quot;backdoor&quot; for the government to create a central bank digital currency (under the guise of privately issued crypto tokens). &quot;This bill regulates stablecoins and provides a backdoor for central bank digital currencies. The Federal Reserve has been planning CBDC for many years, which will open the door to a cashless society and digital currencies for you, and an authoritarian government that controls your ability to buy and sell may use these digital currencies against you.&quot; Some critics believe that the line between central bank digital currencies and centrally managed, government-regulated stablecoins is blurred. Bitcoin advocate Justin Bechler wrote in an X post: &quot;The GENIUS Act forces stablecoins to comply with and control CBDCs; functionally the same as CBDCs, but without the scary name.&quot; Saifedean Ammous, author of The Bitcoin Standard, believes that no matter what form it appears, the US dollar is essentially a central bank digital currency that is already subject to state surveillance and is increasingly digital. Jean Rausis, co-founder of the Smardex decentralized trading platform, said: &quot;Governments realize that if they control stablecoins, they control financial transactions.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946741585465503744</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsUS Congressman warns against GENIUS Act, calling it a CBDC Trojan HorseOn July 20, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. Congresswoman Marjorie Taylor Greene said that the GENIUS Stablecoin Act opened a &quot;backdoor&quot; for the government to create a central bank digital currency (under the gu</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 01:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946741585465503744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Home Office Plans to Sell Approximately $7.000 Billion in Seized Crypto Assets to Fill Fiscal GapAccording to a report by the British newspaper The Daily Telegraph, the UK Home Office is working with the police to sell a batch of seized cryptocurrencies to fill a financial shortfall. The total amount of cryptocurrency seized by the police is not yet clear, but a 2018 raid seized approximately 61,000 Bitcoin from a Ponzi scheme case, which is currently worth over £5.4 billion (approximately $7.0 billion), an increase of approximately 20 times since it was seized. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946739388963024896</link>
      <description>3 hours agoForesightNewsUK Home Office Plans to Sell Approximately $7.000 Billion in Seized Crypto Assets to Fill Fiscal GapAccording to a report by the British newspaper The Daily Telegraph, the UK Home Office is working with the police to sell a batch of seized cryptocurrencies to fill a financial</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 01:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946739388963024896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastercard Executive: GENIUS Act Brings &quot;Turning Point&quot; for Stablecoin AdoptionMastercard&apos;s Global Head of Public Policy, Jesse McWaters, stated that the GENIUS Act marks a &quot;turning point&quot; for the mainstream adoption of stablecoins, with the potential to drive institutional participation and promote the development of compliant stablecoins. He believes the bill ushers in &quot;a new era of regulatory clarity and confidence in digital assets,&quot; allowing regulated institutions to issue dollar-backed stablecoins. Several institutions, including JPMorgan Chase, Citigroup, Bank of America, Amazon, and Apple, are already advancing related plans. McWaters added, &quot;Mastercard has been preparing for this moment for a long time.&quot; (DLNews) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946739620710903808</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyMastercard Executive: GENIUS Act Brings &quot;Turning Point&quot; for Stablecoin AdoptionMastercard&apos;s Global Head of Public Policy, Jesse McWaters, stated that the GENIUS Act marks a &quot;turning point&quot; for the mainstream adoption of stablecoins, with the potential to drive institutional particip</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 01:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946739620710903808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian exchange CoinDCX suffered a $44.20 million attack, officials say it will be fully covered by its own treasury reserves.According to on-chain investigator ZachXBT, the Indian centralized exchange CoinDCX is suspected of being attacked, with losses of approximately $44.20 million, which has not yet been disclosed to the public. The attacker&apos;s address initially received 1 ETH through Tornado Cash to initiate the operation and cross-chained some of the stolen assets from Solana to Ethereum. The affected CoinDCX hot wallet has not been publicly marked or included in the current proof of reserves, and needs to be manually attributed through counterparty analysis. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946741914663841792</link>
      <description>4 hours agoForesightNewsIndian exchange CoinDCX suffered a $44.20 million attack, officials say it will be fully covered by its own treasury reserves.According to on-chain investigator ZachXBT, the Indian centralized exchange CoinDCX is suspected of being attacked, with losses of approximately $44.2</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946741914663841792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF report says El Salvador has not made any new Bitcoin purchases, only integrated existing holdingsAccording to TheBlock, El Salvador has not purchased Bitcoin since February 2025, according to a letter signed by the president of El Salvador&apos;s central bank and the Minister of Finance, which was part of a recent International Monetary Fund (IMF) compliance report. This statement contradicts statements from President Nayib Bukele and his Bitcoin office, which claims that the country&apos;s Bitcoin reserves are approximately 6,242 coins, worth approximately $737.00 million, and that it continues to add one Bitcoin per day. Arkham data also supports El Salvador&apos;s record of adding 1 Bitcoin per day, with most of these transfers coming from addresses labeled as Binance or Bitfinex hot wallets. However, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) compliance report suggests that these transaction records may not be new purchases, but rather the Salvadoran government consolidating its existing Bitcoin holdings. The IMF report noted in a footnote: &quot;The increase in Bitcoin holdings in the strategic Bitcoin reserve fund reflects the government&apos;s consolidation of Bitcoin from multiple held wallets.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946740631995346944</link>
      <description>4 hours agoForesightNewsIMF report says El Salvador has not made any new Bitcoin purchases, only integrated existing holdingsAccording to TheBlock, El Salvador has not purchased Bitcoin since February 2025, according to a letter signed by the president of El Salvador&apos;s central bank and the Minister</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946740631995346944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Man, 74, Goes Missing, Suspected Connection to Son&apos;s Crypto Assets; Police Suspect &quot;Crypto Kidnapping&quot;74-year-old Naiping Hou went missing in California on May 4, and police believe the case may be related to his family&apos;s crypto assets. Hou&apos;s son, Wen Hou, is the chief investment officer of crypto investment firm Coincident Capital and claims that over $1.00 million was stolen from his father&apos;s account. He has offered a $250,000 reward for information leading to his father&apos;s whereabouts. [Decrypt]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946717376840396800</link>
      <description>4 hours ago吴说California Man, 74, Goes Missing, Suspected Connection to Son&apos;s Crypto Assets; Police Suspect &quot;Crypto Kidnapping&quot;74-year-old Naiping Hou went missing in California on May 4, and police believe the case may be related to his family&apos;s crypto assets. Hou&apos;s son, Wen Hou, is the chief invest</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946717376840396800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: LINK is now at $18.54According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is up 5.04% in the past 24h. Now at $18.54.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946664539679318016</link>
      <description>8 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: LINK is now at $18.54According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is up 5.04% in the past 24h. Now at $18.54.$LINKShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 20:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946664539679318016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinDCX: User assets are not affected, and trading activities are operating normallySumit Gupta, co-founder of Indian cryptocurrency exchange CoinDCX, posted: &quot;One of our internal operational accounts used to provide liquidity on partner exchanges was compromised due to a sophisticated server intrusion. I confirm that CoinDCX wallets used to store customer assets were not affected and are completely secure. Before sharing further details, I would like to emphasize the following:
-No user funds were affected;
-User assets are completely safe and protected in cold wallet infrastructure;
-All trading activity and Indian Rupee withdrawals are operating normally.
The incident was quickly brought under control by isolating the affected operational account. Since our operational accounts are separate from customer wallets, the risk was limited to this specific account and will be borne entirely by us - from our own reserves.
Our internal security and operations teams are working around the clock with leading cybersecurity partners to investigate the matter, patch any vulnerabilities, and track the flow of funds. We are working with exchange partners to block and recover assets, including launching a bug bounty program soon. Every security incident is a learning opportunity, and we will learn from this incident to further strengthen our platform.&quot; [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946606234411397120</link>
      <description>12 hours agoOdailyCoinDCX: User assets are not affected, and trading activities are operating normallySumit Gupta, co-founder of Indian cryptocurrency exchange CoinDCX, posted: &quot;One of our internal operational accounts used to provide liquidity on partner exchanges was compromised due to a sophistic</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946606234411397120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson says audit report is on track for mid-August releaseThe audit&apos;s release could impact Cardano&apos;s credibility and investor trust, influencing future blockchain governance and transparency standards.
The post Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson says audit report is on track for mid-August release appeared first on Crypto Briefing.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946786845306580992</link>
      <description>12 hours agoCrypto BriefingCardano founder Charles Hoskinson says audit report is on track for mid-August releaseThe audit&apos;s release could impact Cardano&apos;s credibility and investor trust, influencing future blockchain governance and transparency standards.
The post Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946786845306580992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk says xAI is building Baby Grok to offer kid-friendly contentxAI&apos;s focus on kid-friendly content could reshape educational tools, but raises concerns about AI&apos;s role in children&apos;s digital experiences.
The post Elon Musk says xAI is building Baby Grok to offer kid-friendly content appeared first on Crypto Briefing.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946786834418167808</link>
      <description>12 hours agoCrypto BriefingElon Musk says xAI is building Baby Grok to offer kid-friendly contentxAI&apos;s focus on kid-friendly content could reshape educational tools, but raises concerns about AI&apos;s role in children&apos;s digital experiences.
The post Elon Musk says xAI is building Baby Grok to offer kid-</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946786834418167808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>