<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:21:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Security agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) on Binance Smart Chain (BSC), causing losses of more than $600,000. Since the contract is not open source, investigations show that the vulnerability stems from the lack of slippage protection, and the attacker used a fake liquidity pool to harvest TA tokens (0x539ae81a166e5e80aed211731563e549c411b140) and sold them in a legitimate pool for profit. BlockSec Phalcon strongly recommends that users who have authorized the contract immediately revoke permissions to prevent further losses. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsSecurity agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARA Holdings Issues $850.0 million in Bonds to Purchase BitcoinMARA Holdings announces the issuance of $850.0 million zero-coupon convertible bonds, planning to use them to purchase more Bitcoin. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947978313762410496</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoForesightNewsMARA Holdings Issues $850.0 million in Bonds to Purchase BitcoinMARA Holdings announces the issuance of $850.0 million zero-coupon convertible bonds, planning to use them to purchase more Bitcoin. [Foresight News]#Crypto Stocks$BTC$MARAShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947978313762410496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish coffee chain Vanadi Coffee has increased its holdings by 2 Bitcoin, and currently holds a total of 76 Bitcoin.According to NLNico, Spanish coffee chain Vanadi Coffee has increased its holdings by 2 Bitcoin, and currently holds a total of 76 Bitcoin. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977238095400960</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoForesightNewsSpanish coffee chain Vanadi Coffee has increased its holdings by 2 Bitcoin, and currently holds a total of 76 Bitcoin.According to NLNico, Spanish coffee chain Vanadi Coffee has increased its holdings by 2 Bitcoin, and currently holds a total of 76 Bitcoin. [Foresight News</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977238095400960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly impose a 30% tariff on US products worth about 100.00 billion euros (about 117.00 billion US dollars). A spokesman for the European Commission said on Wednesday that as part of the first wave of countermeasures, the EU will combine the already approved tariff list for 21.00 billion euros of US goods and the previously proposed tariff list for another 72.00 billion euros of US products into a package. According to people familiar with the matter, US exports, including Boeing aircraft, US-made cars and industrial products such as bourbon whiskey, will face tariffs matching Trump&apos;s threat of 30%. These people said that the tariffs will be ready to take effect next month, but only if the negotiations break down and the United States implements its tax measures after the August deadline. An unnamed government official said that in the absence of an agreement, Berlin is even willing to support the activation of the EU&apos;s &quot;anti-coercion tool&quot; (ACI). This tool will only be activated if an agreement cannot be reached. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsEU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly imp</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+8) on July 23. At the same time, the relevant tokens will no longer support Simple Earn and flexible lending services. (This news was generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoOdailyOKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares secures MiCA license in France to cement EU presenceIn addition to its leadership in the EU, CoinShares has been actively expanding in the US market since officially entering in 2023, aiming to compete with major industry peers.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974271371907072</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoPANewsCoinShares secures MiCA license in France to cement EU presenceIn addition to its leadership in the EU, CoinShares has been actively expanding in the US market since officially entering in 2023, aiming to compete with major industry peers.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974271371907072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Pastor Couple Charged in $3.40M Crypto Token ScamProsecutors in Denver, Colorado, have announced that online pastor Eli Regalado and his wife, Kaitlyn, have been indicted on a total of 40 counts for allegedly orchestrating a fraud involving the INDXcoin crypto token. The couple is accused of raising over $3.40 million between 2022 and 2023 by promoting the token to religious communities through their self-built Kingdom Wealth Exchange platform. At least $1.30 million of this amount was allegedly used for personal expenses, including home renovations. The indictment states that approximately 300 investors suffered total losses as a result. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974177159450624</link>
      <description>24 minutes ago吴说Colorado Pastor Couple Charged in $3.40M Crypto Token ScamProsecutors in Denver, Colorado, have announced that online pastor Eli Regalado and his wife, Kaitlyn, have been indicted on a total of 40 counts for allegedly orchestrating a fraud involving the INDXcoin crypto token. The cou</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974177159450624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a &quot;buy&quot; rating with a target price of $35.00.According to CoinDesk, Jefferies initiated coverage of Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a &quot;buy&quot; rating and a price target of $35.00 in its latest research report. The report noted that the passage of the GENIUS Act in the United States has improved the crypto regulatory environment, providing a favorable market structure for Galaxy. Galaxy is also expected to benefit from the growing demand for AI data centers by leasing a 393 megawatt data center in Texas. Currently, approximately two-thirds of its company value comes from its data center business. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947973963057008640</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoForesightNewsJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a &quot;buy&quot; rating with a target price of $35.00.According to CoinDesk, Jefferies initiated coverage of Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a &quot;buy&quot; rating and a price target of $35.00 in its latest research report. The report noted that the passage of the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947973963057008640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $1.9 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $1.3 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to join.Data shows that the Ethereum validator exit queue has surged in the past week, with approximately 521,000 ETH (worth approximately $1.9 billion at current prices) waiting to exit the Ethereum network. The number of ETH requested to exit has increased significantly since July 16, and the exit waiting time has been extended to 8 to 9 days, the longest waiting time since the beginning of 2024. At the same time, more than 359,500 ETH are queued to join the network, worth approximately $1.3 billion, with an expected activation delay of approximately 6 days. This situation reflects two opposing forces in the market: on the one hand, some stakers may be choosing to take profits after Ethereum rebounded 162.00% from its April low, leading to a surge in the exit queue; on the other hand, new deposits driven by regulatory benefits and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue, such as listed companies like SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion increasing their ETH holdings and staking. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947972733899444224</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoOdailyApproximately $1.9 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $1.3 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to join.Data shows that the Ethereum validator exit queue has surged in the past week, with approximately 521,000 ETH (worth appro</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947972733899444224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value foundation of the ecosystem, Giants Protocol will advance its originally scheduled phased lock-up plan, locking 90% of the circulating tokens through smart contracts to ensure market stability and token value support. Giants Protocol stated that several international listed luxury goods groups have recently taken the initiative to contact the project team, intending to obtain priority access to its RWA asset on-chain services by holding G tokens. The official statement said: &quot;As traditional luxury assets accelerate on-chain, G is gradually becoming a key bridge connecting Web2 luxury assets and the Web3 protocol layer.&quot; [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoOdailyGiants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value founda</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been partially liquidated, and there is still a floating loss of $266,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyJames Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been p</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Capital to support its Bitcoin funding strategy. The ATM-style financing tool allows Hilbert Group to flexibly withdraw funds in the next 36 months to purchase more Bitcoin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoPANewsHilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Cap</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadian dollars, with funds coming from the company&apos;s existing cash reserves. As of July 22, 2025, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings increased to 28.89, equivalent to 2,889,000,000.00 satoshis. Based on the company&apos;s 206 million outstanding shares, the number of bitcoins held per share increased to 14.01 satoshis, an increase of more than 8.49 times from 1.65 satoshis / share on June 26, an increase of 750.00%. The company&apos;s cumulative investment in bitcoins reached 4.5 million Canadian dollars, with an average holding cost of 155,800.00 Canadian dollars per coin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsCanadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadia</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart money betting on FET? Price presses against key resistance after stealth accumulationArtificial Intelligence Alliance’s FET token is showing signs of strength as it tests a critical resistance zone after a period of accumulation, setting sights on the $1 target. Artificial Intelligence Alliance (FET) token has spent several weeks in a tight range after bottoming out at $0.56 on June 22, forming what appears to be an accumulation base on the daily chart. Recent price action has turned bullish, with FET now coiling just below a key horizontal resistance zone between $0.80 and $0.90 — a level that has rejected multiple breakout attempts in the past. A confirmed break above this area could pave the way toward the psychological $1.00 milestone, which also marked the peak of the previous rally on May 23. Technical indicators support a potential breakout. Despite a recent pullback from the local high of $0.89 reached two days ago, the price remains firmly above the 20-day EMA ($0.79), which appears to have acted as dynamic support during the accumulation phase. Additionally, the momentum indicator MACD has maintained a bullish crossover since June 2025, with the histogram consistently printing green bars. For context, the FET token is the unified native asset of the ASI Alliance, which includes SingularityNET, Fetch.ai, Ocean Protocol, and most recent addition CUDOS. FET’s accumulation may signal that smart money is eyeing the token as a strategic entry point ahead of key product rollouts. Notably, Singularity Finance, the financial arm of the ASI Alliance, recently released its H2 2025 roadmap outlining several key product launches, including AI-powered portfolio tools, diversified yield vaults, and autonomous trading agents that execute trades automatically without requiring users to write code.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965739838803968</link>
      <description>57 minutes agocrypto.newsSmart money betting on FET? Price presses against key resistance after stealth accumulationArtificial Intelligence Alliance’s FET token is showing signs of strength as it tests a critical resistance zone after a period of accumulation, setting sights on the $1 target. Artifi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965739838803968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bedrock Week 4 BR Trading Challenge is now live with a $50,000.00 prize poolAccording to official sources, the fourth week of the Bedrock BR trading challenge is now live, with a prize pool of $50,000. This challenge simplifies the process, allowing users to trade on Pancake&apos;s BR/USDT pool. The event lasts for 7 consecutive days, earning $16,000.00 per day, totaling $160,000.00, but is only available to the first 5000 claimants. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965174387904512</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoOdailyBedrock Week 4 BR Trading Challenge is now live with a $50,000.00 prize poolAccording to official sources, the fourth week of the Bedrock BR trading challenge is now live, with a prize pool of $50,000. This challenge simplifies the process, allowing users to trade on Pancake&apos;s BR</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965174387904512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget partners with Indian Key Opinion Leader Pushpendra Singh to expand the Southeast Asian blockchain and AI ecosystem.Bitget recently joined forces with Indian crypto influencer Pushpendra Singh to support the Blockchain and AI Summit in Malaysia. The summit, co-sponsored by Bitget and the Confederation of Indian Industries Malaysia (CIIM), brought together builders, investors, and industry representatives from India, South Asia, the Middle East, Singapore, and China to discuss the development of blockchain and artificial intelligence. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947963990084227072</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitget partners with Indian Key Opinion Leader Pushpendra Singh to expand the Southeast Asian blockchain and AI ecosystem.Bitget recently joined forces with Indian crypto influencer Pushpendra Singh to support the Blockchain and AI Summit in Malaysia. The summit, co-sponsored</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947963990084227072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yi Feng Investment&apos;s proposal to acquire the Aavegotchi Treasury is opposed by the communityOn July 22, Aavegotchi community members proposed to purchase the DAO treasury (approximately 16.00M GHST) at a 60% discount to the 14-day average price, worth approximately $3.20M. The proposer, Rongming Investment, is a subsidiary of the Chinese equity financing institution Yifeng Investment. The transaction outlined in the proposal would grant Rongming Investment the right to use and market Aavegotchi IP, dissolve the DAO, and distribute the proceeds to active community members. Due to the rejection of over 90% of the community members, and with only over 2.00M GHST tokens participating, reaching only 28% of the required quorum, the acquisition offer will be rejected if the current trend remains unchanged. Voting is scheduled to end on July 25. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962732178903040</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsYi Feng Investment&apos;s proposal to acquire the Aavegotchi Treasury is opposed by the communityOn July 22, Aavegotchi community members proposed to purchase the DAO treasury (approximately 16.00M GHST) at a 60% discount to the 14-day average price, worth approximately $3.20M. The</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962732178903040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAgentAI&apos;s AlphaX attracted over 86K users and saw a 232% increase in trading volume within two weeks of the Sui chain prediction competition.The &quot;Predict2Win: SUI Season&quot; prediction signal interaction competition launched by AlphaX, a community-incubated product of AI Infra project DeAgentAI, has shown remarkable performance in the two weeks since its launch. It has attracted over 86,000 users, generated 732,000 on-chain transactions, and achieved a transaction volume growth of 232.00%. It ranks 16th in the Suiscan project leaderboard, becoming one of the leading projects in the Sui ecosystem&apos;s AI Infra track. AlphaX is an AI-driven price prediction platform launched by DeAgentAI, focusing on providing users with high-precision cryptocurrency price signal prediction services. The platform analyzes market data through AI algorithms to provide prediction signals for mainstream tokens such as BTC, ETH, and SUI, with an accuracy of up to 72.30%. Users can earn points rewards, token airdrops, and other incentives by participating in predictions and completing on-chain interactions. DeAgentAI is an AI Agent network infrastructure project built on multi-chain ecosystems such as Sui, BSC, and BTC, with the core vision of &quot;Make AI Smarter&quot;. The project is committed to empowering on-chain transactions through AI prediction and feedback mechanisms, and has supported over 190.00M on-chain interactions. This Sui chain prediction competition will last until August 31, with a total prize pool of 100,000.00 USDT. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962672766586880</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyDeAgentAI&apos;s AlphaX attracted over 86K users and saw a 232% increase in trading volume within two weeks of the Sui chain prediction competition.The &quot;Predict2Win: SUI Season&quot; prediction signal interaction competition launched by AlphaX, a community-incubated product of AI Infra project</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962672766586880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CertiK Stablecoin Report 2025: What are the top 5 most secure tokens in the stablecoin race?As stablecoin adoption grows more mainstream, so do the security risks associated with them. Which tokens are leading the race in terms of security? The first half of 2025 saw a surge in stablecoin use cases, with a monthly settlement volume rising by 43% to $1.39 trillion. According to the security firm, this rapidly increasing growth in adoption hides the widening gaps in security posture, compliance, and operational risk that still need to be addressed by the community. As a result, CertiK has managed to rank the top fiat-pegged tokens from a security and risk standpoint. The six-item Skynet rating framework assesses each token based on factors including operational resilience, governance strength, fundamental health, code security, market dynamic and community trust. According to the Skynet framework, Tether’s USDT ( USDT ) ranks at number one with an overall score of 94.72. The security firm highlighted USDT’s decision to increase its circulation from $138.00 billion to $154.00 billion in the first half of 2025. In second place is Circle’s USDC ( USDC ) with 93.37. Having secured a MiCA license and completed an IPO, Circle’s token supply increased from $41.00 billion to $61.00 billion. Although it is still slightly behind Tether, CertiK has dubbed it the “fastest growing” major stablecoin. Ranking in third place is the PayPal-Paxos jointly issued PYUSD ( PYUSD ) with a score of 91.47. The token’s market cap has doubled in the first half of 2025. Recent developments for the token include expansions into Solana ( SOL ) and Arbitrum ( ARB ) as well as a rewards program. In fourth place is USDS by Sky with 90.09. The rebranding of DAI into Sky has helped to expand the token into multiple chains. Since its launch on Solana, it has grown to become the fifth largest stablecoin. Ripple’s RLUSD ( RLUSD ) stands at number five with a Skynet framework score of 89.89. Although it still ranks below USDT and USDC in terms of supply and security mechanisms in place, CertiK noted that the token has experienced zero security incidents since its launch. Other notable tokens mentioned in the top 10 include First Digital USD ( FDUSD ), USDG by Paxos, Ethena’s USDe ( USDE ) and USDtb, as well as World Liberty Financial’s own USD1. According to blockchain security firm CertiK, as many as 344 crypto security incidents occurred in the past year. These incidents led to the theft of $2.47 billion worth of crypto assets industry-wide. Though these incidents are not always linked to stablecoins directly, they often bear the brunt of exploits, more so than regular tokens. For instance, First Digital USD saw its price plummet to $0.76 amid rumors about whether or not its reserves were secure. It was only able to recover its $1.00 value after the issuer disclosed audited holdings to prove that its reserves were safe. This case shows just how easily the cookie crumbles when it comes to stablecoins. Due to the nature of fiat-pegged tokens, its reserves are considered sacred in a way that differs to other tokens. One wrong move could result in the 1:1 ratio backed by real currencies to dip and lead to the token’s downfall. CertiK’s report showed that exploits in the crypto space, such as hacks, death spirals, and price depegs, were mostly caused by operational failures compared to technical flaws in the system. According to the study, vulnerabilities in systems where stablecoins are the primary asset made up a large portion of the losses. [CertiK]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947958189059805184</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsCertiK Stablecoin Report 2025: What are the top 5 most secure tokens in the stablecoin race?As stablecoin adoption grows more mainstream, so do the security risks associated with them. Which tokens are leading the race in terms of security? The first half of 2025 saw a surge in</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947958189059805184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, continuing to set new all-time highsAccording to @sankin_eth&apos;s data dashboard, Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, reaching $5.074B USDC, continuously setting new historical highs. Since the beginning of this year, Hyperliquid AUM has grown by approximately $3.00B USDC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947957019994034176</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, continuing to set new all-time highsAccording to @sankin_eth&apos;s data dashboard, Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, reaching $5.074B USDC, continuously setting new historical highs. Since the beginning of this year, Hyperliquid AUM has grown by approx</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947957019994034176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>