<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:19:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Consensys plans to lay off 49 employees, about 7% of its total workforceOn July 22, according to Bloomberg, Consensys, a software company led by one of the co-founders of the Ethereum blockchain, plans to lay off 49 employees, about 7% of its total employees. The reorganization is aimed at boosting the company&apos;s profitability. Consensys recently acquired a startup with about 30 employees, who will remain in office, and the company will continue to recruit new employees. Consensys laid off 20% of its employees last year due to regulatory uncertainty and the macroeconomic environment. At present, the regulatory environment of the US crypto industry has become more relaxed due to President Trump&apos;s re-election, and Consensys&apos; lawsuit against the US Securities and Exchange Commission has been withdrawn. Some crypto companies are adjusting their business structures to prepare for initial public offerings (IPOs). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947662081012813824</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsConsensys plans to lay off 49 employees, about 7% of its total workforceOn July 22, according to Bloomberg, Consensys, a software company led by one of the co-founders of the Ethereum blockchain, plans to lay off 49 employees, about 7% of its total employees. The reorganization is</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947662081012813824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNC Partners with Coinbase to Offer Cryptocurrency Services to ClientsAccording to Bloomberg, PNC Financial Services Group has partnered with cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase to offer digital currency services to its banking clients. Initially, PNC&apos;s wealth and asset management clients will be able to trade cryptocurrencies directly through their accounts without switching platforms. PNC also plans to explore the application of digital assets in areas such as corporate payments and cash management. PNC executives stated that as cryptocurrencies become more prevalent in payment scenarios, they expect to support customers in settling payments with digital currencies in the future. In addition, PNC anticipates that stablecoin-related businesses will be led by industry alliances in the future, and banks will actively participate. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947660641049530368</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsPNC Partners with Coinbase to Offer Cryptocurrency Services to ClientsAccording to Bloomberg, PNC Financial Services Group has partnered with cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase to offer digital currency services to its banking clients. Initially, PNC&apos;s wealth and asset manage</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947660641049530368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Agriculture Committee Postpones Vote on CFTC Chair Nominee, Coordinating to RescheduleCrypto reporter Eleanor Terrett revealed that after the Senate Agriculture Committee removed CFTC Chairman nominee Brian Quintenz and another nominee from the voting list yesterday, committee members are working to reschedule the vote. A staff member said they are seeking to get all 12 Republican members together to push Quintenz&apos;s nomination to a full Senate vote. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947660685928583168</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoOdailySenate Agriculture Committee Postpones Vote on CFTC Chair Nominee, Coordinating to RescheduleCrypto reporter Eleanor Terrett revealed that after the Senate Agriculture Committee removed CFTC Chairman nominee Brian Quintenz and another nominee from the voting list yesterday, commi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947660685928583168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr loss of 3.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has fallen by 3.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.24%, ETH -4.61%, DOGE -4.57%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658988425273344</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr loss of 3.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has fallen by 3.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.24%, ETH -4.61%, DOGE -4.57%.$ETH$ADA$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658988425273344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram&apos;s built-in crypto wallet TON Wallet is now available to 87 million US usersOn July 22, CNBC reported that Telegram&apos;s built-in TON Wallet crypto wallet went live in the United States this week. 87.00 million American users can now send, receive, and manage cryptocurrencies directly in the app without downloading or logging in. The self-hosted wallet supports stablecoin transfers, token exchanges, and zero-fee coin purchases through MoonPay. In 2024, more than 100.00 million users worldwide have activated the wallet, and the United States had previously postponed its launch due to regulatory uncertainty. Telegram&apos;s expansion is expected to intensify competition with platforms such as Cash App and Coinbase. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658751544938496</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoPANewsTelegram&apos;s built-in crypto wallet TON Wallet is now available to 87 million US usersOn July 22, CNBC reported that Telegram&apos;s built-in TON Wallet crypto wallet went live in the United States this week. 87.00 million American users can now send, receive, and manage cryptocurrencie</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658751544938496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sei TVL surges over 50% to $680.0 million, hitting a new all-time highAccording to DeFiLlama data, Sei&apos;s TVL has increased by over 50% to $680.0 million in the past month, reaching a new all-time high. Among them, the largest native application, Yei Finance, has a TVL of $380.0 million, and the lending protocol Takara Lend ranks second with a TVL of $108.0 million. In addition, the number of daily active addresses and new user addresses on Sei have both increased significantly recently. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658701863407616</link>
      <description>15 minutes ago吴说Sei TVL surges over 50% to $680.0 million, hitting a new all-time highAccording to DeFiLlama data, Sei&apos;s TVL has increased by over 50% to $680.0 million in the past month, reaching a new all-time high. Among them, the largest native application, Yei Finance, has a TVL of $380.0 milli</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658701863407616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius Group&apos;s Bitcoin holdings have increased to 200.According to Cointelegraph, Genius Group has doubled its Bitcoin holdings to 200, and plans to increase its holdings to 1,000 by the end of 2025, with a target of holding 10,000 Bitcoin in the next two years. [Odaily 星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658204574142464</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoOdailyGenius Group&apos;s Bitcoin holdings have increased to 200.According to Cointelegraph, Genius Group has doubled its Bitcoin holdings to 200, and plans to increase its holdings to 1,000 by the end of 2025, with a target of holding 10,000 Bitcoin in the next two years. [Odaily 星球日报]#Bit</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658204574142464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>cointelegraph</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold hits $3,420.00On July 22, spot gold continued to climb, reaching $3,420.00 per ounce, its highest level since June 16, and up 0.68% on the day. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947656541276753920</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsSpot gold hits $3,420.00On July 22, spot gold continued to climb, reaching $3,420.00 per ounce, its highest level since June 16, and up 0.68% on the day. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947656541276753920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Roundup - Western Union Explores Integrating Stablecoin Services1. Western Union Explores Integrating Stablecoin ServicesWestern Union CEO Devin McGranahan stated that the company is exploring launching stablecoin services in its digital wallet and plans to establish cooperation channels for buying and selling stablecoins. He pointed out that stablecoins have great potential in accelerating cross-border transfers, improving the efficiency of fiat currency exchange, and providing a means of storing value for countries with unstable economies.2. Fed Chairman Jerome Powell Accused of Perjury Twice, Congressman Requests Criminal ReferralU.S. Representative Anna Paulina Luna submitted a criminal referral request to the Department of Justice, accusing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell of twice committing perjury in testimony and written statements regarding the Fed building renovation project. The incident occurred as conservatives continue to pressure Trump to replace Powell as soon as possible, but Trump said it is currently &quot;highly unlikely&quot; to remove him from office.3. South Korea to Advance &quot;Virtual Currency Short Selling&quot; Legislation, Plans to Introduce Stock Market-Level RegulationSouth Korean financial regulators plan to introduce regulatory standards equivalent to those of the stock market for token lending services provided by the country&apos;s crypto exchanges. Currently, Bithumb offers token lending services up to 400% of the collateral value, while Upbit offers Bitcoin lending services up to 80% of the margin. Financial authorities believe that such services are essentially equivalent to short selling transactions and are considering introducing corresponding regulatory measures in the ongoing second phase of virtual asset legislation.4. Hong Kong Customs Detects HK$1.15B Money Laundering Case Involving Virtual Assets and Cash SmugglingHong Kong Customs has detected a suspected money laundering case involving approximately HK$1.15B through cash smuggling and virtual assets, arresting a 37-year-old local man and a 50-year-old non-local man. Customs stated that the two men are suspected of smuggling cash out of the country and frequently using funds of unknown origin to conduct large stablecoin and fiat currency transactions, with the amounts inconsistent with their financial situation. Customs raided multiple locations today, seizing items such as phones and bank cards, and arrested the two men under the Organized and Serious Crimes Ordinance. The case is still under investigation.5. White House&apos;s First Crypto Policy Report Expected to Be Released to the Public Before the End of the MonthThe White House&apos;s first crypto policy report will be officially submitted on July 22 (local time) and is expected to be released to the public before the end of this month. White House officials have confirmed the relevant timeline. This report is the result of months of collaboration between task force leaders David Sacks, Bo Hines, and senior officials from the Treasury Department, Department of Commerce, SEC, CFTC, and other departments, aimed at implementing President Trump&apos;s January executive order on strengthening the United States&apos; leadership in the cryptocurrency field. The report is expected to include regulatory and legislative recommendations, but the specific content is not yet clear.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947656524801527808</link>
      <description>24 minutes ago吴说Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Roundup - Western Union Explores Integrating Stablecoin Services1. Western Union Explores Integrating Stablecoin ServicesWestern Union CEO Devin McGranahan stated that the company is exploring launching stablecoin services in its digital wallet and pla</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947656524801527808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale Transfers Over 314 BTC to Coinbase Again, Total Value Exceeds $37.50 MillionAt 21:18 Beijing time, two Bitcoin Trust addresses under Grayscale transferred 235.99 and 78.66 BTC to Coinbase Prime, respectively, totaling 314.65 BTC, which is approximately $37.57M at the current price. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658213017276416</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyGrayscale Transfers Over 314 BTC to Coinbase Again, Total Value Exceeds $37.50 MillionAt 21:18 Beijing time, two Bitcoin Trust addresses under Grayscale transferred 235.99 and 78.66 BTC to Coinbase Prime, respectively, totaling 314.65 BTC, which is approximately $37.57M at the cu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658213017276416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Senate Republicans Release Draft Crypto Market Structure Bill, Advancing Regulatory ClaritySenator Tim Scott, along with Cynthia Lummis and others, has released a draft regulatory bill for the crypto market, intending to build upon the &quot;Clarity for Digital Assets Act&quot; (the &quot;CLARITY Act&quot;) passed in the House of Representatives. The draft requires the SEC to adjust regulatory rules based on the characteristics of crypto assets and defines &quot;ancillary assets&quot; to clarify the scope of non-security digital assets, with the goal of forming a legislative consensus by September 30. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947655639887269888</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoOdailyUS Senate Republicans Release Draft Crypto Market Structure Bill, Advancing Regulatory ClaritySenator Tim Scott, along with Cynthia Lummis and others, has released a draft regulatory bill for the crypto market, intending to build upon the &quot;Clarity for Digital Assets Act&quot; (the &quot;CL</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947655639887269888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui ecosystem parallel multi-party computation network Ika will launch its mainnet on July 29.Ika, the Sui ecosystem&apos;s parallel multi-party computation (MPC) network, announced on X that it will launch its mainnet on July 29. In April of this year, Ika announced a strategic investment from the Sui Foundation, bringing its total funding to over $21.00 million. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653240359505920</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoForesightNewsSui ecosystem parallel multi-party computation network Ika will launch its mainnet on July 29.Ika, the Sui ecosystem&apos;s parallel multi-party computation (MPC) network, announced on X that it will launch its mainnet on July 29. In April of this year, Ika announced a strategi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653240359505920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CertiK releases Skynet stablecoin rating report: USDT, USDC, PYUSD, RLUSD lead the packOn July 22, according to the Skynet Stablecoin Panorama Report for the First Half of 2025 released by Web3 security company CertiK, the total global stablecoin supply has exceeded US$250 billion, with a monthly settlement volume of US$1.4 trillion. USDT, USDC, PYUSD, and RLUSD lead in security, market performance, and compliance. The report pointed out that industry risks are shifting from contract vulnerabilities to centralized platform operational errors, and RWA-supported and yield-based stablecoins are developing rapidly, and are expected to account for 8%-10% of the market by the end of the year. The report emphasizes that transparent compliance and risk control will determine the long-term sustainability of the project. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947652124481703936</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoPANewsCertiK releases Skynet stablecoin rating report: USDT, USDC, PYUSD, RLUSD lead the packOn July 22, according to the Skynet Stablecoin Panorama Report for the First Half of 2025 released by Web3 security company CertiK, the total global stablecoin supply has exceeded US$250 billio</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947652124481703936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy has realized 93,191 Bitcoin in book profits this year, worth $11.1 billion.MicroStrategy founder and Executive Chairman Michael Saylor revealed in a post on the X platform that MSTR has generated a book profit of 93,191 Bitcoins so far this year, worth approximately $11.10B. In the first three weeks of July alone, the company realized a book profit of 5,668 Bitcoins, worth $676.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653141197770752</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyStrategy has realized 93,191 Bitcoin in book profits this year, worth $11.1 billion.MicroStrategy founder and Executive Chairman Michael Saylor revealed in a post on the X platform that MSTR has generated a book profit of 93,191 Bitcoins so far this year, worth approximately $11.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653141197770752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Faces $1.3 Billion Unstaking Wave — Here’s What It Could Mean for ETHAs capital continues to flow strongly into Ethereum in 2025—pushing its price above $3,600—the amount of ETH queued for unstaking has also surged unexpectedly. What could this mean for Ethereum’s price trend? Here are some expert insights. Over 350,000 ETH Waiting to Be Unstaked—What’s the Implication? Udi Wertheimer, a prominent investor in the crypto community, raised concerns after discovering that more than 350,000 ETH—worth approximately $1.3 billion—are currently waiting in the unstaking queue. Unstaking allows users to withdraw their ETH from staking smart contracts, turning it back into freely usable assets. A large wave of unstaking could signal potential selling pressure. This is especially true if investors are looking to take profits after ETH’s 160% rally since its April lows. Earlier in 2024, more than 500,000 ETH were unstaked before ETH surged from $2,100 to over $4,000, and later dropped back to $2,100. Where Might This Unstaked ETH Go? Viktor Bunin, OG Protocol Specialist at Coinbase, suggested that this ETH might be moved into internal treasury funds. These funds could serve financial strategies like long-term investment or portfolio diversification. If that’s the case, this isn’t a sign of panic selling—it’s more likely a form of asset management. This could actually help stabilize the market in the long term. Meanwhile, a report from Lookonchain shows that on-chain data indicates around 23 whales or institutions have accumulated 681,103 ETH (worth $2.57 billion) since July 1. And the accumulation hasn’t stopped. In the fourth week of July, more institutions continued to add billions of dollars worth of ETH. What About ETH Being Staked? Udi Wertheimer’s concern may sound alarming, especially when compared to historical patterns. However, it lacks a key perspective: the amount of ETH currently waiting to be staked. Data from ValidatorQueue shows that the ETH queued for staking actually far exceeds the amount queued for unstaking. Since June, this queue has surged, with over 450,000 ETH waiting to be staked on certain days. This reflects continued investor interest in participating in the Ethereum network through staking. Data from beaconcha.in shows that over 35.7 million ETH is currently staked across various protocols. This accounts for 29.5% of the circulating supply . Ultimately, the balance between ETH entering and leaving staking protocols is a critical factor. It helps determine whether the market is facing real selling pressure or simply witnessing strategic reallocation by institutions and individual investors.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947657210784141312</link>
      <description>42 minutes agobeincryptoEthereum Faces $1.3 Billion Unstaking Wave — Here’s What It Could Mean for ETHAs capital continues to flow strongly into Ethereum in 2025—pushing its price above $3,600—the amount of ETH queued for unstaking has also surged unexpectedly. What could this mean for Ethereum’s pr</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947657210784141312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Beast has deactivated its X accountCrypto Beast (@cryptobeastreal) has deactivated its X account. Prior to this, ZachXBT accused Crypto Beast of manipulating the ALT crash, with associated wallets cashing out over $11.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653149691236352</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyCrypto Beast has deactivated its X accountCrypto Beast (@cryptobeastreal) has deactivated its X account. Prior to this, ZachXBT accused Crypto Beast of manipulating the ALT crash, with associated wallets cashing out over $11.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily]$ALTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653149691236352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks open, Dow down 0.08%, S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, Nasdaq up 0.03%On July 22nd, according to Jinshi Data, the US stock market opened with the Dow down 0.08%, the S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, and the Nasdaq up 0.03%. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947650843964887040</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoTechFlowUS stocks open, Dow down 0.08%, S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, Nasdaq up 0.03%On July 22nd, according to Jinshi Data, the US stock market opened with the Dow down 0.08%, the S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, and the Nasdaq up 0.03%. [Techflow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947650843964887040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana validator Somos Axolotl launches Web3-powered conservation in Mexico CityA nonprofit called Somos Axolotl has launched a conservation effort that taps into the Solana community. Crypto ecosystem has a long history of charitable and conservation aims. One such project, Solana (SOL) validator Somos Axolotl, has recently started a conservation initiative in Mexico City, aimed at protecting the endangered Axolotl. Centered around the historic area of Xochimilco, the project combines public sculpture, conservation, and community outreach with the crypto community. Its goal is to restore the habitat for the iconic, but endangered, Axolotl amphibian in the Xochimilco canal system. The project will also use its funds to promote regenerative agriculture for local residents and promote economic opportunity. What is more, all of the funds for the project will come from operating a Solana validator node. Supporters among Solana holders can help the project by staking their SOL with the Somos Axolotl validators. They receive staking rewards, just as with any validator, while also contributing to Axolotl conservation. Notably, Somos Axolotl is currently the only non-profit validator on the Solana blockchain. Interestingly, Solana validator nodes offer a unique opportunity for non-profit groups. Specifically, running validator nodes has high fixed costs of operation. However, once the node is set up, it is very scalable, meaning that it can service a large number of stakers. At the same time, revenues for a validator increase linearly with the amount of SOL staked with them. This means that a large validator can operate at high profit margins, while offering the same service as smaller ones. For this reason, if a validator manages to attract users through a charitable or conservation initiative, it gains a competitive edge against for-profit validators. For this reason, it is possible that more and more non-profits will join the Solana ecosystem, helping secure its network and making it more decentralized.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947647620927475712</link>
      <description>59 minutes agocrypto.newsSolana validator Somos Axolotl launches Web3-powered conservation in Mexico CityA nonprofit called Somos Axolotl has launched a conservation effort that taps into the Solana community. Crypto ecosystem has a long history of charitable and conservation aims. One such project,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947647620927475712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell said nothing about monetary policy in his latest meeting speechFederal Reserve Chairman Powell delivered a welcome speech at a regulatory conference today, but as expected, he did not make any controversial or news-making remarks. Powell did not give any monetary policy hints in his brief pre-prepared speech, nor did he mention the pressure from the Trump administration. This is not surprising, as Federal Reserve officials are in a &quot;quiet period&quot; before the July 29-30 meeting and are not allowed to make public comments on interest rates and the economy. However, he said he welcomed comments on bank regulatory rules and capital issues. &quot;The Federal Reserve is a dynamic institution,&quot; Powell said. &quot;We are willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework for large banks, and I look forward to hearing from today&apos;s participants.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947644441078812672</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsPowell said nothing about monetary policy in his latest meeting speechFederal Reserve Chairman Powell delivered a welcome speech at a regulatory conference today, but as expected, he did not make any controversial or news-making remarks. Powell did not give any monetary policy hints</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947644441078812672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soluna Holdings Completes $20 Million Financing to Advance Green Data Center Project in Kati, TexasOn July 22, according to Business Wire, Soluna Holdings, a Nasdaq-listed company that develops green data centers for intensive computing applications such as Bitcoin mining and artificial intelligence, announced the completion of a new round of financing of US$20.00 million, with Spring Lane Capital participating. The new funds will be used to expand the Kati green data center project in Texas and further expand its Bitcoin hosting business. The project is scheduled to start construction in the third quarter of 2025 and achieve initial power supply and business start-up in the first quarter of 2026. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947642389548257280</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSoluna Holdings Completes $20 Million Financing to Advance Green Data Center Project in Kati, TexasOn July 22, according to Business Wire, Soluna Holdings, a Nasdaq-listed company that develops green data centers for intensive computing applications such as Bitcoin mining and artific</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947642389548257280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>