<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:58:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CITIC Bank Shijiazhuang Branch Lands Industry&apos;s First Purely Online Digital RMB Government Procurement LoanAccording to People&apos;s Daily, China CITIC Bank&apos;s Xiong&apos;an branch has successfully implemented the first inclusive finance pure online digital RMB government procurement loan (&quot;Digital Currency Government Procurement e-Loan&quot;) in the industry. This business is based on the security of blockchain and the colorability of digital RMB, combined with CITIC Bank&apos;s mature internal risk control system. After verifying the authenticity of the government procurement transaction background, it realizes the rapid verification of the loan amount and the entire process of pure online lending. This model effectively links the three parties of the purchaser, supplier, and bank, promotes information sharing and credit transmission, not only provides suppliers with convenient and efficient financing channels, but also strengthens the payment security of fiscal funds and contract performance supervision, and opens up a new path for credit financing in the field of government procurement. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249012424069120</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoForesightNewsCITIC Bank Shijiazhuang Branch Lands Industry&apos;s First Purely Online Digital RMB Government Procurement LoanAccording to People&apos;s Daily, China CITIC Bank&apos;s Xiong&apos;an branch has successfully implemented the first inclusive finance pure online digital RMB government procurement</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249012424069120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP vs. LILPEPE: Potential 1-year returns on a $2,000.00 investmentDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. As institutional money eyes XRP and altcoins regain momentum, traders are weighing stable bets like XRP against high-upside plays like LILPEPE. Table of Contents The crypto market is thawing out once more. As the possibility of an eventual significant interest in the space grows institutional, with XRP as one of the leading forms of altcoin cryptocurrency, investors are assessing how far the benchmark of 2k holdings can be pushed through hypothetical progression.  As the name XRP has easily become one of the most well-known brands in the crypto world, there has been some doubt among traders about whether this is where they want to be when it comes to massive gains in the new cycle. Enter Little Pepe (LILPEPE), a shot-to-success memecoin with actual infrastructure and genuine community interest.  Currently in the final stage of the presale (Stage 6), LILPEPE offers a price of only $0.0015 and is already listed on CoinMarketCap. Although XRP may be a good hold, investors seeking high returns on their investments are now turning to LILPEPE as a more promising investment option. XRP  has been a pillar of the altcoin market for a long time. Being one of the most tested digital assets, it has stood out in the storm of regulations, crashes, and FUD. Most expect the token to reach new all-time highs with the possible release of XRP-backed ETFs.  XRP is currently trading at $2.90 as of mid-July 2025, and the two most common scenarios suggest either returning to its former peak of approximately $3.50 or even surpassing it should ETF demand intensify. That would be a 5x appreciation over its current price – i.e., a $2,000 investment would rapidly compound in a 12-month optimistic horizon to approximately $10,000.  However, to achieve this, XRP would need to capture billions of dollars of institutional capital, and its current large market cap already creates a mathematical drag on a parabolic advance. For traders seeking 20x, 50x, and 100x returns, XRP may not get there soon enough. So, compare that to Little Pepe, the meme token that is fast becoming no laughing matter. LILPEPE has raised more than $6.8 million at merely $0.0015 during Stage 6 of its presale and is already listed on CoinMarketCap, a positive indication of increasing popularity and reach.  Real world functionality is different from DOGE or SHIB through LILPEPE. It is a Layer-2 blockchain-based token that facilitates blazing-fast and cost-free transactions, providing real utility through its Pepe Pump Pad, a security-enabled launchpad for new meme tokens featuring locked liquidity and protection against rug pulls. It is this mix of meme value over serious infrastructure that is exciting early-stage investors.  At that rate, an investment of $2,000 at $0.15 could turn into an impressive figure of $200,000 by 2026, representing a 100-fold increase from the initial investment.  As much as XRP is enjoying the ride of an ETF and boasts institutional hype, the math is plain and simple when it comes to the sheer upper-bound potential of smaller-cap tokens like LILPEPE. This is the reason why traders are rotating:  A penny to a pawn: LILPEPE is a penny (0.0015) that provides an enormous future, considering a minimal investment. With the market cap of XRP standing at over $30 billion, achieving any percentage gains is tough.  Not a hype: Unlike the majority of meme tokens, LILPEPE will have a place in the blockchain through its launchpad. This places it somewhere between a meme culture and actual DeFi infrastructure. Layer-2 benefit: LILPEPE blockchain is low cost and high speed, and is scalable, which is precisely what memecoins, NFTs, and low-gas DeFi are built to do, and will also be popular in 2025-2026.  Viral energy: LILPEPE is going viral with powerful social campaigns, a giveaway of 777k, and an interesting community is already in the competitive spirit of capturing the early buzz of DOGE and SHIB in previous bull markets. The presale cost rises with every phase, and this is why every postponement eats into possible ROI.  No one doubts the fact that XRP is a perfect choice for an investor seeking stability, institutional support, and an established altcoin. However, to anyone who wishes to take a minor commitment and make it a whole lot bigger, LILPEPE is unlike any other in terms of 100x potential, real-life utility, and unparalleled upside potential, starting with the current price points as its foundation. There is a chance of profiting with XRP; Nevertheless, LILPEPE might grant the profits that can change one’s life, but only the early coins can grant them.  To learn more about Little Pepe, visit the website , Telegram , and X .             Disclosure: This content is provided by a third party. Neither crypto.news nor the author of this article endorses any product mentioned on this page. Users should conduct their own research before taking any action related to the company.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247270370234368</link>
      <description>9 minutes agocrypto.newsXRP vs. LILPEPE: Potential 1-year returns on a $2,000.00 investmentDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. As institutional money eyes XRP and altcoins regain momentum, t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247270370234368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINkLink oracle officially supports USD1 price service, empowering the TRON stablecoin ecosystemAccording to official sources, WINkLink oracle has now added USD1/TRX price service to further expand its decentralized data ecosystem and provide a more secure and reliable price source for stablecoin applications on the TRON network. This move will accelerate the infrastructure construction of DeFi scenarios such as lending, synthetic assets, and derivatives, and help the prosperous development of the TRON ecosystem. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247957162348544</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyWINkLink oracle officially supports USD1 price service, empowering the TRON stablecoin ecosystemAccording to official sources, WINkLink oracle has now added USD1/TRX price service to further expand its decentralized data ecosystem and provide a more secure and reliable price sour</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247957162348544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX&apos;s new &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; program premieres today at 20:00: Discussing passions and self-expression beyond market trends.On July 21st, according to official social media news, the new issue of Huobi HTX&apos;s &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; will hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;Starting from the Individual: Beyond the Market, There is Still Love and Expression.&quot; Deep insight outputter Bi Shi Wang, G+ Women&apos;s Power initiator Gigiz.Eth, and other in-depth content creators will be invited to attend and chat about how to persist in expression during the market cycle and how to see oneself outside of the crypto narrative. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947244478092038144</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX&apos;s new &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; program premieres today at 20:00: Discussing passions and self-expression beyond market trends.On July 21st, according to official social media news, the new issue of Huobi HTX&apos;s &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; will hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the them</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947244478092038144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequans increased its holdings by 1,264 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 2,317 BTC.According to NLNico monitoring, French listed company Sequans recently purchased 1,264 BTC, increasing its total BTC holdings to 2,317 BTC. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947242915780907008</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoOdailySequans increased its holdings by 1,264 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 2,317 BTC.According to NLNico monitoring, French listed company Sequans recently purchased 1,264 BTC, increasing its total BTC holdings to 2,317 BTC. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTC$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947242915780907008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merlin Chain Releases Merlin 2.0 - &quot;Hold, Earn, Invest&quot; Reshaping BTCMerlin Chain has announced its new Merlin 2.0, proposing a development direction of &quot;Reinvent Bitcoin: Hold, Earn, Invest,&quot; aiming to expand Bitcoin from a &quot;store of value&quot; to a &quot;yield-generating, deployable core asset.&quot; Merlin 2.0 focuses on three major areas: BTCFi expansion, chain abstraction technology, and AI applications (such as Merlin Wizard), further enhancing the liquidity and utility of BTC in multi-chain ecosystems. It also lowers the barrier to entry for BTC, allowing users to participate in various investment opportunities across chains without having to exchange other assets, conveniently realizing BTC holding, yield acquisition, and liquidity participation. According to previous reports, since the mainnet launch in February 2024, Merlin Chain has promoted the rise of BTCFi, giving rise to several representative projects including Solv, Bedrock, Avalon, and Babylon, with over $3.80B in BTC cumulatively staked on the chain. Currently, the Merlin-related ecosystem contributes approximately $2.00B in BTCFi TVL, accounting for over 20.00%. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237887540219904</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoOdailyMerlin Chain Releases Merlin 2.0 - &quot;Hold, Earn, Invest&quot; Reshaping BTCMerlin Chain has announced its new Merlin 2.0, proposing a development direction of &quot;Reinvent Bitcoin: Hold, Earn, Invest,&quot; aiming to expand Bitcoin from a &quot;store of value&quot; to a &quot;yield-generating, deployable cor</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237887540219904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Central Bank of Morocco Completes Draft Law on Crypto AssetsAccording to Zhitong Finance, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law that would legalize the use of crypto assets. The law ensures &quot;adequate protection for consumers and investors, strengthens market integrity, combats fraud, manipulation, money laundering and terrorist financing, and maintains financial stability.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236660978929664</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoForesightNewsThe Central Bank of Morocco Completes Draft Law on Crypto AssetsAccording to Zhitong Finance, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law that would legalize the use of crypto ass</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236660978929664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Warning Signs Bitcoin May Be Headed for a Cooldown This JulyBitcoin (BTC) has entered its fourth consecutive month of gains. However, it just ended the first red weekly candle of July. While many analysts believe the bullrun may not be over yet, some concerning signals have begun to emerge, hinting at a possible price correction or consolidation. After Four Months of Gains, Is Bitcoin Due for a Breather? These warning signs don’t necessarily mean Bitcoin will reverse, but they serve as early indicators that demand attention before stronger moves or major volatility occur. First, Bitcoin Whale-to-Exchange Flow data shows a significant increase in July. This metric reflects the volume of BTC large holders (whales) send to exchanges, usually implying an intention to sell. According to analyst Darkfost, in the last two market peaks, whale capital inflows exceeded $75 billion, marking the beginning of a correction or consolidation phase. Between July 14 and July 18, 2025, the figure has already reached $45 billion. This sharp rise indicates increased activity from large investors. Darkfost’s view aligns with recent on-chain observations from Lookonchain. Today, Lookonchain reported that a savvy Bitcoin whale sent 400 BTC (worth $47.1 million) to Binance to take profits, with total realized gains reaching $91.5 million. Beyond whale flows, on-chain data shows another signal: Bitcoin’s Coin Days Destroyed (CDD) in July reached a one-year high. CDD measures how long coins were held before being moved. It reflects the sentiment and behavior of long-term holders. A high CDD value suggests long-term holders are moving their coins and are likely to sell them. According to CryptoQuant, the 30-day average CDD in July surpassed 31 million, the highest since April 2024. A previous report from BeInCrypto noted that a spike in this metric often precedes major market corrections. However, on the positive side, it can also be seen as a redistribution to new investors. Finally, changes in the correlation between altcoins and Bitcoin have raised further concern. According to Alphractal, the Altcoin-Bitcoin Correlation Heatmap recently dropped below zero. This shift means that altcoins have outperformed Bitcoin in recent days. However, historical data shows that a low correlation between Bitcoin and altcoins is often a red flag. Since the start of 2025, this indicator has turned negative thrice. The first was in January, followed by a drop in Bitcoin’s price from $110,000 to $74,900. The second time was in May, when BTC fell from $112,000 to $98,500. Now, we are seeing the third occurrence. A recent report from BeInCrypto also highlighted another concerning signal. The Coinbase Premium has decoupled from the Kimchi Premium. This disconnection suggests an uneven bullrun across global regions, primarily driven by strong institutional demand in the US. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947240976196325376</link>
      <description>56 minutes agobeincrypto3 Warning Signs Bitcoin May Be Headed for a Cooldown This JulyBitcoin (BTC) has entered its fourth consecutive month of gains. However, it just ended the first red weekly candle of July. While many analysts believe the bullrun may not be over yet, some concerning signals have</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947240976196325376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn closed positions in various assets, making a profit of approximately $178,000.00 in 6 daysAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, James Wynn has closed his 10x long positions in DOGE and PEPE, as well as his 40x short position in BTC, with a loss of $625,222.00. In the past 6 days, James deposited 1.25M USDC into HyperLiquid and made a profit of $177,675.00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236412231536640</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoForesightNewsJames Wynn closed positions in various assets, making a profit of approximately $178,000.00 in 6 daysAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, James Wynn has closed his 10x long positions in DOGE and PEPE, as well as his 40x short position in BTC, with a loss of $625,222.00. I</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236412231536640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain compliance tools can slash TradFi costs — Chainlink co-founderInstitutional investors will increasingly adopt blockchain-based compliance solutions and tokenized RWAs, Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov told Cointelegraph. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234608521433088</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBlockchain compliance tools can slash TradFi costs — Chainlink co-founderInstitutional investors will increasingly adopt blockchain-based compliance solutions and tokenized RWAs, Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov told Cointelegraph. [Cointelegraph]#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234608521433088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory releases ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutionOn July 21, according to Xinhua Finance, Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory released DeepLink ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutions, which supports cross-domain long-term stable mixed training of large models with hundreds of billions of parameters in multiple intelligent computing centers over a thousand kilometers, such as connecting the intelligent computing centers between Shanghai and Jinan over 1,500 kilometers, and realizing the interconnection and large-model mixed training of intelligent computing centers in Beijing, Shanghai, Guizhou and other places. At present, the DeepLink open computing system of Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory has been deeply integrated into intelligent computing platforms such as China Unicom, China Telecom, SenseTime, and Yidian, achieving stable operation of &quot;1 platform + N chips + X regions&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234435628027904</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsShanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory releases ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutionOn July 21, according to Xinhua Finance, Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory released DeepLink ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology soluti</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234435628027904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum NFT marketplace weekly trading volume reaches $84.03M, highest since mid-to-late February this year.According to @hildobby&apos;s data panel, in the past week (July 14 to 20), the weekly trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market reached $84,029,000.00, the highest point since mid-to-late February this year. Among them, OpenSea reached $40,143,000.00, and Blur reached $25,552,000.00. In addition, on July 21, with the support of CryptoPunks whales&apos; purchases, the daily trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market has exceeded $25,900,000.00, the highest point since February 18 this year. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947232369966862336</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Ethereum NFT marketplace weekly trading volume reaches $84.03M, highest since mid-to-late February this year.According to @hildobby&apos;s data panel, in the past week (July 14 to 20), the weekly trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market reached $84,029,000.00, the highest point since mid-to-</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947232369966862336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC explores Ethereum token standard for compliant securitiesERC-3643 Association president Dennis O’Connell told Cointelegraph the SEC showed “a noticeable shift in tone” and openness to blockchain standards.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230186244427776</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSEC explores Ethereum token standard for compliant securitiesERC-3643 Association president Dennis O’Connell told Cointelegraph the SEC showed “a noticeable shift in tone” and openness to blockchain standards.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230186244427776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Exchange Lists ESPORTS, GP, ERA and Other Perpetual ContractsOn July 21st, WEEX Exchange announced that it has launched Yooldo (ESPORTS), Graphite Protocol (GP), Caldera (ERA), Taker (TAKER), Pump.fun (PUMP), and Eclipse (ES) perpetual contracts. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229440153243648</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowWEEX Exchange Lists ESPORTS, GP, ERA and Other Perpetual ContractsOn July 21st, WEEX Exchange announced that it has launched Yooldo (ESPORTS), Graphite Protocol (GP), Caldera (ERA), Taker (TAKER), Pump.fun (PUMP), and Eclipse (ES) perpetual contracts. [TechFlow]$ERA$ES$PUMPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229440153243648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two institutional addresses sold 25.5 billion PUMPs in one week and made a profit of nearly $40 million USD.On July 21, according to Ember, two addresses that participated in the institutional private placement of pump.fun recently made a total profit of $39.65 million in one week by selling 25.5 billion PUMP (about $141 million). Among them, the D6ar…Lazd address participated in the private placement with $100 million USDC and obtained 25 billion PUMP. In the past week, 13 billion PUMP (about $71.46 million) was transferred to FalconX and flowed to multiple exchanges, making a profit of $19.50 million; the 58WQ…v33E address obtained 12.5 billion PUMP with $50 million USDC, which has been transferred to the exchange, making a profit of $20.15 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229455345012736</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsTwo institutional addresses sold 25.5 billion PUMPs in one week and made a profit of nearly $40 million USD.On July 21, according to Ember, two addresses that participated in the institutional private placement of pump.fun recently made a total profit of $39.65 million in one week by</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229455345012736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QCP Capital: Ethereum&apos;s performance drives the start of altcoin season, with institutions leading this round of gainsIn its market weekly report released on July 21, QCP Capital stated that multiple altcoin season indicators have exceeded 50, reaching their highest level since December of last year. Coupled with the open interest in ETH perpetual contracts jumping from $18.00B to $28.00B in a week, this marks the potential official start of altcoin season. QCP pointed out that the dominant force in this round of the cycle is institutional investors. Benefiting from the clarity in stablecoin regulatory frameworks brought about by the GENIUS Act, corporate finance departments have begun to increase their holdings of L1 public chain tokens such as ETH, SOL, XRP, and ADA, similar to the role of BTC in the fiscal allocations of Strategy and Metaplanet. If ETH obtains SEC approval for its staking spot ETF in the coming months, it may attract funds to shift from BTC ETFs to ETH, further unlocking yield potential. In fact, the daily net inflow of ETH spot ETFs last week has exceeded that of BTC for two consecutive days, showing a surge in institutional interest in ETH, and BlackRock is also confident in its staking ETH ETF. In addition, bullish call spread trading is active in the ETH options market, with large volumes of call spread positions being established for September and December expirations, highlighting the market&apos;s optimism for the fourth quarter. The current BTC market dominance has fallen from 64% to 60%, while ETH&apos;s market share has risen from 9.7% to 11.6%. If the trend continues, a new round of altcoin season may have begun. QCP stated that it will continue to monitor relevant signals and update developments as soon as possible. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230335943331840</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyQCP Capital: Ethereum&apos;s performance drives the start of altcoin season, with institutions leading this round of gainsIn its market weekly report released on July 21, QCP Capital stated that multiple altcoin season indicators have exceeded 50, reaching their highest level since Decemb</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230335943331840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamix to merge with cryptocurrency firm to form Ether MachineOn July 21, according to the Wall Street Journal, blank check company Dynamix is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company, Ether Machine. Sources said the merged company plans to hold more than $1.5 billion in Ethereum. Ether Machine co-founder Andrew Keys will serve as chairman. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947228416285888512</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsDynamix to merge with cryptocurrency firm to form Ether MachineOn July 21, according to the Wall Street Journal, blank check company Dynamix is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company, Ether Machine. Sources said the merged company plans to hold more than $1.5 bi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947228416285888512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigONE launches $8.1 million hacker bounty programOn July 21, according to BigONE’s announcement, in response to the recent theft of encrypted assets, BigONE has officially launched a hacker bounty program with a total amount of US$8.10M, calling on white hat hackers around the world to help track down the stolen funds and identify the attackers. BigONE said that it welcomes security experts to participate in promoting the recovery of stolen assets and the detection of cases. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223567464943616</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBigONE launches $8.1 million hacker bounty programOn July 21, according to BigONE’s announcement, in response to the recent theft of encrypted assets, BigONE has officially launched a hacker bounty program with a total amount of US$8.10M, calling on white hat hackers around the world</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223567464943616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto investment products see record $4.4 billion in weekly inflows, pushing year-to-date total to $27B: CoinSharesGlobal crypto investment products attracted a record $4.39 billion of inflows last week, their strongest tally since CoinShares began tracking the data in 2014, and more than the previous $4.27 billion peak logged last December after the U.S. general election, the firm&apos;s head of research, James Butterfill, wrote on Monday.

The surge — the 14th consecutive week of net buying — lifted year‑to‑date inflows to $27 billion and pushed assets under management to a new all‑time high of $220 billion. Trading activity in exchange‑traded products also hit a peak, with turnover jumping to $39.2 billion.

Market leader Bitcoin was a primary driver of last week’s flows, but Ethereum was the star and notched a 13th consecutive week of capital allocations, according to Butterfill. Funds linked to the world’s second‑largest cryptocurrency pulled in $2.12 billion, nearly double their prior weekly record of $1.2 billion and taking 2025 inflows to $6.2 billion, already eclipsing last year’s total. Bitcoin products gathered $2.2 billion, down from $2.7 billion the previous week, but still sizable enough to keep overall flows at historic levels.

The United States unsurprisingly dominated geographically with $4.36 billion of inflows to funds offered by firms like BlackRock, Grayscale, and Bitwise, while Switzerland, Hong Kong, and Australia contributed a combined $78.7 million. Brazil and Germany logged modest outflows of $28.1 million and $15.5 million, respectively.

Among other altcoins, Solana, XRP, and Sui products attracted $39 million, $36 million, and $9.3 million, respectively, signaling risk appetite beyond the crypto’s two top heavyweights.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222623654268928</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockCrypto investment products see record $4.4 billion in weekly inflows, pushing year-to-date total to $27B: CoinSharesGlobal crypto investment products attracted a record $4.39 billion of inflows last week, their strongest tally since CoinShares began tracking the data in 2014, and</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222623654268928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address holding 50 WBTC is likely to profit approximately $2.404 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, the address starting with 0x2Be is suspected of clearing 50 WBTC purchased in April last year at a cost of only $65,135. If sold, it will profit approximately $2.404M, with a return rate of approximately 83% for holding the position for 15 months. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947221156860022784</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsAn address holding 50 WBTC is likely to profit approximately $2.404 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, the address starting with 0x2Be is suspected of clearing 50 WBTC purchased in April last year at a cost of only $65,135. If sold, it will profit approximately $2.4</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947221156860022784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 10:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>