<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:23:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00MAccording to crypto analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, a certain whale is currently going long on Bitcoin on both the Aave and Hyperliquid platforms, with a total position value of approximately $91.00M and a current floating profit of over $4.223M. Among them, the address on the Aave platform is cyclically going long on WBTC at an average price of $114,272.00, mortgaging 342.21 WBTC, borrowing $20.00M in stablecoins, with a health factor of 1.57, and a current floating profit of $963,000.00; on the Hyperliquid platform, it is using 10x leverage to go long on BTC, with a position amount of approximately $50.93M, an opening price of $109,655.20, and a floating profit of approximately $3.26M. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497104893300736</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoOdailyA whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00MAccording to crypto analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, a certain whale is currently going long on Bitcoin on both the Aave and Hyperliquid platforms, with a total position value</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497104893300736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Diner restaurant has opened to the public, possibly supporting DOGE paymentsTesla Diner is now open to the public. It is equipped with 80 Tesla Supercharger stalls, provides autonomous vehicle pick-up and drop-off for customers, and Tesla humanoid robot waiters. In addition, some community members have revealed that the restaurant may accept DOGE payments. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496919773499392</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsTesla Diner restaurant has opened to the public, possibly supporting DOGE paymentsTesla Diner is now open to the public. It is equipped with 80 Tesla Supercharger stalls, provides autonomous vehicle pick-up and drop-off for customers, and Tesla humanoid robot waiters. In ad</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496919773499392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican real estate company Grupo Murano plans to create a $10.00B Bitcoin vault over five yearsAccording to Bitcoin Magazine, Mexican listed real estate company Grupo Murano has announced that it will take Bitcoin as its core strategic asset, with an initial investment of $1.00B, and plans to establish a $10.00B Bitcoin treasury within five years. CEO Elías Sacal said that Bitcoin is expected to replace the traditional heavy asset model, improve capital efficiency and avoid high interest rate risks. The company is converting its properties into BTC holdings through asset refinancing and sale-leasebacks, and plans to deploy Bitcoin ATMs and accept BTC hotel payments. 70–80% of its business will be allocated to Bitcoin, and the rest will be used for high-margin real estate development. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496472539058176</link>
      <description>5 minutes ago吴说Mexican real estate company Grupo Murano plans to create a $10.00B Bitcoin vault over five yearsAccording to Bitcoin Magazine, Mexican listed real estate company Grupo Murano has announced that it will take Bitcoin as its core strategic asset, with an initial investment of $1.00B, and</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496472539058176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet Launches Exclusive Point Boost Event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2According to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched an exclusive points bonus event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2. By interacting through linking your OKX Wallet, users can enjoy an additional 10% points bonus. Users can participate in the event via the following link: https://portal.kaia.io/mission/epoch2 It is reported that Kaia is a merger of the Klaytn and Finschia blockchains initially developed by Kakao and LINE, respectively. It has the lowest transaction latency in EVM L1, with a 1-second block time and instant finality, enabling a smooth user experience and opening up possibilities for use cases that require near real-time response. OKX Wallet is a leading one-stop Web3 portal in the industry and supports 130+ popular public chains. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497113336434688</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailyOKX Wallet Launches Exclusive Point Boost Event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2According to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched an exclusive points bonus event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2. By interacting through linking your OKX Wallet, users can enjoy an additional 10% points bonus. Us</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497113336434688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fosun International applies to register multiple trademarks such as &quot;Star Coin&quot; in Hong KongFosun International&apos;s Hong Kong-based technology, finance, service, and investment arm, Fosun Wealth International Holdings, has recently registered trademarks in Hong Kong, including &quot;Fosun International Crypto,&quot; &quot;Fosun Wealth RWA,&quot; and &quot;Star Coin,&quot; indicating that Fosun International will strengthen its involvement in the cryptocurrency and virtual asset industry. It is reported that Fosun International has obtained an upgrade to the SFC&apos;s No. 1 license, which allows it to provide virtual asset trading services to its clients through the establishment of integrated accounts on VATP platforms. Previously, Cai Hua, CEO of Fosun International&apos;s Xinglu Technology, stated in May that they were connecting existing customers to a trading system for RWA tokenization products and preparing several asset tokenization projects. (Hong Kong Wen Wei Po) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947494597169270784</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyFosun International applies to register multiple trademarks such as &quot;Star Coin&quot; in Hong KongFosun International&apos;s Hong Kong-based technology, finance, service, and investment arm, Fosun Wealth International Holdings, has recently registered trademarks in Hong Kong, including &quot;Fos</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947494597169270784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: SOL is now at $202.45According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 8.91% in the past 24h. Now at $202.45.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947493444191477760</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: SOL is now at $202.45According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 8.91% in the past 24h. Now at $202.45.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947493444191477760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changpeng Zhao: Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today.According to Business Daily, Changpeng Zhao stated that Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today. &quot;Giggle is small, but it focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947491851171024896</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoForesightNewsChangpeng Zhao: Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today.According to Business Daily, Changpeng Zhao stated that Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today. &quot;Gig</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947491851171024896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito AI to Launch on Capital Launchpad This WeekKaito AI has announced that it will launch Capital Launchpad this week, providing a fundraising platform for community projects. Project teams can combine social reputation and on-chain holdings for distribution. After eligible users subscribe, the remaining quota can enter the FCFS stage. Platform fees will be returned to the community through the gKAITO mechanism. In addition, the official said that KYC is only a regulatory requirement and will be fully managed by Persona. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947490196438405120</link>
      <description>30 minutes ago吴说Kaito AI to Launch on Capital Launchpad This WeekKaito AI has announced that it will launch Capital Launchpad this week, providing a fundraising platform for community projects. Project teams can combine social reputation and on-chain holdings for distribution. After eligible users s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947490196438405120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea to Advance &quot;Virtual Currency Short Selling&quot; Legislation, Planning to Introduce Stock Market-Level RegulationAccording to Edaily, South Korean financial regulators plan to introduce regulatory standards equivalent to those in the stock market for token lending services offered by the country&apos;s crypto exchanges. Currently, Bithumb offers token lending services up to 400% of the collateral value, while Upbit offers Bitcoin lending services up to 80% of the collateral. Financial authorities believe that such services are essentially equivalent to short selling transactions and are considering introducing corresponding regulatory measures in the ongoing second phase of virtual asset legislation. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488457840676864</link>
      <description>36 minutes ago吴说South Korea to Advance &quot;Virtual Currency Short Selling&quot; Legislation, Planning to Introduce Stock Market-Level RegulationAccording to Edaily, South Korean financial regulators plan to introduce regulatory standards equivalent to those in the stock market for token lending services off</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488457840676864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain game developer Delabs Games completes $5.20M Series A funding round, led by Hashed and othersAccording to GamesBeat, blockchain game developer Delabs Games has completed a $5.20M Series A funding round led by Hashed, TON Ventures, and Kilo Fund, with participation from IVC, Taisu Ventures, Arche Fund (Coin98), YGG, Everyrealm, and Jets Capital. The funds raised will be used to promote the continued development of AI-driven Web3 games through the AI game creation platform Verse8, and to support Delabs Games&apos; upcoming game releases. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488053623017472</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoForesightNewsBlockchain game developer Delabs Games completes $5.20M Series A funding round, led by Hashed and othersAccording to GamesBeat, blockchain game developer Delabs Games has completed a $5.20M Series A funding round led by Hashed, TON Ventures, and Kilo Fund, with participati</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488053623017472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institutional investor withdrew 550.0M PUMP and transferred it to Bybit, worth approximately $2.28MAccording to Solscan data, a pre-sale institutional investor: HmKrZg…G8BkKt removed 550.00M PUMP and 2.344M USDC from Pumpfun AMM between 3:46-4:36 UTC+8 today, and then transferred all 550.00M PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $2.285M [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947485294265913344</link>
      <description>50 minutes ago吴说An institutional investor withdrew 550.0M PUMP and transferred it to Bybit, worth approximately $2.28MAccording to Solscan data, a pre-sale institutional investor: HmKrZg…G8BkKt removed 550.00M PUMP and 2.344M USDC from Pumpfun AMM between 3:46-4:36 UTC+8 today, and then transferred</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947485294265913344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western Union plans to integrate stablecoins into its digital wallet productsOn July 22, according to Cryptobriefing, Devin McGranahan, CEO of Western Union, said in an interview with Bloomberg&apos;s &quot;The Close&quot; column on Monday that Western Union sees stablecoins as an opportunity and the company is actively adjusting its infrastructure and expanding partnerships to integrate related technologies into its global payment network. McGranahan pointed out that Western Union, which has a 175-year history, faces three key opportunities: fast cross-border remittances, stablecoin and fiat currency exchange, and providing customers with value storage tools. He added: &quot;We believe that stablecoins are indeed an opportunity, not a threat.&quot; McGranahan revealed that the company has tested new settlement systems in South America and Africa to speed up the remittance process, while exploring the provision of stablecoin services in its digital wallets through cooperation. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484174625820672</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoPANewsWestern Union plans to integrate stablecoins into its digital wallet productsOn July 22, according to Cryptobriefing, Devin McGranahan, CEO of Western Union, said in an interview with Bloomberg&apos;s &quot;The Close&quot; column on Monday that Western Union sees stablecoins as an opportunity a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484174625820672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Police Seize 7 Illegal Crypto ATMs, Arrest Two SuspectsThe UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and the London Metropolitan Police have jointly seized 7 illegal crypto ATMs and arrested two people on suspicion of money laundering and operating an illegal crypto exchange. Therese Chambers, Executive Director of Enforcement and Market Oversight at the FCA, said, &quot;If users operate crypto ATMs or exchanges illegally, they should be prepared to face serious consequences. There are currently no legally operating crypto ATMs in the UK, so using such devices only fuels crime. We will continue to work with law enforcement to combat financial crime and protect consumers.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947483058597023744</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsUK Police Seize 7 Illegal Crypto ATMs, Arrest Two SuspectsThe UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and the London Metropolitan Police have jointly seized 7 illegal crypto ATMs and arrested two people on suspicion of money laundering and operating an illegal crypto exchange. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947483058597023744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Cut losses on PUMP, sideways trading for too long without a breakoutTrader Eugene stated in his personal channel that he has cleared his PUMP position. He pointed out that PUMP has been trading sideways in the 0.004 range for too long and has failed to break upwards. His personal trading logic is no longer valid, so he chose to stop the loss and leave the market. He emphasized that now is not the time to hold stagnant targets. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484521498955776</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrader Eugene: Cut losses on PUMP, sideways trading for too long without a breakoutTrader Eugene stated in his personal channel that he has cleared his PUMP position. He pointed out that PUMP has been trading sideways in the 0.004 range for too long and has failed to break upwards. H</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484521498955776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xingong Green Hydrogen: Promote the &quot;new energy + RWA&quot; strategy and plan to connect 100,000 sets of equipment to the RWA system in the next five yearsOn July 22, according to People&apos;s Finance, the reporter learned from Xingong Green Hydrogen, a subsidiary of Sichuan Jinding (600678), that Xingong Green Hydrogen explored the transformation of three core products into separable and tradable RWA (real asset tokenization) targets through dynamic asset on-chain technology, including mobile storage and charging robots, skid-mounted hydrogen production and refueling stations, and hydrogen power stations. Among them, from the perspective of Tianhydrogen No. 1 TGHD01, through the confirmation of power generation on the chain, the income per kilowatt-hour is automatically settled into stablecoins (such as USDC), realizing the real-time conversion of &quot;green electricity is income&quot;. It is reported that Xingong Green Hydrogen is promoting three major strategic upgrades: it plans to connect 100,000 sets of equipment to the RWA system (including storage and charging robots, electrolyzers, hydrogen drones, etc.) in the next five years, and the estimated scale of securitized assets is tens of billions of yuan; jointly build the &quot;Hydrogen Energy Industry RWA Alliance&quot; with Bosch Hydrogen Power, Junrui Green Hydrogen, Sinopec, China Power Construction and other companies to open up cross-border hydrogen carbon sink trading channels; jointly launch the &quot;Green Hydrogen Income Pass&quot; standardized contract with partners, and apply to the local financial regulatory bureau for the first batch of pilot projects. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947481310822158336</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsXingong Green Hydrogen: Promote the &quot;new energy + RWA&quot; strategy and plan to connect 100,000 sets of equipment to the RWA system in the next five yearsOn July 22, according to People&apos;s Finance, the reporter learned from Xingong Green Hydrogen, a subsidiary of Sichuan Jinding (600678),</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947481310822158336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berachain PoL V2 contracts complete comprehensive audit and go live on mainnetBerachain tweeted that its PoL V2 contract has completed a full audit and is live on the mainnet. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947480552655572992</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBerachain PoL V2 contracts complete comprehensive audit and go live on mainnetBerachain tweeted that its PoL V2 contract has completed a full audit and is live on the mainnet. [Foresight News]#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947480552655572992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoSoMacro|Trump Escalates Trade Pressure on EU as Powell Faces Criminal Charges ThreatU.S.-Europe trade conflict escalates; Trump administration continues pressure on Powell; Russia-Ukraine talks show no clear progress.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947478346549391360</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSoValueSoSoMacro|Trump Escalates Trade Pressure on EU as Powell Faces Criminal Charges ThreatU.S.-Europe trade conflict escalates; Trump administration continues pressure on Powell; Russia-Ukraine talks show no clear progress.#Macro$SOSOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947478346549391360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance will perform wallet maintenance for BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) and opBNB Chain (opBNB)On July 22, according to the official announcement, Binance will perform wallet maintenance on BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) and opBNB Chain (opBNB) at 11:00 (GMT+8) on July 23, 2025. To support this maintenance, Binance will suspend withdrawal services for BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) and opBNB Chain (opBNB) at 11:00 (GMT+8) on July 23, 2025. The maintenance is expected to take 30 minutes, and withdrawal services will be automatically resumed after the maintenance is completed. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947477189184475136</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBinance will perform wallet maintenance for BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) and opBNB Chain (opBNB)On July 22, according to the official announcement, Binance will perform wallet maintenance on BNB Smart Chain (BEP20) and opBNB Chain (opBNB) at 11:00 (GMT+8) on July 23, 2025. To support this</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947477189184475136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 22On this day in 2021, Musk disclosed that he personally holds Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin, and SpaceX holds Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947476733360099328</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 22On this day in 2021, Musk disclosed that he personally holds Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin, and SpaceX holds Bitcoin.#Bitcoin$BTC$DOGE$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947476733360099328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X denies allegations made against it by French authorities, saying the investigation is politically motivated.X&apos;s Global Government Affairs team tweeted that French authorities have launched a politically motivated criminal investigation against X Corp, accusing it of alleged algorithm manipulation and &quot;fraudulent data extraction.&quot; X denies the allegations. &quot;This investigation, incited by French politician Eric Bothorel, seriously undermines X Corp&apos;s fundamental right to due process and threatens the privacy and freedom of expression of our users. French authorities have requested access to X&apos;s recommendation algorithm and real-time data of all user posts on the platform, so that several experts can analyze the data and claim to reveal the truth about how the X platform operates.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947476733368487936</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsX denies allegations made against it by French authorities, saying the investigation is politically motivated.X&apos;s Global Government Affairs team tweeted that French authorities have launched a politically motivated criminal investigation against X Corp, accusing it of alleged</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 02:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947476733368487936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>