<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:45:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>OKX DEX API Now Supports MEV Protection and Transaction SimulationOKX DEX API now features MEV protection and transaction simulation, fully supporting numerous public chains such as ETH, SOL, and BSC. The MEV protection feature proactively prevents sandwich attacks, helping users avoid asset losses caused by MEV. The transaction simulation API allows users to predict transaction results by simulating the transaction execution process before the actual execution, reducing user risk, optimizing transaction costs, and avoiding losses caused by on-chain operation failures. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947152319070359552</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyOKX DEX API Now Supports MEV Protection and Transaction SimulationOKX DEX API now features MEV protection and transaction simulation, fully supporting numerous public chains such as ETH, SOL, and BSC. The MEV protection feature proactively prevents sandwich attacks, helping users</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947152319070359552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget will distribute BTC or ETH interest rate coupons to users participating in the ERA LaunchpoolBitget has launched a follow-up ERA Launchpool event. Users who participate in the BTC or ETH pool of ERA Launchpool between 18:00 on July 18 and 18:00 on July 20 (UTC+8), and whose net BTC or ETH deposit is positive during the period, will be eligible to receive a 10% BTC and ETH wealth management interest rate hike coupon. The interest rate hike coupon will be automatically distributed to the user&apos;s account within 1 business day after the end of the Launchpool. After obtaining it, it must be activated and used within 7 days, otherwise it will automatically expire. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947152327505104896</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoOdailyBitget will distribute BTC or ETH interest rate coupons to users participating in the ERA LaunchpoolBitget has launched a follow-up ERA Launchpool event. Users who participate in the BTC or ETH pool of ERA Launchpool between 18:00 on July 18 and 18:00 on July 20 (UTC+8), and whos</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947152327505104896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch TA, ZKWASM, and AICE spot trading pairs and the TA contract trading pair.On July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs at the following times: Spot trading pair TA/USDT (July 21, 17:20 UTC+8): $TA is the native token of the Trust AI project, dedicated to improving the efficiency and transparency of financial services through artificial intelligence technology. ZKWASM/USDT (July 22, 20:20 UTC+8): $ZKWASM is the native token of the ZKWASM Hub project, which aims to provide strong support for decentralized applications and promote the development of blockchain technology. AICE/USDT (July 23, 18:00 UTC+8): $AICE is the native token of the AICEAN project, focusing on the combination of artificial intelligence and blockchain to provide innovative solutions and services. Contract trading pair TA/USDT (July 21, 17:00 UTC+8): $TA is the contract trading of the Trust AI project, supporting up to 50x leverage trading, providing investors with flexible trading strategy choices, and helping users obtain profits in market fluctuations. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947148763105873920</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch TA, ZKWASM, and AICE spot trading pairs and the TA contract trading pair.On July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs at the following times: Spot trading pair TA/USDT (July 21, 17:20 UT</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947148763105873920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Will List Coresky (CSKY)Bitget will list Coresky (CSKY) in the Innovation Zone and Meme Zone. The deposit channel is now open, the withdrawal channel will open on July 22 at 21:00, and trading will open today at 20:00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947147091835113472</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Will List Coresky (CSKY)Bitget will list Coresky (CSKY) in the Innovation Zone and Meme Zone. The deposit channel is now open, the withdrawal channel will open on July 22 at 21:00, and trading will open today at 20:00. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947147091835113472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit Will List Trusta AI (TA)Bybit will list Trusta AI (TA). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947145836828053504</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoForesightNewsBybit Will List Trusta AI (TA)Bybit will list Trusta AI (TA). [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947145836828053504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minsheng Securities: Stablecoins are expected to help traditional financial assets conduct &quot;on-chain&quot; transactions.According to Sina Finance, Minsheng Securities stated that, in the short term, cross-border payment scenarios are expected to become an important application scenario for stablecoin adoption. Stablecoins are expected to help improve the efficiency of cross-border payments and reduce cross-border payment costs. Fintech companies related to cross-border payments are expected to continue to benefit, and LianLian DigiTech is recommended for close attention. In the long term, stablecoins are expected to promote virtual asset trading and RWA, STO. Stablecoins are expected to help traditional financial assets conduct &quot;on-chain&quot; transactions. Chinese securities firms are accelerating their layout, such as Guotai Junan International upgrading its virtual asset trading license, and GF Securities has fully connected to HashKey Chain as its core on-chain issuance network and issued its first daily redeemable tokenized security, GF Token. Leading securities firms and exchange targets are expected to benefit more from stablecoin development. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947145836878385152</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsMinsheng Securities: Stablecoins are expected to help traditional financial assets conduct &quot;on-chain&quot; transactions.According to Sina Finance, Minsheng Securities stated that, in the short term, cross-border payment scenarios are expected to become an important application</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 04:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947145836878385152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMart officially launches its Chinese name &quot;币市&quot; (Bì Shì), accelerating its global localization strategy.BitMart has announced the official launch of its new Chinese brand name, &quot;币市&quot; (Bì Shì), and has simultaneously introduced a new brand mascot. Since its establishment in 2017, BitMart has provided services to over ten million users in nearly 200 countries and regions worldwide. The platform now offers over 1,700 spot trading pairs and more than 400 perpetual contracts. In conjunction with the brand upgrade, 币市 (BitMart) will soon launch a series of activities and exclusive services for Chinese users, and will continue to increase investment in the Asia-Pacific region. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947134705090711552</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitMart officially launches its Chinese name &quot;币市&quot; (Bì Shì), accelerating its global localization strategy.BitMart has announced the official launch of its new Chinese brand name, &quot;币市&quot; (Bì Shì), and has simultaneously introduced a new brand mascot. Since its establishment in 2017, Bit</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947134705090711552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMart Futures will soon list TAUSDTAccording to the official announcement, BitMart Futures will launch the TAUSDT perpetual contract on July 21, 2025, at 15:30 (UTC+8), supporting a maximum leverage of 50x. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947134713533845504</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitMart Futures will soon list TAUSDTAccording to the official announcement, BitMart Futures will launch the TAUSDT perpetual contract on July 21, 2025, at 15:30 (UTC+8), supporting a maximum leverage of 50x. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947134713533845504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: SOL is now at $186.28According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 5.02% in the past 24h. Now at $186.28.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947131047962435584</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: SOL is now at $186.28According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 5.02% in the past 24h. Now at $186.28.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947131047962435584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui ecosystem launches BTCFi series of events, participate to win rich rewardsOn July 21, the Sui ecosystem launched a BTCFi series of activities where users holding any BTC-backed assets can earn rewards by completing tasks, including: SatLayer platform xBTC event: From July 9 to October 1, 2025, deposit xBTC on SatLayer to earn satXBTC and earn more rewards; Bluefin tBTC Galxe event: From July 9 to July 23, 2025, complete tasks to win a $5,000.00 prize pool; OKX Wallet Cryptopedia event (Season 36): From June 26 to August 24, 2025, participate in the event to learn how Sui native DeFi works, and complete some simple tasks to get rewards; xBTC Phase 1: From June 24 to August 27, 2025, deposit xBTC, USDC, or SUI on the NAVI or Momentum platform to receive specific event rewards; Lombard Luminary Program: Users can stake BTC on the Lombard platform to earn LBTC and earn rewards; wBTC: Bridge wBTC to Sui via Sui Bridge and participate in Sui DeFi to earn income. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947129640829341696</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowSui ecosystem launches BTCFi series of events, participate to win rich rewardsOn July 21, the Sui ecosystem launched a BTCFi series of activities where users holding any BTC-backed assets can earn rewards by completing tasks, including: SatLayer platform xBTC event: From July 9 to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947129640829341696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Token Unlocks This WeekAccording to Tokenomist, single large unlocks (unlock amount greater than $5.00M) in the next 7 days include AVAIL, VENOM, ALT, SAHARA, SOON, etc.; linear large unlocks (single-day unlock amount greater than $1.00M) in the next 7 days include SOL, WLD, Trump, TIA, DOGE, TAO, AVAX, SUI, DOT, IP, MORPHO, SEI, ETHFI, JTO, NEAR, ENS, FIL, etc., with a total unlock value of over $442.00M.
 [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130627933622272</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Large Token Unlocks This WeekAccording to Tokenomist, single large unlocks (unlock amount greater than $5.00M) in the next 7 days include AVAIL, VENOM, ALT, SAHARA, SOON, etc.; linear large unlocks (single-day unlock amount greater than $1.00M) in the next 7 days include SOL, WLD, Trump,</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130627933622272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: $372.00 million liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with $208.00 million in short positions liquidatedAccording to Coinglass data, approximately $372.00M was liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with long positions accounting for $164.00M and short positions accounting for $208.00M. Among them, Bitcoin liquidations amounted to $41.50M, and Ethereum liquidations amounted to $150.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130718052438016</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsData: $372.00 million liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with $208.00 million in short positions liquidatedAccording to Coinglass data, approximately $372.00M was liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with long positions accounting</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130718052438016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum spot ETFs saw net inflows of $2.18B last week, a new all-time high for weekly net inflows.SoSoValue data shows that Ethereum spot ETFs saw a net inflow of $2.18B during last week&apos;s trading days (Eastern Time, July 14 to July 18). The Ethereum spot ETF with the largest net inflow last week was Blackrock&apos;s ETF ETHA, with a weekly net inflow of $1.76B, and the total historical net inflow of ETHA currently reaches $8.06B. The second largest was Grayscale&apos;s Ethereum Mini Trust ETF ETH, with a weekly net inflow of $202.00M, and the total historical net inflow of ETH currently reaches $1.03B. It is worth noting that all nine Ethereum ETFs saw net inflows last week, among which the weekly net inflows of ETHA and ETH both hit record highs. As of press time, the total net asset value of Ethereum spot ETFs is $18.37B, the ETF net asset ratio (market value as a percentage of the total market value of Ethereum) reaches 4.19%, and the cumulative historical net inflow has reached $7.49B. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947142262647705600</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyEthereum spot ETFs saw net inflows of $2.18B last week, a new all-time high for weekly net inflows.SoSoValue data shows that Ethereum spot ETFs saw a net inflow of $2.18B during last week&apos;s trading days (Eastern Time, July 14 to July 18). The Ethereum spot ETF with the largest net in</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947142262647705600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Founder: Over 1 Million GPUs to be Deployed Before Year-EndOpenAI founder Sam Altman tweeted, &quot;We will deploy over 1 million GPUs by the end of this year. I am very proud of the team, but now they better figure out how to increase that number by 100x.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947140781378916352</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsOpenAI Founder: Over 1 Million GPUs to be Deployed Before Year-EndOpenAI founder Sam Altman tweeted, &quot;We will deploy over 1 million GPUs by the end of this year. I am very proud of the team, but now they better figure out how to increase that number by 100x.&quot; [Foresight News]S</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947140781378916352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK working to sell $7B in seized Bitcoin to boost budget: ReportA new report suggests the UK Treasury is working to sell up to $7 billion worth of seized Bitcoin, but one person has slammed the report as “sensationalism” amid a crypto bull run.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947140382760652800</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUK working to sell $7B in seized Bitcoin to boost budget: ReportA new report suggests the UK Treasury is working to sell up to $7 billion worth of seized Bitcoin, but one person has slammed the report as “sensationalism” amid a crypto bull run.#Bitcoin$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947140382760652800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale used high leverage to long ETH, BTC, HYPE, and PEPE, and is currently showing a floating profit of $1.14M.According to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale (0x4a20) on Hyperliquid is using leverage to long ETH (25x), BTC (40x), HYPE (10x), and PEPE (10x). The total position size of this address on Hyperliquid is approximately $121.00M, with a current floating profit of $1.14M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947142271074062336</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA certain whale used high leverage to long ETH, BTC, HYPE, and PEPE, and is currently showing a floating profit of $1.14M.According to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale (0x4a20) on Hyperliquid is using leverage to long ETH (25x), BTC (40x), HYPE (10x), and PEPE (10x). The total positio</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947142271074062336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale made a total profit of $73.66 million on Hyperliquid, and its long positions included ETH, BTC, HYPE and PEPEOn July 21, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the total profit of the whale 0x4a20 on Hyperliquid reached $73.66 million. The current long positions are: ETH (25x leverage), BTC (40x leverage), HYPE (10x leverage) and PEPE (10x leverage), all of which use the highest leverage configuration. Total position size: $121.00 million. Unrealized profit: $1.14 million [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947138758273159168</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsA whale made a total profit of $73.66 million on Hyperliquid, and its long positions included ETH, BTC, HYPE and PEPEOn July 21, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the total profit of the whale 0x4a20 on Hyperliquid reached $73.66 million. The current long positions are: ETH (25x l</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947138758273159168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Current bull market cycle led by institutions, whether it will benefit altcoins remains uncertainPresto Research analyst Min Jung said that supported by sustained institutional demand (especially from cryptocurrency fund management companies), Bitcoin continues to hover near its all-time high, and the price of ETH has also benefited from the push of institutional investors. More and more listed companies are starting to include ETH in their corporate treasuries, and the market is showing early signs of an altcoin season, but it is uncertain whether this strong momentum will extend to the broader altcoin market. (The Block) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947139764616712192</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyAnalyst: Current bull market cycle led by institutions, whether it will benefit altcoins remains uncertainPresto Research analyst Min Jung said that supported by sustained institutional demand (especially from cryptocurrency fund management companies), Bitcoin continues to hover near</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947139764616712192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 101.33 WBTC from Binance 7 hours ago, worth $11.98 million.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa) monitoring, a certain whale withdrew 101.33 WBTC from Binance 7 hours ago, worth $11.98M. Since May 12, the address has accumulated 206.35 WBTC (approximately $23.22M) with an average price of $112,545.00, and currently has a floating profit of $1.233M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947137229390630912</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA whale withdrew 101.33 WBTC from Binance 7 hours ago, worth $11.98 million.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi (@ai_9684xtpa) monitoring, a certain whale withdrew 101.33 WBTC from Binance 7 hours ago, worth $11.98M. Since May 12, the address has accumulated 206.35 WBTC (approximatel</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947137229390630912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America Merrill Lynch: Stablecoins will have a disruptive impact on traditional bank deposits and payment systems.According to Wall Street Insights, Bank of America Merrill Lynch&apos;s latest research report shows that as the U.S. regulatory framework for stablecoins gradually takes shape, stablecoins will have a disruptive impact on traditional bank deposits and payment systems within the next 2-3 years. The U.S. President has signed the GENIUS Act, setting a preliminary framework for stablecoin regulation. In the short term, the stablecoin market is expected to grow by $250-750 billion, which will boost demand for U.S. short-term Treasury bonds. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947135768631988224</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBank of America Merrill Lynch: Stablecoins will have a disruptive impact on traditional bank deposits and payment systems.According to Wall Street Insights, Bank of America Merrill Lynch&apos;s latest research report shows that as the U.S. regulatory framework for stablecoins gradu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947135768631988224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>