<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:31:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Archax Acquires German Digital Asset Firm DDA to Expand European Crypto ETP FootprintUK-based digital asset exchange Archax will acquire Deutsche Digital Assets (DDA), a regulated German crypto asset management company, to strengthen its business presence in major European financial markets such as the UK, Germany, and France. DDA currently manages approximately $70.00M in assets and focuses on distributing crypto exchange-traded products (ETPs) through European banks and asset management institutions. This acquisition will bring new licenses to Archax, including portfolio management and investment advisory under German BaFin regulation, enabling it to better serve EU institutional clients. (CoinDesk) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947617899678289920</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyArchax Acquires German Digital Asset Firm DDA to Expand European Crypto ETP FootprintUK-based digital asset exchange Archax will acquire Deutsche Digital Assets (DDA), a regulated German crypto asset management company, to strengthen its business presence in major European financ</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947617899678289920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>coindesk</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.44% in the past 1H, up 0.24% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947613988454883328</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.44% in the past 1H, up 0.24% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947613988454883328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 300 BTC to Binance again, worth approximately $35.61M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale once again deposited 300 BTC into Binance, worth approximately $35.61M. Currently, the whale address still holds 800 BTC, worth approximately $95.00M, with a profit of $93.33M. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947615393116082176</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailyA whale deposited 300 BTC to Binance again, worth approximately $35.61M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale once again deposited 300 BTC into Binance, worth approximately $35.61M. Currently, the whale address still holds 800 BTC, worth approximately $95.00M, with a prof</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947615393116082176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Announces Proposed Initial Public Offering of STRC SharesStrategy (NASDAQ: MSTR , STRK , STRF , STRD ) announced plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of variable rate Series A perpetual extended preferred stock ( STRC stock) and conduct an initial public offering, subject to market and other conditions. The proceeds will be used for general corporate purposes, including Bitcoin acquisitions and working capital. The initial annualized monthly dividend rate for STRC stock is 9.00% , and the company has the right to adjust the dividend rate in accordance with relevant regulations. Morgan Stanley, Barclays, Moelis &amp; Company and TD Securities serve as joint bookrunners for this offering. The offering will be made through an effective registration statement with the SEC and will be sold only by prospectus. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947612514288422912</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoPANewsStrategy Announces Proposed Initial Public Offering of STRC SharesStrategy (NASDAQ: MSTR , STRK , STRF , STRD ) announced plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of variable rate Series A perpetual extended preferred stock ( STRC stock) and conduct an initial public offering, subject to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947612514288422912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Ethereum buyers took profits near $2,520.00, but still hold nearly 2.00M ETHA heatmap of Ethereum&apos;s cost basis distribution released by blockchain data analysis firm Glassnode shows that since July 1, buyers have been taking profits significantly around $2,520.00, and the red area is gradually weakening. However, these buyers still hold nearly 2.00M ETH. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947607674225184768</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoForesightNewsGlassnode: Ethereum buyers took profits near $2,520.00, but still hold nearly 2.00M ETHA heatmap of Ethereum&apos;s cost basis distribution released by blockchain data analysis firm Glassnode shows that since July 1, buyers have been taking profits significantly around $2,520.0</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947607674225184768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot tradingOn July 22, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot trading at 21:00 (UTC+8) on July 23. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605879021129728</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoPANewsGate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot tradingOn July 22, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot trading at 21:00 (UTC+8) on July 23. [PANews]$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605879021129728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWF Labs co-founder: Falcon Finance funds have all been withdrawn from CEX, and the new transparency page will be launched this weekOn July 22, Andrei Grachev, co-founder of DWF Labs and co-founder of Falcon Finance, wrote that Falcon Finance has withdrawn all funds from centralized exchanges and obtained a confirmation letter from the auditor. Currently, Falcon Finance is designing the structure of a new transparency page, which is expected to be launched this week. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605399893200896</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsDWF Labs co-founder: Falcon Finance funds have all been withdrawn from CEX, and the new transparency page will be launched this weekOn July 22, Andrei Grachev, co-founder of DWF Labs and co-founder of Falcon Finance, wrote that Falcon Finance has withdrawn all funds from centralized</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605399893200896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy&apos;s per-share equivalent of Bitcoin has increased by 20.8% since the beginning of the year, TD Cowen reiterates MSTR&apos;s target price of $680.00Investment bank TD Cowen stated that the premium for Strategy is reasonable. After increasing its holdings by another 6,220 BTC last week, one share of MSTR stock now corresponds to 20.8% more Bitcoin than on January 1. TD Cowen reiterated its $680.00 target price for MSTR stock and expects that by 2027, Strategy will hold nearly 900,000 BTC, and the flywheel strategy of Bitcoin treasury will continue to provide it with momentum. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605308901969920</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyStrategy&apos;s per-share equivalent of Bitcoin has increased by 20.8% since the beginning of the year, TD Cowen reiterates MSTR&apos;s target price of $680.00Investment bank TD Cowen stated that the premium for Strategy is reasonable. After increasing its holdings by another 6,220 BTC last we</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605308901969920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between Rolex, Benner, and Buffett: What is the Crypto Market Trying to Tell Us?The present month so far has been quite bullish for the crypto market. Bitcoin (BTC) hit a new all-time high just over a week ago. Ethereum (ETH) is also continuing to rally, reaching multi-month highs. In fact, in the past 24 hours alone, the total market capitalization has increased by $41 billion. Amid this, market watchers are increasingly anticipating the next move. Analysts are now examining luxury watch prices, historical market cycles, and classic valuation metrics to gauge the market’s trajectory.

How Luxury Watches Reflect Market Psychology: The ‘Rolex Indicator’ Explained

Major technical indicators, chart patterns, the Fear and Greed Index, Bitcoin dominance, and DXY performance have become increasingly popular tools for predicting trends in the crypto market. However, some analysts contend that behavioral indicators offer a more accurate and insightful view of the market. In a detailed post on X (formerly Twitter), a pseudonymous analyst, Pix, highlighted the ‘Rolex Indicator’ as a potential tool for predicting the market top. The analyst explained that the Rolex Indicator gauges market psychology by examining the user behavior around luxury goods like watches. As new money enters the market, individuals purchase status symbols like watches to display their success. Pix noted that watch prices have historically lagged behind crypto bull runs, peaking only after widespread wealth distribution, such as during the 2021 NFT boom. This spike marked the top of the bull market. The analyst added that Bitcoin hit a record peak and many altcoins have seen double-digit surges over the past month. Yet, luxury watches haven’t yet followed suit.

Another analyst, Atlas, also shared a similar sentiment. He emphasized that while greed is increasing, it hasn’t hit its full potential just yet. Furthermore, the analyst outlined more behavioral signs. He pointed out that rising “flex culture” on crypto Twitter, profit screenshots, and job-quitting posts are signs of shifting market sentiment. While there are more posts like this than six months ago, it’s still below 2021 levels.

Benner or Buffett: The Debate Over the Market’s Next Big Move 

Meanwhile, the Benner Cycle, a historical model rooted in recurring market patterns, also offers a similar outlook. According to the cycle, the market has not peaked yet and could do so by 2026. Therefore, it indicates that there’s still room to grow. This suggests that the current market conditions could represent a phase of accumulation and positioning before a significant upward movement.

Nonetheless, the Warren Buffett Indicator introduces a note of caution. This metric compares the country’s stock market’s total capitalization to its Gross Domestic Product (GDP). Warren Buffett has referred to this ratio as It is used to assess whether a stock market is overvalued or undervalued relative to its underlying economy. A value above 100% usually indicates that the former is the case. Notably, in July, the ratio exceeded 200%. It could be a signal that the market is in a bubble or that stock prices are excessively inflated. This raises concerns about a potential correction in risk assets, including cryptocurrencies.

The juxtaposition of these indicators highlights a market at a crossroads. The Rolex Indicator and Benner Cycle point to ongoing growth, while the Buffett Indicator warns of overheating. The crypto market’s next move may hinge on whether confidence translates into speculative excess or triggers a broader reassessment of valuations.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947614954874228736</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoBetween Rolex, Benner, and Buffett: What is the Crypto Market Trying to Tell Us?The present month so far has been quite bullish for the crypto market. Bitcoin (BTC) hit a new all-time high just over a week ago. Ethereum (ETH) is also continuing to rally, reaching multi-month high</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947614954874228736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list Uranium.io (XU3O8) for spot trading, and launch HODLer Airdrop and trading competition with a total prize pool of 10,962 XU3O8According to the official announcement, Gate will launch Uranium.io (XU3O8) spot trading on July 24 at 16:00 (UTC+8). To give back to platform users, XU3O8 HODLer Airdrop and trading competition are launched, with a total prize pool of 10,962 XU3O8. Gate has now launched the 272nd HODLer Airdrop, which will end on July 24 at 14:00 (UTC+8). Users holding 1 GT can participate in the free airdrop and share 4,474 XU3O8. Gate will launch the Uranium.io (XU3O8) trading competition from July 24 at 16:00 to July 31 at 16:00 (UTC+8). Users can share 6,488 XU3O8 by completing spot trading, inviting friends, and completing the first order exclusive task for new users. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602795083616256</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGate will list Uranium.io (XU3O8) for spot trading, and launch HODLer Airdrop and trading competition with a total prize pool of 10,962 XU3O8According to the official announcement, Gate will launch Uranium.io (XU3O8) spot trading on July 24 at 16:00 (UTC+8). To give back to platform</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602795083616256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts.On July 22, according to the official announcement, LBank launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts for the first time on July 22, 2025, at 16:10 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602141049016320</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowLBank has launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts.On July 22, according to the official announcement, LBank launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts for the first time on July 22, 2025, at 16:10 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [Techflow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602141049016320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernstein raises price targets for Meta and AlphabetOn July 22, Bernstein raised its target price for Alphabet (GOOG.O) from $185 to $195 and its target price for Meta Platforms (META.O) from $700 to $775. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947601609597145088</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBernstein raises price targets for Meta and AlphabetOn July 22, Bernstein raised its target price for Alphabet (GOOG.O) from $185 to $195 and its target price for Meta Platforms (META.O) from $700 to $775. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947601609597145088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: US Treasury sustainability will be a key issue in the second half of this yearAramea Asset Management analyst Felix Herrmann said in a report that the debate over U.S. debt sustainability could dominate U.S. markets in the second half of this year. The chief economist said this would lead to upside risks for long-term U.S. Treasury yields. He said that the U.S. debt will increase significantly in the short term, partly due to the so-called &quot;Big, Beautiful Bill.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602803631607808</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyInstitutions: US Treasury sustainability will be a key issue in the second half of this yearAramea Asset Management analyst Felix Herrmann said in a report that the debate over U.S. debt sustainability could dominate U.S. markets in the second half of this year. The chief economist s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602803631607808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futu Launches ChinaAMC Tokenized Money Fund, Exploring On-Chain Subscription and Redemption with Stablecoin Application ScenariosFutu Holdings (FUTU) and China Asset Management (Hong Kong) have announced a partnership in the Web3.0 field. Futu will be the exclusive broker to list tokenized money market funds issued by China Asset Management (Hong Kong) on its platform, covering three currencies: HKD, RMB, and USD. Currently, the HKD product has been launched on the Futu platform, and the USD product is expected to be launched this week. The two parties plan to explore a &quot;on-chain&quot; and &quot;off-chain&quot; dual subscription and redemption mechanism in the future, and support 7×24-hour on-chain trading and receipt services. In addition, Zeng Yuchao, Managing Director of Futu Holdings, said that after the issuance of stablecoins, Futu will support the use of stablecoins on the platform. For example, users can use stablecoins as platform balances or holding assets to directly buy stocks, and Futu will handle the fiat currency clearing and settlement process for users. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947600484093415424</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Futu Launches ChinaAMC Tokenized Money Fund, Exploring On-Chain Subscription and Redemption with Stablecoin Application ScenariosFutu Holdings (FUTU) and China Asset Management (Hong Kong) have announced a partnership in the Web3.0 field. Futu will be the exclusive broker to list tokeniz</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947600484093415424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance alpha is now live with ZKWASMOn July 22, the official page showed that Binance alpha is now live on ZKWASM. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022319751168</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowBinance alpha is now live with ZKWASMOn July 22, the official page showed that Binance alpha is now live on ZKWASM. [TechFlow]#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022319751168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of England Governor Bailey: Stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank accountAccording to Zhitong Finance, Bank of England Governor Bailey stated that stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank account. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022751764480</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBank of England Governor Bailey: Stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank accountAccording to Zhitong Finance, Bank of England Governor Bailey stated that stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank account. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022751764480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMP falls below private placement price, nearly 30B PUMP from two major whales has flowed into exchangesAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, after the PUMP price fell below its private/public sale price of $0.004, the largest token holding address, which spent 100.00M USDC to purchase 25.00B PUMP in the private placement round, has deposited 17.00B PUMP to the exchange through FalconX, worth approximately $89.50M, and currently still holds 8.00B PUMP, worth approximately $29.58M. In addition, the second largest token holding address of PUMP previously spent 50.00M USDC to purchase 12.50B PUMP, worth approximately $71.37M, and has now transferred all of them to the exchange. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947598166060978176</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说PUMP falls below private placement price, nearly 30B PUMP from two major whales has flowed into exchangesAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, after the PUMP price fell below its private/public sale price of $0.004, the largest token holding address, which spent 100.00M USDC to purchase 2</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947598166060978176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank Points System Officially LaunchedAccording to official news, LBank has announced the official launch of its points system, where users can earn points through various methods such as depositing assets, spot and margin trading, perpetual contracts, KYC verification, and inviting friends. The first phase of the program will last for 90 days, and users can accumulate points for daily active behaviors. The higher the trading volume and the more friends invited, the more points will be earned. As another innovative exploration of LBank&apos;s trading incentive mechanism, the points system integrates the multi-dimensional drivers of &quot;holding + trading + social fission,&quot; and is open and transparent. It aims to empower users at different levels, help asset growth, and promote a virtuous cycle of ecological co-construction. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597772366827520</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyLBank Points System Officially LaunchedAccording to official news, LBank has announced the official launch of its points system, where users can earn points through various methods such as depositing assets, spot and margin trading, perpetual contracts, KYC verification, and inviting</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597772366827520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: Dollar may fall further as US economic growth slowsInsight Investment analyst Francesca Fornasari said in a report that the dollar may weaken further in the second half of 2025 as U.S. economic growth slows. She said that economic weakness could pave the way for further interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The dollar&apos;s continued decline as the world&apos;s reserve currency will also put pressure on the dollar. However, given the uncertainty of the U.S. policy outlook and the current aggressive short bets against the dollar, the dollar&apos;s decline should be gradual and moderate. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597780839321600</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyInstitutions: Dollar may fall further as US economic growth slowsInsight Investment analyst Francesca Fornasari said in a report that the dollar may weaken further in the second half of 2025 as U.S. economic growth slows. She said that economic weakness could pave the way for further</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597780839321600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Public Companies Turn to Bitcoin This Week As Corporate Adoption RisesCorporate Bitcoin adoption is gaining momentum, as more publicly listed companies worldwide are shifting their treasury strategies from cash to digital assets. Although investor sentiment varies, the overall market is witnessing growing institutional alignment with Bitcoin as a reserve and strategic asset. Bitcoin Adoption Accelerates as Firms Embrace BTC MicroStrategy (MSTR) remains a notable leader in corporate Bitcoin adoption . The firm recently announced plans to issue 5.00 million Series A STRC preferred shares to raise capital for additional BTC purchases . The capital is intended for working capital needs and explicitly aligns with a long-term Bitcoin reserve strategy . Beyond MicroStrategy, other companies are actively adopting Bitcoin on their balance sheets. US-listed Profusa secured a $100.00 million equity credit line to build a Bitcoin reserve. Similarly, EV startup Volcon acquired over 280 BTC and completed a $500.00 million private funding round to support further accumulation. In Europe, Swedish-listed H100 Group increased its holdings to over 510 BTC after purchasing an additional 140 BTC. Perhaps the most symbolic move comes from Grupo Murano, a major real estate conglomerate in Mexico, which declared Bitcoin a “core strategic asset” with an initial investment of $1.00 billion. This shows a growing corporate consensus that Bitcoin is more than a speculative tool—it is becoming part of global financial policy. Market Signals Support Confidence Recent data shows that public companies’ net purchases of Bitcoin reached $953.00 million last week alone, with MSTR accounting for over $700.00 million. This surge coincides with a sharp increase in Google Trends searches for “ Buy Bitcoin ,” suggesting a revival of retail interest alongside institutional momentum. Overall, corporate Bitcoin adoption reflects a broader financial paradigm shift. Bitcoin is no longer treated as a fringe or experimental asset. From tech to real estate, businesses are increasingly incorporating Bitcoin into their treasury models, not only for diversification but also as a hedge and a symbol of forward-thinking strategy.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599073850970112</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoMore Public Companies Turn to Bitcoin This Week As Corporate Adoption RisesCorporate Bitcoin adoption is gaining momentum, as more publicly listed companies worldwide are shifting their treasury strategies from cash to digital assets. Although investor sentiment varies, the overa</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599073850970112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>