<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:17:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Phase 1: 125 ASP tokens airdrop available for those with more than 225 pointsBinance announced that it has become the first trading platform to list Aspecta (ASP) tokens, and trading will start at 18:00 Beijing time on July 24, 2025. Eligible users can apply for 125 ASP token airdrops within 24 hours after trading starts through Binance Alpha Points. The airdrop activity is divided into two phases: in the first phase, you need to hold at least 225 Alpha points in the first 18 hours; in the second phase, you need to hold at least 200 Alpha points in the last 6 hours. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948295980163600384</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsBinance Alpha Phase 1: 125 ASP tokens airdrop available for those with more than 225 pointsBinance announced that it has become the first trading platform to list Aspecta (ASP) tokens, and trading will start at 18:00 Beijing time on July 24, 2025. Eligible users can apply for 125 A</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948295980163600384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6% in pre-market trading, with Musk saying Tesla may face some difficult quarters.On July 24, according to data from Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network, Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6.00% in pre-market trading. Tesla&apos;s total revenue for the second quarter decreased by 12.00% year-on-year to $22.50B, and Musk said that Tesla may face several difficult quarters next. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294093439832064</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoTechFlowTesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6% in pre-market trading, with Musk saying Tesla may face some difficult quarters.On July 24, according to data from Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network, Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6.00% in pre-market trading. Tesla&apos;s total revenue for the second quarter</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294093439832064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Meme tokens listed on JuCoin chain, expanding the JuCoin Preferred Zone lineupOn July 24, 2025, according to official sources, JuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection Preferred Zone officially launched three popular Memes: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, which are now fully open for trading. Users can enter through the &quot;Trading&quot; - &quot;On-chain Trading&quot; section on the JuCoin App or homepage. It is reported that memecoin emphasizes the community-driven pure Meme spirit; PYTHIA represents a pioneering experiment in the integration of AI and biotechnology; AOL Coin pays tribute to the America Online cultural heritage. This launch will further enrich the JuCoin on-chain ecosystem and meet users&apos; diversified asset allocation needs. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294852696936448</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailyThree Meme tokens listed on JuCoin chain, expanding the JuCoin Preferred Zone lineupOn July 24, 2025, according to official sources, JuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection Preferred Zone officially launched three popular Memes: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, which are now fully open for</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294852696936448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huang Licheng closed his position of 1,229 ETH and lost $80,000. The long positions of ETH, PUMP and HYPE still had a floating loss of about $8.711 million.On July 24, according to Ai Yi’s monitoring, Huang Licheng closed 1,229 ETH positions in the past hour, with a loss of about $80,000. Currently, his long positions in ETH, PUMP and HYPE still have a floating loss of about $8.711 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948293552563359744</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoPANewsHuang Licheng closed his position of 1,229 ETH and lost $80,000. The long positions of ETH, PUMP and HYPE still had a floating loss of about $8.711 million.On July 24, according to Ai Yi’s monitoring, Huang Licheng closed 1,229 ETH positions in the past hour, with a loss of about</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948293552563359744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; has lost over $8.71M on Hyperliquid due to long positions.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi, &quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; closed 1,229 ETH in the past 1 hour and lost $80,000.00, and the remaining ETH, PUMP, and HYPE long positions are still at a floating loss of $8,711,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294861144264704</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdaily&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; has lost over $8.71M on Hyperliquid due to long positions.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi, &quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; closed 1,229 ETH in the past 1 hour and lost $80,000.00, and the remaining ETH, PUMP, and HYPE long positions are still at a floating loss of $8,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294861144264704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast at 8 PM today: How to Learn and Earn through BlumHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast today at 20:00, with the theme &quot;How to Learn and Earn through Blum.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292101573251072</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast at 8 PM today: How to Learn and Earn through BlumHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast today at 20:00, with the theme &quot;How to Learn and Earn through Blum.&quot;$BLUM$HTXShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292101573251072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT platform Pixel Vault may cease operationsAccording to the official announcement, NFT platform Pixel Vault announced that after more than four years of development, the company has begun the process of potentially ceasing operations. The company had attempted to create a profitable and sustainable crypto entertainment business, but was unsuccessful. Currently, Pixel Vault is in discussions with multiple parties regarding the possibility of acquiring the company and its assets in order to continue serving the community. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948291599938686976</link>
      <description>19 minutes ago吴说NFT platform Pixel Vault may cease operationsAccording to the official announcement, NFT platform Pixel Vault announced that after more than four years of development, the company has begun the process of potentially ceasing operations. The company had attempted to create a profitabl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948291599938686976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to 637,500.00.According to the latest information from the validatorqueue website, the number of ETH waiting to be unstaked has increased to 637,450, with net redemptions reaching 316,000. The waiting queue length is 11 days and 2 hours, a record high. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292338601758720</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyThe number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to 637,500.00.According to the latest information from the validatorqueue website, the number of ETH waiting to be unstaked has increased to 637,450, with net redemptions reaching 316,000. The waiting queue length is 11 days an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292338601758720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch BNKR spot trading
According to official news on July 24, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs


BNKR/USDT (July 24, 17:00 UTC+8): $BNKR is the native token of the Bankr project. Bankr is an advanced AI agent that can help you with swaps, research, and more.


 [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289446029365248</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch BNKR spot trading
According to official news on July 24, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs


BNKR/USDT (July 24, 17:00 UTC+8): $BNKR is the native token of the Bankr project. Bankr is</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289446029365248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT: Ripple co-founder-linked address transferred 50,000,000 XRP, approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchangesAccording to on-chain detective ZachXBT, starting on July 17, 2025, wallet addresses associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen transferred 50,000,000 XRP (approximately $175,000,000.00) to four addresses, of which approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchanges or related service platforms. Some of the funds also flowed into two new addresses, each receiving 5,000,000 XRP. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289501415149568</link>
      <description>28 minutes ago吴说ZachXBT: Ripple co-founder-linked address transferred 50,000,000 XRP, approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchangesAccording to on-chain detective ZachXBT, starting on July 17, 2025, wallet addresses associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen transferred 50,000,000 XRP (app</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289501415149568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet has now added a new encrypted payment channel, supporting mainstream consumer platforms including Hema, Honor of Kings, Sinopec, and JD.com.Bitget Wallet has announced the addition of cryptocurrency payment functionality for a variety of everyday consumption scenarios, covering e-commerce shopping, digital entertainment, game top-ups, global travel, and other areas, allowing users to complete one-stop consumption using crypto assets within the wallet. Currently, the platforms and services supported by this function include Sinopec, Suning.com, JD.com, Hema, Tmall Supermarket, Honor of Kings, Steam, and mobile phone top-ups, among others. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289826477903872</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet has now added a new encrypted payment channel, supporting mainstream consumer platforms including Hema, Honor of Kings, Sinopec, and JD.com.Bitget Wallet has announced the addition of cryptocurrency payment functionality for a variety of everyday consumption scenari</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289826477903872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amended class action calls Pump.fun a ‘slot machine cabinet’ in $5.5B caseAn amended lawsuit accuses Pump.fun and key Solana partners of operating an unlicensed digital casino that funneled billions through deceptive memecoin schemes.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288055307210752</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoPANewsAmended class action calls Pump.fun a ‘slot machine cabinet’ in $5.5B caseAn amended lawsuit accuses Pump.fun and key Solana partners of operating an unlicensed digital casino that funneled billions through deceptive memecoin schemes.#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288055307210752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Congress to Advance Veterans Affairs Blockchain Pilot BillThe U.S. Congress is considering the &quot;Department of Veterans Affairs Distributed Ledger Technology Innovation Act of 2025&quot; (H.R. 3455), which aims to promote the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) to study the application of blockchain technology in the claims process to improve transparency, traceability, and reduce the risk of fraud and abuse. The bill passed a hearing by the House Veterans Affairs Subcommittee on June 11 and is awaiting a full House vote. If passed, the VA will submit a feasibility study and pilot recommendation report within one year. [CryptoSlate]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288300611080192</link>
      <description>34 minutes ago吴说US Congress to Advance Veterans Affairs Blockchain Pilot BillThe U.S. Congress is considering the &quot;Department of Veterans Affairs Distributed Ledger Technology Innovation Act of 2025&quot; (H.R. 3455), which aims to promote the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) to study the application</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288300611080192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Ventures to Support AI Platform Bankr Through Base Ecosystem FundCoinbase Ventures announced that it will support AI agent platform Bankr through the Base ecosystem fund. Bankr is one of the agent platforms integrated into Coinbase&apos;s newly launched Base app. Trading agents react faster than humans, operate 24/7, and have the potential to make more data-driven decisions. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948287303650185216</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoOdailyCoinbase Ventures to Support AI Platform Bankr Through Base Ecosystem FundCoinbase Ventures announced that it will support AI agent platform Bankr through the Base ecosystem fund. Bankr is one of the agent platforms integrated into Coinbase&apos;s newly launched Base app. Trading agen</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948287303650185216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Pi Coin Be Listed on Binance? New Developments in Pi Wallet Spark SpeculationSpeculation is growing that Pi Network’s Pi Coin (PI) could potentially be listed on Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange. This comes following reports from several Pioneers who noticed Binance support options appearing in the Pi Wallet. However, neither Binance nor the Pi Core Team has confirmed or commented on the development, leaving the rumor mill to run wild. Pi Coin on Binance? Rumors Grow Stronger Amid New Wallet Features The listing of Pi Coin on Binance has been a longstanding concern for the Pi Network community, known as Pioneers. Since the launch of the open network, Pioneers have consistently advocated for Pi to be listed on the exchange. However, this has not yet materialized. Recently, the integration of Binance-related support options within the Pi Wallet has renewed the community’s optimism. This has raised hopes that a partnership between Pi Network and Binance may soon be realized. In a recent post on X (formerly Twitter), a prominent Pioneer, Mr Spock, highlighted that ‘Binance Connect Support’ and ‘Binance P2P Support ‘ options now appear under the Help &amp; Support tab of the Pi Wallet. For context, Binance Connect is the exchange’s fiat-to-crypto service. It facilitates the easy purchase and conversion of fiat currencies into cryptocurrencies through various payment methods. The exchange shut the service down in 2023. Nevertheless, Binance later relaunched in 2024. Meanwhile, Binance P2P enables direct peer-to-peer transactions with more than 800 payment methods and over 100 fiat currencies. However, Mr Spock added that the development doesn’t directly confirm that Pi Network will be available to trade on Binance immediately. Nonetheless, he noted that it strongly suggests that ‘something big is coming.’ Furthermore, PiScan data revealed that a mysterious wallet address has accumulated over 336 million Pi. This has fueled theories that it might belong to an exchange preparing for listing. Despite the circulating reports on X, it is also worth noting that Binance is not a part of KYB-verified businesses on Pi Network. Moreover, besides the exchange, Pi Wallet also lists support for other payment processors like MoonPay and Stripe. These businesses are also not KYB-verified. The Pi Core Team has remained silent on the matter, leaving the community to grapple with unverified reports. Premature speculation has historically led to community disappointment. Until an official announcement from Pi Network or Binance materializes, the current developments remain rumors.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288863688003584</link>
      <description>50 minutes agobeincryptoCould Pi Coin Be Listed on Binance? New Developments in Pi Wallet Spark SpeculationSpeculation is growing that Pi Network’s Pi Coin (PI) could potentially be listed on Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange. This comes following reports from several Pioneers who noticed</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288863688003584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 巨鲸 deposited about $7.00M in HyperLiquid to go long on PEPE, BONK, POPCAT, etc.On July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited about 6,998,000.000 USDC into the HyperLiquid platform and opened or increased long positions in multiple tokens, including: PEPE, BONK, WIF, POPCAT, Trump with 10x leverage, ZK, PUMP with 5x leverage, and LDO, PURR, CHILLGUY with 3x leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282208929779712</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoPANewsA 巨鲸 deposited about $7.00M in HyperLiquid to go long on PEPE, BONK, POPCAT, etc.On July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited about 6,998,000.000 USDC into the HyperLiquid platform and opened or increased long positions in multiple tokens, including: PEPE,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282208929779712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday and deposited into Bybit.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address yesterday. This address is marked by Solscan as &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2,&quot; i.e., a private placement investor. After receiving the returned funds from Binance yesterday, these 2 billion tokens have been deposited into Bybit, with a value reduced by $6.00M compared to when they were deposited into Binance. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282276646817792</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdaily2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday and deposited into Bybit.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address yesterday.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282276646817792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Espresso Foundation has completed the snapshot.The blockchain infrastructure Espresso Foundation tweeted that it has completed taking a snapshot. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278173883502592</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsEspresso Foundation has completed the snapshot.The blockchain infrastructure Espresso Foundation tweeted that it has completed taking a snapshot. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278173883502592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic cooperation with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron.According to official sources, Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX recently reached a strategic partnership with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron. Through this collaboration, Safeheron will assist APACX in building a decentralized protocol for stablecoin trading and settlement targeting the Southeast Asian market, constructing a value network for the interconnection and application of multiple stablecoins, especially providing APACX with top-tier security and risk control capabilities. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948279780838805504</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyStablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic cooperation with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron.According to official sources, Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX recently reached a strategic partnership with digital asset self-custody</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948279780838805504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizen Completes Token Migration, ZEN Converted to Base Chain ERC-20 Token, Launches Three-Layer Privacy Application ChainThe Horizen blockchain has migrated its native token ZEN from the original L1 mainnet to the Base chain and converted it to a standard ERC-20 token as part of its Horizen 2.0 three-layer privacy application chain deployment. The total supply of ZEN remains unchanged at 21.00 million. The project team stated that this is the first step in Horizen&apos;s privacy-focused restart of its ecosystem. Previously, Coinbase issued a statement saying that it would automatically complete the conversion of mainnet ZEN to Base chain ERC-20 tokens for users. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948277528602415104</link>
      <description>1 hour agoChainCatcherHorizen Completes Token Migration, ZEN Converted to Base Chain ERC-20 Token, Launches Three-Layer Privacy Application ChainThe Horizen blockchain has migrated its native token ZEN from the original L1 mainnet to the Base chain and converted it to a standard ERC-20 token as part</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948277528602415104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 08:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>