<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:29:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>iShares Ethereum ETF becomes 3rd-fastest ETF to hit $10B in assets</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948389074955472896</link>
      <description>14:24iShares Ethereum ETF becomes 3rd-fastest ETF to hit $10B in assets</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948389074955472896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, will ship on August 4th; users with unconfirmed addresses may miss the first batch.Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, announced that it will begin shipping on August 4th. If users have pre-ordered but have not yet confirmed their shipping address and taxes, the device may be delayed, thus missing the first batch of shipments. Users are reminded to update as soon as possible. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948388922261835776</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoForesightNewsSolana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, will ship on August 4th; users with unconfirmed addresses may miss the first batch.Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, announced that it will begin shipping on August 4th. If users have pre-ordered but have not yet confirmed t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948388922261835776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun Appears at TRON.Inc Name Change Bell-Ringing CeremonyOn July 24th, TRON founder Justin Sun, as a strategic advisor to TRON.Inc, was invited to participate in the Nasdaq Stock Exchange opening bell ringing ceremony to celebrate the official renaming of Nasdaq-listed TRON. Inc (stock code: TRON). In June of this year, SRM Entertainment, the predecessor of TRON. Inc and a Nasdaq-listed company, announced plans to launch a TRON corporate treasury strategy of up to $210.00M and rename itself Tron Inc. On July 16th, SRM Entertainment was officially renamed Tron Inc, and on July 17, 2025, it will change its stock code on Nasdaq from &quot;SRM&quot; to &quot;TRON&quot;.
Justin Sun said, &quot;I am very proud to tell you that TRON (TRX) has been strategically reserved by a Nasdaq-listed company. I believe that this is not only a big step for TRON.Inc, but also an important moment for the entire blockchain industry, which is worth remembering together. This also marks the real beginning of the cryptocurrency era. Finally, I would also like to thank my family for their support along the way; and also thank our team, who have been working day and night to build the entire ecosystem.&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387980774805504</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyJustin Sun Appears at TRON.Inc Name Change Bell-Ringing CeremonyOn July 24th, TRON founder Justin Sun, as a strategic advisor to TRON.Inc, was invited to participate in the Nasdaq Stock Exchange opening bell ringing ceremony to celebrate the official renaming of Nasdaq-listed TRO</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387980774805504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine increases its market stock offering to $4.50B to increase its Ethereum holdingsBitmine Immersion (BMNR) has increased the size of its &quot;at-the-market&quot; (ATM) program from $2.00 billion to $4.50 billion. The company filed a prospectus supplement with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on July 24, authorizing the continuous sale of common stock in the open market through two brokerage firms, Cantor Fitzgerald and ThinkEquity. This additional issuance provides financial support for the company to further increase its ETH holdings and expand its asset reserves. According to previous reports, Bitmine updated its ETH holdings, and as of 11:59 PM ET on July 23, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing time today), Bitmine held a total of 566,776 ETH, worth more than $2.00 billion. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387989222133760</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoOdailyBitmine increases its market stock offering to $4.50B to increase its Ethereum holdingsBitmine Immersion (BMNR) has increased the size of its &quot;at-the-market&quot; (ATM) program from $2.00 billion to $4.50 billion. The company filed a prospectus supplement with the U.S. Securities and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387989222133760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign sponsors American esports club NTMR to compete in the Esports World Cup
On July 24, blockchain digital infrastructure company Sign announced a partnership with well-known esports club NTMR to jointly establish the Sign Esports club, which will compete in the 2025 Esports World Cup with a brand new orange brand.
Sign is a technology company building blockchain infrastructure, providing token distribution services to 40 million blockchain users.
NTMR is one of the most active esports clubs in North America, with its teams repeatedly achieving excellent results in events such as Overwatch 2 and Rainbow Six. Recent achievements include winning the first stage of the 2025 Overwatch Championship Series North America and the Marvel Rivals North American Invitational Tournament, as well as reaching the top three in the 2025 Global Finals, demonstrating strong dominance.
 [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385430822522880</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoTechFlowSign sponsors American esports club NTMR to compete in the Esports World Cup
On July 24, blockchain digital infrastructure company Sign announced a partnership with well-known esports club NTMR to jointly establish the Sign Esports club, which will compete in the 2025 Esports W</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385430822522880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Digital to issue first GENIUS‑compliant stablecoin in US with Ethena LabsAnchorage Digital, the first federally chartered crypto bank in the United States, will issue Ethena Labs’ USDtb token onshore as the first stablecoin engineered to comply with the new GENIUS Act, the companies said on Thursday.

Ethena’s USDtb is a yield-bearing dollar token primarily backed by BlackRock’s BUIDL and crypto collateral rather than traditional reserves to maintain its $1 peg. The synthetic stablecoin has circulated offshore since December and amassed $1.45 billion in total value locked, according to DefiLlama data.

Under the partnership, Anchorage Digital Bank will mint and redeem USDtb tokens directly in the U.S., bringing the asset under a federal regulatory umbrella for the first time. Anchorage said its stablecoin issuance platform will serve as a turnkey infrastructure for Ethena’s stablecoin to “launch and distribute fully regulated digital dollars.”

The move comes one week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act, the country’s first law governing stablecoin issuance. Industry players and U.S. officials like Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent expect the legislation to accelerate demand from asset managers, payments firms, and corporates looking for yield‑bearing, programmable dollars.

The passage of GENIUS gives federally regulated institutions a green light and clarity to participate in the stablecoin ecosystem, Anchorage CEO Nathan McCauley noted in the release.

Guy Young, Ethena Labs CEO, added that products like USDtb stand to benefit from federal oversight and regulated appetite. “While we’ve already seen strong demand for USDtb, we expect GENIUS compliance to empower our partners and holders to confidently and significantly expand its use across new products and platforms,” he said.

Anchorage’s announcement positions it alongside giants such as Circle and PayPal, which already operate dollar‑pegged tokens but must adapt to GENIUS requirements. Major banks like JPMorganand Citihave flagged plans to experiment with stablecoins and deposit‑backed tokens once the rules settle. [companies]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385281941508096</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoThe BlockAnchorage Digital to issue first GENIUS‑compliant stablecoin in US with Ethena LabsAnchorage Digital, the first federally chartered crypto bank in the United States, will issue Ethena Labs’ USDtb token onshore as the first stablecoin engineered to comply with the new GENIUS Ac</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385281941508096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoonPay Launches Liquid Staking Token mpSOL on SolanaOn July 24, according to SolanaFloor, MoonPay has launched the liquidity staking token $mpSOL on the Solana blockchain. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680090673152</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoPANewsMoonPay Launches Liquid Staking Token mpSOL on SolanaOn July 24, according to SolanaFloor, MoonPay has launched the liquidity staking token $mpSOL on the Solana blockchain. [PANews]#Layer1$MAG7.SSI$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680090673152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK crypto hopes stall, but ‘encouraging signs’ are thereThe crypto industry in the UK is pushing for the government to change the rules of the road, and it just may be working.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680128421888</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoPANewsUK crypto hopes stall, but ‘encouraging signs’ are thereThe crypto industry in the UK is pushing for the government to change the rules of the road, and it just may be working.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680128421888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrifuge V3 Goes Live on Six EVM Chains via Wormhole, Migrating to the Ethereum EcosystemReal World Asset (RWA) tokenization platform Centrifuge has launched Centrifuge V3 on six EVM chains: Ethereum, Plume, Base, Arbitrum, Avalanche, and BNB Chain. Exclusively supported by Wormhole, this launch aims to build a unified multi-chain foundation for institutional-grade asset management and next-generation financial products. This move marks the completion of Centrifuge&apos;s migration to the Ethereum ecosystem, with new features including: cross-chain product issuance, borderless investor access, and seamless liquidity across the DeFi ecosystem. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383362611220480</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoForesightNewsCentrifuge V3 Goes Live on Six EVM Chains via Wormhole, Migrating to the Ethereum EcosystemReal World Asset (RWA) tokenization platform Centrifuge has launched Centrifuge V3 on six EVM chains: Ethereum, Plume, Base, Arbitrum, Avalanche, and BNB Chain. Exclusively supported</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383362611220480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - US initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19 were 217,000, with expectations of 226,000.1. U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19 at 217,000, expected 226,000U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19 at 217,000, expected 226,000, previous value 221,000.2. European Central Bank keeps deposit facility rate unchanged at 2%, in line with market expectationsThe European Central Bank kept the deposit facility rate unchanged at 2.00%, in line with market expectations, after cutting interest rates for seven consecutive meetings. The main refinancing rate and marginal lending rate remain unchanged at 2.15% and 2.40% respectively.3. Arkham: U.S. Government Has Not Sold 170,000 BTC, Holds at Least 198,000 TotalThe U.S. Marshals Service stated in response to a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request that it holds 28,988 Bitcoins (approximately $3.4 billion). Multiple federal agencies, including the FBI, the Department of Justice, and the Drug Enforcement Administration, currently hold at least 198,000 Bitcoins (approximately $23.5 billion) in total, and these assets have had no transfer records in the past 4 months.4. Ghana Plans to Issue Licenses to Cryptocurrency PlatformsThe Bank of Ghana plans to submit a draft regulatory framework for crypto platforms to parliament by September, intending to issue licenses to virtual asset platforms to regulate the crypto trading market involving millions of users in the country, obtain financial data, and enhance cross-border trade capabilities. The central bank governor stated that the lack of regulation has led to a large number of crypto transactions not being included in the official financial system, affecting the local currency, the Cedi. Data shows that Ghana&apos;s crypto transaction volume reached $3.00 billion between July 2023 and June 2024, with approximately 3 million Ghanaian adults (17% of the adult population) using virtual currencies.5. Tether Plans to Return to the U.S. Market, Focusing on Institutional Stablecoin BusinessTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated that after U.S. President Donald Trump signed the stablecoin bill, Tether is planning to return to the U.S. market, focusing on institutional clients and providing stablecoin products for payments, interbank settlement, and trading. Ardoino emphasized that the company has no intention of going public and will continue to focus on emerging markets and expand its business in the United States.6. 70-Year-Old Hong Kong Man Falls Victim to Cryptocurrency Romance ScamA retired 70-year-old Hong Kong man received a message on WhatsApp from someone claiming to be a female neighbor, and subsequently developed a twilight romance, but never met the person. The woman claimed to work at the Singapore Exchange and had inside information on cryptocurrency investments, falsely claiming that she would receive rich returns. The old man transferred a total of HK$3,272,700.00 in 37 transactions to 34 bank accounts provided by the woman. It was not until the old man reached the ATM withdrawal limit and went to the bank in person to withdraw a large amount of cash that the bank staff noticed the abnormality of the transaction and immediately notified the Anti-Deception Coordination Centre, which finally uncovered the scam. The old man lost more than HK$3.27 million in total and owed nearly one million in debt as a result. The Hong Kong police said that they had received nearly 20 online romance scams related to investment in the past two weeks, with 40% of the victims being over 60 years old, with a total loss of more than HK$10.00 million.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948381459844239360</link>
      <description>33 minutes ago吴说Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - US initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19 were 217,000, with expectations of 226,000.1. U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19 at 217,000, expected 226,000U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948381459844239360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5Yahoo Finance quotes show that Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377912905895936</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoOdailyTesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5Yahoo Finance quotes show that Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5. [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377912905895936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;U.S. President Trump denies he wants to &quot;destroy Musk&apos;s company.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377921361612800</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoOdailyTrump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;U.S. President Trump denies he wants to &quot;destroy Musk&apos;s company.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377921361612800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito: Capital Launchpad&apos;s first products, Theoriq and Espresso, will be launched tomorrow.Kaito Al announces that the first products of its Capital Launchpad will officially launch tomorrow, with Theoriq and Espresso conducting their community initial distribution on Capital Launchpad on July 25 at 20:00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376297218052096</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoForesightNewsKaito: Capital Launchpad&apos;s first products, Theoriq and Espresso, will be launched tomorrow.Kaito Al announces that the first products of its Capital Launchpad will officially launch tomorrow, with Theoriq and Espresso conducting their community initial distribution on Capi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376297218052096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$TRUMP Goes Live On TRON NetworkJuly 24, 2025 - Geneva, Switzerland - TRON DAO, a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps, announced today the official deployment of $TRUMP on the TRON blockchain. The token expansion is enabled by LayerZero’s Omnichain Fungible Token (OFT) standard and Stargate Finance’s user interface and liquidity transport protocol. Together, they provide a framework for cross-chain transfers of $TRUMP while maintaining a unified supply. This development positions TRON at the forefront of the evolving digital asset landscape, where real-world value transfer, speed, and accessibility are critical to mainstream growth.

The deployment of $TRUMP on TRON introduces the token to one of the most actively used blockchain networks in the world. TRON hosts over 321 million user accounts and over $20 billion in daily transfer volume, with a circulating supply of more than $80 billion in USDT on the network. Its infrastructure is optimized for high-speed and low-cost transactions, making it an ideal blockchain for a token like $TRUMP that seeks to scale across everyday use cases—from DeFi engagement to community activations and potentially real-world payments.

“TRON is built to support scale, inclusion, and real-world use,” said Justin Sun, Founder of TRON. “The launch of $TRUMP on TRON reflects our belief in giving community-powered assets a network that can help them thrive globally.”

LayerZero’s integration plays a critical role in this launch, offering secure and seamless cross-chain functionality through its Omnichain Fungible Token (OFT) standard. This allows $TRUMP to move across supported blockchains without relying on traditional bridges or wrapped assets, reducing fragmentation and increasing accessibility. Stargate Finance, a liquidity network for cross-chain transfer for assets built on top of LayerZero protocol, supports $TRUMP bridging to and from TRON, further strengthening its liquidity and multichain utility.

By bringing $TRUMP into the TRON ecosystem, TRON DAO plans to explore DeFi and payment utility to the token as they continue to champion a vision of open, scalable blockchain infrastructure that supports emerging digital assets and unlocks new channels for community and financial participation. The commitment reinforces TRON DAO’s commitment to expanding its reach through innovative, user-centric initiatives that align with the decentralized ethos of the crypto space. With the addition of $TRUMP, TRON continues to prove itself as a dynamic technology for the next generation of token-based innovation.

About TRON DAO

TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.

Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON blockchain has experienced significant growth since its MainNet launch in May 2018. TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin, exceeding $80 billion. As of July 2025, the TRON blockchain has recorded over 321 million in total user accounts, more than 10 billion in total transactions, and over $25 billion in total value locked (TVL), based on TRONSCAN.

TRONNetwork | TRONDAO | X | YouTube | Telegram | Discord | Reddit | GitHub | Medium | Forum

Media Contact

Yeweon Park

[emailprotected]

This post is commissioned by TRON and does not serve as a testimonial or endorsement by The Block. This post is for informational purposes only and should not be relied upon as a basis for investment, tax, legal or other advice. You should conduct your own research and consult independent counsel and advisors on the matters discussed within this post. Past performance of any asset is not indicative of future results.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376149897318400</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoThe Block$TRUMP Goes Live On TRON NetworkJuly 24, 2025 - Geneva, Switzerland - TRON DAO, a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps, announced today the official deployment of $TRUMP on the TRON blockchain</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376149897318400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum’s daily gas usage hits a record highOn July 24, according to everstake.eth, on July 21, 2025, Ethereum&apos;s daily Gas usage reached 149,673,860,000, setting a record high. Analysis pointed out that this milestone shows that the Ethereum ecosystem continues to prosper, with on-chain applications, users, and actual value growing continuously. The continued rise in Gas usage reflects real market demand and adoption. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375739375620096</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoPANewsEthereum’s daily gas usage hits a record highOn July 24, according to everstake.eth, on July 21, 2025, Ethereum&apos;s daily Gas usage reached 149,673,860,000, setting a record high. Analysis pointed out that this milestone shows that the Ethereum ecosystem continues to prosper, with</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375739375620096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine’s Ethereum holdings exceed $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETHOn July 24, according to PR Newswire, BitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE AMERICAN: BMNR) announced that its Ethereum (ETH) holdings have exceeded $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETH, far exceeding the $250 million in the first private placement completed on July 8. Thomas &quot;Tom&quot; Lee, chairman of the company&apos;s board of directors, said that BitMine is one step closer to achieving its goal of holding and staking 5% of the world&apos;s total ETH. CEO Jonathan Bates said that the company will continue to advance the Ethereum treasury strategy to help the development of the Ethereum ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375281416343552</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoPANewsBitMine’s Ethereum holdings exceed $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETHOn July 24, according to PR Newswire, BitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE AMERICAN: BMNR) announced that its Ethereum (ETH) holdings have exceeded $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETH, far exceeding the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375281416343552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USYC interest-bearing stablecoin will be issued natively on BNB ChainOn July 24, according to BNB Chain Chinese, Circle&apos;s interest-bearing stablecoin USYC (with U.S. Treasury bonds as the underlying asset) will soon be natively issued on BNB Chain. This move will significantly improve the capital efficiency of global users, achieve income acquisition, maintain liquidity, and increase transaction speed, and can be operated on the entire chain. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372368744845312</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUSYC interest-bearing stablecoin will be issued natively on BNB ChainOn July 24, according to BNB Chain Chinese, Circle&apos;s interest-bearing stablecoin USYC (with U.S. Treasury bonds as the underlying asset) will soon be natively issued on BNB Chain. This move will significantly improv</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372368744845312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMGE Technology Group: Accelerating the layout of IP RWA, WEB3 aggregated payment, and WEB3 e-sports game platformsCMGE announced that the company is accelerating a series of strategic initiatives, including accelerating the RWA (Real World Assets) on-chain plan for the &quot;The Legend of Sword and Fairy&quot; IP, launching a Web3 aggregated payment tool, and self-developing and self-operating a decentralized Web3 e-sports game platform. The company believes that breakthroughs in key areas such as RWA and stablecoins are strongly promoting Web3 to cross the conceptual gap and move towards large-scale commercial applications, demonstrating its great potential to reshape asset value and technological landscape. (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372861525233664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyCMGE Technology Group: Accelerating the layout of IP RWA, WEB3 aggregated payment, and WEB3 e-sports game platformsCMGE announced that the company is accelerating a series of strategic initiatives, including accelerating the RWA (Real World Assets) on-chain plan for the &quot;The Legend o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372861525233664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sei Network has launched native USDC and CCTP V2According to the official announcement, native USDC and CCTP V2 are now live on the Sei Network. Circle Mint now fully supports native USDC on Sei. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372869976756224</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySei Network has launched native USDC and CCTP V2According to the official announcement, native USDC and CCTP V2 are now live on the Sei Network. Circle Mint now fully supports native USDC on Sei. [Odaily Planet Daily News]#Crypto Stocks$USDC$SEI$CRCLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372869976756224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement), supporting 1-20 times leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369608704069632</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsGate has launched ASP perpetual contract tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement), supporting 1-20 times leverage. [PANews]$USDT$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369608704069632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK AI firm Satsuma Technology raises $135 million to build a Bitcoin vaultReported on July 24 that according to Cointelegraph, British artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology announced that it had successfully raised $135.00 million to build one of the largest Bitcoin vaults in the UK. The company said that all the promised funds are expected to arrive in the next two weeks. This financing is expected to make Satsuma the second largest corporate Bitcoin holder in the UK, second only to The Smarter Web Company. At the same time, this may also become the largest single Bitcoin purchase record for a British company. Satsuma completed this financing through convertible bonds, aiming to accelerate business growth and promote the deep integration of Bitcoin and artificial intelligence. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369519503806464</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUK AI firm Satsuma Technology raises $135 million to build a Bitcoin vaultReported on July 24 that according to Cointelegraph, British artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology announced that it had successfully raised $135.00 million to build one of the largest Bitcoin vaul</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369519503806464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>