<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:57:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs, BNY Mellon to offer tokenized money market funds for clients</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948000992997478400</link>
      <description>12:42Goldman Sachs, BNY Mellon to offer tokenized money market funds for clients</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948000992997478400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Stock Options Launch Trading on the NYSEBitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE: BMNR) has announced that options trading on the company&apos;s common stock began on July 23 on the New York Stock Exchange. The company is committed to accumulating 5% of the global ETH supply through its Ethereum vault strategy. Options trading is expected to increase BMNR stock liquidity and enhance investor risk management and position adjustment flexibility. (prnewswire) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948002934247198720</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoOdailyBitMine Stock Options Launch Trading on the NYSEBitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE: BMNR) has announced that options trading on the company&apos;s common stock began on July 23 on the New York Stock Exchange. The company is committed to accumulating 5% of the global ETH supply throug</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948002934247198720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature&apos;s Miracle Announces $20 Million XRP Corporate Treasury PlanOn July 23, according to PRNewswire, vertical farming technology company Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc. (OTCQB: NMHI) announced that it will set up an XRP corporate treasury plan of up to $20.00 million. The company will use the proceeds from equity financing from GHS Investments to purchase XRP and meet working capital needs. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948003678513860608</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoPANewsNature&apos;s Miracle Announces $20 Million XRP Corporate Treasury PlanOn July 23, according to PRNewswire, vertical farming technology company Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding Inc. (OTCQB: NMHI) announced that it will set up an XRP corporate treasury plan of up to $20.00 million. The company</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948003678513860608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGBX lists ONDO/USDT, JITOSOL/USDT, PENGU/USDT, B/USDT, and C/USDTOfficial news, MGBX was launched on July 23, 2025 with ONDO/USDT, JITOSOL/USDT, PENGU/USDT, B/USDT and C/USDT. Deposit opening time: July 23, 2025 19:00 (SGT). Trading opening time: July 23, 2025 19:30 (SGT) [Odaily News].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948000422131732480</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoOdailyMGBX lists ONDO/USDT, JITOSOL/USDT, PENGU/USDT, B/USDT, and C/USDTOfficial news, MGBX was launched on July 23, 2025 with ONDO/USDT, JITOSOL/USDT, PENGU/USDT, B/USDT and C/USDT. Deposit opening time: July 23, 2025 19:00 (SGT). Trading opening time: July 23, 2025 19:30 (SGT) [Odail</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948000422131732480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL4 Mining: Cloud mining platform for XRP investors to earn stable, daily passive incomeDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. ALL4 Mining lets users earn stable returns with zero effort using smart contracts and powerful cloud mining strategies. In the digital currency field, XRP has always been a popular investment option that has attracted much attention. However, many holders often face a common challenge: how to convert their XRP holdings into continuous passive income? ALL4 Mining, with its innovative solutions and market-leading technology, is opening a new door for XRP investors, providing an important way to convert holdings into stable daily returns. Through the ALL4 Mining platform, XRP holders can easily participate in a series of proven mining and investment strategies. It also optimizes returns through smart contracts and advanced algorithms to provide investors with stable and considerable returns. In such a rapidly changing market, it is particularly important to ensure asset appreciation and stable returns. ALL4 Mining is committed to providing every investor with tailored solutions, so that your XRP is not just a digital currency holding number, but also a continuous source of income. Step 1: Register an account Create your free account in less than a minute and get a welcome bonus of $15.00, which will allow you to earn $0.60 per day for free as your initial deposit. Step 2: Choose a plan Choose from a variety of profitable mining plans to suit your financial goals. Whether you are looking for short-term gains or long-term returns, ALL4 Mining has you covered. Step 3: Start earning Watch your income grow without any management. Daily profits will be automatically deposited into your account and you can withdraw them to your cryptocurrency wallet address. Get a stable passive income by participating in the following featured contracts: The profit will be automatically credited to your account the next day after purchasing the contract. When the account reaches $100.00, you can choose to withdraw it to your crypto wallet or continue to purchase contracts to earn more profit. Everything is safe and transparent. Control your financial freedom anytime, anywhere, just download the official app with one click. Interested investors can download the mobile app today. ALL4 Mining is a fast-growing digital asset mining service provider and a global leader in cloud mining services. The company was founded in 2019 and is headquartered in London, UK. After years of development, the company currently has more than 200 mining farms around the world, members in more than 200 countries and regions, and enjoys the trust of more than 9 million users worldwide. We believe that everyone should benefit from cloud mining and become a leader in the cloud mining industry. ALL4 Mining is committed to building a safe, compliant, transparent, clean, green, low-carbon, and environmentally friendly infrastructure power grid, providing a variety of stable and intelligent data processing service solutions for global customers. With a growing global mining network, ALL4 Mining provides institutional clients and digital asset enthusiasts with a more efficient mining experience. ALL4 Mining provides an innovative and efficient way for XRP holders to convert their digital assets into continuous passive income. By simply registering and choosing a suitable mining plan, you can start enjoying stable daily returns without any complicated operations. With its leading technology and market insights, ALL4 Mining helps investors achieve steady appreciation of their assets in the ever-changing digital currency market. Join ALL4 Mining now to start your digital currency appreciation journey and let XRP become the source of your continued wealth growth. To learn more, visit the official website. Official email of the platform: [email protected] Disclosure: This content is provided by a third party. Neither crypto.news nor the author of this article endorses any product mentioned on this page. Users should conduct their own research before taking any action related to the company.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947998444660002816</link>
      <description>22 minutes agocrypto.newsALL4 Mining: Cloud mining platform for XRP investors to earn stable, daily passive incomeDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. ALL4 Mining lets users earn stable retur</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947998444660002816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpLink Gaming Generates 567 ETH in Revenue Through Ethereum StakingSharpLink Gaming officially announced that its Ethereum holdings are 360,807, and it has generated a yield of 567 ETH through staking. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947997898121220096</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoOdailySharpLink Gaming Generates 567 ETH in Revenue Through Ethereum StakingSharpLink Gaming officially announced that its Ethereum holdings are 360,807, and it has generated a yield of 567 ETH through staking. [Odaily]#Crypto Stocks$ETH$MAG7.SSI$SBETShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947997898121220096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs partners with BNY Mellon to launch tokenized money market fund investment serviceAccording to CNBC, Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon have jointly launched a new service for institutional investors, allowing them to invest in tokenized money market funds through Goldman Sachs&apos; blockchain platform. The project has already secured participation from several asset management firms, including BlackRock and Fidelity. The two banks stated that the project will lay the foundation for money market funds in a &quot;24/7 real-time trading&quot; digital financial system and is expected to expand into the use of collateral in financial transactions in the future. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947996261940006912</link>
      <description>31 minutes ago吴说Goldman Sachs partners with BNY Mellon to launch tokenized money market fund investment serviceAccording to CNBC, Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon have jointly launched a new service for institutional investors, allowing them to invest in tokenized money market funds through Goldman Sach</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947996261940006912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Ethereum&apos;s rise driven by ETFs and corporate funds, with supply-demand imbalance as the main reasonAccording to Bitwise analysis, since May 15, ETFs and corporate treasuries have purchased approximately 2.83M ETH, far exceeding the newly generated output during the same period, with a supply-demand ratio as high as 32:1. CIO Matt Hougan pointed out that this round of increase is mainly driven by structural capital inflows, rather than emotional factors. He expects that the net purchase volume of ETH may reach $2.00B in the next year, continuing to push up prices. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947995393488392192</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyAnalysis: Ethereum&apos;s rise driven by ETFs and corporate funds, with supply-demand imbalance as the main reasonAccording to Bitwise analysis, since May 15, ETFs and corporate treasuries have purchased approximately 2.83M ETH, far exceeding the newly generated output during the same</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947995393488392192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Ends Kraken Founder Jesse Powell Probe, Returns Seized DevicesThe FBI has officially closed its investigation into Kraken founder Jesse Powell and returned multiple electronic devices seized during a 2023 raid. Federal prosecutors sent Powell a declination letter confirming that no charges were filed and that the case is now closed. Federal Authorities Close Case, Return Devices With the FBI’s decision, a high-profile legal chapter ends for one of crypto’s leading figures. According to Fortune and court documents, the US Department of Justice issued a formal declination letter, confirming Powell will face no charges. Numerous electronic devices seized during the investigation have now been returned, verifying the matter’s conclusion. Attorney statements and filings confirm the case’s closure, and the lack of any public press release from the DOJ or FBI further shows that no criminal findings arose. Importantly, the FBI’s inquiry was completely separate from Powell’s work at Kraken or any cryptocurrency issue. Investigators focused instead on allegations related to the Verge Center for the Arts, a Sacramento nonprofit Powell co-founded. According to reports, this dispute centered on a $500,000.00 donation from Powell and disagreements among board members. Powell’s legal filings in the California Superior Court detail his civil claims against board members. Powell alleges mismanagement and breach of fiduciary duty, which triggered the federal probe. Powell Responds to Investigation’s End The raid and investigation took a toll on Powell’s reputation and daily life. During the probe, he endured scrutiny as authorities held his devices. Now, with his property restored and no charges filed, Powell states he intends to move forward. Powell’s statement reflects both relief and determination to resume momentum at Kraken. As the legal saga ends, his focus now shifts to ongoing civil litigation against Verge’s board, maintaining that the allegations lacked merit. Legal experts point out that reputational and financial impacts can linger, even after investigations close without charges. Therefore, Powell’s priority is rebuilding his public image and defending his philanthropic intentions in court. [Fortune]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948003732758794240</link>
      <description>43 minutes agobeincryptoFBI Ends Kraken Founder Jesse Powell Probe, Returns Seized DevicesThe FBI has officially closed its investigation into Kraken founder Jesse Powell and returned multiple electronic devices seized during a 2023 raid. Federal prosecutors sent Powell a declination letter confirmi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948003732758794240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Launchpool launches Elympics (ELP)On July 23, Gate will launch Elympics (ELP) spot trading for the first time at 20:00 (UTC+8) on July 24, 2025. Staking mining will be launched from 20:00 on July 24, 2025 to 20:00 on August 14, 2025 (UTC+8). Staking ELP and GT to participate in Launchpool will allow you to share ELP tokens for free. Among them, the ELP mining pool is expected to reach an annualized rate of 1303.57%, and the GT mining pool is expected to reach an annualized rate of 4.78%. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947992440597712896</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsGate Launchpool launches Elympics (ELP)On July 23, Gate will launch Elympics (ELP) spot trading for the first time at 20:00 (UTC+8) on July 24, 2025. Staking mining will be launched from 20:00 on July 24, 2025 to 20:00 on August 14, 2025 (UTC+8). Staking ELP and GT to participate</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947992440597712896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has listed Codatta (XNY)According to the official page, Binance Alpha has launched Codatta (XNY). [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947992868064399360</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha has listed Codatta (XNY)According to the official page, Binance Alpha has launched Codatta (XNY). [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947992868064399360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha has listed XNYOn July 23, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched XNY. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947991508812107776</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoTechFlowBinance Alpha has listed XNYOn July 23, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched XNY. [TechFlow]$BNBShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 12:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947991508812107776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Russia is using Kyrgyzstan’s crypto market to bypass sanctions: reportHas Russia turned Kyrgyzstan’s booming crypto market into a backdoor for moving funds? A new report sheds light on how Kyrgyz-registered exchanges are helping Russian networks evade sanctions. According to TRM Labs, Kyrgyzstan’s crypto industry has exploded from near-zero to billions in activity since passing its “On Virtual Assets” law back in 2022. By October 2024, authorities had issued 126 virtual asset service provider (VASP) licenses, with licensed platforms recording $4.2 billion in transactions in the first seven months of 2024 alone. But with the region’s relatively weak oversight on the local industry, the rapid growth has made it an attractive base for entities seeking to bypass sanctions. TRM Labs’ report points to crypto exchanges Grinex and Meer, which sprang up in Kyrgyzstan shortly after U.S. law enforcement disrupted Russia’s Garantex in March 2025. On-chain analysis suggests both firms, suspected to be successors, used similar wallet infrastructure and transaction patterns as Garantex, helping Russian users move funds through A7A5, a Russian ruble-tied stablecoin that has long come under scrutiny. Crypto.news reported earlier in June that an FT research revealed that the A7A5 stablecoin has quietly moved billions since launch, and has ties to sanctioned entities that suggest it may be part of broader efforts to bypass Western sanctions and enable cross-border payments for Russian entities. Another exchange, Envoys Vision Digital Exchange (EVDE), was found to have ties to wallets linked to the Rusich Group, a sanctioned Russian paramilitary organization. Many of these platforms also display signs of being shell companies, including identical registration addresses, shared founders, and recycled contact information, suggesting coordinated or shared illicit control. TRM Labs warns that while Kyrgyzstan may be exploited rather than complicit, weak oversight leaves the door wide open. Without tighter controls on VASP registrations, clearer ownership rules, and stronger checks on shell companies, Russia’s financial networks will keep exploiting the country’s crypto infrastructure. If left unaddressed, similar tactics could also spread to neighboring Kazakhstan and Uzbekistan, which are already rolling out crypto-friendly regulations, undermining international sanctions. [TRM Labs]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983858556801024</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsHow Russia is using Kyrgyzstan’s crypto market to bypass sanctions: reportHas Russia turned Kyrgyzstan’s booming crypto market into a backdoor for moving funds? A new report sheds light on how Kyrgyz-registered exchanges are helping Russian networks evade sanctions. According to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983858556801024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Benson: Trump said he would not fire PowellJuly 23 news, according to Jinshi, US Treasury Secretary Bessant said: We are not in a hurry to nominate the chairman of the Federal Reserve. The Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a little wrong&quot;. (Talking about interest rate decisions) I don&apos;t know what the Fed is thinking. The review of the Federal Reserve may be to set up a committee. The Bank of England has done a good job in reviewing its past monetary policy. The frustration of the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. Trump has said that he will not fire Powell. Economist El-Erian said that Powell should resign, which is a bit surprising. My regular talks with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell are still continuing. (Talking about Bowman as a candidate for Federal Reserve Chairman) Reluctant to reveal the name of the candidate. Powell has not yet indicated that he will leave his position on the board. Since the global financial crisis, regulation has been too strict. Trump always has a plan, it&apos;s just not always obvious. Trump has created the biggest negotiating leverage on tariffs. The selection of a successor to Governor Kugler is being carried out simultaneously. US Treasury Secretary Bessant (talking about Trump&apos;s tariff plan) The market reaction was relatively calm. U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson also said that he believes regional banks are strong contenders for the Federal Reserve chairmanship. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983109521215488</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUS Treasury Secretary Benson: Trump said he would not fire PowellJuly 23 news, according to Jinshi, US Treasury Secretary Bessant said: We are not in a hurry to nominate the chairman of the Federal Reserve. The Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a little wrong&quot;. (Talking about interest rate d</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983109521215488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Evening News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses BONK, becoming the largest Solana ecosystem Meme coin by market cap;
2. Analyst: Ethereum faces short-term pullback risk, but the current increase is still relatively small from a large cycle perspective;
3. Matrixport: The crypto market faces short-term volatility, but the overall upward trend is not over;
4. Merlin Founder: 2.0 upgrade officially released, aiming to create a &quot;yield-generating, tradable&quot; BTC;
5. Tether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits;
6. Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks will outperform Ethereum this cycle;
7. Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach a $15.80M financing agreement to increase Bitcoin holdings;
8. Crypto mining company MARA to issue $850.00M in convertible notes to purchase more Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982797888622592</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyPlanet Evening News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses BONK, becoming the largest Solana ecosystem Meme coin by market cap;
2. Analyst: Ethereum faces short-term pullback risk, but the current increase is still relatively small from a large cycle perspective;
3. Matrixport: The crypto ma</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982797888622592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Trump says he will not fire PowellAccording to Jinshi, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent said, &quot;We are not in a hurry to nominate the Federal Reserve Chairman. Frustration with the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. Trump has said he will not fire Powell. Powell has also not indicated that he will leave his board position.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981973129072640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Trump says he will not fire PowellAccording to Jinshi, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent said, &quot;We are not in a hurry to nominate the Federal Reserve Chairman. Frustration with the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. Trum</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981973129072640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Bessent: Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off&quot;US Treasury Secretary Bessent says the Federal Reserve&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off,&quot; and (regarding interest rate decisions) he doesn&apos;t know what the Federal Reserve is considering. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982806327562240</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTreasury Secretary Bessent: Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off&quot;US Treasury Secretary Bessent says the Federal Reserve&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off,&quot; and (regarding interest rate decisions) he doesn&apos;t know what the Federal Reserve is considering. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982806327562240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate launches the second round of VIP financial carnival, complete the task and win a box of MaotaiOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch the second phase of the &quot;VIP Financial Management Summer Carnival&quot; for a limited time. The registration period is from 18:00 on July 22 to 18:00 on August 5 (UTC+8). After VIP users complete the registration, participate in Yubibao Financial Management and complete the challenge to win a whole box of Feitian Moutai. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981438208512000</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsGate launches the second round of VIP financial carnival, complete the task and win a box of MaotaiOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch the second phase of the &quot;VIP Financial Management Summer Carnival&quot; for a limited time. The registration period is fr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981438208512000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) on Binance Smart Chain (BSC), causing losses of more than $600,000. Since the contract is not open source, investigations show that the vulnerability stems from the lack of slippage protection, and the attacker used a fake liquidity pool to harvest TA tokens (0x539ae81a166e5e80aed211731563e549c411b140) and sold them in a legitimate pool for profit. BlockSec Phalcon strongly recommends that users who have authorized the contract immediately revoke permissions to prevent further losses. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSecurity agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly impose a 30% tariff on US products worth about 100.00 billion euros (about 117.00 billion US dollars). A spokesman for the European Commission said on Wednesday that as part of the first wave of countermeasures, the EU will combine the already approved tariff list for 21.00 billion euros of US goods and the previously proposed tariff list for another 72.00 billion euros of US products into a package. According to people familiar with the matter, US exports, including Boeing aircraft, US-made cars and industrial products such as bourbon whiskey, will face tariffs matching Trump&apos;s threat of 30%. These people said that the tariffs will be ready to take effect next month, but only if the negotiations break down and the United States implements its tax measures after the August deadline. An unnamed government official said that in the absence of an agreement, Berlin is even willing to support the activation of the EU&apos;s &quot;anti-coercion tool&quot; (ACI). This tool will only be activated if an agreement cannot be reached. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsEU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly impose</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+8) on July 23. At the same time, the relevant tokens will no longer support Simple Earn and flexible lending services. (This news was generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyOKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+8) o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>