<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>10K Declares Failure, Airdrops Over $2.30M to Presale ParticipantsWatch-to-earn project 10kdotworld announced its failure due to issues such as presale pressure, bot farming, and creator access. The project team used the WATCHCOIN treasury, originally intended for rewards, to airdrop over $2.30M worth of WATCHCOIN tokens to users who participated in the presale. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947856325635018752</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNews10K Declares Failure, Airdrops Over $2.30M to Presale ParticipantsWatch-to-earn project 10kdotworld announced its failure due to issues such as presale pressure, bot farming, and creator access. The project team used the WATCHCOIN treasury, originally intended for rewards,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947856325635018752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches $50,000 KOKOK Trading Event to Support Solana Meme Ecosystem DevelopmentAccording to official news, Bitget Wallet launched a KOKOK trading event with a total prize pool of $50,000.00 from July 22nd to July 29th. Rewards will be distributed based on the user&apos;s total KOKOK trading volume. The higher the trading volume, the more rewards will be received. The top 10 traders will also share an exclusive prize pool. Participants can also get additional lottery tickets for the weekly FOMO Thursdays staking event. KOKOK is one of the fastest-growing meme coins in the Solana ecosystem recently. According to on-chain data, the total market value of Solana meme coins has exceeded $14.00B, and daily protocol fees on platforms such as Bonk.fun exceed $1.00M. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947854234732531712</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoTechFlowBitget Wallet Launches $50,000 KOKOK Trading Event to Support Solana Meme Ecosystem DevelopmentAccording to official news, Bitget Wallet launched a KOKOK trading event with a total prize pool of $50,000.00 from July 22nd to July 29th. Rewards will be distributed based on the us</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947854234732531712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Exchange Launches New &quot;Spot Pro&quot; System, Further Improving Performance and ExperienceOn July 23, according to an announcement by WEEX Exchange, in order to continuously optimize the trading experience, WEEX launched a new &quot;Spot Pro&quot; system, completely replacing the old spot system. The new system performance reaches 20,000 TPS, and the matching efficiency is greatly improved; placing and canceling orders is smoother, and data is pushed more timely; slippage is smaller, and the transaction price is better; it will support 3,000+ currency pairs, and the liquidity is stronger; the fund account is separated from the trading account, and asset management is clearer. WEEX reminds users to update the App version as soon as possible, and transfer the assets of the original &quot;Spot&quot; account to the &quot;Spot Pro&quot; account with one click. Before 17:59 on July 27, users who meet the conditions can receive 1 - 5 U contract experience funds after completing the transfer, and enjoy 0 transaction fees for all currencies in &quot;Spot Pro&quot;. After that, the system will automatically transfer, and the old &quot;Spot&quot; system will be offline on August 1. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947854211043102720</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoTechFlowWEEX Exchange Launches New &quot;Spot Pro&quot; System, Further Improving Performance and ExperienceOn July 23, according to an announcement by WEEX Exchange, in order to continuously optimize the trading experience, WEEX launched a new &quot;Spot Pro&quot; system, completely replacing the old spo</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947854211043102720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to ban public sector from making ransomware paymentsThe UK will prohibit its public sector, such as its health service and local councils, from paying ransomware in a bid to “smash the cyber criminal business model.”</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947851431100354560</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoPANewsUK to ban public sector from making ransomware paymentsThe UK will prohibit its public sector, such as its health service and local councils, from paying ransomware in a bid to “smash the cyber criminal business model.”Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947851431100354560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLG hacker deposits ~$746,000.00 into Tornado CashCertiK&apos;s Alert System detected approximately 140.7 BNB (approximately $746,000.00 USD) being deposited into Tornado Cash, with these funds being related to the GLG hack that occurred on July 21st. The hacker minted 8.50M tokens from the Mint contract and sold them for 745,000.00 BSC-USD. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947851500700635136</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoForesightNewsGLG hacker deposits ~$746,000.00 into Tornado CashCertiK&apos;s Alert System detected approximately 140.7 BNB (approximately $746,000.00 USD) being deposited into Tornado Cash, with these funds being related to the GLG hack that occurred on July 21st. The hacker minted 8.50M to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947851500700635136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH strategic reserves reach a record high of $7.00BOn July 23, according to Strategic Eth Reserve data, the total strategic ETH reserve has reached 1.87M ETH (approximately $7.00B), with 58 participating entities, accounting for 1.55% of the total ETH supply. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947851389861957632</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoTechFlowETH strategic reserves reach a record high of $7.00BOn July 23, according to Strategic Eth Reserve data, the total strategic ETH reserve has reached 1.87M ETH (approximately $7.00B), with 58 participating entities, accounting for 1.55% of the total ETH supply. [TechFlow]#Layer1</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947851389861957632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USELESS adopts the Chainlink CCIP standard to achieve cross-chain functionality between BNB Chain and SolanaUSELESS Announces Adoption of Chainlink CCIP Standard, USELESS Can Now Achieve Native Transfers Between BNB Chain and Solana. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947850833462366208</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoForesightNewsUSELESS adopts the Chainlink CCIP standard to achieve cross-chain functionality between BNB Chain and SolanaUSELESS Announces Adoption of Chainlink CCIP Standard, USELESS Can Now Achieve Native Transfers Between BNB Chain and Solana. [Foresight News]#Layer1$BNB$MAG7.SSI$SO</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947850833462366208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDC Enterprise plans to increase its Bitcoin holdings to 10,000 by the end of this yearOn July 23, according to Businesswire, Norma Chu, founder, chairman, and CEO of DDC Enterprise, a NYSE-listed company, published a shareholder letter, which pointed out that it received a $528.00 million transformation capital commitment earlier this month. So far, investors such as Anson Funds, Animoca Brands, and Kenetic Capital have provided about $53.00 million in initial financing funds. It has now submitted a general F-3 shelved registration statement to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. The shelved registration will allow it to conduct a rights issue of up to $500.00 million to support its Bitcoin expansion strategy. In addition, the company also announced a new Bitcoin increase plan: it plans to increase its Bitcoin holdings to 10,000 by the end of 2025, and become one of the top three listed companies using a Bitcoin reserve strategy within three years. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947850023043141632</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoPANewsDDC Enterprise plans to increase its Bitcoin holdings to 10,000 by the end of this yearOn July 23, according to Businesswire, Norma Chu, founder, chairman, and CEO of DDC Enterprise, a NYSE-listed company, published a shareholder letter, which pointed out that it received a $528.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947850023043141632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch DNUT, YALA, and COA spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23:

Spot trading pairs

DNUT/USDT (July 23, 12:00 UTC+8): The DNUT token is a meme coin on the Solana blockchain.

YALA/USDT (July 23, 12:00 UTC+8): $YALA is the native token of the Yala project. Yala enables BTC holders to earn yield and move liquidity between ecosystems, blockchains, and protocols.

COA/USDT (July 23, 18:20 UTC+8): $COA is the native token of the Alliance Games project. Alliance Games is a decentralized infrastructure platform built specifically for game development and hosting. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947848389236641792</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch DNUT, YALA, and COA spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23:

Spot trading pairs

DNUT/USDT (July 23, 12:00 UTC+8): The DNUT token is a meme coin on the Solana bl</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947848389236641792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese media: Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba to announce his resignation at the end of AugustAccording to Japan&apos;s Mainichi Shimbun, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba has indicated to those around him that he will announce his intention to resign no later than August, based on the results of the House of Councillors election compiled by the Liberal Democratic Party (LDP) in August. It is reported that Ishiba plans to hold talks with LDP Chief Advisor Taro Aso, LDP Vice President Yoshihide Suga, and former Prime Minister Fumio Kishida on the same day to discuss his personal future. Ishiba immediately expressed his intention to stay in office after the crushing defeat in the House of Councillors election, but he is currently facing growing calls for his resignation and criticism within the party, and the timing of his final decision may still change. In addition to local organizations across the country demanding the Prime Minister&apos;s resignation and reform of the party structure, veteran and young lawmakers have also proposed convening a &quot;General Meeting of Members of Both Houses,&quot; a decision-making body second only to the party convention, to demand an early election vote. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947848208848015360</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoForesightNewsJapanese media: Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba to announce his resignation at the end of AugustAccording to Japan&apos;s Mainichi Shimbun, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba has indicated to those around him that he will announce his intention to resign no later tha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947848208848015360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale PENGU short position was liquidated last night and lost $13.15 million, and then reopened the short positionOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the PENGU 3x short position at address 0x670...af6e0 was liquidated at 9 o&apos;clock last night and lost $13.15 million. He then opened an ant position of 2x PENGU short position, worth $520,000, with a current floating loss of $100,000. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947845428804603904</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsA whale PENGU short position was liquidated last night and lost $13.15 million, and then reopened the short positionOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the PENGU 3x short position at address 0x670...af6e0 was liquidated at 9 o&apos;clock last nigh</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947845428804603904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eddie Yue: Avoid over-hyping stablecoins; only a few stablecoin licenses will be issued in the initial phase.According to Jinshi, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, spoke again about stablecoins, saying that with the recent hype surrounding the concept of stablecoins, the market has seen excessive excitement. Some listed companies, regardless of whether their main business is related to stablecoins or digital assets, have seen their share prices rise and stock trading volume increase significantly as soon as they announce their intention to develop stablecoin business, which is like turning stone into gold, and the company&apos;s visibility has also been greatly improved. In fact, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority has made it clear earlier that it will only issue a few stablecoin licenses at most in the initial stage, which means that there will be many disappointed parties. Even if a license is obtained, based on our desire for steady development, coupled with the resources required in the initial stage, the contribution to the company&apos;s short-term profits will be uncertain to a certain extent. We hope that investors will remain calm when digesting the market&apos;s &quot;positive&quot; news. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947843966460514304</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoForesightNewsEddie Yue: Avoid over-hyping stablecoins; only a few stablecoin licenses will be issued in the initial phase.According to Jinshi, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, spoke again about stablecoins, saying that with the recent hype surrounding the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947843966460514304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of rules for stablecoin issuers next weekOn July 23, according to Zhitong Finance, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority will release a summary of the rules for stablecoin issuers next week. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842454397145088</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsHong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of rules for stablecoin issuers next weekOn July 23, according to Zhitong Finance, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority will release a summary of the rules for stablecoin issuers next week. [PANews]#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842454397145088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoSoMacro | Trump Secures Asia Trade Wins as China Talks LoomTrump secures Japan, Philippines trade deals; China-U.S. talks expected Monday; Powell addresses regulatory meeting.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842386927316992</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSoValueSoSoMacro | Trump Secures Asia Trade Wins as China Talks LoomTrump secures Japan, Philippines trade deals; China-U.S. talks expected Monday; Powell addresses regulatory meeting.#Macro$SOSOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842386927316992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Data Exchange held a closed-door seminar on &quot;New Opportunities in the Capital Market: RDA&quot; to discuss topics such as RWA.On July 23, according to the WeChat public account of Shanghai Data Exchange, as introduced by Jinshi, on July 21, Shanghai Data Exchange held a closed-door seminar on &quot;New Opportunities in the Capital Market: RDA&quot;. More than ten financial institutions including Cathay Haitong Securities, CITIC Construction Investment Securities, CICC, Orient Securities, Ping An Securities, Huaxin Securities, Shanxi Securities, Zheshang Securities, Tianfeng Asset Management, Huatai Asset Management, and Debang Asset Management attended the seminar to discuss key topics such as data value, RWA and RDA. Shanghai Data Exchange proposed the new RDA paradigm for the first time, emphasizing the anchoring of real-number integrated physical assets, and the role of data in authenticity verification and value enhancement of other physical assets. On the one hand, RDA can help accelerate the process of marketization and value of data elements, and on the other hand, it can promote the coordinated development of data elements and other elements, improve the docking efficiency of physical assets and capital, promote the development of new quality productivity, and promote the implementation of the deep integration system of the real economy and the digital economy. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947841779663654912</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsShanghai Data Exchange held a closed-door seminar on &quot;New Opportunities in the Capital Market: RDA&quot; to discuss topics such as RWA.On July 23, according to the WeChat public account of Shanghai Data Exchange, as introduced by Jinshi, on July 21, Shanghai Data Exchange held a closed-do</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947841779663654912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hut 8 Subsidiary Obtains Dubai International Financial Centre LicenseBitcoin mining firm Hut 8 Corp. has announced that its subsidiary, Hut 8 Investment Ltd, has obtained a commercial license from the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC). The license authorizes it to conduct proprietary investments and certain non-financial commercial activities within the DIFC&apos;s legal and regulatory framework based on international standards and common law principles. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947840403621564416</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsHut 8 Subsidiary Obtains Dubai International Financial Centre LicenseBitcoin mining firm Hut 8 Corp. has announced that its subsidiary, Hut 8 Investment Ltd, has obtained a commercial license from the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC). The license authorizes it to co</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947840403621564416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 23Today in 2024, the Ethereum spot ETF was officially approved for listing and trading.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123314462720</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 23Today in 2024, the Ethereum spot ETF was officially approved for listing and trading.#ETF$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123314462720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created wallet received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet further received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M. Currently, the wallet holds 105,977 ETH, worth approximately $396.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123511595008</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsA newly created wallet received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet further received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M. Currently, the wallet holds 105,977 ETH, worth approximate</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123511595008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Traded MEI Pharma Completes $100.00M Private Placement for Litecoin Strategic ReservePublicly traded MEI Pharma completes $100 million private placement, selling 29,239,767 shares of common stock at $3.42 per share (or in lieu thereof, pre-funded warrants). MEI has appointed Litecoin founder and PIPE lead investor Charlie Lee to its board of directors and GSR as its digital asset and treasury management advisor to oversee the implementation of its Litecoin strategic reserve. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123356405760</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsPublicly Traded MEI Pharma Completes $100.00M Private Placement for Litecoin Strategic ReservePublicly traded MEI Pharma completes $100 million private placement, selling 29,239,767 shares of common stock at $3.42 per share (or in lieu thereof, pre-funded warrants). MEI has ap</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123356405760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale shorted 1,817.69 BTC with a margin of 36.200 million USDOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;10 big targets first&quot; whale made another move, starting with a short position of 1,817.69 BTC (about $217.00 million), with a margin of $36.20 million and an opening price of $119,425.00. According to the position screenshot of @Jason60704294, the position may have been opened on Binance, but it was not displayed in &quot;Contract Smart Money&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837422796820480</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsA whale shorted 1,817.69 BTC with a margin of 36.200 million USDOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;10 big targets first&quot; whale made another move, starting with a short position of 1,817.69 BTC (about $217.00 million), with a margin of $36.2</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837422796820480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>