<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:35:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>KeyCorp CEO: If customers have demand for cryptocurrency, we will provide corresponding services to meet this demandOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, the CEO of KeyCorp Bank, which has an asset size of US$185.00 billion, said, &quot;As long as our customers have demand for cryptocurrencies and want to use them as a means of storing value and hold them in their wallets, we will meet this demand (provide corresponding services).&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948255320182165504</link>
      <description>53seconds agoPANewsKeyCorp CEO: If customers have demand for cryptocurrency, we will provide corresponding services to meet this demandOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, the CEO of KeyCorp Bank, which has an asset size of US$185.00 billion, said, &quot;As long as our customers have demand for crypto</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948255320182165504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Onchain Trading Lists Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, and Other TokensBitget Onchain Trading has launched MEME tokens Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, ORGO, ZKWASM, TRUST, COA, and DEBT from the Solana, Base, and BNB Smart Chain ecosystems. Users can start trading in the Onchain Trading section. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948255223381823488</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Onchain Trading Lists Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, and Other TokensBitget Onchain Trading has launched MEME tokens Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, ORGO, ZKWASM, TRUST, COA, and DEBT from the Solana, Base, and BNB Smart Chain ecosystems. Users can start trading in the Onchai</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948255223381823488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dexari self-custody trading app officially launched on iOS and Android, no invitation code required, supports up to 40x leverage tradingDexari has announced the official launch of its self-custody trading app on iOS and Android platforms, with no invitation code required for user registration. The platform is powered by Hyperliquid and supports spot and perpetual contract trading with up to 40x leverage, featuring advanced orders, TradingView charts, no KYC, no blocking, and a MoonPay fiat gateway. Currently, Dexari is in the preliminary stage of points accumulation, with snapshots to be completed soon. Users can earn points and USDC rewards through trading, inviting friends (25% profit sharing + 10% commission discount), and participating in social tasks. In addition, Dexari has launched a content creation reward campaign (UGC Campaign), announcing winners weekly with a total prize pool of over $5,000.00, and participants can receive up to 80% commission discounts, Discord identity badges, and additional points rewards. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254596715057152</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoOdailyDexari self-custody trading app officially launched on iOS and Android, no invitation code required, supports up to 40x leverage tradingDexari has announced the official launch of its self-custody trading app on iOS and Android platforms, with no invitation code required for user</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254596715057152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Afternoon News1. Trump will visit the Federal Reserve on Thursday;
2. Azuki partners with OpenSea to release Mizuki short film ERC-1155 collectibles;
3. Nasdaq-listed Lion Group increases its holdings of SUI tokens, bringing the total investment portfolio to $9.60M;
4. GSR withdrew approximately $9.87M worth of ETH from Binance 2 hours ago and transferred it to an associated wallet;
5. Faraday Future, under Jia Yueting, announces a strategic partnership with digital asset infrastructure platform HabitTrade;
6. Arkham: The U.S. government&apos;s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000;
7. Bithumb will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs;
8. A whale has closed its PUMP short position, profiting a total of $2.45M;
9. Bitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $85.96M yesterday, continuing the net outflow for 3 consecutive days;
10. Ethereum spot ETFs had a total net inflow of $332.00M yesterday, continuing the net inflow for 14 consecutive days.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254605149802496</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoOdailyPlanet Afternoon News1. Trump will visit the Federal Reserve on Thursday;
2. Azuki partners with OpenSea to release Mizuki short film ERC-1155 collectibles;
3. Nasdaq-listed Lion Group increases its holdings of SUI tokens, bringing the total investment portfolio to $9.60M;
4. GSR</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254605149802496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zircuit to Launch AI Trading Engine &quot;Hyperliquid for AI Trading,&quot; Expanding $950.00M Deposit EcosystemZircuit has announced the launch of an AI trading engine, &quot;Hyperliquid for AI Trading,&quot; which supports cross-chain automated execution on EVM and Solana chains, and provides real-time signal capture and one-click trading strategy deployment. The trading engine has several core features, including: AI signal detection, optimal path cross-chain execution, gas and slippage management automation, and security protection inherited from the Zircuit Vault system. The product is currently in closed beta and will be open to the world in August 2025, with an ecosystem incentive program to be launched in Q4 (allocating a total of 10.00M ZRC for community-built AI models). Previously, Zircuit launched the on-chain yield product &quot;Deposit Vaults,&quot; which currently manages over $950.00M in assets, covering stablecoins, ETH, and BTC. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254613605519360</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoOdailyZircuit to Launch AI Trading Engine &quot;Hyperliquid for AI Trading,&quot; Expanding $950.00M Deposit EcosystemZircuit has announced the launch of an AI trading engine, &quot;Hyperliquid for AI Trading,&quot; which supports cross-chain automated execution on EVM and Solana chains, and provides real-</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254613605519360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Proposes Increasing Block Limit to 100M CU via SIMD-0286 ProposalAccording to Cointelegraph, Solana plans to increase block capacity by 66% from 60.00M CU to 100.00M CU through the SIMD-0286 proposal. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948253509324967936</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNewsSolana Proposes Increasing Block Limit to 100M CU via SIMD-0286 ProposalAccording to Cointelegraph, Solana plans to increase block capacity by 66% from 60.00M CU to 100.00M CU through the SIMD-0286 proposal. [Foresight News]#Layer1$MAG7.SSI$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948253509324967936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiNFT index 24hr loss of 10.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has fallen by 10.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU -11.35%, APE -10.12%, SUPER -9.98%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948248825549250560</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiNFT index 24hr loss of 10.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has fallen by 10.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU -11.35%, APE -10.12%, SUPER -9.98%.$APE$SUPER$PENGUShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948248825549250560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority: It is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the public from August 1.The Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, Eddie Yue, reminded the public that there have recently been fraudulent activities involving the promotion of digital assets and stablecoins, causing losses to the public. The &quot;Stablecoin Ordinance&quot; came into effect on August 1st, and according to the ordinance, it is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the Hong Kong public from the effective date. Eddie Yue revealed that the greater focus of central banks and financial regulatory authorities in various countries recently is on how to prevent stablecoins from being used as money laundering tools by criminals, especially in cross-border use scenarios. The Bank for International Settlements devoted considerable space in its latest annual economic report to emphasizing the importance of preventing stablecoin money laundering risks. Eddie Yue believes that a balance between strictness and flexibility is an art of regulation. After all, the regulated stablecoin business is in its initial stage. It is obviously more conducive to the sustainable and healthy development of the market and issuing institutions to be strict and stable first, and then moderately relax according to practical experience, rather than starting too loosely and then cleaning up the chaos. [Securities Times]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948247042186350592</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoOdailyHong Kong Monetary Authority: It is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the public from August 1.The Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, Eddie Yue, reminded the public that there have recently been fraudulent activities involving the promotion of dig</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948247042186350592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azuki Announces Collaboration with OpenSea to Release &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts&quot; NFT CollectionAzuki has announced a collaboration with OpenSea to release an ERC-1155 collectible, &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts,&quot; based on the &quot;Mizuki&quot; animated short film. The proceeds will be used to support the production of the short film and creators&apos; work. The first round of Mint will be open for 1 week, followed by a regular Mint that will last for 6 months, priced at 0.0014 ETH, with no wallet or whitelist restrictions. In the last cycle, Azuki raised over 20,000 ETH through the Elemental Beans series. After the reveal, the works were criticized for lacking originality and resembling old works, which triggered strong dissatisfaction in the community. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948241940276908032</link>
      <description>54 minutes ago吴说Azuki Announces Collaboration with OpenSea to Release &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts&quot; NFT CollectionAzuki has announced a collaboration with OpenSea to release an ERC-1155 collectible, &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts,&quot; based on the &quot;Mizuki&quot; animated short film. The proceeds will be used to su</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948241940276908032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale withdrew 76,000 SOL again and staked them, with cumulative withdrawals reaching 164,000 SOL.According to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale today again withdrew 76,000 SOL from Kraken, worth approximately $14.50M. Since July 8, the address has cumulatively withdrawn 164,000 SOL (approximately $30.14M) from Kraken and used them for staking. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948239496893501440</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA certain whale withdrew 76,000 SOL again and staked them, with cumulative withdrawals reaching 164,000 SOL.According to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale today again withdrew 76,000 SOL from Kraken, worth approximately $14.50M. Since July 8, the address has cumulatively withdrawn 164,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948239496893501440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese artist Takashi Murakami to launch NFT trading cards on-chain via Base AppRenowned Japanese artist Takashi Murakami has announced the launch of his NFT series, &quot;108 Flowers Revised.&quot; Based on his iconic &quot;Superflat&quot; style floral imagery, the series will be available for minting on the Base App on July 31. This new work continues his creative style of blending pop culture with anime aesthetics, and his past collaborators include luxury and trendy brands such as Louis Vuitton and Supreme. It is worth noting that a large number of NFTs issued by Takashi Murakami last week have fallen sharply in price, resulting in heavy losses for investors. [TheBlock]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948236995398012928</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Japanese artist Takashi Murakami to launch NFT trading cards on-chain via Base AppRenowned Japanese artist Takashi Murakami has announced the launch of his NFT series, &quot;108 Flowers Revised.&quot; Based on his iconic &quot;Superflat&quot; style floral imagery, the series will be available for minting on</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948236995398012928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOAT Network One Piece Season 3 is now live, with over 2 Bitcoin in past on-chain incentives.GOAT Network officially launched Season 3 of One Piece last week, which is also the final round of community LFG before the TGE. Throughout the One Piece campaign, GOAT has continuously driven real user engagement through on-chain tasks designed around yield. In addition to airdrop rewards, more than 2.00 BTC in incentives have already been distributed through pre-mining tasks and Artemis staking, and Artemis stakers continue to receive BTC rewards daily. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948233210500026368</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsGOAT Network One Piece Season 3 is now live, with over 2 Bitcoin in past on-chain incentives.GOAT Network officially launched Season 3 of One Piece last week, which is also the final round of community LFG before the TGE. Throughout the One Piece campaign, GOAT has continuousl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948233210500026368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraday Future and HabitTrade Reach Strategic CooperationAccording to Gelonghui, Faraday Future announced a strategic partnership with HabitTrade. HabitTrade is a global multi-market broker and digital asset infrastructure platform. FF stated that it plans to leverage this partnership to provide its shareholders with exclusive offers on the HabitTrade platform, further enhancing shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial services. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948234456833265664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyFaraday Future and HabitTrade Reach Strategic CooperationAccording to Gelonghui, Faraday Future announced a strategic partnership with HabitTrade. HabitTrade is a global multi-market broker and digital asset infrastructure platform. FF stated that it plans to leverage this partnershi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948234456833265664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase Believes Prediction of Stablecoin Market Cap Increasing to $2 Trillion is &quot;Slightly Optimistic&quot;According to The Economic Times, JPMorgan Chase believes that the often-mentioned prediction that the stablecoin market could grow to $2.00T is &quot;slightly optimistic&quot; in the recent push for the first approval of cryptocurrency market regulation legislation in the United States. Currently, the market capitalization of all stablecoins is approximately $260.00B. JPMorgan Chase stated, &quot;We find it hard to believe that the market can grow significantly in the coming years, as the infrastructure/ecosystem supporting stablecoins is far from developed and will take time to build.&quot; Despite the recent increase in market interest in stablecoins, they still account for less than 1% of global capital flows, indicating that this digital asset still has a long way to go in disrupting the financial system. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231322014650368</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsJPMorgan Chase Believes Prediction of Stablecoin Market Cap Increasing to $2 Trillion is &quot;Slightly Optimistic&quot;According to The Economic Times, JPMorgan Chase believes that the often-mentioned prediction that the stablecoin market could grow to $2.00T is &quot;slightly optimistic&quot; i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231322014650368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong 70-Year-Old Man Falls Victim to Cryptocurrency Romance ScamA 70-year-old retired Hong Kong man received a message on WhatsApp from someone claiming to be a female neighbor, which led to a &quot;twilight romance,&quot; but he never met the person. The woman claimed to work at the Singapore Exchange and have insider information on some cryptocurrency investments, falsely claiming that he would receive substantial returns. The man transferred a total of HK$3,272,700.00 in 37 transactions to 34 bank accounts provided by the woman. It was not until the man personally went to the bank to withdraw a large sum of cash because he had reached the ATM withdrawal limit that bank staff noticed the transaction was unusual and immediately notified the Anti-Deception Coordination Centre, which finally exposed the scam. The man lost more than HK$3.27M in total and incurred nearly HK$1M in debt as a result. Hong Kong police said they had received nearly 20 online romance scams related to investment in the past two weeks, with 40% of the victims being over 60 years old, with a total loss of more than HK$10.00M. [Wenweipo Hong Kong]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229840624226304</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Hong Kong 70-Year-Old Man Falls Victim to Cryptocurrency Romance ScamA 70-year-old retired Hong Kong man received a message on WhatsApp from someone claiming to be a female neighbor, which led to a &quot;twilight romance,&quot; but he never met the person. The woman claimed to work at the Singapor</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229840624226304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday, marking a 3 days of consistent outflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 23th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net inflow yesterday was BlackRock&apos;s ETF IBIT, with a daily net inflow of 142.56M USD, and the total historical net inflow of IBIT currently stands at 57.12B USD.The second highest was Grayscale Bitcoin Mini Trust ETF BTC, with a daily net inflow of 10.49M USD, and the total historical net inflow of BTC currently stands at 1.66B USD.The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net outflow yesterday was Fidelity&apos;s ETF FBTC, with a daily net outflow of 227.24M USD, and the total historical net inflow of FBTC currently stands at 12.32B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 153.25B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.53%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.47B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229479523504128</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday, marking a 3 days of consistent outflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 23th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net inflow y</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229479523504128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly listed company Lion Group announces total cryptocurrency acquisition costs have reached $9.60 millionOn July 24, Lion Group (NASDAQ: LGHL) announced that it has purchased additional SUI tokens, bringing the total acquisition cost of its HYPE, SOL and SUI tokens to approximately $9.6 million. These tokens are a core component of LGHL&apos;s strategic reserve funds, which are dedicated to investing in the next-generation Layer-1 blockchain ecosystem. As of July 23, 2025, LGHL&apos;s reserve asset holdings are as follows: 128,929 HYPE, 6,629 SOL, and 1,015,680 SUI. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948228893512634368</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsPublicly listed company Lion Group announces total cryptocurrency acquisition costs have reached $9.60 millionOn July 24, Lion Group (NASDAQ: LGHL) announced that it has purchased additional SUI tokens, bringing the total acquisition cost of its HYPE, SOL and SUI tokens to approximat</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948228893512634368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkham: The US government’s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000Arkham stated that the US government has not sold its 170,000 BTC (about $20 billion) in the past four months. Among them, the US Marshals Service (USMS) currently holds about 28,988 BTC (about $3.4 billion), while other agencies such as the FBI, the Department of Justice (DOJ), the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) and local prosecutors&apos; offices hold at least 198,000 BTC (about $23.5 billion) in total. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227735171698688</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsArkham: The US government’s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000Arkham stated that the US government has not sold its 170,000 BTC (about $20 billion) in the past four months. Among them, the US Marshals Service (USMS) currently holds about 28,988 BTC (about $3.4 billion), while ot</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227735171698688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller Joins Paradigm TeamParadigm co-founder Matt Huang tweeted that former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller has joined the Paradigm team to help its portfolio design in cutting-edge areas. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227236993241088</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsFormer OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller Joins Paradigm TeamParadigm co-founder Matt Huang tweeted that former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller has joined the Paradigm team to help its portfolio design in cutting-edge areas. [Foresight News]#FundraisingShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227236993241088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripple: Beware of XRP-related scams on YouTubeOn July 24, Ripple issued a warning on the X platform, noting that XRP-related scams are increasing on the YouTube platform. After the scammers steal the account, they will update the page content and pretend to be the official Ripple account. Ripple or the company&apos;s executives will never ask users to send them XRP. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948224201592213504</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsRipple: Beware of XRP-related scams on YouTubeOn July 24, Ripple issued a warning on the X platform, noting that XRP-related scams are increasing on the YouTube platform. After the scammers steal the account, they will update the page content and pretend to be the official Ripple ac</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948224201592213504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 05:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>