<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:11:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Research allocates ENS again after a year, withdraws $5.5 million worth of ENS from BinanceOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, Trend Research, which is affiliated with LD Capital, has configured ENS again after a year. 10 hours ago, 203,105 ENS (worth $5.5 million) were withdrawn from Binance. A year ago, it made a swing trade of 80,000 ENS and left the market with an estimated loss of $122,000.00 based on the deposit and withdrawal prices. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947826282624733184</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsTrend Research allocates ENS again after a year, withdraws $5.5 million worth of ENS from BinanceOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, Trend Research, which is affiliated with LD Capital, has configured ENS again after a year. 10 hours ago, 203,1</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947826282624733184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Research Buys ENS Again After a Year, Spending $5.50MAccording to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, Trend Research, associated with LD Capital, withdrew 203,105 ENS from Binance 10 hours ago, worth approximately $5.50M. A year ago, the institution conducted a swing trade of 80,000 ENS, and it is estimated that it lost approximately $122,000.00 USD based on the deposit and withdrawal prices. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825939421614080</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsTrend Research Buys ENS Again After a Year, Spending $5.50MAccording to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, Trend Research, associated with LD Capital, withdrew 203,105 ENS from Binance 10 hours ago, worth approximately $5.50M. A year ago, the institution conducted a swing trade of 80</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825939421614080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Finance has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission to provide digital asset deposit and withdrawal servicesOn July 23, according to PR Newswire, Eddid Financial announced that its Eddid Securities and Futures has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission to provide digital asset deposit and withdrawal services, laying the foundation for the group to further develop digital asset transactions in the future, including stablecoins and tokenized physical asset (RWA) product distribution. The group&apos;s flagship trading application Eddid ONE will also be upgraded, and investors will be able to directly deposit and withdraw a variety of cryptocurrencies, including BTC, ETH, USDC, USDT, and USDT-TRC. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825589260144640</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoPANewsEd Finance has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission to provide digital asset deposit and withdrawal servicesOn July 23, according to PR Newswire, Eddid Financial announced that its Eddid Securities and Futures has been approved by the Hong Kong Securitie</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825589260144640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum ICO Participant Wakes Up After Four Years of Dormancy, Transfers 800 ETH, Profits Over $13.36MAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, an Ethereum ICO participant deposited 800 ETH, worth approximately $2.96M, into Kraken after four years of dormancy. This participant obtained 8,950 ETH at a price of $2,783.00 and still holds 1,780 ETH, worth approximately $6.66M. The participant has realized a profit of $13.36M, with a return of 480x. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825286691442688</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNewsEthereum ICO Participant Wakes Up After Four Years of Dormancy, Transfers 800 ETH, Profits Over $13.36MAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, an Ethereum ICO participant deposited 800 ETH, worth approximately $2.96M, into Kraken after four years of dormancy. This participant</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825286691442688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine Announces It Will Use All Net Proceeds from ARK Invest Share Acquisition to Purchase EthereumBitmine announced that it will use all net proceeds ($177.00M) from the $182.00M ARK Invest share acquisition deal to purchase more Ethereum and deposit it into its vault. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825286804688896</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsBitmine Announces It Will Use All Net Proceeds from ARK Invest Share Acquisition to Purchase EthereumBitmine announced that it will use all net proceeds ($177.00M) from the $182.00M ARK Invest share acquisition deal to purchase more Ethereum and deposit it into its vault. [</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825286804688896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CIO Predicts: ETPs and Financial Firms Will Purchase $20.00B Worth of ETH Next YearBitwise CIO Matt Hougan said that since May 15, the Ethereum spot ETP market has seen inflows of over $5.00B, and listed companies such as Bitmine and SharpLink have announced Ethereum strategic reserves. ETPs and corporate treasuries have collectively purchased 2.83M ETH, worth over $10.00B, equivalent to 32 times the net new supply over the same period. He predicts that ETPs and financial companies will purchase $20.00B worth of ETH next year, equivalent to 5.33M ETH at current prices, equivalent to 7 times the net new supply over the same period. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947824307405344768</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsBitwise CIO Predicts: ETPs and Financial Firms Will Purchase $20.00B Worth of ETH Next YearBitwise CIO Matt Hougan said that since May 15, the Ethereum spot ETP market has seen inflows of over $5.00B, and listed companies such as Bitmine and SharpLink have announced Ethereu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947824307405344768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street giant Citadel Securities calls on the SEC not to provide securities rule exemptions for tokenized stocksOn July 23 that according to The Block, Citadel Securities, one of the world&apos;s largest market makers, submitted a letter to the SEC Crypto Working Group, opposing the provision of securities rule exemptions for tokenized stocks. The company believes that such assets may lead to a loss of liquidity in traditional markets and create the risk of investors confusing the issuer.
Citadel emphasized in the letter that although it supports technological innovation, issuing &quot;securities-like&quot; products using regulatory arbitrage is not real innovation. This position was echoed by Republican SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce, who made it clear that tokenized securities still need to comply with existing securities regulations. SEC Chairman Paul Atkins revealed last week that the agency is studying an &quot;innovation exemption&quot; mechanism that allows new types of transactions. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947823059855757312</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsWall Street giant Citadel Securities calls on the SEC not to provide securities rule exemptions for tokenized stocksOn July 23 that according to The Block, Citadel Securities, one of the world&apos;s largest market makers, submitted a letter to the SEC Crypto Working Group, opposing t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947823059855757312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins NFTs Genesis 4th AnniversaryPudgy Penguins NFTs officially opened for minting 4 years ago today. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947821523054383104</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoForesightNewsPudgy Penguins NFTs Genesis 4th AnniversaryPudgy Penguins NFTs officially opened for minting 4 years ago today. [Foresight News]#NFTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947821523054383104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is currently about 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024On July 23, according to CoinDesk, the size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is about 519,000 ETH (worth about $1.9 billion), a record high since January 2024, and the current exit waiting time exceeds 9 days. Analysis pointed out that this is mainly related to the profit-taking of stakers after the ETH price rose 160% from the low point in April. Data shows that despite the exit wave, the demand for Ethereum staking remains strong - there are currently 357,000 ETH (worth $1.3 billion) waiting to enter the staking queue, with a waiting time of more than 6 days. This phenomenon is partly due to the continued increase in holdings by Ethereum treasury companies such as SharpLink Gaming, and the increase in institutional participation after the SEC clarified at the end of May that staking does not violate securities laws. Since late May, the number of active validators has increased by 54,000, reaching a historical peak of 1.1 million. Industry insiders pointed out that the surge in exit queues may also include institutional investors who have unstaked their shares to participate in ETH treasury company fundraising. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947819458152386560</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoPANewsThe size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is currently about 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024On July 23, according to CoinDesk, the size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is about 519,000 ETH (worth about $1.9 billion), a record high since January 2024, and the c</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947819458152386560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Square to Roll Out Native Bitcoin Payment Service for Select MerchantsJack Dorsey announced on the X platform that his payment company, Square, will launch native Bitcoin payment services for its first few merchants. Previously, at the Bitcoin 2025 conference held in Las Vegas in May 2025, they attempted to use the Lightning Network for fast, low-cost transactions. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947817775439564800</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoForesightNewsSquare to Roll Out Native Bitcoin Payment Service for Select MerchantsJack Dorsey announced on the X platform that his payment company, Square, will launch native Bitcoin payment services for its first few merchants. Previously, at the Bitcoin 2025 conference held in Las V</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947817775439564800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk&apos;s xAI Seeks $12 Billion to Build Second Data CenterOn July 23, according to Techinasia, Elon Musk&apos;s AI startup xAI is seeking $12.00B in funding to build its second data center, Colossus 2. The company has already built its first data center, Colossus, in Memphis, Tennessee, with 200,000 GPUs, and is in talks with private equity firms such as Valor Equity Partners, which has invested in SpaceX and Tesla, to raise funds. Although xAI is valued at $75.00B and has previously raised at least $20.00B, the company is still not profitable and is expected to consume approximately $13.00B in cash by 2025. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947816443869679616</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoTechFlowMusk&apos;s xAI Seeks $12 Billion to Build Second Data CenterOn July 23, according to Techinasia, Elon Musk&apos;s AI startup xAI is seeking $12.00B in funding to build its second data center, Colossus 2. The company has already built its first data center, Colossus, in Memphis, Tennesse</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947816443869679616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Tapiero&apos;s company will merge to form a new brand, 50T, and launch a new $500.00M crypto fund, &quot;50T Fund&quot;Digital asset investor Dan Tapiero is merging private equity firm 10T Holdings with 1RoundTable Partners to form a new brand called 50T. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947814539232038912</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoForesightNewsDan Tapiero&apos;s company will merge to form a new brand, 50T, and launch a new $500.00M crypto fund, &quot;50T Fund&quot;Digital asset investor Dan Tapiero is merging private equity firm 10T Holdings with 1RoundTable Partners to form a new brand called 50T. [Foresight News]#Fundraising</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947814539232038912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US prosecutors seek to recover $7.10M in cryptocurrency related to an oil and gas investment scamAccording to The Block, the U.S. Attorney&apos;s Office for the Western District of Washington has filed a civil forfeiture lawsuit involving $7.10M in cryptocurrency related to an oil and gas investment scam. Prosecutors allege that Geoffrey K. Auyeung, 47, and his associates lured investors into transferring funds into so-called &quot;crude oil tank escrow accounts,&quot; promising profits through leasing tank space. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947814295383592960</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoForesightNewsUS prosecutors seek to recover $7.10M in cryptocurrency related to an oil and gas investment scamAccording to The Block, the U.S. Attorney&apos;s Office for the Western District of Washington has filed a civil forfeiture lawsuit involving $7.10M in cryptocurrency related to an</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947814295383592960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiCeFi index 24hr gain of 3.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has risen by 3.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: MNT +3.54%, HYPE +3.45%, BNB +3.27%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812736330063872</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiCeFi index 24hr gain of 3.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has risen by 3.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: MNT +3.54%, HYPE +3.45%, BNB +3.27%.$BNB$MNT$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812736330063872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources: Crypto prediction market Polymarket may issue its own stablecoinAccording to CoinDesk, the crypto prediction market Polymarket may issue its own stablecoin to users. Sources say that because Polymarket&apos;s ecosystem is closed, it only needs to exchange USDC for its own issued stablecoin to have yield reserves. A Polymarket representative said that no final decision has been made on the stablecoin issue. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812714277785600</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoForesightNewsSources: Crypto prediction market Polymarket may issue its own stablecoinAccording to CoinDesk, the crypto prediction market Polymarket may issue its own stablecoin to users. Sources say that because Polymarket&apos;s ecosystem is closed, it only needs to exchange USDC for its</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812714277785600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US SEC Approves Bitwise Crypto Index ETF Conversion Application, Then Urgently Halts ItAccording to The Block, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approved Bitwise&apos;s application for &quot;accelerated conversion&quot; of the 10 Crypto Index ETF on July 22, but it was subsequently halted by SEC Assistant Secretary Sherry R. Haywood, who announced that it would be re-examined. Bitwise&apos;s fund covers assets including BTC, ETH, XRP, SOL, ADA, SUI, LINK, AVAX, LTC, and DOT. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812714386837504</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoForesightNewsUS SEC Approves Bitwise Crypto Index ETF Conversion Application, Then Urgently Halts ItAccording to The Block, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approved Bitwise&apos;s application for &quot;accelerated conversion&quot; of the 10 Crypto Index ETF on July 22, but it was su</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812714386837504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Trade talks with EU to take place on WednesdayOn July 23, according to Jinshi Data, after announcing a trade agreement with Japan, US President Trump said that EU representatives would hold trade negotiations with the US on Wednesday. Trump said, &quot;Tomorrow it will be Europe&apos;s turn, and the day after that, some other countries will come.&quot; [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812086793129984</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoTechFlowTrump: Trade talks with EU to take place on WednesdayOn July 23, according to Jinshi Data, after announcing a trade agreement with Japan, US President Trump said that EU representatives would hold trade negotiations with the US on Wednesday. Trump said, &quot;Tomorrow it will be Eur</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812086793129984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares Submits S-1 Filing for ONDO ETF21Shares submits S-1 application to the US SEC for ONDO ETF. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812714462334976</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNews21Shares Submits S-1 Filing for ONDO ETF21Shares submits S-1 application to the US SEC for ONDO ETF. [Foresight News]#ETF$ONDOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947812714462334976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arca transferred 2.183M PENDLE to Kraken, expected profit of approximately $2.13MAccording to Ember Monitoring, Arca transferred 2.183M PENDLE (approximately $10.44M) to the Kraken exchange 2 hours ago. The institution withdrew these PENDLE from Binance a month ago at a price of $3.80 per token, and now transferred them all to Kraken at a price of $4.78 per token, with an estimated profit of approximately $2.13M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947808930768113664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsArca transferred 2.183M PENDLE to Kraken, expected profit of approximately $2.13MAccording to Ember Monitoring, Arca transferred 2.183M PENDLE (approximately $10.44M) to the Kraken exchange 2 hours ago. The institution withdrew these PENDLE from Binance a month ago at a price</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947808930768113664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six ETF issuers submit amendments to cryptocurrency ETF physical redemption, sending a &quot;positive signal&quot; to the US SECOn July 23, according to The Block, 21Shares, Fidelity, Franklin Templeton, Galaxy, VanEck and WisdomTree all submitted revised proposals to the US SEC on Tuesday, requesting that their spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs, as well as future cryptocurrency ETFs, adopt a physical subscription and redemption mechanism. Analysts believe that this move shows that the SEC&apos;s approval attitude towards cryptocurrency ETFs is turning positive. “More positive signals, indicating that the U.S. SEC is taking positive steps and is likely working on details,” said James Seyffart, an ETF analyst at Bloomberg. Seyffart added that the mechanism only applies to “authorized participants” such as large Wall Street institutions and market makers — not retail traders — who can redeem their ETF shares for underlying assets. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947807894816968704</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSix ETF issuers submit amendments to cryptocurrency ETF physical redemption, sending a &quot;positive signal&quot; to the US SECOn July 23, according to The Block, 21Shares, Fidelity, Franklin Templeton, Galaxy, VanEck and WisdomTree all submitted revised proposals to the US SEC on Tuesday, re</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947807894816968704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 01:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>