<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi to Mars, they are pioneering narratives! Sun, who is flying to space, and the women who are changing the industry.&quot; YIYI, Damei Una, Li Qian, Silvia Wanqing, Crayon Xiaomi and other crypto KOLs will gather together to discuss the female power unique to Web3. This event will be broadcast simultaneously via Huobi Live and X Space, with constant red envelope rain, so stay tuned. Book a live broadcast: https://www.htx.com.de/zh-cn/live/detail/h5?id=79115&amp;invite_code=ip549223&amp;inviter_id=11351630 [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</link>
      <description>1 minute agoTechFlowHuobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure with native on-chain staking rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoForesightNewsREX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure w</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SunPump✖️SunGenX Space Meme Challenge Officially LaunchedOn July 23, it was reported that SunPump and SunGenX jointly launched the &quot;Space Meme Challenge&quot;, coinciding with TRON founder Justin Sun&apos;s upcoming space trip. The challenge is now open to the global crypto community for creative Meme submissions. The competition has a total prize pool of 500.00 USDT, including a &quot;Meme King Award&quot; of 200.00 USDT, two &quot;Community Popularity Awards&quot; of 100.00 USDT each, and ten &quot;Special Finalist Awards&quot; of 10.00 USDT each. Participants only need to post their work on the X platform with the hashtag and @ the official account between July 23 and 30 to participate. This creative event not only gives outstanding works the opportunity to shine in space with Justin Sun, but will also promote the influence of TRON&apos;s ecological culture among young users. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942587549159424</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoTechFlowSunPump✖️SunGenX Space Meme Challenge Officially LaunchedOn July 23, it was reported that SunPump and SunGenX jointly launched the &quot;Space Meme Challenge&quot;, coinciding with TRON founder Justin Sun&apos;s upcoming space trip. The challenge is now open to the global crypto community for</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942587549159424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito is postponing the Espresso launch to July 24th at 20:00.Due to KYC process issues, Kaito has postponed the launch of Espresso to 20:00 on July 24th. Kaito has partnered with identity platform Persona to update the KYC address verification section. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942693002350592</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoForesightNewsKaito is postponing the Espresso launch to July 24th at 20:00.Due to KYC process issues, Kaito has postponed the launch of Espresso to 20:00 on July 24th. Kaito has partnered with identity platform Persona to update the KYC address verification section. [Foresight News]Shar</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942693002350592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side.The Ministry of Commerce stated that, as agreed upon by both China and the United States, He Lifeng, member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and Vice Premier of the State Council, will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the United States. The two sides will follow the important consensus reached by the two heads of state during their phone call on June 5th, give full play to the role of the China-U.S. economic and trade consultation mechanism, and continue to conduct consultations on economic and trade issues of mutual concern based on the principles of mutual respect, peaceful coexistence, and win-win cooperation. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942527096655872</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyHe Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side.The Ministry of Commerce stated that, as agreed upon by both China and the United States, He Lifeng, member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and Vice Premi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942527096655872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2B PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address. A week ago, this portion of tokens was deposited into Binance and then transferred to the address &quot;9SnqX...seSGz&quot;, and half an hour ago, it was transferred back in batches from that address. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947937510591631360</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoOdaily2B PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associ</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947937510591631360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU surpasses BONK to become the meme coin with the highest market value on the Solana chain, and its market value ranking rises to 54th.On July 23, according to the latest data from coingecko, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) has surpassed Bonk (BONK) and ranked 54th in cryptocurrency market capitalization, becoming the Memecoin with the highest market capitalization in the Solana ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947935295181230080</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsPENGU surpasses BONK to become the meme coin with the highest market value on the Solana chain, and its market value ranking rises to 54th.On July 23, according to the latest data from coingecko, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) has surpassed Bonk (BONK) and ranked 54th in cryptocurrency m</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947935295181230080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should Investors Buy Low-Cap Altcoins in Q3 2025? Analysts Weigh InCrypto investors are well aware of the risks involved in low-cap altcoins. However, this segment often delivers impressive returns, sometimes multiplying investments several times over. So, should investors start buying low-cap altcoins in July, especially now that experts believe altcoin season has begun? Opportunities and Risks for Low-Cap Altcoins in Q3 2025 Although the total market cap reached a new high in July, capital flows mainly into Bitcoin and major altcoins. TradingView data supports this. While the total crypto market cap nears $4 trillion, the market cap excluding the top 100 altcoins stands at just $15.4 billion. CoinMarketCap data shows that the top 100 altcoins each have a market cap above $700 million. Altcoins outside this group—those below $700 million—are categorized as mid-cap or low-cap. This capital disparity suggests that investors remain cautious. They prefer altcoins with high liquidity or those that institutional players and listed companies notice. However, another interpretation offers hope. Some analysts believe the current capital inflow is still in its early phase . Many analysts share the same view as investor Mister Crypto. According to them, the market is still in phase two. In this stage, investors mostly favor Ethereum . Capital will eventually rotate to large, mid, and low caps . This delay creates a window of opportunity for many investors to buy early and at a good price . It’s also a chance to get ahead of the broader capital flow. Still, analysts like João Wedson remain skeptical of ultra-low-cap altcoins—especially those outside the top 300. These coins usually have a market cap of less than $200 million. He cites the Open Interest to Market Cap Ratio as a warning signal for these coins. Data shows that open interest for coins outside the top 300 is unusually high compared to their market caps. When open interest significantly surpasses market capitalization, it indicates that traders are focusing on short-term movements in the derivatives market instead of actively trading the tokens in spot markets. Consequently, these altcoins experience low liquidity and encounter extreme volatility . On X, excitement about altcoin season is spreading fast in July. However, whether investors should buy low-cap altcoins in Q3/2025 still depends heavily on their personal risk appetite and investment strategy.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947940340698255360</link>
      <description>38 minutes agobeincryptoShould Investors Buy Low-Cap Altcoins in Q3 2025? Analysts Weigh InCrypto investors are well aware of the risks involved in low-cap altcoins. However, this segment often delivers impressive returns, sometimes multiplying investments several times over. So, should investors st</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947940340698255360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit Will List DIA Perpetual ContractsBybit will launch DIA perpetual contracts. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947932700089847808</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoForesightNewsBybit Will List DIA Perpetual ContractsBybit will launch DIA perpetual contracts. [Foresight News]#DeFi$DIAShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947932700089847808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit and Cactus Custody Announce Strategic Partnership, Cactus Oasis Officially Integrated into Bybit PlatformBybit has announced a strategic partnership with Cactus Custody, a compliant and licensed digital asset custody institution under the Matrixport Group. The two parties will launch a new over-the-counter settlement solution through the Cactus Oasis platform, aiming to improve the asset security and capital utilization efficiency of institutional clients. It is reported that institutional clients can托管their assets in regulated independent accounts and only transfer them to the exchange at the time of settlement, without the need for pre-funding. The solution is also equipped with risk control mechanisms, including dual authorization and pre-authorization models, and strictly complies with regulatory requirements. Cactus Custody holds a Hong Kong Monetary Authority TCSP license, and this integration will be officially launched on July 28.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947930763973955584</link>
      <description>55 minutes ago吴说Bybit and Cactus Custody Announce Strategic Partnership, Cactus Oasis Officially Integrated into Bybit PlatformBybit has announced a strategic partnership with Cactus Custody, a compliant and licensed digital asset custody institution under the Matrixport Group. The two parties will</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947930763973955584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Will Remove GPS/FDUSD and Other Spot Trading Pairs on July 25According to the official announcement, Binance will remove and cease trading services for the GPS/FDUSD and HIVE/FDUSD spot trading pairs at 03:00 (UTC) on July 25, 2025. At the same time, Binance will terminate the spot trading bot services for the above trading pairs. Users can still trade the relevant currencies on other available trading pairs. (This news flash is generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947932457088651264</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoOdailyBinance Will Remove GPS/FDUSD and Other Spot Trading Pairs on July 25According to the official announcement, Binance will remove and cease trading services for the GPS/FDUSD and HIVE/FDUSD spot trading pairs at 03:00 (UTC) on July 25, 2025. At the same time, Binance will terminat</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947932457088651264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Citigroup eyeing stablecoin issuance? Here’s what we knowCitigroup claims to be exploring stablecoin adoption amidst accelerated regulations in the United States and Hong Kong to accommodate. How far are they willing to dive? Major financial institutions are now seeking opportunities to benefit from the current stablecoin wave that’s been sweeping the globe. Companies in Hong Kong and the United States have expressed interest in issuing their own stablecoins pegged to local currencies. The global banking firm Citigroup is no exception. In a recent earnings call, CEO Jane Fraser said to stakeholders that the bank is currently aiming to delve deeper into stablecoins and digital assets in order to fulfill clients’ needs. In addition, the bank also hopes to attract new clients and unlock new revenue streams through stablecoins. These comments are reaffirmed by New York-based head of services at Citigroup, Shahmir Khaliq in an interview with South China Morning Post. The executive called stablecoins a “global phenomenon,” especially with recent developments in the United States and Hong Kong’s own Stablecoin Ordinance bill that is scheduled to come into effect on August 1. “We welcome regulators providing us guidance and insight on the stablecoin landscape, allowing us to continue developing new services that help our clients run their businesses every day,” said Khaliq. How far do you think banks are willing to go to embrace stablecoins? Earlier this year, the banking group expressed interest in offering technology-based services and the issuance of what they called a “Citi stablecoin.” Recently, it has also stated that its plans to help clients navigate reserve management as stablecoins require backing its value in reserves. It would also offer services that could convert stablecoins into fiat currencies and vice versa. “Consumers and companies will have multiple payment options, and ultimately, the adoption of stablecoins will depend on factors like cost and ease of access,” he said, adding that banks are able to provide the bridge between stablecoins and fiat. Although the bank is undoubtedly curious about stablecoins and how they will be able to make use of them, it is also taking a cautious stance as it observes the need for “clear accounting rules regarding stablecoins and their impact on balance sheets and liquidity” according to Khaliq. He believes that there is still a long way to go before true regulatory clarity can be achieved in terms of stablecoins, stating that it is still “very early” in its development. Back in April 2025, Citigroup’s latest report showed that stablecoin issuers are poised to become some of the largest holders of U.S. Treasuries by 2030 if the U.S. adopts a regulatory framework. Now that it has, only time will tell if it will reach the predicted $1 trillion surge in additional demand for U.S. Treasuries. Most recently, the Trump Administration passed the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for U.S. Stablecoins Act or GENIUS Act. It received majority vote from the House of Representatives on July 18. The bill is aimed at providing the first federal framework for stablecoins. Hong Kong is next in line. The special administrative region recently passed the Stablecoin Ordinance, which mandates companies to register for a stablecoin issuance license in order to offer services and issue stablecoins pegged to the Hong Kong dollar. It is scheduled to come into effect on August 1. Even China has begun to mull over softening its stance on digital assets as more and more countries are competing to issue their own stablecoins linked to local currencies, in an attempt to overthrow USD-pegged stablecoin dominance. [Citigroup]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947927496934100992</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsIs Citigroup eyeing stablecoin issuance? Here’s what we knowCitigroup claims to be exploring stablecoin adoption amidst accelerated regulations in the United States and Hong Kong to accommodate. How far are they willing to dive? Major financial institutions are now seeking oppor</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947927496934100992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, the number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000, with net redemptions reaching 271,000. On-chain data shows that in the past week, two HTX-related wallets have cumulatively redeemed 110,000 ETH, with a total value of over $400 million. In addition, institutions such as Abraxas Capital Mgmt have also carried out staking redemptions. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924910063554560</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyThe number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, the number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000, with net redemptions reaching 271,000. On-chain data shows that in the past week, two HTX-r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924910063554560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought 475 WBTC and established a long position of 434.6 BTC.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;0x3E38&quot; bought 475 WBTC ($56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 and went long on BTC by borrowing on Aave. He also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC ($51.60M) on Hyperliquid with 10x leverage. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924926937239552</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA whale bought 475 WBTC and established a long position of 434.6 BTC.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;0x3E38&quot; bought 475 WBTC ($56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 and went long on BTC by borrowing on Aave. He also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC ($51.60M) o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924926937239552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch XNY spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Hotbit Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23: Spot trading pair XNY/USDT (July 23 21:20 UTC+8): $XNY is the native token of the Codatta project. Codatta is an open, decentralized, multi-chain protocol that combines blockchain-based data infrastructure with a collaborative network of human contributors and professional AI agents. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923761684090880</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch XNY spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Hotbit Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23: Spot trading pair XNY/USDT (July 23 21:20 UTC+8): $XNY is the native token of the Codatta project. Codatta is an o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923761684090880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>edgeX 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.15BOn July 23, according to the official announcement, edgeX&apos;s 24-hour trading volume exceeded $1.15B, marking a major milestone in the platform&apos;s development. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923515503611904</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowedgeX 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.15BOn July 23, according to the official announcement, edgeX&apos;s 24-hour trading volume exceeded $1.15B, marking a major milestone in the platform&apos;s development. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923515503611904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; Recruitment ProgramBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; recruitment campaign, which will recruit 300 users from the Chinese community to become &quot;Scan Chain Product Promoters&quot; by sharing their experiences using the Bitget Wallet scan chain function to discover meme potential coins. The event will run from July 23 to August 1. Participants need to use the Bitget Wallet scan chain function and publish tweets to share the process of screening potential coins and their personal experiences. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947922407586598912</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitget Wallet Launches &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; Recruitment ProgramBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; recruitment campaign, which will recruit 300 users from the Chinese community to become &quot;Scan Chain Product Promoters&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947922407586598912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainCatcher announces a partnership with Volcano Engine to drive the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure.ChainCatcher has announced a partnership with Volcengine to assist Volcengine in promoting its cloud computing services, including cloud servers, storage, and enterprise-level solutions. Through this collaboration, both parties will jointly promote the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure. As an influential media platform in the Web3 field, ChainCatcher&apos;s collaboration will combine its industry resources with Volcengine&apos;s technical advantages to provide Web3 companies with more efficient cloud service support. As a leading global cloud computing service provider, Volcengine&apos;s collaboration will further strengthen its presence in Web3 and emerging technology fields. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921955025391616</link>
      <description>1 hour agoChainCatcherChainCatcher announces a partnership with Volcano Engine to drive the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure.ChainCatcher has announced a partnership with Volcengine to assist Volcengine in promoting its cloud computing services, including cloud servers, storage, and ente</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921955025391616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale starting with 0x3E3 is going long on BTC in Aave and Hyperliquid, with total profits exceeding $5.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale starting with 0x3E3 borrowed from Aave to purchase 475 WBTC (worth approximately $56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 to long BTC. The address also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC (worth approximately $51.60M) with 10x leverage on Hyperliquid. The total profit has now exceeded $5.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921620428984320</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsA whale starting with 0x3E3 is going long on BTC in Aave and Hyperliquid, with total profits exceeding $5.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale starting with 0x3E3 borrowed from Aave to purchase 475 WBTC (worth approximately $56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.0</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921620428984320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant analyst: Ethereum may experience a pullback in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too largeOn July 23, CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan said that Ethereum has recently risen sharply and may experience a correction in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too large. He pointed out that compared with the overheated market in March and November 2024, the current market is not high. Although Ethereum has performed slowly in this cycle, it has bottomed out and may continue to rise in the second half of 2025. He also mentioned that the rise of Ethereum often drives the performance of other currencies, and investors can pay attention to the subsequent market trends. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917982683959296</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCryptoQuant analyst: Ethereum may experience a pullback in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too largeOn July 23, CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan said that Ethereum has recently risen sharply and may experience a correction in the short term, but th</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917982683959296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 08:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>