<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:47:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermOn July 24th, Bitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range. At the same time, the altseason index shows an upward trend, indicating that funds are rotating into mainstream altcoins such as Ethereum, XRP, and Solana, with related assets increasing by 20%-40% recently. Ryan Lee pointed out, &quot;The active performance of sectors such as AI, RWA, and Memecoin also shows the market&apos;s strong focus on specific narratives. However, the altseason index has not yet broken through the 75% confirmation threshold, and the current market is more likely a phase of rotation rather than a full-blown altseason. To push the market to continue into the mid-to-late third quarter, the key lies in whether Bitcoin&apos;s market share can remain below 60%. At the same time, institutional fund inflows, regulatory benefits, and improved fundamentals in the Layer 1 and DeFi sectors are all important signals to confirm the start of altseason.&quot; [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333605029220352</link>
      <description>1 minute agoTechFlowBitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermOn July 24th, Bitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range. At the same time, the al</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333605029220352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nansen data: In the past 7 days, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea have both surged by over 100%.According to Nansen data, possibly influenced by the upcoming announcement related to the TGE this month, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea has surged by over 100% in the past 7 days. On July 21st, the number of active addresses reached 75,700.00, the highest in nearly four months; the number of transactions on the same day exceeded 200,000.00, the first time in nearly 5 months. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333306109562880</link>
      <description>2 minutes ago吴说Nansen data: In the past 7 days, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea have both surged by over 100%.According to Nansen data, possibly influenced by the upcoming announcement related to the TGE this month, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea ha</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333306109562880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT criticizes Yaps’ marketing for damaging the project’s brand imageOn July 24, crypto investigator ZachXBT pointed out in an article that Yaps&apos; activities are becoming one of the main reasons for the dilution of the project&apos;s brand image. He said that the mechanism attracts &quot;low-value farmers&quot; who publish a large amount of AI-generated content to gain incentives rather than truly attracting &quot;sticky funds&quot; and organic users. ZachXBT called on the industry to &quot;normalize the blocking of such teams and expose false data&quot; to curb the phenomenon of &quot;rampant low-quality content&quot; in the industry. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332537612406784</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoPANewsZachXBT criticizes Yaps’ marketing for damaging the project’s brand imageOn July 24, crypto investigator ZachXBT pointed out in an article that Yaps&apos; activities are becoming one of the main reasons for the dilution of the project&apos;s brand image. He said that the mechanism attracts</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332537612406784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVNU Launches Starknet Paymaster, Enabling Developers to Sponsor User Gas Fees in 5 MinutesAVNU, a trading center on Starknet, has announced the launch of Starknet Paymaster, an open-source, production-ready, developer-first method for extracting Gas fees. It allows Starknet developers to sponsor or extract user fees in 5 minutes, accepting any token as a Gas fee. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331432258113536</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoForesightNewsAVNU Launches Starknet Paymaster, Enabling Developers to Sponsor User Gas Fees in 5 MinutesAVNU, a trading center on Starknet, has announced the launch of Starknet Paymaster, an open-source, production-ready, developer-first method for extracting Gas fees. It allows Starkn</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331432258113536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.49% in the past 1H, down 0.19% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331038785626112</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.49% in the past 1H, down 0.19% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331038785626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermBitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range, while the altcoin season index shows an upward trend, indicating that funds are rotating towards mainstream altcoins such as Ethereum, XRP, and Solana, with related assets rising by 20%-40% recently. Ryan Lee pointed out, &quot;The active performance of sectors such as AI, RWA, and Memecoin also shows the market&apos;s strong focus on specific narratives. However, the altcoin season index has not yet broken through the 75% confirmation threshold, and the current market is more likely a phase of rotation rather than a full-blown altcoin season. To drive the market to continue into the mid-to-late third quarter, the key lies in whether Bitcoin&apos;s market share can remain below 60%. At the same time, institutional fund inflows, regulatory benefits, and improved fundamentals in the Layer 1 and DeFi sectors are all important signals to confirm the start of the altcoin season.&quot; [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332610312278016</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoOdailyBitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermBitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range, while the altcoin season index shows a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332610312278016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotions from Aug. 1Starting Aug. 1, offering or advertising unlicensed stablecoins to retail investors in Hong Kong could land violators with a $50,000.00 Hong Kong dollars fine and six months in jail.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948330184045826048</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotions from Aug. 1Starting Aug. 1, offering or advertising unlicensed stablecoins to retail investors in Hong Kong could land violators with a $50,000.00 Hong Kong dollars fine and six months in jail.#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948330184045826048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana developers consider increasing block limit by 66% to 100 million compute units to further increase network capacitySolana developers are considering increasing the block limit from 60 million compute units to 100 million compute units via the SIMD-0286 proposal, which would achieve a 66% capacity increase, provided validators opt-in to the upgrade. The proposal aims to further increase Solana network capacity, allowing for more transactions per second to be processed. Compute units are the basic unit of measurement for transaction complexity and resource consumption in the Solana network, and increasing the block compute unit limit will directly enhance the network&apos;s transaction processing capabilities. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332618767994880</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoOdailySolana developers consider increasing block limit by 66% to 100 million compute units to further increase network capacitySolana developers are considering increasing the block limit from 60 million compute units to 100 million compute units via the SIMD-0286 proposal, which woul</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332618767994880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Using Kyrgyzstan Crypto Infrastructure to Evade Sanctions and Fund War in UkraineOn July 24, according to a report by TRM Labs cited by Cryptonews, Russian entities are using Kyrgyzstan&apos;s cryptocurrency infrastructure to bypass international sanctions and procure dual-use goods. The report shows that since Kyrgyzstan passed the Law on Virtual Assets in January 2022, the country has developed into a significant cryptocurrency hub. As of October 2024, the country has issued 126 Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) licenses, and transaction volume has surged from $59.00 million in 2022 to $4.20 billion in the first seven months of 2024. TRM Labs found that several exchanges registered in Kyrgyzstan are actually shell entities, reusing the same addresses and contact information, and have transactional ties to sanctioned Russian organizations, including the Rusich paramilitary group fighting alongside the Wagner Group. After the Russian exchange Garantex was targeted by law enforcement in March 2025, new entities registered in Kyrgyzstan, such as Grinex and Meer, exhibited similar trading patterns. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948329885751119872</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoTechFlowRussia Using Kyrgyzstan Crypto Infrastructure to Evade Sanctions and Fund War in UkraineOn July 24, according to a report by TRM Labs cited by Cryptonews, Russian entities are using Kyrgyzstan&apos;s cryptocurrency infrastructure to bypass international sanctions and procure dual-us</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948329885751119872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK-listed Satsuma Completes Over £100.00M Funding Round, Will Accelerate its Bitcoin Accumulation StrategyUK-listed Satsuma Technology PLC (Tao Alpha PLC) has announced the completion of its second round of convertible bond private placement, with the amount raised significantly exceeding the original minimum target of £100.00M. Satsuma stated that the financing will be used to expand its business and strengthen its Bitcoin adoption and decentralized AI strategy. The relevant convertible bond shares will be applied for listing on the London Main Board market after conversion. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328383770857472</link>
      <description>22 minutes ago吴说UK-listed Satsuma Completes Over £100.00M Funding Round, Will Accelerate its Bitcoin Accumulation StrategyUK-listed Satsuma Technology PLC (Tao Alpha PLC) has announced the completion of its second round of convertible bond private placement, with the amount raised significantly exce</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328383770857472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowMist CISO: Core Administrator of World&apos;s Largest Dark Web Crime Platform XSS.is Arrested23pds, Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at SlowMist, posted on the X platform that the core administrator of XSS.is, the world&apos;s largest dark web crime platform, has been arrested. This platform has been active for a long time and is one of the main trading places for Stealer tools (information stealers) in the cryptocurrency industry. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948327582923034624</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoOdailySlowMist CISO: Core Administrator of World&apos;s Largest Dark Web Crime Platform XSS.is Arrested23pds, Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at SlowMist, posted on the X platform that the core administrator of XSS.is, the world&apos;s largest dark web crime platform, has been arrested</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948327582923034624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bifrost Launches $3.00M Multi-Chain Liquidity Incentive to Drive Polkadot DeFi into a Multi-Chain EcosystemOn July 24th, to open up asset channels between Polkadot and the mainstream multi-chain ecosystem, vDOT/ETH and vDOT/BNB liquidity pools will be officially launched on Uniswap V4 on July 25th, and a 12-month liquidity incentive program with a total of 795,000 DOT incentives will be launched simultaneously. This integration provides DOT with a stable and sustainable liquidity entry point into the Ethereum ecosystem, expanding its actual usability in mainstream DeFi networks. As part of the DeFi Singularity program, the first round of incentives now covers Arbitrum, Base, BNB Chain, and the Ethereum mainnet, and liquidity rewards are simultaneously launched around the vDOT/ETH and DOT/ETH pools. Users can participate in liquidity provision through Uniswap V4 and receive incentives in real-time on the Merkl platform. vDOT is a DOT liquid staking token launched by Bifrost, and currently has a cumulative staked TVL of over $74,000,000.00, widely used in governance, lending, DEX and other scenarios. This round of incentives is seen as an important step in promoting vDOT to become a multi-chain yield-bearing asset, and also brings higher liquidity and DeFi integration potential to DOT. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325752528769024</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoTechFlowBifrost Launches $3.00M Multi-Chain Liquidity Incentive to Drive Polkadot DeFi into a Multi-Chain EcosystemOn July 24th, to open up asset channels between Polkadot and the mainstream multi-chain ecosystem, vDOT/ETH and vDOT/BNB liquidity pools will be officially launched on Uni</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325752528769024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto mining firm Bitzero announces completion of $25.00M fundingBitzero, a crypto mining company backed by renowned investor Kevin O&apos;Leary, has announced the completion of a $25.00M funding round, which it intends to use to expand its business footprint in North America and Europe. The company stated that it will initially use part of the funds to purchase 2,900 Bitmain S21 Pro miners, which are expected to be deployed within 4 to 6 months, increasing annual revenue by approximately $10.00M. Headquartered in Vancouver, Bitzero focuses on using low-carbon energy sources such as hydropower to support high-performance computing and blockchain tasks, and is currently advancing the construction of four new facilities in North Dakota, Norway, and Finland. [TheBlock]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325420419584000</link>
      <description>33 minutes ago吴说Crypto mining firm Bitzero announces completion of $25.00M fundingBitzero, a crypto mining company backed by renowned investor Kevin O&apos;Leary, has announced the completion of a $25.00M funding round, which it intends to use to expand its business footprint in North America and Europe.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325420419584000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK and India sign free trade agreementOn July 24, Bloomberg reported that the UK and India have officially signed a free trade agreement, eliminating tariffs on a number of products including cars and alcohol. The agreement was reached after three years of negotiations. It is the largest trade agreement since the UK&apos;s withdrawal from the EU and the most important trade agreement for India in a decade. According to the agreement, 90% of tariff items exported by the UK to India will be reduced, of which 85% will be completely duty-free within ten years; 99% of tariff items exported by India to the UK will also be reduced. The agreement is expected to increase the output of the UK economy by 4.8 billion pounds per year and bring long-term trade growth to the two countries. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324399509213184</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoPANewsUK and India sign free trade agreementOn July 24, Bloomberg reported that the UK and India have officially signed a free trade agreement, eliminating tariffs on a number of products including cars and alcohol. The agreement was reached after three years of negotiations. It is the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324399509213184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsSenseTime announced the placement of 1.667 billion new Class B shares, with expected total fundraising of approximately HKD 2.5 billion, subscribed by international long-term capital Infini Capital. The company announced that it intends to use approximately 20% of the net proceeds from the placement to explore the technological integration of AI and innovative vertical fields, including embodied intelligent robots, blockchain, Real World Assets (RWA), digital assets, and stablecoins, and will consider cooperating with strategic partners to carry out related businesses and obtain qualifications. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324449689866240</link>
      <description>37 minutes ago吴说SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsSenseTime announced the placement of 1.667 billion new Class B shares, with expected total fundraising of approximately HKD</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324449689866240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance alpha is now live with ASPOn July 24, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched ASP. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323539651727360</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoTechFlowBinance alpha is now live with ASPOn July 24, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched ASP. [深潮 TechFlow]$BNBShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323539651727360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treehouse Opens TREE Token Airdrop InquiryDecentralized fixed income layer Treehouse has announced the opening of airdrop queries and is about to launch its TGE. Users who accumulated more than 100 points in its GoNuts Season 1 campaign and passed the Sybil check can receive TREE tokens. In addition, as a reward to long-term users, Treehouse will also provide an additional 100% vault reward on top of the base share. At the same time, Treehose NFT holders will also receive a fixed amount of TREE airdrop rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323444252282880</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoForesightNewsTreehouse Opens TREE Token Airdrop InquiryDecentralized fixed income layer Treehouse has announced the opening of airdrop queries and is about to launch its TGE. Users who accumulated more than 100 points in its GoNuts Season 1 campaign and passed the Sybil check can recei</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323444252282880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA), supporting USD1 and GT subscriptionsAccording to the official announcement, Gate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA) from 13:00 on July 26, 2025 to 13:00 on July 29, 2025 (UTC+8), supporting users to subscribe to IKA tokens with USD1 and GT. The subscription price is 0.025 USD1, and the total subscription amount is 200,000,000 IKA. Limited purchase, first come first served. The GT subscription price will be calculated based on the average opening price of GT on July 24, 25, and 26 (UTC+8), and will be announced 2 hours before the subscription starts. The upper limit of the number of tokens that a single person can obtain is 2,000,000 IKA, which will be uniformly distributed within 4 hours after the subscription ends. At the same time, Gate will launch Ika (IKA) spot trading at 18:00 (UTC+8) on July 29, 2025, opening the IKA/USD1 trading pair. In addition, Gate Launchpad will also launch a new user benefit event from now until 00:00 (UTC+8) on August 1, 2025. Registration and transactions can share 2,000 GT, and the first order loss will be subsidized 100%. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325068215488512</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoOdailyGate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA), supporting USD1 and GT subscriptionsAccording to the official announcement, Gate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA) from 13:00 on July 26, 2025 to 13:00 on July 29, 2025 (UTC+8), supporting users to subscribe to IKA tokens with USD1 and GT. The</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325068215488512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>67% of Gen Z Crypto Traders Use AI to Manage Volatility, MEXC Study ShowsA recent behavioral study from MEXC Research reveals a dramatic generational shift in crypto trading. According to in-platform analytics of over 780,000 users, 67% of Gen Z traders (ages 18–27) already use or actively adopt AI-powered tools. This cohort is embracing automation for purposes beyond convenience, to manage risk, reduce emotional bias, and delegate strategic decisions in volatile market conditions. AI Adoption Soars Among Gen Z Traders on MEXC MEXC’s Q2 2025 behavioral intelligence report shows that two-thirds of Gen Z users activated at least one AI bot or rule-based strategy in the last 90 days. However, usage goes deeper than bot deployment. These users actively incorporate AI into their trading behaviors, with 22.1% engaging with AI tools at least four times a month. Based on the report, Gen Z now accounts for 60% of all AI bot activations on the platform. This cohort averages 11.4 days per month interacting with AI tools, which is more than twice the engagement of users over 30. Their usage is also intentional, with the study showing 73% of Gen Z traders activate bots during volatility spikes but shut them off during low-volume or sideways markets. For them, AI is not a blanket solution. Rather, it is a selective, situational advantage. Emotional Regulation and Delegation: The Gen Z Edge MEXC Research’s findings suggest that, beyond trusting AI, Gen Z uses it as a psychological buffer. Traders using bots saw a 47% reduction in panic sell-offs during market stress, compared to those trading manually. Rather than reacting to every market twitch, Gen Z configures automated strategies with clear rules, then steps back. This method, described in the report as “structured delegation,” reduces decision fatigue and cognitive overload and mirrors broader digital behaviors in the workplace. According to a May 2025 survey by Resume.org, over 50% of Gen Z workers view ChatGPT as a co-worker or “friend.” AI is going beyond replacing human judgment to enhance emotional discipline for these users. Risk Management Reimagined The shift toward AI is also transforming how risk is managed. Gen Z users who engage with AI trading tools are: These patterns reflect a new style of semi-automated trading, where bots act as fail-safes in moments of high emotion or uncertainty . AI is going beyond accelerating trades, enforcing discipline when it matters most. Gen Z vs Millennials: Two Trading Operating Systems Further, MEXC’s cross-generational analysis reveals a fundamental divergence in trading psychology . On the one hand, millennials lean toward structured, thesis-driven approaches that heavily use charts, research, and manual oversight. On the other hand, Gen Z approaches trading like they use Discord or TikTok — rapid, reactive, and interface-dependent. Rather than long-form strategies, Gen Z favors modular, customizable tools that allow for flexible control. Their trading activity is shaped by emotional bandwidth and attention cycles. They toggle automation on and off based on market mood and personal stress levels, a behavior foreign to the older cohort’s more static strategies. This reflects broader patterns in copy trading , influencer-led decision-making, and social-driven investment communities. This report suggests that Gen Z is already building the future of crypto trading rather than waiting for it. However, in their pursuit of prioritizing speed, clarity, and emotional control, users must also be wary of blind trust. Overreliance on AI tools can introduce new risks, including algorithmic bias, flawed datasets, and model opacity, posing systemic threats. [MEXC Research]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328121991761920</link>
      <description>46 minutes agobeincrypto67% of Gen Z Crypto Traders Use AI to Manage Volatility, MEXC Study ShowsA recent behavioral study from MEXC Research reveals a dramatic generational shift in crypto trading. According to in-platform analytics of over 780,000 users, 67% of Gen Z traders (ages 18–27) already u</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328121991761920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coingecko Report: Comparison of Cost Price vs. Current Value of ETH Assets Held by Major Listed CompaniesAccording to a Coingecko report, as of July 23, 2025, SharpLink Gaming holds 360,807 ETH, ranking first, with over 95% deployed on staking platforms. SharpLink Gaming&apos;s entry price for ETH was $1.03B, with an average purchase price of $2,864.00, currently valued at $1.33B, with unrealized gains of 29.0%. Bitmine entered the market at $977.30M, with an average purchase price of $3,251.00, currently valued at $1.11B, with unrealized gains of 13.7%. Bit Digital&apos;s ETH appreciation was as high as 85.8%, from $239.30M to $444.50M. Although Exodus has the smallest holdings, its unrealized gains are the highest, at 102.7%. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948321327454162944</link>
      <description>54 minutes ago吴说Coingecko Report: Comparison of Cost Price vs. Current Value of ETH Assets Held by Major Listed CompaniesAccording to a Coingecko report, as of July 23, 2025, SharpLink Gaming holds 360,807 ETH, ranking first, with over 95% deployed on staking platforms. SharpLink Gaming&apos;s entry pric</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948321327454162944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>