<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:54:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized data platform D-GN completes $5.00M seed round of financingDecentralized data platform D-GN completes $5.00M seed round led by droppGroup, a US-based AI and blockchain solutions provider, with participation from Saudi businessman Hamoud Al-Rumayyan and cryptocurrency firm Hub Culture. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395964074627072</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsDecentralized data platform D-GN completes $5.00M seed round of financingDecentralized data platform D-GN completes $5.00M seed round led by droppGroup, a US-based AI and blockchain solutions provider, with participation from Saudi businessman Hamoud Al-Rumayyan and cryptoc</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395964074627072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: ETH is now at $3,705.389According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,705.389.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395146662862848</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: ETH is now at $3,705.389According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,705.389.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395146662862848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is up 1.50% in the past 1H, up 2.97% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395126324682752</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is up 1.50% in the past 1H, up 2.97% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395126324682752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America: Stablecoin market to grow by $25B-$75B in the near termBank of America (BofA), one of the four largest banks in the United States, released a report stating that with the GENIUS Act officially signed into law last week, U.S. stablecoin regulation has entered a critical turning point, and the stablecoin supply is expected to grow by $25.00B to $75.00B in the short term. The report points out that regulatory clarity will drive product launches, infrastructure investment, and alliance stablecoin issuance models among banks. BofA also noted that the increased demand for short-term U.S. Treasury bonds from stablecoin reserves may prompt the Treasury Department to adjust the structure of Treasury bond issuance. [CoinDesk]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948394962437083136</link>
      <description>5 minutes ago吴说Bank of America: Stablecoin market to grow by $25B-$75B in the near termBank of America (BofA), one of the four largest banks in the United States, released a report stating that with the GENIUS Act officially signed into law last week, U.S. stablecoin regulation has entered a critica</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948394962437083136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Ethereum core developer: The bullish logic for ETH in the coming years is not corporate balance sheet allocation, but the global adoption of stablecoins.Former Ethereum core developer Eric Conner posted on social media that the bullish logic for ETH in the next few years is not corporate balance sheet allocation, but the global adoption of stablecoins. He pointed out that people around the world want access to USD exposure, and this demand will see explosive growth. In the process, potentially billions of people will discover the Ethereum network. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395527736987648</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailyFormer Ethereum core developer: The bullish logic for ETH in the coming years is not corporate balance sheet allocation, but the global adoption of stablecoins.Former Ethereum core developer Eric Conner posted on social media that the bullish logic for ETH in the next few years is</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395527736987648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America: Doubts about the Fed&apos;s independence put pressure on the dollar, market concerns about easing bias intensify.On July 24, according to Jinshi Data, Bank of America strategist Alex Cohen said that uncertainty surrounding the Fed&apos;s leadership prospects is weakening the dollar&apos;s performance, with related concerns &quot;clearly affecting the dollar earlier than other assets&quot; and may be the main obstacle to the dollar&apos;s failure to rebound. &quot;Even if future leadership changes are carried out in a more conventional manner, the market is beginning to anticipate a more relaxed Fed environment,&quot; Cohen noted. Trump continues to pressure Fed Chairman Powell to cut interest rates and plans to visit the Fed headquarters today, further highlighting signs of political intervention. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948393647522779136</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoTechFlowBank of America: Doubts about the Fed&apos;s independence put pressure on the dollar, market concerns about easing bias intensify.On July 24, according to Jinshi Data, Bank of America strategist Alex Cohen said that uncertainty surrounding the Fed&apos;s leadership prospects is weakening</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948393647522779136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America: U.S. stablecoin supply may increase by $25 billion to $75 billion in the short term due to the GENIUS ActOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, Bank of America said that with the passage of the GENIUS Act, the supply of stablecoins is expected to grow by $25 billion to $75 billion in the short term. The bill lays the foundation for stablecoin regulation in the United States and promotes the development of related infrastructure and tokenized finance. Bank of America also pointed out that the banking industry is preparing to issue stablecoins through a consortium model, and this growth is expected to drive an increase in demand for U.S. Treasuries and promote the widespread adoption of digital assets. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948392923267141632</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsBank of America: U.S. stablecoin supply may increase by $25 billion to $75 billion in the short term due to the GENIUS ActOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, Bank of America said that with the passage of the GENIUS Act, the supply of stablecoins is expected to grow by $25 billion</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948392923267141632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1.0350 million ETH since July, bringing its total holdings to 2.8000 million.According to Lookonchain monitoring, BlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1,035,653 ETH since July 1st, worth approximately $3.76B. BlackRock currently holds a total of 2.80M ETH, worth approximately $10.22B. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948393003449651200</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoOdailyBlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1.0350 million ETH since July, bringing its total holdings to 2.8000 million.According to Lookonchain monitoring, BlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1,035,653 ETH since July 1st, worth approximately $3.76B. Bl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948393003449651200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether: Gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold (XAUT) has a market cap of approximately $814.00MTether has released the latest data for Tether Gold (XAUT) for the second quarter of 2025. The total circulation of the gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold is 246,524.33 coins, corresponding to 246,524.38 troy ounces of physical gold (approximately 7.66 tons), with a market value of approximately $814.00M. All physical gold reserves of XAUT are stored in Switzerland and meet London delivery standards. Tether stated that the current global macro environment is turbulent, and gold-based digital assets are becoming an important tool in investors&apos; hedging portfolios. XAUT serves as a compliant on-chain gold solution that can be transferred. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948389936792670208</link>
      <description>27 minutes ago吴说Tether: Gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold (XAUT) has a market cap of approximately $814.00MTether has released the latest data for Tether Gold (XAUT) for the second quarter of 2025. The total circulation of the gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold is 246,524.33 coins, corresponding to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948389936792670208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, will ship on August 4th; users with unconfirmed addresses may miss the first batch.Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, announced that it will begin shipping on August 4th. If users have pre-ordered but have not yet confirmed their shipping address and taxes, the device may be delayed, thus missing the first batch of shipments. Users are reminded to update as soon as possible. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948388922261835776</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoForesightNewsSolana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, will ship on August 4th; users with unconfirmed addresses may miss the first batch.Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, announced that it will begin shipping on August 4th. If users have pre-ordered but have not yet confirmed</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948388922261835776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine increases its market stock offering to $4.50B to increase its Ethereum holdingsBitmine Immersion (BMNR) has increased the size of its &quot;at-the-market&quot; (ATM) program from $2.00 billion to $4.50 billion. The company filed a prospectus supplement with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on July 24, authorizing the continuous sale of common stock in the open market through two brokerage firms, Cantor Fitzgerald and ThinkEquity. This additional issuance provides financial support for the company to further increase its ETH holdings and expand its asset reserves. According to previous reports, Bitmine updated its ETH holdings, and as of 11:59 PM ET on July 23, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing time today), Bitmine held a total of 566,776 ETH, worth more than $2.00 billion. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387989222133760</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoOdailyBitmine increases its market stock offering to $4.50B to increase its Ethereum holdingsBitmine Immersion (BMNR) has increased the size of its &quot;at-the-market&quot; (ATM) program from $2.00 billion to $4.50 billion. The company filed a prospectus supplement with the U.S. Securities and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387989222133760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign sponsors American esports club NTMR to compete in the Esports World Cup
On July 24, blockchain digital infrastructure company Sign announced a partnership with well-known esports club NTMR to jointly establish the Sign Esports club, which will compete in the 2025 Esports World Cup with a brand new orange brand.
Sign is a technology company building blockchain infrastructure, providing token distribution services to 40 million blockchain users.
NTMR is one of the most active esports clubs in North America, with its teams repeatedly achieving excellent results in events such as Overwatch 2 and Rainbow Six. Recent achievements include winning the first stage of the 2025 Overwatch Championship Series North America and the Marvel Rivals North American Invitational Tournament, as well as reaching the top three in the 2025 Global Finals, demonstrating strong dominance.
 [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385430822522880</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoTechFlowSign sponsors American esports club NTMR to compete in the Esports World Cup
On July 24, blockchain digital infrastructure company Sign announced a partnership with well-known esports club NTMR to jointly establish the Sign Esports club, which will compete in the 2025 Esports W</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385430822522880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Digital to issue first GENIUS‑compliant stablecoin in US with Ethena LabsAnchorage Digital, the first federally chartered crypto bank in the United States, will issue Ethena Labs’ USDtb token onshore as the first stablecoin engineered to comply with the new GENIUS Act, the companies said on Thursday.

Ethena’s USDtb is a yield-bearing dollar token primarily backed by BlackRock’s BUIDL and crypto collateral rather than traditional reserves to maintain its $1 peg. The synthetic stablecoin has circulated offshore since December and amassed $1.45 billion in total value locked, according to DefiLlama data.

Under the partnership, Anchorage Digital Bank will mint and redeem USDtb tokens directly in the U.S., bringing the asset under a federal regulatory umbrella for the first time. Anchorage said its stablecoin issuance platform will serve as a turnkey infrastructure for Ethena’s stablecoin to “launch and distribute fully regulated digital dollars.”

The move comes one week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act, the country’s first law governing stablecoin issuance. Industry players and U.S. officials like Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent expect the legislation to accelerate demand from asset managers, payments firms, and corporates looking for yield‑bearing, programmable dollars.

The passage of GENIUS gives federally regulated institutions a green light and clarity to participate in the stablecoin ecosystem, Anchorage CEO Nathan McCauley noted in the release.

Guy Young, Ethena Labs CEO, added that products like USDtb stand to benefit from federal oversight and regulated appetite. “While we’ve already seen strong demand for USDtb, we expect GENIUS compliance to empower our partners and holders to confidently and significantly expand its use across new products and platforms,” he said.

Anchorage’s announcement positions it alongside giants such as Circle and PayPal, which already operate dollar‑pegged tokens but must adapt to GENIUS requirements. Major banks like JPMorganand Citihave flagged plans to experiment with stablecoins and deposit‑backed tokens once the rules settle. [companies]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385281941508096</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoThe BlockAnchorage Digital to issue first GENIUS‑compliant stablecoin in US with Ethena LabsAnchorage Digital, the first federally chartered crypto bank in the United States, will issue Ethena Labs’ USDtb token onshore as the first stablecoin engineered to comply with the new GENIUS Ac</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385281941508096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoonPay Launches Liquid Staking Token mpSOL on SolanaOn July 24, according to SolanaFloor, MoonPay has launched the liquidity staking token $mpSOL on the Solana blockchain. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680090673152</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoPANewsMoonPay Launches Liquid Staking Token mpSOL on SolanaOn July 24, according to SolanaFloor, MoonPay has launched the liquidity staking token $mpSOL on the Solana blockchain. [PANews]#Layer1$MAG7.SSI$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680090673152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK crypto hopes stall, but ‘encouraging signs’ are thereThe crypto industry in the UK is pushing for the government to change the rules of the road, and it just may be working.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680128421888</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoPANewsUK crypto hopes stall, but ‘encouraging signs’ are thereThe crypto industry in the UK is pushing for the government to change the rules of the road, and it just may be working.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383680128421888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrifuge V3 Goes Live on Six EVM Chains via Wormhole, Migrating to the Ethereum EcosystemReal World Asset (RWA) tokenization platform Centrifuge has launched Centrifuge V3 on six EVM chains: Ethereum, Plume, Base, Arbitrum, Avalanche, and BNB Chain. Exclusively supported by Wormhole, this launch aims to build a unified multi-chain foundation for institutional-grade asset management and next-generation financial products. This move marks the completion of Centrifuge&apos;s migration to the Ethereum ecosystem, with new features including: cross-chain product issuance, borderless investor access, and seamless liquidity across the DeFi ecosystem. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383362611220480</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoForesightNewsCentrifuge V3 Goes Live on Six EVM Chains via Wormhole, Migrating to the Ethereum EcosystemReal World Asset (RWA) tokenization platform Centrifuge has launched Centrifuge V3 on six EVM chains: Ethereum, Plume, Base, Arbitrum, Avalanche, and BNB Chain. Exclusively supported</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948383362611220480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - US initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19 were 217,000, with expectations of 226,000.1. U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19 at 217,000, expected 226,000U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19 at 217,000, expected 226,000, previous value 221,000.2. European Central Bank keeps deposit facility rate unchanged at 2%, in line with market expectationsThe European Central Bank kept the deposit facility rate unchanged at 2.00%, in line with market expectations, after cutting interest rates for seven consecutive meetings. The main refinancing rate and marginal lending rate remain unchanged at 2.15% and 2.40% respectively.3. Arkham: U.S. Government Has Not Sold 170,000 BTC, Holds at Least 198,000 TotalThe U.S. Marshals Service stated in response to a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request that it holds 28,988 Bitcoins (approximately $3.4 billion). Multiple federal agencies, including the FBI, the Department of Justice, and the Drug Enforcement Administration, currently hold at least 198,000 Bitcoins (approximately $23.5 billion) in total, and these assets have had no transfer records in the past 4 months.4. Ghana Plans to Issue Licenses to Cryptocurrency PlatformsThe Bank of Ghana plans to submit a draft regulatory framework for crypto platforms to parliament by September, intending to issue licenses to virtual asset platforms to regulate the crypto trading market involving millions of users in the country, obtain financial data, and enhance cross-border trade capabilities. The central bank governor stated that the lack of regulation has led to a large number of crypto transactions not being included in the official financial system, affecting the local currency, the Cedi. Data shows that Ghana&apos;s crypto transaction volume reached $3.00 billion between July 2023 and June 2024, with approximately 3 million Ghanaian adults (17% of the adult population) using virtual currencies.5. Tether Plans to Return to the U.S. Market, Focusing on Institutional Stablecoin BusinessTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated that after U.S. President Donald Trump signed the stablecoin bill, Tether is planning to return to the U.S. market, focusing on institutional clients and providing stablecoin products for payments, interbank settlement, and trading. Ardoino emphasized that the company has no intention of going public and will continue to focus on emerging markets and expand its business in the United States.6. 70-Year-Old Hong Kong Man Falls Victim to Cryptocurrency Romance ScamA retired 70-year-old Hong Kong man received a message on WhatsApp from someone claiming to be a female neighbor, and subsequently developed a twilight romance, but never met the person. The woman claimed to work at the Singapore Exchange and had inside information on cryptocurrency investments, falsely claiming that she would receive rich returns. The old man transferred a total of HK$3,272,700.00 in 37 transactions to 34 bank accounts provided by the woman. It was not until the old man reached the ATM withdrawal limit and went to the bank in person to withdraw a large amount of cash that the bank staff noticed the abnormality of the transaction and immediately notified the Anti-Deception Coordination Centre, which finally uncovered the scam. The old man lost more than HK$3.27 million in total and owed nearly one million in debt as a result. The Hong Kong police said that they had received nearly 20 online romance scams related to investment in the past two weeks, with 40% of the victims being over 60 years old, with a total loss of more than HK$10.00 million.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948381459844239360</link>
      <description>58 minutes ago吴说Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - US initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19 were 217,000, with expectations of 226,000.1. U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19 at 217,000, expected 226,000U.S. Initial Jobless Claims for the week ending July 19</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948381459844239360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5Yahoo Finance quotes show that Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377912905895936</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5Yahoo Finance quotes show that Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5. [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377912905895936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;U.S. President Trump denies he wants to &quot;destroy Musk&apos;s company.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377921361612800</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;U.S. President Trump denies he wants to &quot;destroy Musk&apos;s company.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377921361612800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito: Capital Launchpad&apos;s first products, Theoriq and Espresso, will be launched tomorrow.Kaito Al announces that the first products of its Capital Launchpad will officially launch tomorrow, with Theoriq and Espresso conducting their community initial distribution on Capital Launchpad on July 25 at 20:00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376297218052096</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsKaito: Capital Launchpad&apos;s first products, Theoriq and Espresso, will be launched tomorrow.Kaito Al announces that the first products of its Capital Launchpad will officially launch tomorrow, with Theoriq and Espresso conducting their community initial distribution on Capital</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376297218052096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>