<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US appeals court overturns Yuga Labs’ $9.00M win against Ryder Ripps</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231810885947392</link>
      <description>03:59US appeals court overturns Yuga Labs’ $9.00M win against Ryder Ripps</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 04:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231810885947392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $85.96M yesterday, with net outflows continuing for 3 consecutive days.According to SoSoValue data, yesterday (Eastern Time, July 23) Bitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $85.96M. The Bitcoin spot ETF with the largest single-day net inflow yesterday was Blackrock&apos;s ETF IBIT, with a single-day net inflow of $143.00M. Currently, IBIT&apos;s total historical net inflow has reached $57.12B. The second largest was Grayscale&apos;s Bitcoin Mini Trust ETF BTC, with a single-day net inflow of $10.49M, and the current total historical net inflow of BTC has reached $1.66B. The Bitcoin spot ETF with the largest single-day net outflow yesterday was Fidelity&apos;s ETF FBTC, with a single-day net outflow of $227.00M, and the current total historical net inflow of FBTC has reached $12.32B. As of press time, the total net asset value of Bitcoin spot ETFs is $153.25B, the ETF net asset ratio (market value as a percentage of the total market value of Bitcoin) is 6.53%, and the cumulative historical net inflow has reached $54.47B. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231940854845440</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoOdailyBitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $85.96M yesterday, with net outflows continuing for 3 consecutive days.According to SoSoValue data, yesterday (Eastern Time, July 23) Bitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $85.96M. The Bitcoin spot ETF with the largest single-day</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231940854845440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase Believes Prediction of Stablecoin Market Cap Increasing to $2 Trillion is &quot;Slightly Optimistic&quot;According to The Economic Times, JPMorgan Chase believes that the often-mentioned prediction that the stablecoin market could grow to $2.00T is &quot;slightly optimistic&quot; in the recent push for the first approval of cryptocurrency market regulation legislation in the United States. Currently, the market capitalization of all stablecoins is approximately $260.00B. JPMorgan Chase stated, &quot;We find it hard to believe that the market can grow significantly in the coming years, as the infrastructure/ecosystem supporting stablecoins is far from developed and will take time to build.&quot; Despite the recent increase in market interest in stablecoins, they still account for less than 1% of global capital flows, indicating that this digital asset still has a long way to go in disrupting the financial system. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231322014650368</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoForesightNewsJPMorgan Chase Believes Prediction of Stablecoin Market Cap Increasing to $2 Trillion is &quot;Slightly Optimistic&quot;According to The Economic Times, JPMorgan Chase believes that the often-mentioned prediction that the stablecoin market could grow to $2.00T is &quot;slightly optimistic</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948231322014650368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana implemented SIMD-0256 yesterday, increasing the block limit by 20%On July 24, according to crypto KOL MartyParty, Solana implemented an upgrade yesterday based on the SIMD-0256 proposal, increasing the block size by 20%. This upgrade increased the block computing unit limit from 50.00 million CUs to 60.00 million CUs, allowing each block to accommodate more transactions, thereby improving network throughput and performance. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948230813400764416</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsSolana implemented SIMD-0256 yesterday, increasing the block limit by 20%On July 24, according to crypto KOL MartyParty, Solana implemented an upgrade yesterday based on the SIMD-0256 proposal, increasing the block size by 20%. This upgrade increased the block computing unit limit</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948230813400764416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong 70-Year-Old Man Falls Victim to Cryptocurrency Romance ScamA 70-year-old retired Hong Kong man received a message on WhatsApp from someone claiming to be a female neighbor, which led to a &quot;twilight romance,&quot; but he never met the person. The woman claimed to work at the Singapore Exchange and have insider information on some cryptocurrency investments, falsely claiming that he would receive substantial returns. The man transferred a total of HK$3,272,700.00 in 37 transactions to 34 bank accounts provided by the woman. It was not until the man personally went to the bank to withdraw a large sum of cash because he had reached the ATM withdrawal limit that bank staff noticed the transaction was unusual and immediately notified the Anti-Deception Coordination Centre, which finally exposed the scam. The man lost more than HK$3.27M in total and incurred nearly HK$1M in debt as a result. Hong Kong police said they had received nearly 20 online romance scams related to investment in the past two weeks, with 40% of the victims being over 60 years old, with a total loss of more than HK$10.00M. [Wenweipo Hong Kong]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229840624226304</link>
      <description>10 minutes ago吴说Hong Kong 70-Year-Old Man Falls Victim to Cryptocurrency Romance ScamA 70-year-old retired Hong Kong man received a message on WhatsApp from someone claiming to be a female neighbor, which led to a &quot;twilight romance,&quot; but he never met the person. The woman claimed to work at the Sing</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229840624226304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday, marking a 3 days of consistent outflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 23th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net inflow yesterday was BlackRock&apos;s ETF IBIT, with a daily net inflow of 142.56M USD, and the total historical net inflow of IBIT currently stands at 57.12B USD.The second highest was Grayscale Bitcoin Mini Trust ETF BTC, with a daily net inflow of 10.49M USD, and the total historical net inflow of BTC currently stands at 1.66B USD.The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net outflow yesterday was Fidelity&apos;s ETF FBTC, with a daily net outflow of 227.24M USD, and the total historical net inflow of FBTC currently stands at 12.32B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 153.25B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.53%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.47B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229479523504128</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday, marking a 3 days of consistent outflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 85.96M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 23th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net infl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948229479523504128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly listed company Lion Group announces total cryptocurrency acquisition costs have reached $9.60 millionOn July 24, Lion Group (NASDAQ: LGHL) announced that it has purchased additional SUI tokens, bringing the total acquisition cost of its HYPE, SOL and SUI tokens to approximately $9.6 million. These tokens are a core component of LGHL&apos;s strategic reserve funds, which are dedicated to investing in the next-generation Layer-1 blockchain ecosystem. As of July 23, 2025, LGHL&apos;s reserve asset holdings are as follows: 128,929 HYPE, 6,629 SOL, and 1,015,680 SUI. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948228893512634368</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsPublicly listed company Lion Group announces total cryptocurrency acquisition costs have reached $9.60 millionOn July 24, Lion Group (NASDAQ: LGHL) announced that it has purchased additional SUI tokens, bringing the total acquisition cost of its HYPE, SOL and SUI tokens to approx</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948228893512634368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkham: The US government’s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000Arkham stated that the US government has not sold its 170,000 BTC (about $20 billion) in the past four months. Among them, the US Marshals Service (USMS) currently holds about 28,988 BTC (about $3.4 billion), while other agencies such as the FBI, the Department of Justice (DOJ), the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) and local prosecutors&apos; offices hold at least 198,000 BTC (about $23.5 billion) in total. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227735171698688</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoPANewsArkham: The US government’s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000Arkham stated that the US government has not sold its 170,000 BTC (about $20 billion) in the past four months. Among them, the US Marshals Service (USMS) currently holds about 28,988 BTC (about $3.4 billion), whil</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227735171698688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller Joins Paradigm TeamParadigm co-founder Matt Huang tweeted that former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller has joined the Paradigm team to help its portfolio design in cutting-edge areas. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227236993241088</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoForesightNewsFormer OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller Joins Paradigm TeamParadigm co-founder Matt Huang tweeted that former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller has joined the Paradigm team to help its portfolio design in cutting-edge areas. [Foresight News]#FundraisingShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227236993241088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripple: Beware of XRP-related scams on YouTubeOn July 24, Ripple issued a warning on the X platform, noting that XRP-related scams are increasing on the YouTube platform. After the scammers steal the account, they will update the page content and pretend to be the official Ripple account. Ripple or the company&apos;s executives will never ask users to send them XRP. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948224201592213504</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoPANewsRipple: Beware of XRP-related scams on YouTubeOn July 24, Ripple issued a warning on the X platform, noting that XRP-related scams are increasing on the YouTube platform. After the scammers steal the account, they will update the page content and pretend to be the official Ripple</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948224201592213504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches New VIP Event, Complete Tasks to Unlock 50,000 BGBBitget has launched a new VIP event. During the event, users who complete net deposit, contract, or spot trading volume tasks can receive corresponding BGB airdrop rewards, with a total prize pool of 50,000 BGB. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223766089240576</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Launches New VIP Event, Complete Tasks to Unlock 50,000 BGBBitget has launched a new VIP event. During the event, users who complete net deposit, contract, or spot trading volume tasks can receive corresponding BGB airdrop rewards, with a total prize pool of 50,000</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223766089240576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to start next creditor payout on Sep. 30 with $1.9 billion granted by courtFTX announced Wednesday that it is expected to start distributing the next batch of creditor claims on Sep. 30. The record date for claim holders is set for Aug. 15.

Its latest announcement also revealed that the bankruptcy court gave the greenlight to cut down the claims reserve from $6.5 billion to $4.3 billion, which releases $1.9 billion to be distributed to holders in the upcoming disbursement. However, it did not explicitly state how much would be allocated for the Sept. 30 distribution.

FTX has so far handed out approximately $6.2 billion to former customers across two distributions — $1.2 billion in February and $5.0 billion in May this year. The overall repayment plan aims to distribute between $14.7 billion and $16.5 billion, with recoveries varying based on claim type and valuation.

Around 98% of the creditors are expected to receive at least 119% of their claims based on the value at the time of the bankruptcy. Some creditors have criticized the plan, noting that the overall crypto market has significantly appreciated in value since the bankruptcy in 2022.

The payout is expected to be made through BitGo, Kraken and Payoneer. Traders anticipate that these FTX distributions could inject significant liquidity into the crypto market, especially for altcoins.

Meanwhile, the FTX Recovery Trust submitted a motion on July 4 requesting the court to authorize the implementation of new measures to assess creditor claim distributions in restricted jurisdictions overseas.

The motion sought to immediately forfeit and reverse claims in countries designated as &quot;restricted jurisdictions,&quot; where distributions would be deemed illegal. Potentially affected countries included China, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Pakistan. The proposal drew backlash and formal objections from creditors in those regions.

At a hearing on Tuesday, the court acknowledged the objections to the proposed motion and ordered FTX to revise it —removing the clause that would allow for the &quot;immediate&quot; forfeiture of claims and adding an option for creditors in restricted regions to transfer and receive their claims through a different jurisdiction, according to an X post by FTX Historian. [FTX Historian]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223295937122304</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoThe BlockFTX to start next creditor payout on Sep. 30 with $1.9 billion granted by courtFTX announced Wednesday that it is expected to start distributing the next batch of creditor claims on Sep. 30. The record date for claim holders is set for Aug. 15.

Its latest announcement also re</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223295937122304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistics: Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated a total of 466,253 ETH, worth 1.7 billion yuanNew wallets have purchased 40,591 ETH (worth 148 million yuan) today. Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated 466,253 ETH (worth 1.7 billion yuan).
 Specific details:
 The 0x8eEa address received 138,345 ETH (worth 505 million yuan) from FalconX in the past 5 days;
 The 0x9684 address received 122,691 ETH (worth 448 million yuan) from FalconX in the past 13 days;
 The 0x35fb address withdrew 103,274 ETH (worth 377 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 15 days;
 The 0x3dF3 address received 43,787 ETH (worth 160 million yuan) from Galaxy Digital in the past 5 days;
 The 0xD479 address withdrew 32,902 ETH (worth 120 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 5 days;
 The 0xf877 address has withdrawn 12,913 ETH (worth 47 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 10 days;
 The 0x6A95 address withdrew 12,341 ETH (worth 45 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 9 days. [Lookonchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221416465305600</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoPANewsStatistics: Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated a total of 466,253 ETH, worth 1.7 billion yuanNew wallets have purchased 40,591 ETH (worth 148 million yuan) today. Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated 466,253 ETH (worth 1.7 billion yuan).
 Specific details:
 The 0x8eEa a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221416465305600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX launches grid strategy special event, with up to 10,000 USDT strategy position airdrops availableAccording to official sources, OKX will launch a strategy trading special event from 11:00 on July 24, 2025 to 23:59 on August 24, 2025 (UTC+8). The first theme is &quot;grid strategy&quot;. Participating users will have the opportunity to receive a 10,000.00 USDT grid strategy position airdrop and limited peripheral rewards. During the event, users can quickly understand the grid strategy through interesting videos, and start BTC spot grid or contract grid strategy trading with one click. The system defaults to AI intelligent parameters, and users can also choose &quot;custom parameters&quot;. At the same time, you can also participate in the &quot;OKX Chinese&quot; official Twitter original content sharing to win more rewards. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221881844305920</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoOdailyOKX launches grid strategy special event, with up to 10,000 USDT strategy position airdrops availableAccording to official sources, OKX will launch a strategy trading special event from 11:00 on July 24, 2025 to 23:59 on August 24, 2025 (UTC+8). The first theme is &quot;grid strategy&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221881844305920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb to List LISTA and MERL KRW Trading PairsSouth Korea&apos;s second-largest crypto exchange, Bithumb, will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs. Trading will open at 4:00 PM and 6:00 PM local time, respectively. Lista DAO is a decentralized stablecoin lending protocol powered by LSDfi. Merlin Chain is a Bitcoin Layer 2 powered by Bitmap. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216915113086976</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Bithumb to List LISTA and MERL KRW Trading PairsSouth Korea&apos;s second-largest crypto exchange, Bithumb, will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs. Trading will open at 4:00 PM and 6:00 PM local time, respectively. Lista DAO is a decentralized stablecoin lending protocol powered by LSDfi.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216915113086976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Momentum Ignites Hong Kong Race for Crypto DominanceIn this week’s Hong Kong Edition, we survey the fizzing stablecoin scene, speak with the man behind Bar Leone and look into the stocks leaving Chinese tech in the dust. For the Review, we visit a new modern Korean restaurant from the chef formerly of Singapore’s famed Odette. To subscribe to this weekly newsletter for free, click here.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948217933922111488</link>
      <description>1 hour agoBloombergStablecoin Momentum Ignites Hong Kong Race for Crypto DominanceIn this week’s Hong Kong Edition, we survey the fizzing stablecoin scene, speak with the man behind Bar Leone and look into the stocks leaving Chinese tech in the dust. For the Review, we visit a new modern Korean rest</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948217933922111488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26.According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will launch DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26. Eligible users can go to the Alpha activity page to use Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop after trading opens. Specific rules will be announced separately. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216849795190784</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance Alpha will list DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26.According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will launch DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26. Eligible users can go to the Alpha activity page to use Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop after trading opens. Specific rul</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216849795190784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale has closed their PUMP short position, netting a profit of $2.448M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has closed its PUMP short position on Hyperliquid, with a cumulative profit of $2.448 million. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948214328607444992</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA certain whale has closed their PUMP short position, netting a profit of $2.448M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has closed its PUMP short position on Hyperliquid, with a cumulative profit of $2.448 million. [Odaily Planet Daily]$PUMP$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948214328607444992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget CEO: The next bull market will be driven by application implementation, compliance, and technical value.Bitget CEO Gracy Chen tweeted, &quot;I don&apos;t think the next bull market will be driven by retail investors and meme coins again, nor will it be tied to the halving cycle. Instead, it will depend on how many applications can be implemented, how clear compliance regulations are, and how much real value technology can create.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211919416004608</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitget CEO: The next bull market will be driven by application implementation, compliance, and technical value.Bitget CEO Gracy Chen tweeted, &quot;I don&apos;t think the next bull market will be driven by retail investors and meme coins again, nor will it be tied to the halving cycle.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211919416004608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After School Club NFT Launches Utility Token GEMThe Eclipse ecosystem NFT series After School Club has launched a utility token, GEM. GEM will be rewarded by providing ASC holders with practical uses and long-term benefit alignment within the Eclipse ecosystem. The initial airdrop snapshot was completed on July 21, with each ASC NFT allocated 5 GEM tokens, for a total airdrop of 50,000 GEM (10% of the supply). In addition, monthly airdrops will continue for 45 months, with 1 GEM allocated per ASC NFT each month, for a total allocation of 450,000 GEM (90% of the supply). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211585964642304</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsAfter School Club NFT Launches Utility Token GEMThe Eclipse ecosystem NFT series After School Club has launched a utility token, GEM. GEM will be rewarded by providing ASC holders with practical uses and long-term benefit alignment within the Eclipse ecosystem. The initial air</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211585964642304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined, over 7.5% has been permanently lostOn July 24, according to Curated Crypto data, only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined. It is estimated that more than 7.5% of the total Bitcoin supply has permanently disappeared from circulation due to lost wallets, forgotten private keys, or being destroyed. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948208958342238208</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowData: Only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined, over 7.5% has been permanently lostOn July 24, according to Curated Crypto data, only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined. It is estimated that more than 7.5% of the total Bitcoin supply has permanently disappeared from circulation du</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948208958342238208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>