<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:17:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bifrost Launches $3.00M Multi-Chain Liquidity Incentive to Drive Polkadot DeFi into a Multi-Chain EcosystemOn July 24th, to open up asset channels between Polkadot and the mainstream multi-chain ecosystem, vDOT/ETH and vDOT/BNB liquidity pools will be officially launched on Uniswap V4 on July 25th, and a 12-month liquidity incentive program with a total of 795,000 DOT incentives will be launched simultaneously. This integration provides DOT with a stable and sustainable liquidity entry point into the Ethereum ecosystem, expanding its actual usability in mainstream DeFi networks. As part of the DeFi Singularity program, the first round of incentives now covers Arbitrum, Base, BNB Chain, and the Ethereum mainnet, and liquidity rewards are simultaneously launched around the vDOT/ETH and DOT/ETH pools. Users can participate in liquidity provision through Uniswap V4 and receive incentives in real-time on the Merkl platform. vDOT is a DOT liquid staking token launched by Bifrost, and currently has a cumulative staked TVL of over $74,000,000.00, widely used in governance, lending, DEX and other scenarios. This round of incentives is seen as an important step in promoting vDOT to become a multi-chain yield-bearing asset, and also brings higher liquidity and DeFi integration potential to DOT. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325752528769024</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoTechFlowBifrost Launches $3.00M Multi-Chain Liquidity Incentive to Drive Polkadot DeFi into a Multi-Chain EcosystemOn July 24th, to open up asset channels between Polkadot and the mainstream multi-chain ecosystem, vDOT/ETH and vDOT/BNB liquidity pools will be officially launched on Unis</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325752528769024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto mining firm Bitzero announces completion of $25.00M fundingBitzero, a crypto mining company backed by renowned investor Kevin O&apos;Leary, has announced the completion of a $25.00M funding round, which it intends to use to expand its business footprint in North America and Europe. The company stated that it will initially use part of the funds to purchase 2,900 Bitmain S21 Pro miners, which are expected to be deployed within 4 to 6 months, increasing annual revenue by approximately $10.00M. Headquartered in Vancouver, Bitzero focuses on using low-carbon energy sources such as hydropower to support high-performance computing and blockchain tasks, and is currently advancing the construction of four new facilities in North Dakota, Norway, and Finland. [TheBlock]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325420419584000</link>
      <description>3 minutes ago吴说Crypto mining firm Bitzero announces completion of $25.00M fundingBitzero, a crypto mining company backed by renowned investor Kevin O&apos;Leary, has announced the completion of a $25.00M funding round, which it intends to use to expand its business footprint in North America and Europe.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325420419584000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK and India sign free trade agreementOn July 24, Bloomberg reported that the UK and India have officially signed a free trade agreement, eliminating tariffs on a number of products including cars and alcohol. The agreement was reached after three years of negotiations. It is the largest trade agreement since the UK&apos;s withdrawal from the EU and the most important trade agreement for India in a decade. According to the agreement, 90% of tariff items exported by the UK to India will be reduced, of which 85% will be completely duty-free within ten years; 99% of tariff items exported by India to the UK will also be reduced. The agreement is expected to increase the output of the UK economy by 4.8 billion pounds per year and bring long-term trade growth to the two countries. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324399509213184</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsUK and India sign free trade agreementOn July 24, Bloomberg reported that the UK and India have officially signed a free trade agreement, eliminating tariffs on a number of products including cars and alcohol. The agreement was reached after three years of negotiations. It is the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324399509213184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsSenseTime announced the placement of 1.667 billion new Class B shares, with expected total fundraising of approximately HKD 2.5 billion, subscribed by international long-term capital Infini Capital. The company announced that it intends to use approximately 20% of the net proceeds from the placement to explore the technological integration of AI and innovative vertical fields, including embodied intelligent robots, blockchain, Real World Assets (RWA), digital assets, and stablecoins, and will consider cooperating with strategic partners to carry out related businesses and obtain qualifications. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324449689866240</link>
      <description>7 minutes ago吴说SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsSenseTime announced the placement of 1.667 billion new Class B shares, with expected total fundraising of approximately HKD</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948324449689866240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance alpha is now live with ASPOn July 24, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched ASP. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323539651727360</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoTechFlowBinance alpha is now live with ASPOn July 24, the official page showed that Binance alpha has launched ASP. [深潮 TechFlow]$BNBShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323539651727360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treehouse Opens TREE Token Airdrop InquiryDecentralized fixed income layer Treehouse has announced the opening of airdrop queries and is about to launch its TGE. Users who accumulated more than 100 points in its GoNuts Season 1 campaign and passed the Sybil check can receive TREE tokens. In addition, as a reward to long-term users, Treehouse will also provide an additional 100% vault reward on top of the base share. At the same time, Treehose NFT holders will also receive a fixed amount of TREE airdrop rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323444252282880</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoForesightNewsTreehouse Opens TREE Token Airdrop InquiryDecentralized fixed income layer Treehouse has announced the opening of airdrop queries and is about to launch its TGE. Users who accumulated more than 100 points in its GoNuts Season 1 campaign and passed the Sybil check can recei</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323444252282880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana devs eye 66% block limit increase to 100M compute units to further boost network capacitySolana core developers have published a new improvement document, SIMD-0286, that would increase the network’s per-block compute limit from 60 million to 100 million compute units, a 66% boost aimed at delivering more throughput for decentralized finance users and builders, according to the Solana Foundation’s GitHub proposal.

Block limits define the amount of computational work that validators can process within each 400-millisecond block. Bigger ceilings allow high-intensity programs, such as order-book DEXs and MEV auctioneers, to run without encountering “compute budget exceeded” errors, although they also require validators to handle heavier loads.

The network last raised block limits on July 23 through the activation of SIMD 0256, which raised capacity to 60 million CUs, helping Solana process roughly 1,700 transactions per second in daytime traffic. But developer demand for more headroom has grown as restaking protocols, NFT mints, and DePIN projects crowd block space. The change, currently being discussed and tested, would take effect in an upcoming software release and activate automatically at a future epoch once validators upgrade and agree to the higher ceiling.

Solana’s SIMD‑0286 proposal arrives as rival chains shell out their own upgrades. Ethereum’s Pectra hard fork improved the utility of ephemeral data blobs for roll‑ups introduced in the Dencun update. The Bitcoin community is exploring the OP_CAT opcode for smart contract extensions, such as covenants, and better scripting, a move that could greenlight more programmable operations on the network.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323335707889664</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoThe BlockSolana devs eye 66% block limit increase to 100M compute units to further boost network capacitySolana core developers have published a new improvement document, SIMD-0286, that would increase the network’s per-block compute limit from 60 million to 100 million compute units,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948323335707889664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA), supporting USD1 and GT subscriptionsAccording to the official announcement, Gate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA) from 13:00 on July 26, 2025 to 13:00 on July 29, 2025 (UTC+8), supporting users to subscribe to IKA tokens with USD1 and GT. The subscription price is 0.025 USD1, and the total subscription amount is 200,000,000 IKA. Limited purchase, first come first served. The GT subscription price will be calculated based on the average opening price of GT on July 24, 25, and 26 (UTC+8), and will be announced 2 hours before the subscription starts. The upper limit of the number of tokens that a single person can obtain is 2,000,000 IKA, which will be uniformly distributed within 4 hours after the subscription ends. At the same time, Gate will launch Ika (IKA) spot trading at 18:00 (UTC+8) on July 29, 2025, opening the IKA/USD1 trading pair. In addition, Gate Launchpad will also launch a new user benefit event from now until 00:00 (UTC+8) on August 1, 2025. Registration and transactions can share 2,000 GT, and the first order loss will be subsidized 100%. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325068215488512</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoOdailyGate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA), supporting USD1 and GT subscriptionsAccording to the official announcement, Gate Launchpad will launch Ika (IKA) from 13:00 on July 26, 2025 to 13:00 on July 29, 2025 (UTC+8), supporting users to subscribe to IKA tokens with USD1 and GT. The</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948325068215488512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coingecko Report: Comparison of Cost Price vs. Current Value of ETH Assets Held by Major Listed CompaniesAccording to a Coingecko report, as of July 23, 2025, SharpLink Gaming holds 360,807 ETH, ranking first, with over 95% deployed on staking platforms. SharpLink Gaming&apos;s entry price for ETH was $1.03B, with an average purchase price of $2,864.00, currently valued at $1.33B, with unrealized gains of 29.0%. Bitmine entered the market at $977.30M, with an average purchase price of $3,251.00, currently valued at $1.11B, with unrealized gains of 13.7%. Bit Digital&apos;s ETH appreciation was as high as 85.8%, from $239.30M to $444.50M. Although Exodus has the smallest holdings, its unrealized gains are the highest, at 102.7%. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948321327454162944</link>
      <description>24 minutes ago吴说Coingecko Report: Comparison of Cost Price vs. Current Value of ETH Assets Held by Major Listed CompaniesAccording to a Coingecko report, as of July 23, 2025, SharpLink Gaming holds 360,807 ETH, ranking first, with over 95% deployed on staking platforms. SharpLink Gaming&apos;s entry pric</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948321327454162944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese nail salon operator Convano Inc. bought 79.92 BTC this week.According to NL Nico monitoring, Japanese nail salon operator Convano Inc. has announced the official launch of its Bitcoin treasury strategy and has increased its holdings by approximately 22.63 BTC again. This week, it has spent 1,399,998,574.00 yen to purchase 79.92 BTC, with an average purchase price of 17,517,065.00 yen. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948322548009209856</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyJapanese nail salon operator Convano Inc. bought 79.92 BTC this week.According to NL Nico monitoring, Japanese nail salon operator Convano Inc. has announced the official launch of its Bitcoin treasury strategy and has increased its holdings by approximately 22.63 BTC again. This</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948322548009209856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: BNB Chain and TRON Dominate Stablecoin Active Address UsageAccording to Messari&apos;s stablecoin report &quot;State of Stablecoins,&quot; citing Artemis data, as of June 30, 2025, BNB Chain leads in stablecoin usage with 11.80M active addresses, followed by TRON (9.60M addresses) and Polygon PoS (4.90M addresses). Data shows that since 2023, BNB Chain and TRON have steadily grown in the number of active addresses, significantly leading other networks, including Ethereum (2.50M addresses) and Solana (3.10M addresses). [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948320024078389248</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoOdailyReport: BNB Chain and TRON Dominate Stablecoin Active Address UsageAccording to Messari&apos;s stablecoin report &quot;State of Stablecoins,&quot; citing Artemis data, as of June 30, 2025, BNB Chain leads in stablecoin usage with 11.80M active addresses, followed by TRON (9.60M addresses) and P</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948320024078389248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bitget 2025 King&apos;s Cup Global Invitational - KCGI is now officially underway, with a total prize pool of 6.00M USDT.The Bitget 2025 King&apos;s Cup Global Invitational Tournament KCGI is now officially underway. This year&apos;s event features five core stages: Team League, Copy Trading &amp; Trading Bot Competition, Hot Coin Arena, OnChain Challenge, and Hot Coin Airdrop, with a total prize pool of 6.00M USDT. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948318238877749248</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoForesightNewsThe Bitget 2025 King&apos;s Cup Global Invitational - KCGI is now officially underway, with a total prize pool of 6.00M USDT.The Bitget 2025 King&apos;s Cup Global Invitational Tournament KCGI is now officially underway. This year&apos;s event features five core stages: Team League, Copy</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948318238877749248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian fintech Finder wins court battle over crypto yield productAustralia’s Federal Court ruled Finder’s Earn product is not a financial instrument, defeating ASIC’s appeal in a major win for the country’s fintech sector.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948315348419284992</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoPANewsAustralian fintech Finder wins court battle over crypto yield productAustralia’s Federal Court ruled Finder’s Earn product is not a financial instrument, defeating ASIC’s appeal in a major win for the country’s fintech sector.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948315348419284992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky 联创 has repurchased 24.53M SKY and transferred it back to the staking address, worth approximately $2.08MAccording to @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, Sky (formerly MakerDAO) co-founder Rune continues to use SKY&apos;s staking rewards to repurchase SKY. An hour ago, he claimed SKY staking rewards: 1.90M USDS + 10.378M SPK (1.30M), then transferred them to his repurchase address, and has now repurchased 24.53M SKY (2.08M) and transferred them back to the staking address. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312952955801600</link>
      <description>53 minutes ago吴说Sky 联创 has repurchased 24.53M SKY and transferred it back to the staking address, worth approximately $2.08MAccording to @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, Sky (formerly MakerDAO) co-founder Rune continues to use SKY&apos;s staking rewards to repurchase SKY. An hour ago, he claimed SKY staking reward</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312952955801600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes: Cryptocurrency tax treatment remains unchanged after new US billReported on July 24 that, according to Forbes, despite the recent passage of the GENIUS Act and the CLARITY Act in the Senate, the U.S. Internal Revenue Service (IRS) still regards cryptocurrencies as &quot;intangible property&quot; for taxation, and the relevant tax regulations have not changed substantially for investors and traders. The GENIUS Act strengthens the compliance requirements for stablecoin issuers, but does not affect the tax classification of crypto assets. The CLARITY Act proposes a regulatory framework for digital asset securities and commodities, but also does not change the existing position of the IRS. Experts pointed out that currently cryptocurrency transactions do not need to comply with the wash sale rules of securities, and investors can flexibly carry forward losses, but they cannot enjoy the preferential tax treatment of some securities or commodity transactions. Unless the U.S. tax law is further revised, cryptocurrencies will still be taxed as property. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312559228096512</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoPANewsForbes: Cryptocurrency tax treatment remains unchanged after new US billReported on July 24 that, according to Forbes, despite the recent passage of the GENIUS Act and the CLARITY Act in the Senate, the U.S. Internal Revenue Service (IRS) still regards cryptocurrencies as &quot;intang</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312559228096512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Tether is ready to operate in the US market and will target the institutional marketTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated, &quot;Tether is ready to operate in the US market.&quot; A week ago, President Donald Trump signed the &quot;genius bill,&quot; regulating stablecoins in the US, and publicly thanked Ardoino for his work in the bill. Ardoino stated, &quot;We are developing an internal strategy for the US and plan to announce it in the next two months.&quot; The new US stablecoin will target the institutional market. Ardoino concluded by reiterating that Tether has no intention of going public like its US competitor Circle. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312580321251328</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoForesightNewsTether CEO: Tether is ready to operate in the US market and will target the institutional marketTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated, &quot;Tether is ready to operate in the US market.&quot; A week ago, President Donald Trump signed the &quot;genius bill,&quot; regulating stablecoins in the US, an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312580321251328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese AI company Quantum to buy up to 3,000 Bitcoin within 12 monthsAccording to CoinDesk Japan, Japanese listed company Quantum Solutions has announced that it will purchase up to 3,000 Bitcoin (approximately 53.85B JPY) in the next 12 months, officially entering the cryptocurrency field. The company stated that this move is aimed at responding to the global crypto market expansion and the popularity of Bitcoin as &quot;digital gold,&quot; while also diversifying assets, reducing exchange rate risks, and hedging against inflation. Quantum plans to initially invest approximately 1.48B JPY and will gradually implement the plan using borrowed funds. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948311356540784640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsJapanese AI company Quantum to buy up to 3,000 Bitcoin within 12 monthsAccording to CoinDesk Japan, Japanese listed company Quantum Solutions has announced that it will purchase up to 3,000 Bitcoin (approximately 53.85B JPY) in the next 12 months, officially entering the crypt</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948311356540784640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes: US stablecoins still treated as property for tax purposes, GENIUS Act does not change tax rulesAccording to Forbes, although the US recently passed the GENIUS Act, the IRS still considers digital assets as property, and the key tax rules remain unchanged for traders and investors. The GENIUS Act imposes strict reserve, audit, and disclosure requirements on US stablecoin issuers, including 1:1 asset backing and monthly financial attestations; however, the bill does not reclassify stablecoins for tax purposes. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948305713092169728</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsForbes: US stablecoins still treated as property for tax purposes, GENIUS Act does not change tax rulesAccording to Forbes, although the US recently passed the GENIUS Act, the IRS still considers digital assets as property, and the key tax rules remain unchanged for traders an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948305713092169728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghana’s Central Bank plans to launch crypto regulatory framework to promote digital assetsOn July 24, the Central Bank of Ghana plans to introduce a licensing system for crypto platforms to regulate digital assets and capture related revenues. Central Bank Governor Johnson Asiama revealed that the regulatory framework is expected to be submitted to parliament for review in September this year. The new bill aims to use cryptocurrencies to promote cross-border trade, attract strategic investments, and collect financial data to advance the country’s digital asset sector. Earlier news, the Governor of the Central Bank of Ghana said: Ghana is finalizing the regulatory framework for cryptocurrency transactions. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302725002891264</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsGhana’s Central Bank plans to launch crypto regulatory framework to promote digital assetsOn July 24, the Central Bank of Ghana plans to introduce a licensing system for crypto platforms to regulate digital assets and capture related revenues. Central Bank Governor Johnson Asiama rev</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302725002891264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has launched U-margined perpetual contracts.On July 24, according to the official announcement, LBank has launched U-based perpetual contracts on July 24, 2025, at 14:30 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301297815457792</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowLBank has launched U-margined perpetual contracts.On July 24, according to the official announcement, LBank has launched U-based perpetual contracts on July 24, 2025, at 14:30 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301297815457792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 10:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>