<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:25:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$25.2965 millionOn July 24, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$25.2965 million. Among them: The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$5.6603 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$10.0176 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$800,700.00, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$2,024,500.00; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$2.3861 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$4.4072 million. Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948342558664495104</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$25.2965 millionOn July 24, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$25.2965 million. Among them: The trans</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948342558664495104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruihe Digital Technology Holdings announces HK$80.00 million cryptocurrency investment planOn July 24, according to the announcement of Ruihe Digital Technology Holdings Co., Ltd. (03680.HK), the board of directors has approved a budget of HK$80.00 million to develop Web3.0 business and invest in cryptocurrency assets in the next two years. The company said that this move is aimed at responding to the Hong Kong government&apos;s policy of supporting the development of Web3.0 and cryptocurrency industries. It plans to focus on digital asset services in Greater China and provide funds through internal resources or fundraising activities. The company believes that cryptocurrency asset investment is in line with the global trend of digital asset institutionalization and will help enhance overall competitiveness. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948342496500715520</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsRuihe Digital Technology Holdings announces HK$80.00 million cryptocurrency investment planOn July 24, according to the announcement of Ruihe Digital Technology Holdings Co., Ltd. (03680.HK), the board of directors has approved a budget of HK$80.00 million to develop Web3.0 busine</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948342496500715520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlockSec: Unverified contract on BSC was attacked, resulting in a loss of over $600,000.00According to BlockSec monitoring, a malicious transaction targeting an unverified contract on Binance Smart Chain (BSC) was discovered, resulting in losses exceeding $600,000.00. As the contract is not open source, our investigation indicates that the root cause is a lack of slippage protection. This vulnerability allowed the attacker to exploit the contract, using a fake liquidity pool to obtain TA tokens, and then selling these tokens in a legitimate pool for profit. It is recommended that users who have granted approval to this contract immediately revoke these permissions to prevent further losses. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948340787892260864</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoForesightNewsBlockSec: Unverified contract on BSC was attacked, resulting in a loss of over $600,000.00According to BlockSec monitoring, a malicious transaction targeting an unverified contract on Binance Smart Chain (BSC) was discovered, resulting in losses exceeding $600,000.00. As t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948340787892260864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale address that has been dormant for 14.5 years has been awakened. The address holds nearly 4,000 BTC, with an average holding cost of $0.375.According to on-chain analyst Ember, an ancient whale that accumulated 3,962.6 BTC 14 and a half years ago (January 2011) ended its dormancy 20 minutes ago and made a test transfer. When this address accumulated these BTC in 2011, the price of BTC was only $0.375. Today, 14 and a half years later, the price of BTC is 315,000.0 times what it was then. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948340147782750208</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoOdailyA whale address that has been dormant for 14.5 years has been awakened. The address holds nearly 4,000 BTC, with an average holding cost of $0.375.According to on-chain analyst Ember, an ancient whale that accumulated 3,962.6 BTC 14 and a half years ago (January 2011) ended its d</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948340147782750208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US court restarts trademark lawsuit related to Yuga Labs, rules BAYC NFT is a protectable trademarkA U.S. court has reinstated Yuga Labs&apos; trademark lawsuit against conceptual artist Ryder Ripps and developer Jeremy Cahen. The court ruled that a jury must decide whether the duo&apos;s parody NFT series misled consumers. Yuga Labs co-founder Greg Solano said that the court found in this appeal that Yuga&apos;s BAYC NFTs are protectable trademarks and not purely a scam, and also confirmed that NFTs can be protected as &quot;goods&quot; under the Lanham Act, rejecting arguments that NFTs are too intangible to qualify for trademark protection under U.S. law. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948339027387682816</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoForesightNewsUS court restarts trademark lawsuit related to Yuga Labs, rules BAYC NFT is a protectable trademarkA U.S. court has reinstated Yuga Labs&apos; trademark lawsuit against conceptual artist Ryder Ripps and developer Jeremy Cahen. The court ruled that a jury must decide whether the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948339027387682816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto hacks surpass $3.1B in 2025 as access flaws persist: HackenOver $3.1 billion in crypto has been lost in 2025, according to a Hacken report. Access-control exploits are the primary cause.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948338531335737344</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoPANewsCrypto hacks surpass $3.1B in 2025 as access flaws persist: HackenOver $3.1 billion in crypto has been lost in 2025, according to a Hacken report. Access-control exploits are the primary cause.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948338531335737344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin brand refresh, airdrop of 1,000 Labubu to launch a global creative solicitation, igniting the summer shanzhai season.On July 24th, the global crypto asset trading platform Hotcoin announced the renewal of its official website and launched the &quot;Trading Cute Friends&quot; global creative doll clothing solicitation event in collaboration with the well-known trendy toy IP Labubu. From now until July 31st, users can go to the official Twitter account (@hotcoinzh) to receive the new brand logo integrated into Labubu&apos;s creative doll clothing, and have the opportunity to share 1,000 sets of customized physical dolls. The final winning work selected by popular vote will be officially adopted and mass-produced, and the creator will also have the opportunity to receive $ETH in prize money. This brand upgrade and cross-border linkage marks Hotcoin&apos;s focus on creating a younger crypto new ecosystem, and welcoming the hot altcoin season together with community users. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337575722291200</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin brand refresh, airdrop of 1,000 Labubu to launch a global creative solicitation, igniting the summer shanzhai season.On July 24th, the global crypto asset trading platform Hotcoin announced the renewal of its official website and launched the &quot;Trading Cute Friends&quot; glob</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337575722291200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotion from AugustOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, Hong Kong will begin to implement the Stablecoin Ordinance on August 1, 2025, prohibiting the provision or promotion of unlicensed fiat-backed stablecoins (FRS) to retail investors. Violators may be fined up to HK$50,000.00 and imprisoned for six months. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) issued a warning on Wednesday, reminding investors to stay away from unlicensed stablecoins to avoid accidentally violating the law. HKMA President Yu Weiwen said that the new regulations are aimed at bringing credibility and stability to the stablecoin industry while protecting investors from fraud and excessive speculation. Although there are currently as many as 50 companies applying for stablecoin licenses, most applications lack practical implementation plans and only a few licenses will be approved. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337439373856768</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotion from AugustOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, Hong Kong will begin to implement the Stablecoin Ordinance on August 1, 2025, prohibiting the provision or promotion of unlicensed fiat-backed stablecoins (FRS) to retail i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337439373856768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale cleared out its last 100 Bitcoin, netting a total profit of approximately $12.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;1EGQSh&quot; address deposited its remaining 100 BTC (approximately $11.88M) into Binance an hour ago, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M (+65%). [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337631573643264</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyA whale cleared out its last 100 Bitcoin, netting a total profit of approximately $12.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;1EGQSh&quot; address deposited its remaining 100 BTC (approximately $11.88M) into Binance an hour ago, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337631573643264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank will be the first to launch Ponzimon (PONZI)According to official news on July 24, LBank will launch Ponzimon (PONZI) for the first time on July 24, 2025, at 18:30 (SGT), and open the PONZI/USDT trading pair. The deposit service will be opened on July 24 at 18:30 (SGT), and the withdrawal service will be opened on July 25 at 19:00 (SGT). [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337401834835968</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoTechFlowLBank will be the first to launch Ponzimon (PONZI)According to official news on July 24, LBank will launch Ponzimon (PONZI) for the first time on July 24, 2025, at 18:30 (SGT), and open the PONZI/USDT trading pair. The deposit service will be opened on July 24 at 18:30 (SGT), a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337401834835968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building crypto vaults with Veda co-founder Sun RaghupathiEpisode 35 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and Veda co-founder and CEO Sun Raghupathi.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or wherever you listen to podcasts. Please send feedback and revision requests to[emailprotected]

Tim and Sun discussed how DeFi vaults are simplifying complex finance systems and looking to drive mainstream and institutional adoption. Sun explained on Veda&apos;s Vault architecture, the importance of security, and the evolving competitive landscape in the DeFi space.

OUTLINE
00:00 – Introduction 
00:25 – What is Veda? 
03:31 – Potential Contagion Risks 
04:30 – GMX Hack 
05:39 – DeFi Hacks 
08:16 – Challenges of Building Vaults 
09:48 – DeFi&apos;s Evolution 
15:23 – Institutional Involvement 
16:58 – Vault Uses in TradFi 
17:47 – Tokenized Stocks 
20:44 – Vaults vs. Staking 
22:48 – Types of Vault Strategies 
24:39 – AI in Vault Management 
25:47 – Veda’s Future Plans 
26:37 – Conclusion

The Block Newsletters
The Block&apos;s newsletters bring you the latest news and analysis of the fast-moving crypto and DeFi markets. To subscribe, visit theblock.co/newsletters

Guest links:
Sun - ⁠⁠https://x.com/sunandr_⁠ 
Veda - ⁠⁠⁠https://x.com/veda_labs⁠

Are you hiring in crypto?
Use Campus to quickly find your best candidates with our challenging Crypto Assessment Test.
Faster hiring, stronger teams.

Sign up for a trial today:theblock.co/campus

[The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336925928132608</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoThe BlockBuilding crypto vaults with Veda co-founder Sun RaghupathiEpisode 35 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and Veda co-founder and CEO Sun Raghupathi.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or w</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336925928132608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Wallet launches BNB and XRP incentive activities to support the use of on-chain assetsOn July 24, according to an official announcement, Gate Wallet hit a new high around the price of BNB and officially launched two online incentive activities covering the two major assets of BNB and XRP.
During the event, new users who complete their first BNB transaction in their wallet (amount ≥ $100) can receive a maximum $10.00 airdrop, limited to the first 1,000 participants. All users who top up BNB can also share a $10,000.00 prize pool based on their top-up ratio, with a maximum single-person reward of $100.00.
In the XRP incentive activity, users who deposit no less than 10 XRP can participate in the $5,000.00 airdrop; those who complete XRP transactions (amount ≥ $50.00) can also participate in the $20,000.00 prize pool. The rewards are distributed according to the transaction ratio, and a single person can get up to $200.00. The activity ends on August 10.
Gate Wallet is the industry-leading multi-chain crypto wallet, connecting 100+ public chains, millions of assets and tens of thousands of DApps in one stop, opening up a professional-level Web3 experience and providing the best solution for every Web3 need. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336439938322432</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoPANewsGate Wallet launches BNB and XRP incentive activities to support the use of on-chain assetsOn July 24, according to an official announcement, Gate Wallet hit a new high around the price of BNB and officially launched two online incentive activities covering the two major assets o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336439938322432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-chain detective ZachXBT: Some projects are running Yaps campaigns to attract low-quality users and AI-generated content, which will only dilute brand value.On-chain detective ZachXBT posted on his personal channel, pointing out that some projects are currently attracting low-quality users and AI-generated content by running Yaps campaigns, which dilutes brand value and fails to bring long-term funds and real user growth. He called on the community to actively block related projects and question false data indicators in order to curb the &quot;proliferation of low-quality content&quot; in the ecosystem. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948335125921599488</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoOdailyOn-chain detective ZachXBT: Some projects are running Yaps campaigns to attract low-quality users and AI-generated content, which will only dilute brand value.On-chain detective ZachXBT posted on his personal channel, pointing out that some projects are currently attracting low-q</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948335125921599488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nansen data: In the past 7 days, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea have both surged by over 100%.According to Nansen data, possibly influenced by the upcoming announcement related to the TGE this month, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea has surged by over 100% in the past 7 days. On July 21st, the number of active addresses reached 75,700.00, the highest in nearly four months; the number of transactions on the same day exceeded 200,000.00, the first time in nearly 5 months. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333306109562880</link>
      <description>41 minutes ago吴说Nansen data: In the past 7 days, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea have both surged by over 100%.According to Nansen data, possibly influenced by the upcoming announcement related to the TGE this month, the number of active addresses and transactions on Linea h</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948333306109562880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVNU Launches Starknet Paymaster, Enabling Developers to Sponsor User Gas Fees in 5 MinutesAVNU, a trading center on Starknet, has announced the launch of Starknet Paymaster, an open-source, production-ready, developer-first method for extracting Gas fees. It allows Starknet developers to sponsor or extract user fees in 5 minutes, accepting any token as a Gas fee. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331432258113536</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoForesightNewsAVNU Launches Starknet Paymaster, Enabling Developers to Sponsor User Gas Fees in 5 MinutesAVNU, a trading center on Starknet, has announced the launch of Starknet Paymaster, an open-source, production-ready, developer-first method for extracting Gas fees. It allows Starkn</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331432258113536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.49% in the past 1H, down 0.19% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331038785626112</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.49% in the past 1H, down 0.19% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948331038785626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermBitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range, while the altcoin season index shows an upward trend, indicating that funds are rotating towards mainstream altcoins such as Ethereum, XRP, and Solana, with related assets rising by 20%-40% recently. Ryan Lee pointed out, &quot;The active performance of sectors such as AI, RWA, and Memecoin also shows the market&apos;s strong focus on specific narratives. However, the altcoin season index has not yet broken through the 75% confirmation threshold, and the current market is more likely a phase of rotation rather than a full-blown altcoin season. To drive the market to continue into the mid-to-late third quarter, the key lies in whether Bitcoin&apos;s market share can remain below 60%. At the same time, institutional fund inflows, regulatory benefits, and improved fundamentals in the Layer 1 and DeFi sectors are all important signals to confirm the start of the altcoin season.&quot; [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332610312278016</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailyBitget Research Institute: Altseason Index Shows an Upward Trend, Funds May Rotate to Altcoins in the Short TermBitget Research Institute&apos;s chief analyst Ryan Lee stated that Bitcoin&apos;s dominance has recently fallen back to the 59%-61% range, while the altcoin season index shows a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332610312278016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana developers consider increasing block limit by 66% to 100 million compute units to further increase network capacitySolana developers are considering increasing the block limit from 60 million compute units to 100 million compute units via the SIMD-0286 proposal, which would achieve a 66% capacity increase, provided validators opt-in to the upgrade. The proposal aims to further increase Solana network capacity, allowing for more transactions per second to be processed. Compute units are the basic unit of measurement for transaction complexity and resource consumption in the Solana network, and increasing the block compute unit limit will directly enhance the network&apos;s transaction processing capabilities. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332618767994880</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoOdailySolana developers consider increasing block limit by 66% to 100 million compute units to further increase network capacitySolana developers are considering increasing the block limit from 60 million compute units to 100 million compute units via the SIMD-0286 proposal, which woul</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948332618767994880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK-listed Satsuma Completes Over £100.00M Funding Round, Will Accelerate its Bitcoin Accumulation StrategyUK-listed Satsuma Technology PLC (Tao Alpha PLC) has announced the completion of its second round of convertible bond private placement, with the amount raised significantly exceeding the original minimum target of £100.00M. Satsuma stated that the financing will be used to expand its business and strengthen its Bitcoin adoption and decentralized AI strategy. The relevant convertible bond shares will be applied for listing on the London Main Board market after conversion. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328383770857472</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说UK-listed Satsuma Completes Over £100.00M Funding Round, Will Accelerate its Bitcoin Accumulation StrategyUK-listed Satsuma Technology PLC (Tao Alpha PLC) has announced the completion of its second round of convertible bond private placement, with the amount raised significantly exceedin</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948328383770857472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SlowMist CISO: Core Administrator of World&apos;s Largest Dark Web Crime Platform XSS.is Arrested23pds, Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at SlowMist, posted on the X platform that the core administrator of XSS.is, the world&apos;s largest dark web crime platform, has been arrested. This platform has been active for a long time and is one of the main trading places for Stealer tools (information stealers) in the cryptocurrency industry. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948327582923034624</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySlowMist CISO: Core Administrator of World&apos;s Largest Dark Web Crime Platform XSS.is Arrested23pds, Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at SlowMist, posted on the X platform that the core administrator of XSS.is, the world&apos;s largest dark web crime platform, has been arrested. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948327582923034624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>