<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:40:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>US looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scam</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908899146895360</link>
      <description>06:36US looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scam</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908899146895360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Ecosystem Protocol Strata Opens Pre-DepositEthena ecosystem protocol Strata opens pre-deposits. The first phase of the campaign will accept two tokens, USDe and eUSDe, and depositing the corresponding funds will qualify users for Ethena rewards and Strata points. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908817592848384</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsEthena Ecosystem Protocol Strata Opens Pre-DepositEthena ecosystem protocol Strata opens pre-deposits. The first phase of the campaign will accept two tokens, USDe and eUSDe, and depositing the corresponding funds will qualify users for Ethena rewards and Strata points. [Fo</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908817592848384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backed.fi&apos;s xStocks on-chain trading volume exceeds $300 million.Backed.fi&apos;s tokenized U.S. stock product, xStocks, has surpassed $300.00M in on-chain trading volume within four weeks of launching on Bybit, Kraken, and the Solana decentralized finance (DeFi) platform, indicating growing demand for tokenized U.S. stocks. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947907675509035008</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNewsBacked.fi&apos;s xStocks on-chain trading volume exceeds $300 million.Backed.fi&apos;s tokenized U.S. stock product, xStocks, has surpassed $300.00M in on-chain trading volume within four weeks of launching on Bybit, Kraken, and the Solana decentralized finance (DeFi) platform, indic</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947907675509035008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 0.61% in the past 1H, down 0.07% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947904108332539904</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 0.61% in the past 1H, down 0.07% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947904108332539904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIMCO: Trump may reshape the Fed through personnel appointmentsOn July 23, according to Jinshi, Pacific Investment Management Company (PIMCO) economist Tiffany Wilding pointed out in a report that although US President Trump may continue to criticize the Federal Reserve and call for interest rate cuts in the short term, he will not replace the current chairman Powell. Instead, Trump will influence the Fed&apos;s decision-making through upcoming appointments, including the term of Governor Kugler, which expires in January, and the term of Chairman Powell, which expires in May. It should be noted that Powell&apos;s term as a governor will last until January 2028. Wilding emphasized that no matter who Trump nominates to take over as chairman, the new leader must make a convincing monetary policy proposal, first obtain Senate approval, and then win the support of the majority of the Federal Open Market Committee. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947903980260102144</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoPANewsPIMCO: Trump may reshape the Fed through personnel appointmentsOn July 23, according to Jinshi, Pacific Investment Management Company (PIMCO) economist Tiffany Wilding pointed out in a report that although US President Trump may continue to criticize the Federal Reserve and call</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947903980260102144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 AI engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB ChainSummary: According to official news, Web3 artificial intelligence engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB Chain. It is reported that Orbofi is an AI agent creation platform where users can easily create exclusive, multimodal, personalized, socialized, and tokenized agents. Previously, Orbofi AI completed $2.80M in financing through private placements and public token sales, with participation from Cogitent Ventures, OIG Capital, CSP DAO, Zephyrus Capital, and Halvings Capital, among others. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902359694282752</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoForesightNewsWeb3 AI engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB ChainSummary: According to official news, Web3 artificial intelligence engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB Chain. It is reported that Orbofi is an AI agent creation platform where users can easily create exclusive, mu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902359694282752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DogeOS proposes to enable ZKP native verification capabilities on the Dogecoin network by introducing new opcodesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Dogecoin&apos;s ecological application development layer DogeOS officially submitted a technical proposal to Dogecoin Core, intending to implement zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) native verification function through a new opcode (OP_CHECKZKP). The upgrade will support off-chain applications such as Rollup and smart contracts, while maintaining the lightweight and high-speed characteristics of the main chain. The proposal adopts a modular design, and the first version supports Groth16 proof verification, and old version nodes can be compatible. To avoid performance risks, it is initially set that only one zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) can be used for each script and only five zero-knowledge proofs can be used for each block. DogeOS simultaneously develops a zk virtual machine compatible with EVM, allowing Ethereum native applications to run directly on Dogecoin infrastructure. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900229071736832</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsDogeOS proposes to enable ZKP native verification capabilities on the Dogecoin network by introducing new opcodesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Dogecoin&apos;s ecological application development layer DogeOS officially submitted a technical proposal to Dogecoin Core, intending to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900229071736832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merlin Founder: 2.0 Upgrade Officially Released, Aiming to Create &quot;Yield-Generating and Tradable&quot; BTCIn an exclusive interview with Odaily, Jeff, the founder of the Bitcoin Layer2 project Merlin Chain, stated that the Merlin 2.0 upgrade plan has been officially released. This version will focus on &quot;BTC&apos;s yield-generating and cross-chain trading capabilities,&quot; aiming to upgrade Bitcoin from a single store-of-value asset to an on-chain currency with profitability and liquidity. Jeff pointed out that Merlin Chain&apos;s core goals in the future will revolve around two directions: first, to enhance the practicality of BTC, making it available for multi-chain interaction, DeFi investment, and asset trading; and second, to lower the barriers for retail and institutional investors to enter the BTC ecosystem, so that BTC can not only outperform the market but also participate in new narratives and new projects, capturing higher potential returns. He also revealed that Merlin will continue to optimize the BTCfi ecosystem, expand AI-driven chain abstraction technology, and launch a series of user-friendly products in the next stage to promote BTC as a true &quot;universal currency&quot; on the chain. Click to read the original interview: &quot;Odaily Exclusive Interview with Merlin Founder Jeff: I Want to Give Up Every Day, But I Still Look Forward to Crossing the Cycle&quot; [Odaily].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902272100438016</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdailyMerlin Founder: 2.0 Upgrade Officially Released, Aiming to Create &quot;Yield-Generating and Tradable&quot; BTCIn an exclusive interview with Odaily, Jeff, the founder of the Bitcoin Layer2 project Merlin Chain, stated that the Merlin 2.0 upgrade plan has been officially released. This ver</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902272100438016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-linked World Liberty Financial buys over 3,400 ETH for $13.00 million, onchain data showsWorld Liberty Financial, a crypto project linked to U.S. President Donald Trump, spent millions to acquire more Ethereum on Tuesday as the cryptocurrency sees surging institutional demand.

Citing Arkham Intelligence data, onchain researcher Lookonchain reported that World Liberty added 3,473 ETH at an average price of $3,743 across a number of wallets during Tuesday evening. It appears to have staked some of the newly acquired ether.

The project currently owns roughly 73,616 ETH, worth about $275.9 million at current market prices, according to Lookonchain.

World Liberty&apos;s move comes amid rising institutional demand for ether. On Tuesday, spot Ethereum exchange-traded funds recorded $533.9 million in net inflows, while spot bitcoin ETFs saw a net outflow of $67.9 million, according to SoSoValue data.

The Block&apos;s price page shows that ether remained flat in the past 24 hours at $3,729. However, the second-largest cryptocurrency rose 20% in the past week and 67.1% in the past 30 days.

Meanwhile, World Liberty is preparing for the upcoming unlock of its WLFI token. The team said last week that it is aiming to have WLFI to officially begin trading within the next two months.

&quot;We&apos;re targeting 6 to 8 weeks for the full awakening — strategic alignments (alliances, grand stages, smart unlocks) take time to realize full potential,&quot; the project said last week. [Lookonchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900415118479360</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoThe BlockTrump-linked World Liberty Financial buys over 3,400 ETH for $13.00 million, onchain data showsWorld Liberty Financial, a crypto project linked to U.S. President Donald Trump, spent millions to acquire more Ethereum on Tuesday as the cryptocurrency sees surging institutional d</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900415118479360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Will Launch PENGU, CVX, and SLP Perpetual ContractsAccording to the official announcement, Binance Futures will launch PENGU/USDC, CVX/USDT, and SLP/USDT perpetual contracts successively on July 23, 2025, with up to 75x leverage. Among them, the PENGU/USDC contract will be launched at 7:30 (UTC), and the CVX/USDT and SLP/USDT contracts will be launched at 11:30 and 11:45 (UTC) respectively. (This news was generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902280547766272</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoOdailyBinance Will Launch PENGU, CVX, and SLP Perpetual ContractsAccording to the official announcement, Binance Futures will launch PENGU/USDC, CVX/USDT, and SLP/USDT perpetual contracts successively on July 23, 2025, with up to 75x leverage. Among them, the PENGU/USDC contract will b</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902280547766272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches Sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Event, Jointly Airdropping SYRUP with Maple FinanceBitget Wallet&apos;s sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event will officially start on July 23 at 21:00. This time, it will be jointly launched with Maple Finance to distribute a total of approximately 228,000 SYRUP tokens, with 120,000 participation slots available. This event features a special &quot;Super Lucky Koi Award,&quot; where one individual can win SYRUP worth $6,666.00.
&quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; is a brand airdrop event launched by Bitget Wallet. Users only need to stake $10.00 to participate, and the staked amount will be 100% returned afterward. Users can participate in the event through the Bitget Wallet App, explore on-chain staking gameplay, and receive airdrops. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899760412790784</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet Launches Sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Event, Jointly Airdropping SYRUP with Maple FinanceBitget Wallet&apos;s sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event will officially start on July 23 at 21:00. This time, it will be jointly launched with Maple Finance to distribute a total of approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899760412790784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polymarket forecasts a 67% probability that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot;According to Polymarket platform data, the probability of predicting that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot; has reached 67%, and the total prize pool is currently over $129,000.00. Prior news stated that Polymarket spent $112.00M to acquire the US compliant exchange QCX, and will legally return to the US market. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899768897867776</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyPolymarket forecasts a 67% probability that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot;According to Polymarket platform data, the probability of predicting that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot; has reached 67%, and the total prize pool is currently over $129,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899768897867776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: At least 200 Alpha points users can claim 1,500 COA token airdropAccording to official sources, Binance will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23, 2025, at 17:00 (UTC+8). After trading begins, users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha points can claim an airdrop of 1,500 COA tokens. First come, first served. If the event has not ended, the score threshold will automatically decrease by 10 points every hour. Please note that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha points. Users need to confirm the claim on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours, otherwise they will be deemed to have given up receiving the airdrop. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899777374556160</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoOdailyBinance: At least 200 Alpha points users can claim 1,500 COA token airdropAccording to official sources, Binance will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23, 2025, at 17:00 (UTC+8). After trading begins, users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha points can claim an airdrop of 1,500</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899777374556160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Expects Trump administration to raise base tariff rate to 15%Goldman Sachs&apos; chief U.S. economist, David Mericle, expects the U.S.&apos;s base &quot;like-for-like&quot; tariff rate to increase from 10% to 15%, with tariffs on copper and critical minerals reaching 50% - a move that could exacerbate inflationary pressures and dampen economic growth. To reflect the new tariff assumptions and incorporate the impact of import tariffs in an &quot;initial observation,&quot; Goldman Sachs has adjusted its forecasts for U.S. inflation and GDP growth accordingly. Goldman Sachs lowered its core inflation forecast for 2025 from 3.4% to 3.3%, raised its 2026 forecast from 2.6% to 2.7%, and raised its 2027 forecast from 2.0% to 2.4%. Mericle said tariffs are expected to cumulatively push up core prices by 1.7% over 2-3 years. He added that tariffs would reduce GDP growth by 1 percentage point this year, 0.4 percentage points in 2026, and 0.3 percentage points in 2027. Goldman Sachs has accordingly lowered its GDP growth forecast for 2025 to 1.0%. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899785813495808</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoOdailyGoldman Sachs: Expects Trump administration to raise base tariff rate to 15%Goldman Sachs&apos; chief U.S. economist, David Mericle, expects the U.S.&apos;s base &quot;like-for-like&quot; tariff rate to increase from 10% to 15%, with tariffs on copper and critical minerals reaching 50% - a move that</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899785813495808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.5 billion.According to validatorqueue.com data, there are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.50 billion, which accounts for 29.50% of the circulating supply of Ethereum. Charts show that while the amount of ETH staked has recently decreased, it remains at a historical high. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947897233889890304</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailyThere are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.5 billion.According to validatorqueue.com data, there are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.50 billion, which accounts for 29.50% of the circulating supply of Ethereum. Cha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947897233889890304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC approves, then instantly pauses Bitwise’s ETF conversionAnalysts speculate the Securities and Exchange Commission could be stalling until it creates listing standards for crypto ETFs, or is trying to stop its sole Democrat commissioner from disrupting the approval process.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947893335015886848</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSEC approves, then instantly pauses Bitwise’s ETF conversionAnalysts speculate the Securities and Exchange Commission could be stalling until it creates listing standards for crypto ETFs, or is trying to stop its sole Democrat commissioner from disrupting the approval process.#ETFSha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947893335015886848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Afternoon News1. CZ: Altcoin Season Index continues to rise, FOMO season may be coming;
2. FTX Hearing Minutes: Allows creditors in restricted jurisdictions to transfer claims to unrestricted jurisdictions;
3. DMG Blockchain Solutions plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasury including BTC;
4. PUMP falls below private placement price, some whales are still in profit, Machi Big Brother&apos;s long position has a floating loss of over $4.00M;
5. 10K announces project failure, has airdropped over $2.30M in tokens to pre-sale users;
6. South Korean blockchain infrastructure provider DSRV completes approximately $11.60M Series B first round of financing;
7. Binance Alpha will launch Lnfi Network (LN) on July 25;
8. Publicly listed company DigitalX increases its holdings by 74.7 Bitcoin, with total holdings reaching 499.8;
9. Bitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $67.93M yesterday, with only Grayscale ETF GBTC achieving a net inflow;
10. Ethereum spot ETFs had a total net inflow of $534.00M yesterday, the third highest in history.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947894717143912448</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyPlanet Afternoon News1. CZ: Altcoin Season Index continues to rise, FOMO season may be coming;
2. FTX Hearing Minutes: Allows creditors in restricted jurisdictions to transfer claims to unrestricted jurisdictions;
3. DMG Blockchain Solutions plans to establish a diversified digital a</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947894717143912448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui is now integrated with the Fireblocks platform and will support native custody and staking services.Sui officially announced that the Sui network has formally connected to the enterprise-grade digital asset infrastructure platform Fireblocks, aiming to provide services to institutional users seeking high performance and security. Currently, Fireblocks supports native custody of SUI and Sui ecosystem tokens, MPC wallet strategy control, and will subsequently support access to DeFi via WalletConnect, as well as integrate Fireblocks Trust&apos;s staking services. Sui stated that its high throughput and scalability are becoming the preferred path for financial institutions and game studios to access the next generation of digital asset world. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947892198208507904</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySui is now integrated with the Fireblocks platform and will support native custody and staking services.Sui officially announced that the Sui network has formally connected to the enterprise-grade digital asset infrastructure platform Fireblocks, aiming to provide services to institu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947892198208507904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasuryOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, DMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, announced that it is evaluating the institutional-level fund management strategy of its subsidiary Systemic Trust Company and plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasury. At this stage, the company&apos;s digital asset portfolio consists only of Bitcoin. It has begun to evaluate the use of existing mining income and additional funds to acquire other digital assets besides Bitcoin. DMG Blockchain Solutions currently holds approximately 341 Bitcoins, ranking 54th among listed Bitcoin treasury companies. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947889317124313088</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsDMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasuryOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, DMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, announced that it is evaluating the institutional-level fund management</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947889317124313088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed company SEALSQ plans to set up a $30.00 million cryptocurrency investment fundOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, SEALSQ Corp, a Nasdaq-listed public key infrastructure development company, announced that it is setting up a cryptocurrency investment fund of approximately US$30.00 million and plans to use the funds to purchase digital assets, including BTC, ETH, HBAR, etc. In addition, the company also stated that its cryptocurrency investment fund will serve as a strategic funding tool responsible for developing strategies for purchasing and holding cryptocurrencies, similar to how companies invest in traditional assets such as bonds or stocks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947887286087127040</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsListed company SEALSQ plans to set up a $30.00 million cryptocurrency investment fundOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, SEALSQ Corp, a Nasdaq-listed public key infrastructure development company, announced that it is setting up a cryptocurrency investment fund of approximately U</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947887286087127040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX into Bybit, worth $4.53 millionOn July 23, according to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX worth $4.53 million into Bybit. The whale deposited 2.53 million SPX worth $4.55 million into Bybit on the 20th, earning a profit of $4.46 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947886982985748480</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsA whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX into Bybit, worth $4.53 millionOn July 23, according to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX worth $4.53 million into Bybit. The whale deposited 2.53 million SPX worth $4.55 million into Bybit on the 20th, earni</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947886982985748480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 06:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>