<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:54:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale is suspected of selling 700 WBTC in the past 3 days, worth $82.40MAccording to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, &quot;the address that built a position of 1,074 WBTC at an average price of $10,708.00 four years ago&quot; has allegedly sold 700 WBTC (worth $82.40M) in the past three days, at an average price of $117,697.00. If this portion has been sold, it will yield a profit of $74.89M; currently, the selling progress of the position built four years ago is more than halfway through, and the wallet still holds 800 WBTC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947475198592962560</link>
      <description>1 minute ago吴说A certain whale is suspected of selling 700 WBTC in the past 3 days, worth $82.40MAccording to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, &quot;the address that built a position of 1,074 WBTC at an average price of $10,708.00 four years ago&quot; has allegedly sold 700 WBTC (worth $82.40M) in the past three days,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947475198592962560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale had previously purchased 9,187.52 ETH and liquidated it four hours ago, making a profit of $5.08 million in two weeks.On July 22, according to monitoring by on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the whale 0x8C0...0F364 spent $25.00 million to buy 9187.52 ETH on 07.10 and liquidated it four hours ago to take profits. The cost was $2,721.00 and the average selling price was $3,757.00 - a profit of $5.08 million in two weeks, with a return rate of 20.30%. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947475039037444096</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsA whale had previously purchased 9,187.52 ETH and liquidated it four hours ago, making a profit of $5.08 million in two weeks.On July 22, according to monitoring by on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the whale 0x8C0...0F364 spent $25.00 million to buy 9187.52 ETH on 07.10 and liquidate</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947475039037444096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito AI to Launch on Capital LaunchpadAI-powered crypto data platform Kaito AI tweeted that it will launch Capital Launchpad this week. The platform will allow users to participate in token private sales and new project investments, adopting an allocation mechanism based on social reputation, on-chain holdings, and other indicators, replacing the traditional first-come, first-served model. Project parties can independently set financing terms, including investment amount, valuation, and lock-up period conditions, and can review investor qualifications and allocate quotas in stages. The official statement said that all Capital Launchpad fees will be returned to the community. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947473545206714368</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoForesightNewsKaito AI to Launch on Capital LaunchpadAI-powered crypto data platform Kaito AI tweeted that it will launch Capital Launchpad this week. The platform will allow users to participate in token private sales and new project investments, adopting an allocation mechanism based o</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947473545206714368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ark Invest Trims Coinbase Shares Worth $90.58M, Also Sells Robinhood and Block HoldingsCathie Wood&apos;s investment firm, Ark Invest, sold a total of 218,986 Coinbase shares (COIN) on Monday, worth approximately $90.58M, involving its three ETF products: ARKK sold 174,746 shares, ARKW sold 27,663 shares, and ARKF sold 16,577 shares. This reduction occurred after Coinbase&apos;s stock price hit an all-time high last Friday (over $437), at which time the U.S. House of Representatives passed legislation on stablecoins and the digital asset regulatory framework. In addition, ARKW sold 109,824 Robinhood shares (worth $11.46M), and ARKF sold 90,061 Block shares (worth $7.00M). Ark Invest consistently follows a strategy of not exceeding 10% of a fund&apos;s portfolio in a single stock, and therefore regularly rebalances positions based on asset price changes. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947474469161553920</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailyArk Invest Trims Coinbase Shares Worth $90.58M, Also Sells Robinhood and Block HoldingsCathie Wood&apos;s investment firm, Ark Invest, sold a total of 218,986 Coinbase shares (COIN) on Monday, worth approximately $90.58M, involving its three ETF products: ARKK sold 174,746 shares, ARKW</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947474469161553920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 90% of Ethereum addresses are profitable, the highest since December 2024On July 22, according to Sentora monitoring, more than 90% of Ethereum addresses are currently in a profitable state, a new high since December 2024. Since there are relatively few addresses that have purchased Ethereum above the current price, the on-chain resistance appears to be weak. The first significant resistance level is slightly below the $4,000.00 mark, and currently about 2.39 million addresses hold ETH that is still in a loss. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947472266157903872</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsOver 90% of Ethereum addresses are profitable, the highest since December 2024On July 22, according to Sentora monitoring, more than 90% of Ethereum addresses are currently in a profitable state, a new high since December 2024. Since there are relatively few addresses that have p</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947472266157903872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coolpad Group Establishes RWA Business Unit to Explore Tokenization of Property AssetsCoolpad Group (02369.HK) has announced the official establishment of the &quot;Real World Asset Tokenization Division&quot; (RWA Division), which will coordinate the tokenization of real-world assets such as properties. Coolpad stated that the company had already started exploring Web3.0-related initiatives in 2023. The establishment of the RWA Division is aimed at more systematically adapting to the development trend of Web3.0 technology and actively responding to the innovative direction advocated by the Hong Kong SAR government&apos;s &quot;Digital Asset Development Policy Declaration 2.0.&quot; The department is personally led by Chen Jiajun, Chairman of the Board and CEO of the company. [Zhitong Finance]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947474477621465088</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyCoolpad Group Establishes RWA Business Unit to Explore Tokenization of Property AssetsCoolpad Group (02369.HK) has announced the official establishment of the &quot;Real World Asset Tokenization Division&quot; (RWA Division), which will coordinate the tokenization of real-world assets such</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947474477621465088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood CEO admits OpenAI tokenized stock is ‘controversial’ but is still doubling down on itOn July 22, according to Decrypt, Robinhood CEO Vlad Tenev admitted that the company&apos;s recent move to provide tokenized stocks is controversial, but he remains steadfast in his determination to expand the program. Tenev said: &quot;Being the first to truly tokenize these companies is a major milestone. Of course, every time you take the lead in doing something interesting, there will always be some controversy. I don&apos;t really care about the response to these controversies. The key is to put a product that is truly useful to customers in their hands, and I think (this launch) has achieved this to a large extent.&quot; Tenev also expressed his eagerness to advance Robinhood’s tokenized stock initiatives, which he recently said could soon expand to thousands of private companies. “Now it’s just a matter of scaling it to more companies and finding the path to get to phase two and phase three integrations in DeFi,” he added, referring to Robinhood’s long-term plans to integrate its tokenized stock product with decentralized finance markets. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947471733409992704</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsRobinhood CEO admits OpenAI tokenized stock is ‘controversial’ but is still doubling down on itOn July 22, according to Decrypt, Robinhood CEO Vlad Tenev admitted that the company&apos;s recent move to provide tokenized stocks is controversial, but he remains steadfast in his determin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947471733409992704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of STRC stock, with the funds raised to be used to purchase BitcoinStrategy plans to IPO 5 million shares of Series A Floating Rate Perpetual Preferred Stock (STRC stock), with the funds raised to be used for general corporate purposes, including purchasing Bitcoin and replenishing working capital. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947471750782799872</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoForesightNewsStrategy plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of STRC stock, with the funds raised to be used to purchase BitcoinStrategy plans to IPO 5 million shares of Series A Floating Rate Perpetual Preferred Stock (STRC stock), with the funds raised to be used for general corporate purpo</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947471750782799872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Research transferred 1.50M FORM to CEX, and has cashed out 6.00M in the last 3 months, with a profit of approximately $3.90MAccording to crypto analyst Ember@EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, Trend Research transferred 1.50M FORM (worth $5.12M) to Binance today. Since withdrawing 9.00M FORM from Binance at the end of April, the address has transferred 3.00M at the end of May (price $2.56), 1.50M at the end of June ($2.58), and now another 1.50M at a price of $3.41.
The three transfers total 6.00M FORM, with an average price of approximately $2.78, and an estimated profit of approximately $3.90M. Currently, Trend Research still holds 3.00M FORM, worth approximately $10.44M at the current price. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947471936112316416</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoOdailyTrend Research transferred 1.50M FORM to CEX, and has cashed out 6.00M in the last 3 months, with a profit of approximately $3.90MAccording to crypto analyst Ember@EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, Trend Research transferred 1.50M FORM (worth $5.12M) to Binance today. Since withdrawing 9.00M</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947471936112316416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Profusa Signs $100.00M Equity Credit Agreement, Launches Bitcoin Treasury StrategyNasdaq-listed digital health company Profusa (ticker: PFSA) has announced an equity credit agreement with Ascent Partners Fund LLC to raise up to $100 million through the issuance of common stock. The company stated that the net proceeds from the financing will be used entirely to purchase Bitcoin (and may also be used to repay debt), provided that the company&apos;s cash balance is higher than $5.00 million at the time of the equity sale. This agreement marks the official launch of Profusa&apos;s Bitcoin treasury strategy. (Business Insider) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469415465635840</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoOdailyPublicly Listed Profusa Signs $100.00M Equity Credit Agreement, Launches Bitcoin Treasury StrategyNasdaq-listed digital health company Profusa (ticker: PFSA) has announced an equity credit agreement with Ascent Partners Fund LLC to raise up to $100 million through the issuance of</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469415465635840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet GM News1. Bittensor ecosystem company xTAO to list in Canada, secures $22.80M investment from DCG, etc.; 2. BTCS discloses company&apos;s ETH and cash market value reaches $242.00M; 3. Coinbase: US users can now legally participate in crypto perpetual contract trading through the Coinbase platform; 4. Ethena Labs announces $360.00M PIPE transaction for StablecoinX, will establish ENA treasury company; 5. FTX applies for extension to respond, due to creditors opposing the freezing of $470.00M in overseas claims; 6. GameSquare approved to additionally inject $150.00M into its crypto treasury and increase holdings by 8,351 ETH; 7. Polymarket plans to return to the US market by acquiring a trading platform; 8. Robinhood CEO responds to OpenAI tokenized stock controversy, says it will continue to advance and expand business; 9. SOL treasury company Upexi announces purchase of 100,000 SOL for $17.70M, total holdings reach 1.82M; 10. Sonic Labs co-founder: all 1.866M S tokens allocated for airdrop have been destroyed; 11. Strategy increased its holdings by 6,220 BTC last week, at an average price of $118,940.00; 12. Strategy plans to issue 5 million shares of STRC stock, raising funds for Bitcoin acquisition; 13. Justin Sun will complete space flight on Blue Origin spacecraft, becoming the youngest Chinese astronaut in history; 14. Data: Over 90% of Ethereum addresses are in a profitable state, a new high since December 2024; 15. US SEC Chairman: ETH is not a security; 16. US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: If inflation data is low, interest rates should be lowered; 17. US-listed company DeFi Development Corp increases holdings by 141,383 SOL, total holdings near 1.00M; 18. Market news: Crypto company BitGo secretly files for IP0 in the US; 19. Trump Media &amp; Technology Group (DJT.O) announces its total Bitcoin reserve purchases have reached $2.00B; 20. The White House&apos;s first crypto policy report is expected to be released to the public before the end of this month; 21. Binance: From July 22, limit order trading of BSC chain Alpha tokens can get 4 times the trading volume Alpha points; 22. Listed company NextGen Digital launches crypto reserve strategy, has purchased $1.00M worth of BTC; 23. Bit Origin spends approximately $10.00M to purchase 40.54M DOGE, establishing a corporate Dogecoin treasury. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469423904575488</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoOdailyPlanet GM News1. Bittensor ecosystem company xTAO to list in Canada, secures $22.80M investment from DCG, etc.; 2. BTCS discloses company&apos;s ETH and cash market value reaches $242.00M; 3. Coinbase: US users can now legally participate in crypto perpetual contract trading through t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469423904575488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dayu Water Saving: The company currently has no business revenue in the RWA field.On July 22, Dayu Water Saving said on the interactive platform that the company is actively studying and promoting the RWA path of high-end agricultural products and water conservancy assets, and is studying and promoting business cooperation with relevant intermediaries. The company currently has no business income in the RWA field. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947468908982456320</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoTechFlowDayu Water Saving: The company currently has no business revenue in the RWA field.On July 22, Dayu Water Saving said on the interactive platform that the company is actively studying and promoting the RWA path of high-end agricultural products and water conservancy assets, and</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947468908982456320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-powered governance protocol Quack AI completes $3.60 million financing round, with participation from Animoca Brands and othersAI-powered governance protocol Quack AI completes $3.60M funding round with participation from Animoca Brands, 071labs, Skyland Ventures, Kenetic, Scaling Labs, Carv, and Merlin Chain. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469189237460992</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoForesightNewsAI-powered governance protocol Quack AI completes $3.60 million financing round, with participation from Animoca Brands and othersAI-powered governance protocol Quack AI completes $3.60M funding round with participation from Animoca Brands, 071labs, Skyland Ventures, Kenet</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469189237460992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New wallet withdraws 1.89M SPX from CEX, worth $3.67MAccording to OnchainLens monitoring, a newly created wallet withdrew 1.89M SPX from Bybit today, with a total value of approximately $3.67M based on the current price. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469432360292352</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailyNew wallet withdraws 1.89M SPX from CEX, worth $3.67MAccording to OnchainLens monitoring, a newly created wallet withdrew 1.89M SPX from Bybit today, with a total value of approximately $3.67M based on the current price. [Odaily]$SPXShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947469432360292352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet withdrew 1.89 million SPX from Bybit 11 hours ago, worth $3.67 millionOn July 22, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, 11 hours ago, a newly created wallet withdrew 1.89 million SPX (worth US$3.67 million) from Bybit. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947467969068290048</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoPANewsA new wallet withdrew 1.89 million SPX from Bybit 11 hours ago, worth $3.67 millionOn July 22, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, 11 hours ago, a newly created wallet withdrew 1.89 million SPX (worth US$3.67 million) from Bybit. [PANews]$SPXShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947467969068290048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcon Makes Initial Purchase of 280.14 Bitcoin and Completes Over $500.00M Private Placement to Purchase BitcoinUS-listed electric vehicle company Volcon has purchased 280.14 Bitcoin for the first time and has completed a private placement of over $500.00M. It plans to use more than 95% of the total proceeds from the private placement to purchase Bitcoin. The private placement included participation from institutions such as FalconX, Pantera, Borderless, and Relayer Capital. In the coming weeks, Volcon plans to change its company name to Empery Digital, Inc., and its stock ticker to EMPD. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947467252693749760</link>
      <description>32 minutes ago吴说Volcon Makes Initial Purchase of 280.14 Bitcoin and Completes Over $500.00M Private Placement to Purchase BitcoinUS-listed electric vehicle company Volcon has purchased 280.14 Bitcoin for the first time and has completed a private placement of over $500.00M. It plans to use more than</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947467252693749760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcon Makes Initial Purchase of 280.14 Bitcoin and Completes Over $500.00M Private Placement to Purchase BitcoinUS-listed electric vehicle company Volcon has purchased 280.14 Bitcoin for the first time and has completed a private placement of over $500 million. It plans to use more than 95% of the total proceeds from the private placement to purchase Bitcoin. Institutions including FalconX, Pantera, Borderless, and Relayer Capital participated in this private placement. In the coming weeks, Volcon plans to change its name to Empery Digital, Inc., and its stock ticker to EMPD. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947466705169305600</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoForesightNewsVolcon Makes Initial Purchase of 280.14 Bitcoin and Completes Over $500.00M Private Placement to Purchase BitcoinUS-listed electric vehicle company Volcon has purchased 280.14 Bitcoin for the first time and has completed a private placement of over $500 million. It plans t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947466705169305600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 1.77% in the past 1H, down 0.96% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947466097434255360</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 1.77% in the past 1H, down 0.96% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947466097434255360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questflow Announces $6.50M Seed RoundAI agent economic orchestration platform Questflow announced the completion of a $6.50M seed round led by @CyberFund, with participation from well-known investment institutions such as Delphi Labs, Systemic Ventures, Animoca Brands, and HashKey Capital. It also received funding from Aptos, Coinbase Developer Platform, and Virtuals Protocol. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947465496425418752</link>
      <description>39 minutes ago吴说Questflow Announces $6.50M Seed RoundAI agent economic orchestration platform Questflow announced the completion of a $6.50M seed round led by @CyberFund, with participation from well-known investment institutions such as Delphi Labs, Systemic Ventures, Animoca Brands, and HashKey Ca</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947465496425418752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bittensor ecosystem company xTAO to list in Canada, secures $22.80 million in fundingAccording to The Block, Bittensor ecosystem company xTAO will be listed on the TSXV in Canada on July 23, with the stock code XTAO.U. It has also completed a $22.80M financing round with participation from DCG, Animoca Brands, Arca, Borderless Capital, and FalconX. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947464445295087616</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsBittensor ecosystem company xTAO to list in Canada, secures $22.80 million in fundingAccording to The Block, Bittensor ecosystem company xTAO will be listed on the TSXV in Canada on July 23, with the stock code XTAO.U. It has also completed a $22.80M financing round with p</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 01:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947464445295087616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 01:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>