<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:49:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Giants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value foundation of the ecosystem, Giants Protocol will advance its originally scheduled phased lock-up plan, locking 90% of the circulating tokens through smart contracts to ensure market stability and token value support. Giants Protocol stated that several international listed luxury goods groups have recently taken the initiative to contact the project team, intending to obtain priority access to its RWA asset on-chain services by holding G tokens. The official statement said: &quot;As traditional luxury assets accelerate on-chain, G is gradually becoming a key bridge connecting Web2 luxury assets and the Web3 protocol layer.&quot; [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailyGiants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value foundat</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches Spot Trading Event, Allocates 50,000 BGB AirdropBitget has launched the Trading Club Championship, Phase 1, with trading scopes including spot currency pairs, spot flash swaps, spot margin, and small-amount swaps. During the event, users who accumulate a daily purchase amount that reaches the specified level can obtain corresponding points. There is no limit to the points that can be earned, and eligible users will have the opportunity to unlock an airdrop reward of 24,500 BGB. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947969915188744192</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Launches Spot Trading Event, Allocates 50,000 BGB AirdropBitget has launched the Trading Club Championship, Phase 1, with trading scopes including spot currency pairs, spot flash swaps, spot margin, and small-amount swaps. During the event, users who accumulate a dai</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947969915188744192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been partially liquidated, and there is still a floating loss of $266,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyJames Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been p</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Capital to support its Bitcoin funding strategy. The ATM-style financing tool allows Hilbert Group to flexibly withdraw funds in the next 36 months to purchase more Bitcoin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsHilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Cap</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadian dollars, with funds coming from the company&apos;s existing cash reserves. As of July 22, 2025, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings increased to 28.89, equivalent to 2,889,000,000.00 satoshis. Based on the company&apos;s 206 million outstanding shares, the number of bitcoins held per share increased to 14.01 satoshis, an increase of more than 8.49 times from 1.65 satoshis / share on June 26, an increase of 750.00%. The company&apos;s cumulative investment in bitcoins reached 4.5 million Canadian dollars, with an average holding cost of 155,800.00 Canadian dollars per coin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoPANewsCanadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadia</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart money betting on FET? Price presses against key resistance after stealth accumulationArtificial Intelligence Alliance’s FET token is showing signs of strength as it tests a critical resistance zone after a period of accumulation, setting sights on the $1 target. Artificial Intelligence Alliance (FET) token has spent several weeks in a tight range after bottoming out at $0.56 on June 22, forming what appears to be an accumulation base on the daily chart. Recent price action has turned bullish, with FET now coiling just below a key horizontal resistance zone between $0.80 and $0.90 — a level that has rejected multiple breakout attempts in the past. A confirmed break above this area could pave the way toward the psychological $1.00 milestone, which also marked the peak of the previous rally on May 23. Technical indicators support a potential breakout. Despite a recent pullback from the local high of $0.89 reached two days ago, the price remains firmly above the 20-day EMA ($0.79), which appears to have acted as dynamic support during the accumulation phase. Additionally, the momentum indicator MACD has maintained a bullish crossover since June 2025, with the histogram consistently printing green bars. For context, the FET token is the unified native asset of the ASI Alliance, which includes SingularityNET, Fetch.ai, Ocean Protocol, and most recent addition CUDOS. FET’s accumulation may signal that smart money is eyeing the token as a strategic entry point ahead of key product rollouts. Notably, Singularity Finance, the financial arm of the ASI Alliance, recently released its H2 2025 roadmap outlining several key product launches, including AI-powered portfolio tools, diversified yield vaults, and autonomous trading agents that execute trades automatically without requiring users to write code.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965739838803968</link>
      <description>25 minutes agocrypto.newsSmart money betting on FET? Price presses against key resistance after stealth accumulationArtificial Intelligence Alliance’s FET token is showing signs of strength as it tests a critical resistance zone after a period of accumulation, setting sights on the $1 target. Artifi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965739838803968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bedrock Week 4 BR Trading Challenge is now live with a $50,000.00 prize poolAccording to official sources, the fourth week of the Bedrock BR trading challenge is now live, with a prize pool of $50,000. This challenge simplifies the process, allowing users to trade on Pancake&apos;s BR/USDT pool. The event lasts for 7 consecutive days, earning $16,000.00 per day, totaling $160,000.00, but is only available to the first 5000 claimants. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965174387904512</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyBedrock Week 4 BR Trading Challenge is now live with a $50,000.00 prize poolAccording to official sources, the fourth week of the Bedrock BR trading challenge is now live, with a prize pool of $50,000. This challenge simplifies the process, allowing users to trade on Pancake&apos;s BR</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965174387904512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget partners with Indian Key Opinion Leader Pushpendra Singh to expand the Southeast Asian blockchain and AI ecosystem.Bitget recently joined forces with Indian crypto influencer Pushpendra Singh to support the Blockchain and AI Summit in Malaysia. The summit, co-sponsored by Bitget and the Confederation of Indian Industries Malaysia (CIIM), brought together builders, investors, and industry representatives from India, South Asia, the Middle East, Singapore, and China to discuss the development of blockchain and artificial intelligence. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947963990084227072</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget partners with Indian Key Opinion Leader Pushpendra Singh to expand the Southeast Asian blockchain and AI ecosystem.Bitget recently joined forces with Indian crypto influencer Pushpendra Singh to support the Blockchain and AI Summit in Malaysia. The summit, co-sponso</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947963990084227072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yi Feng Investment&apos;s proposal to acquire the Aavegotchi Treasury is opposed by the communityOn July 22, Aavegotchi community members proposed to purchase the DAO treasury (approximately 16.00M GHST) at a 60% discount to the 14-day average price, worth approximately $3.20M. The proposer, Rongming Investment, is a subsidiary of the Chinese equity financing institution Yifeng Investment. The transaction outlined in the proposal would grant Rongming Investment the right to use and market Aavegotchi IP, dissolve the DAO, and distribute the proceeds to active community members. Due to the rejection of over 90% of the community members, and with only over 2.00M GHST tokens participating, reaching only 28% of the required quorum, the acquisition offer will be rejected if the current trend remains unchanged. Voting is scheduled to end on July 25. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962732178903040</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoForesightNewsYi Feng Investment&apos;s proposal to acquire the Aavegotchi Treasury is opposed by the communityOn July 22, Aavegotchi community members proposed to purchase the DAO treasury (approximately 16.00M GHST) at a 60% discount to the 14-day average price, worth approximately $3.20M.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962732178903040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAgentAI&apos;s AlphaX attracted over 86K users and saw a 232% increase in trading volume within two weeks of the Sui chain prediction competition.The &quot;Predict2Win: SUI Season&quot; prediction signal interaction competition launched by AlphaX, a community-incubated product of AI Infra project DeAgentAI, has shown remarkable performance in the two weeks since its launch. It has attracted over 86,000 users, generated 732,000 on-chain transactions, and achieved a transaction volume growth of 232.00%. It ranks 16th in the Suiscan project leaderboard, becoming one of the leading projects in the Sui ecosystem&apos;s AI Infra track. AlphaX is an AI-driven price prediction platform launched by DeAgentAI, focusing on providing users with high-precision cryptocurrency price signal prediction services. The platform analyzes market data through AI algorithms to provide prediction signals for mainstream tokens such as BTC, ETH, and SUI, with an accuracy of up to 72.30%. Users can earn points rewards, token airdrops, and other incentives by participating in predictions and completing on-chain interactions. DeAgentAI is an AI Agent network infrastructure project built on multi-chain ecosystems such as Sui, BSC, and BTC, with the core vision of &quot;Make AI Smarter&quot;. The project is committed to empowering on-chain transactions through AI prediction and feedback mechanisms, and has supported over 190.00M on-chain interactions. This Sui chain prediction competition will last until August 31, with a total prize pool of 100,000.00 USDT. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962672766586880</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoOdailyDeAgentAI&apos;s AlphaX attracted over 86K users and saw a 232% increase in trading volume within two weeks of the Sui chain prediction competition.The &quot;Predict2Win: SUI Season&quot; prediction signal interaction competition launched by AlphaX, a community-incubated product of AI Infra pro</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947962672766586880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CertiK Stablecoin Report 2025: What are the top 5 most secure tokens in the stablecoin race?As stablecoin adoption grows more mainstream, so do the security risks associated with them. Which tokens are leading the race in terms of security? The first half of 2025 saw a surge in stablecoin use cases, with a monthly settlement volume rising by 43% to $1.39 trillion. According to the security firm, this rapidly increasing growth in adoption hides the widening gaps in security posture, compliance, and operational risk that still need to be addressed by the community. As a result, CertiK has managed to rank the top fiat-pegged tokens from a security and risk standpoint. The six-item Skynet rating framework assesses each token based on factors including operational resilience, governance strength, fundamental health, code security, market dynamic and community trust. According to the Skynet framework, Tether’s USDT ( USDT ) ranks at number one with an overall score of 94.72. The security firm highlighted USDT’s decision to increase its circulation from $138.00 billion to $154.00 billion in the first half of 2025. In second place is Circle’s USDC ( USDC ) with 93.37. Having secured a MiCA license and completed an IPO, Circle’s token supply increased from $41.00 billion to $61.00 billion. Although it is still slightly behind Tether, CertiK has dubbed it the “fastest growing” major stablecoin. Ranking in third place is the PayPal-Paxos jointly issued PYUSD ( PYUSD ) with a score of 91.47. The token’s market cap has doubled in the first half of 2025. Recent developments for the token include expansions into Solana ( SOL ) and Arbitrum ( ARB ) as well as a rewards program. In fourth place is USDS by Sky with 90.09. The rebranding of DAI into Sky has helped to expand the token into multiple chains. Since its launch on Solana, it has grown to become the fifth largest stablecoin. Ripple’s RLUSD ( RLUSD ) stands at number five with a Skynet framework score of 89.89. Although it still ranks below USDT and USDC in terms of supply and security mechanisms in place, CertiK noted that the token has experienced zero security incidents since its launch. Other notable tokens mentioned in the top 10 include First Digital USD ( FDUSD ), USDG by Paxos, Ethena’s USDe ( USDE ) and USDtb, as well as World Liberty Financial’s own USD1. According to blockchain security firm CertiK, as many as 344 crypto security incidents occurred in the past year. These incidents led to the theft of $2.47 billion worth of crypto assets industry-wide. Though these incidents are not always linked to stablecoins directly, they often bear the brunt of exploits, more so than regular tokens. For instance, First Digital USD saw its price plummet to $0.76 amid rumors about whether or not its reserves were secure. It was only able to recover its $1.00 value after the issuer disclosed audited holdings to prove that its reserves were safe. This case shows just how easily the cookie crumbles when it comes to stablecoins. Due to the nature of fiat-pegged tokens, its reserves are considered sacred in a way that differs to other tokens. One wrong move could result in the 1:1 ratio backed by real currencies to dip and lead to the token’s downfall. CertiK’s report showed that exploits in the crypto space, such as hacks, death spirals, and price depegs, were mostly caused by operational failures compared to technical flaws in the system. According to the study, vulnerabilities in systems where stablecoins are the primary asset made up a large portion of the losses. [CertiK]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947958189059805184</link>
      <description>55 minutes agocrypto.newsCertiK Stablecoin Report 2025: What are the top 5 most secure tokens in the stablecoin race?As stablecoin adoption grows more mainstream, so do the security risks associated with them. Which tokens are leading the race in terms of security? The first half of 2025 saw a surge</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947958189059805184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, continuing to set new all-time highsAccording to @sankin_eth&apos;s data dashboard, Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, reaching $5.074B USDC, continuously setting new historical highs. Since the beginning of this year, Hyperliquid AUM has grown by approximately $3.00B USDC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947957019994034176</link>
      <description>59 minutes ago吴说Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, continuing to set new all-time highsAccording to @sankin_eth&apos;s data dashboard, Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, reaching $5.074B USDC, continuously setting new historical highs. Since the beginning of this year, Hyperliquid AUM has grown by ap</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947957019994034176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fartcoin derivatives open interest ranks among the top ten, speculative boom emergesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Fartcoin (FARTCOIN), a meme coin of the Solana ecosystem, has now become one of the top ten tokens in terms of open interest in cryptocurrency derivatives. Data shows that the nominal open interest of Fartcoin-related futures has exceeded $1.00 billion, surpassing mainstream currencies such as Litecoin, LINK, and AVAX. It is worth noting that Fartcoin&apos;s open interest has reached 65.00% of its market value, while its market value ranks 83rd in the world. This abnormally high open interest is considered a signal of overheated market speculation. Similar phenomena are also reflected in other small-cap currencies, which may lead to large-scale investor liquidation risks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947953345834061824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFartcoin derivatives open interest ranks among the top ten, speculative boom emergesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Fartcoin (FARTCOIN), a meme coin of the Solana ecosystem, has now become one of the top ten tokens in terms of open interest in cryptocurrency derivatives. Data show</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947953345834061824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted on the X platform, saying, &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world economy (except for food and energy production) is essentially a status game, so how could the internet society be any different?&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955124432867328</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyArthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted on the X platform, saying, &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world economy (e</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955124432867328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southeast Asian stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Philippine OTC institution Moneybees to optimize the remittance experience for overseas Filipino workers.Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Moneybees, the largest over-the-counter (OTC) institution in the Philippines. This collaboration optimizes the remittance experience for Overseas Filipino Workers (OFW) by combining stablecoin technology with offline exchange networks. Users who receive stablecoin remittances can convert APACX-incubated Philippine Peso stablecoin PHT into cash at Moneybees&apos; more than 1,000 offline locations in the Philippines. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952904685555712</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsSoutheast Asian stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Philippine OTC institution Moneybees to optimize the remittance experience for overseas Filipino workers.Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX has reached a strategic partn</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952904685555712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Companies’ Bitcoin Bet: Can They Weather the Bear Market Storm?Public companies worldwide have been going all-in on Bitcoin (BTC) this year. Whether it’s through equity or debt issuance, firms have accelerated their push to acquire BTC and add it to their balance sheets. While Bitcoin continues to appreciate in value, the firms have also benefited through their stock surge and paper gains. But the looming question is: What will happen if a bear market returns? Will institutional confidence hold steady, or will it waver in the face of  volatility ? BeInCrypto spoke to industry experts to examine the possibilities in a potential bear market and whether these firms will contribute to more stability or downfall. Is Institutional Interest in Bitcoin a Double-Edged Sword? Over the past few months,  BeInCrypto has extensively  reported on corporate Bitcoin acquisitions. The trend pioneered by Michael Saylor, co-founder of (Micro) Strategy, has inspired many others to follow suit. Dean Chen, an analyst at Bitunix, highlighted that the growing influx of institutional capital has solidified Bitcoin’s  position as ‘digital gold.’ Furthermore, John Glover, Ledn’s Chief Information Officer (CIO), attributed Bitcoin’s reputation for stability in recent years to the increasing involvement of institutions. Glover said that with Bitcoin’s volatility decreasing over time, it is increasingly behaving like a traditional asset.  Nonetheless, as with all traditional assets, the market experiences cycles, with bull markets typically followed by bear markets. He anticipates that any future bear market for Bitcoin will likely be less severe compared to past cycles. Still, corrections are inevitable. Notably, the executive  added that while institutes bring capital,  they also bring constraints. Chen pointed out that institutional investors tend to exit faster than retail investors. Thus, if the market moves in the opposite direction, high-frequency trading funds and quant strategies are likely to sell off their positions. However, Marcin Kazmierczak, the COO and Co-Founder of Redstone, offered an alternative viewpoint. He noted that while institutional investors might encounter difficulties during bear markets, their involvement has brought  advanced risk management practices  to the cryptocurrency space.  The Success of Corporate Financing Models for Bitcoin Acquisition Institutional investors use a mix of financing  methods to buy Bitcoin , with debt being the most common one. In a post on X, Redbox Global revealed that Bitcoin-focused companies are facing a significant $12.8 billion debt maturity wall by 2028. These concerns are not new.  Previously, Sygnum Bank  and  other market analysts  have also raised alarms about the sustainability of the strategies.  Chen highlighted that Strategy raised $42.87 billion since 2020 through zero-coupon convertible notes and equity issuances to buy over 600,000 BTC at an average cost of $71,268.00. This strategy boosts Bitcoin accumulation in bull markets. Nevertheless, it strains finances in bear markets with interest payments and falling stock prices.  Moreover,  Strategy’s debt makes up about 24.3%  of its capital structure. He added that its convertible bonds may trigger mandatory conversion or redemption if Bitcoin drops below a certain threshold. Other companies like Marathon Digital issue equity before bonds, lowering the leverage. Despite this, they have higher capital costs and limited resilience. Still, Glover emphasized that companies with strong capital structures—like staggered maturities and low-interest debt—will fare better. He stated that Strategy’s model can handle significant losses. However, new firms face a higher risk of forced sales in a downturn. Anthony Georgiades, Founder and General Partner at Innovating Capital, also called the strategies a ‘high-stakes play.’ Meanwhile, Kazmierczak noted that companies using convertible debt strategies have demonstrated innovative ways to balance growth with risk management. According to him, their effectiveness ultimately depends on the strength of their core business and their ability to service debt through operational cash flows, rather than relying purely on Bitcoin appreciation.  He believes  smart treasury strategies involve appropriately sizing positions  relative to overall balance sheets. Kazmierczak detailed that many public companies holding Bitcoin have demonstrated sound management by treating BTC allocations as a part of their overall reserves. What Will Happen to Bitcoin’s Price if Institutions Start Selling? While the experts showed cautious optimism regarding the financing strategies, centralization is more concerning. As of the latest  data  from Bitcoin Treasuries, the top three publicly listed Bitcoin treasury companies collectively hold about 695,000 BTC, accounting for  3.31% of the total  BTC supply. So, what happens  when or more decide to sell?  He elaborated that hedging options are available in the space, and the liquidity of markets like  futures  and options continues to grow. Therefore, Glover hopes that BTC treasury companies are strategic in managing their risk to withstand a bear market. Nonetheless, Bitcoin isn’t the only asset that will be impacted. The decline of the largest cryptocurrency could also lead to a broader market downfall.  The CIO of Ledn stressed that  ‘Bitcoin is still the  anchor  for the entire market.’ He noted that if large holders begin offloading, it sends a message that even the ‘safe’ end of crypto isn’t secure. Factors That Could Influence Companies’ Ability to Hold Bitcoin Bitcoin and the crypto sector aren’t immune to macroeconomic pressures. Whether it’s  President Trump’s tariffs  or  the Israel-Iran conflict , the market has reacted quickly by going into a free fall. The experts also outlined factors that are most likely to influence BTC treasury companies’ ability to hold Bitcoin through a bear market. Furthermore, Bitunix’s Chen also revealed that regulatory factors could play an important role. According to him, the  Clarity Act could reduce compliance costs  for institutions, thereby supporting long-term Bitcoin holdings by treasury firms. Besides this, shareholder pressure is another key factor to consider. Chen explained that if Bitcoin crashes, coordinated shareholder actions—such as calling a special meeting—could force the board to adopt a more conservative strategy and liquidate assets to reduce risk. Despite this, Glover stresses that a potential bear market wouldn’t erase Bitcoin. However, it will serve as a crucial test for  institutional conviction in the asset . [BeInCrypto]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955933849653248</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoPublic Companies’ Bitcoin Bet: Can They Weather the Bear Market Storm?Public companies worldwide have been going all-in on Bitcoin (BTC) this year. Whether it’s through equity or debt issuance, firms have accelerated their push to acquire BTC and add it to their balance sheets. W</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955933849653248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSouth Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that Galaxy Digital is well-positioned to capture upside opportunities in a favorable cryptocurrency regulatory environment. The investment bank noted that the passage of the U.S. GENIUS Act provides a &quot;favorable market structure&quot; for Galaxy&apos;s business. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that Gal</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits.Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino posted that the Tether Group has invested in over 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. Relevant investment information has been published on the official Tether website. Paolo Ardoino stated that the source of funds is independent of USDT and other stablecoin reserves (reaching $13.70B in 2024) and falls within the business scope of Tether Investments investment division. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952604511801344</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits.Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino posted that the Tether Group has invested in over 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. Relevant investment</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952604511801344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 10:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>