<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:51:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>MicroStrategy Increases Senior Note Offering to $2.00 Billion, Plans to Use STRC Proceeds to Increase Bitcoin HoldingsMicroStrategy has increased its latest round of preferred stock issuance from $500 million to $2.00 billion, intending to price its Series A perpetual preferred stock &quot;Stretch&quot; at $90 per share. This round of issuance is led by Morgan Stanley, Barclays, Moelis &amp; Co., and TD Securities, with plans to issue 5.00 million shares. The funds raised will be used for purposes including the purchase of Bitcoin. To date, MicroStrategy holds a total of 607,770 Bitcoin, with a market value of approximately $72.40 billion. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948422535078547456</link>
      <description>12 minutes ago吴说MicroStrategy Increases Senior Note Offering to $2.00 Billion, Plans to Use STRC Proceeds to Increase Bitcoin HoldingsMicroStrategy has increased its latest round of preferred stock issuance from $500 million to $2.00 billion, intending to price its Series A perpetual preferred stock</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948422535078547456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase: Crypto market inflows have reached $60.00B so far this year, with investors&apos; interest in altcoins on the riseJPMorgan Chase analysts estimate that $600.00B in capital has flowed into digital assets since the beginning of the year, mainly driven by inflows into crypto funds, active trading in CME futures, and venture capital fundraising activities. Analysts point out that inflows have grown by nearly 50.00% since the end of May and are on track to easily surpass last year&apos;s historical record. Analysts say that the increasingly friendly regulatory environment in the United States is one of the key drivers. Investor interest in altcoins is also on the rise. Among them, Ethereum is the biggest beneficiary due to its dominance in decentralized finance (DeFi) and smart contracts, and its increasing inclusion in corporate treasury allocations along with Bitcoin. More and more asset management companies intend to launch crypto ETFs based on altcoins and introduce staking mechanisms. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948423189821984768</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyJPMorgan Chase: Crypto market inflows have reached $60.00B so far this year, with investors&apos; interest in altcoins on the riseJPMorgan Chase analysts estimate that $600.00B in capital has flowed into digital assets since the beginning of the year, mainly driven by inflows into cry</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948423189821984768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 1.96M FARTCOIN from Kraken and exchanged it for $2.72M USDCAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale address withdrew approximately 1.96M FARTCOIN from the Kraken exchange and exchanged them for $2.72M USDC at a price of approximately $1.39 per coin. The relevant address is: HL6s4Nr9hKG2Nz7RjpaJbhnRPgKSCrPRppTJyQm1C5zU. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948420702540992512</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoOdailyA whale withdrew 1.96M FARTCOIN from Kraken and exchanged it for $2.72M USDCAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale address withdrew approximately 1.96M FARTCOIN from the Kraken exchange and exchanged them for $2.72M USDC at a price of approximately $1.39 per coin. The rele</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948420702540992512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOO X Hacked, Loses Over $12.00M, Platform Temporarily Suspends WithdrawalsCyvers Alerts posted on the X platform that it detected multiple suspicious transactions involving the trading platform WOO X, covering the BTC, ETH, BNB, and ARB networks, with estimated losses exceeding $12.00M. On the Ethereum network, a suspicious address received $1.00M worth of USDT and additional ETH from WOO&apos;s hot wallet. The $1.00M USDT was subsequently exchanged for ETH, after which approximately $7.30M was transferred to a new address. The WOO team has confirmed the incident and stated, &quot;We are investigating a restricted incident that occurred earlier today on the WOO X platform.&quot; Currently, user funds and transactions are not affected, but withdrawals have been temporarily suspended during the investigation. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948418166417330176</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoOdailyWOO X Hacked, Loses Over $12.00M, Platform Temporarily Suspends WithdrawalsCyvers Alerts posted on the X platform that it detected multiple suspicious transactions involving the trading platform WOO X, covering the BTC, ETH, BNB, and ARB networks, with estimated losses exceeding</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948418166417330176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celestia buys back over 43 million TIA held by Polychain, plans to transfer them to new investors and unlock them in batchesThe Celestia Foundation has announced an agreement with Polychain Capital to purchase 43,451,616.09 TIA from the latter for $62.50M. To complete this transaction, Polychain will unstake all of its staked TIA. The Foundation will allocate these TIA to new investors and use a staggered unlocking method, with the unlocking period starting on August 16 and ending on November 14. According to previous disclosures, Polychain invested approximately $20.00M in the Celestia project. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948414232592191488</link>
      <description>45 minutes ago吴说Celestia buys back over 43 million TIA held by Polychain, plans to transfer them to new investors and unlock them in batchesThe Celestia Foundation has announced an agreement with Polychain Capital to purchase 43,451,616.09 TIA from the latter for $62.50M. To complete this transactio</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948414232592191488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today&apos;s on-chain fund flow: Arbitrum net inflow of $25.00M, Base net outflow of $44.90MOn July 24, according to Artemis data, Arbitrum saw a net inflow of $25.00M today, and Ethereum saw a net inflow of $14.30M; Base saw a net outflow of $44.90M, and Starknet saw a net outflow of $5.90M. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413262491619328</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoTechFlowToday&apos;s on-chain fund flow: Arbitrum net inflow of $25.00M, Base net outflow of $44.90MOn July 24, according to Artemis data, Arbitrum saw a net inflow of $25.00M today, and Ethereum saw a net inflow of $14.30M; Base saw a net outflow of $44.90M, and Starknet saw a net outflow</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413262491619328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. House of Representatives promotes the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, emphasizing its non-partisan natureOn July 24, according to Eleanor Terrett, at a press conference before the House of Representatives&apos; August recess, House Majority Whip Tom Emmer said he would work hard to win more Senate Democrats&apos; support for his Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act. The bill aims to make it clear that blockchain developers and infrastructure providers (such as miners, validators, and node operators) are not considered money transmitters as long as they do not host funds. Emmer called the bill a &quot;non-partisan issue,&quot; emphasizing that there are clear rules to protect Americans and innovators, and said he welcomes the Senate&apos;s adjustments and improvements to the bill during the review process. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948411763346706432</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoPANewsU.S. House of Representatives promotes the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, emphasizing its non-partisan natureOn July 24, according to Eleanor Terrett, at a press conference before the House of Representatives&apos; August recess, House Majority Whip Tom Emmer said he would work</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948411763346706432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two new wallets accumulate $388.00M worth of ETHAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, two newly created wallets have accumulated ETH worth $388.00M, of which: wallet 0x3dF received 87,275 ETH worth $326.00M from Galaxy OTC; wallet 0x286 received 16,472 ETH worth $61.43M from FalconX. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413148486242304</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoOdailyTwo new wallets accumulate $388.00M worth of ETHAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, two newly created wallets have accumulated ETH worth $388.00M, of which: wallet 0x3dF received 87,275 ETH worth $326.00M from Galaxy OTC; wallet 0x286 received 16,472 ETH worth $61.43M from Falc</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413148486242304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semler Scientific Purchases 175 BTC and Launches Public Bitcoin DashboardSemler Scientific announced it has added 175 Bitcoin to its treasury for $20.8 million, according to a new SEC filing. The purchase was made between July 17 and July 23 at an average price of $119,230 per BTC. The transaction was funded through proceeds from the company’s at-the-market (ATM) stock offering. Semler Scientific has acquired 175 BTC for $21 million and has achieved BTC Yield of 31.3% YTD. Now holding 5,021 BTC. $SMLR With this latest acquisition, Semler now holds 5,021 BTC, valued at approximately $594.8 million based on prices on July 23. The company has spent $475.8 million on Bitcoin so far, with an average purchase price of $94,772 per BTC, resulting in an unrealized gain of nearly $119 million. “We are witnessing the global monetization of Bitcoin as a superior form of money,” said the Chairman of Semler Scientific Eric Semler. “The trend to adopt Bitcoin as part of corporate treasury is clearly accelerating. Semler Scientific, as the 2nd U.S. public company to adopt the Bitcoin Standard, has been at the forefront of this movement.” Semler also disclosed a year-to-date BTC Yield of 31.3 percent. This key performance indicator tracks the value creation of Bitcoin holdings relative to shareholder dilution, helping investors evaluate the impact of funding BTC purchases through stock issuance. As part of its transparency efforts, Semler has launched a new Bitcoin dashboard on its website. The dashboard will regularly update market data on its stock and Bitcoin, BTC Yield, BTC Gain metrics, Bitcoin purchases, and overall holdings. The company said the site will serve as a key disclosure tool under Regulation FD and may contain material information. Semler’s ATM program, initiated in April 2025 with firms like Barclays, Cantor Fitzgerald, and others, allows the company to sell up to $500 million of its stock. As of July 23, Semler has raised $194.3 million through the sale of nearly 4.93 million shares, including trades set to settle on July 24.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948425079074918400</link>
      <description>56 minutes agobitcoinmagazineSemler Scientific Purchases 175 BTC and Launches Public Bitcoin DashboardSemler Scientific announced it has added 175 Bitcoin to its treasury for $20.8 million, according to a new SEC filing. The purchase was made between July 17 and July 23 at an average price of $119,2</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948425079074918400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TON Foundation and Kingsway Capital plan to raise $400 million for the Toncoin treasury from an unnamed crypto financial firmThe TON Foundation and Kingsway Capital are planning to raise $400.00M for a crypto financial firm with TONCOIN as its treasury. The unnamed financial firm will take on a structure known as a &quot;private investment in public equity.&quot; Under the structure, an existing publicly traded company sells its shares to a group of investors, with Kingsway being one of the company&apos;s investors. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948411083575857152</link>
      <description>58 minutes ago吴说TON Foundation and Kingsway Capital plan to raise $400 million for the Toncoin treasury from an unnamed crypto financial firmThe TON Foundation and Kingsway Capital are planning to raise $400.00M for a crypto financial firm with TONCOIN as its treasury. The unnamed financial firm wil</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948411083575857152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injective Launches On-Chain Digital Asset Library, Ethereum Treasury Firm SBET Now Live On-ChainInjective Introduces On-Chain Digital Asset Treasury (DAT), SBET is Ethereum&apos;s Largest DAT and is Now Live on the Injective Chain. The SBET DAT is built using Injective&apos;s iAssets framework, which features native programmability, governance hooks, integrated liquidity, and cross-protocol composability. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948410639977877504</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsInjective Launches On-Chain Digital Asset Library, Ethereum Treasury Firm SBET Now Live On-ChainInjective Introduces On-Chain Digital Asset Treasury (DAT), SBET is Ethereum&apos;s Largest DAT and is Now Live on the Injective Chain. The SBET DAT is built using Injective&apos;s iAssets fr</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948410639977877504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONK: Platform fees drive the destruction of 500 billion BONK, worth approximately $18.62 millionOn July 24, BONK’s official Twitter account stated that driven by the transaction fees of the Letsbonk.Fun platform, 500 billion BONK (approximately US$18.62 million) had just been destroyed. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948410320774565888</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBONK: Platform fees drive the destruction of 500 billion BONK, worth approximately $18.62 millionOn July 24, BONK’s official Twitter account stated that driven by the transaction fees of the Letsbonk.Fun platform, 500 billion BONK (approximately US$18.62 million) had just been destro</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948410320774565888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Punchbowl：美国众议院委员会对美联储的翻修工程展开调查On July 24, according to Punchbowl: The U.S. House of Representatives committee has launched an investigation into the Federal Reserve renovation project. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948409159082381312</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsPunchbowl：美国众议院委员会对美联储的翻修工程展开调查On July 24, according to Punchbowl: The U.S. House of Representatives committee has launched an investigation into the Federal Reserve renovation project. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948409159082381312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock Ethereum ETF&apos;s assets exceeded $10 billion in one yearReported on July 24 that according to The Block, BlackRock&apos;s Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) ETHA has exceeded $10 billion in assets under management in less than a year, becoming the third ETF in history to reach this milestone within a year. Eric Balchunas, senior analyst at Bloomberg ETF, said on the X platform that ETHA&apos;s assets jumped from $5 billion to $10 billion in just 10 days, showing the strong appeal of Ethereum among institutional investors. Data shows that on July 23, the cumulative inflows of nine tradable Ethereum funds in the United States reached $8.65 billion, while ETHA had a net inflow of $325 million on the same day. Analysts predict that ETFs and Ethereum-related companies may purchase $20 billion worth of Ethereum in the next year, further boosting market demand. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948406865251078144</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBlackRock Ethereum ETF&apos;s assets exceeded $10 billion in one yearReported on July 24 that according to The Block, BlackRock&apos;s Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) ETHA has exceeded $10 billion in assets under management in less than a year, becoming the third ETF in history to reach th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948406865251078144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK is Sitting On Billions In Bitcoin, But How Will The Government Use It?This week, the United Kingdom made headlines after reports revealed it was considering selling $7.00 billion worth of Bitcoin confiscated during a 2018 law enforcement seizure. The extra cash comes at a crucial time for the UK as it grapples with a fragile financial position. While the UK considers selling its seized Bitcoin, doing so could lead to billions in lost opportunities. Mark Pearce, General Counsel at Alkimi, emphasized that the situation presents a complex dilemma rather than a clear-cut solution for the UK. A £5 Billion Question For British Leaders The United Kingdom’s Chancellor, Rachel Reeves, is currently sitting on over 61,000 Bitcoins worth over £5.00 billion. The substantial stockpile came from a major law enforcement seizure in 2018 that disrupted a major money laundering operation in the UK. The funds originated from a massive Chinese Ponzi scheme that had defrauded approximately 128,000 investors in China since 2014. Recent reports suggest that Reeves is considering selling these confiscated Bitcoin assets to help address the UK’s weakened fiscal position. The government faces significant financial challenges, with a budget deficit of £57.80 billion. The UK’s national debt has also reached historically high levels, currently amounting to £2.87 trillion. These financial pressures, paired with increasing costs for paying interest on that debt and growing demands for government spending, are creating a significant political challenge for the current government. Given the context, it’s no surprise that the Chancellor is considering filling in the gaps with revenue from selling its Bitcoin stockpile. The UK’s Fiscal Tightrope The UK government selling its seized Bitcoin could help close the current hole in its public finances. Such an injection could reduce further government borrowing, easing pressure on the national debt and associated interest payments. Skeptics who perceive Bitcoin as a highly volatile and unproductive asset would also celebrate the move. Some see the government holding billions of pounds worth of a speculative asset as imprudent when public finances are strained. Selling allows it to deploy this capital for immediate public benefit. Since the amount the government would sell is small compared to Bitcoin’s total market capitalization, the market impact would be minimal. However, he also questioned whether it would be prudent for the government to sell these assets in the short term. To Sell Or Not To Sell? Though Jian Wen, one of the key money laundering facilitators behind the Chinese Ponzi scheme, has been convicted and sentenced, other parts of the criminal case are still ongoing. Specifically, the fate of the Bitcoin stockpile is still subject to continuing civil recovery proceedings. The UK government is actively seeking to formalize its ownership of the assets for the Treasury. Until this process is finalized, Pearce believes the government should not sell off its holdings. This waiting period also offers a welcome delay for Bitcoin enthusiasts, who believe the UK should hold onto its Bitcoin to benefit from its increasing value. The High Cost of Selling Early Selling the seized Bitcoin offers the UK government immediate financial benefits, but also risks forfeiting significant future gains. Selling now means locking in the current value and potentially forfeiting billions of pounds that would be generated if Bitcoin’s price continues to climb. This risk has already been compared to when former Chancellor Gordon Brown sold off a significant portion of the UK’s gold reserves. The UK can also look to its German neighbor as an example of a missed opportunity. Last July, Germany sold nearly 50,000 BTC for over $2.89 billion. Authorities reportedly chose to sell due to concerns about the cryptocurrency’s volatility. Almost immediately after the sales, Bitcoin’s price continued its upward trajectory. Today, it rests at $118,400. Arkham Intelligence estimated that if Germany had held onto the Bitcoin, its value would have been $5.24 billion by May 2025. What Lies Ahead: A Blueprint for Seized Crypto The UK government faces a highly disputed decision. While the immediate multi-billion-pound windfall from selling its seized Bitcoin offers a crucial lifeline for its strained public finances, it must carefully weigh this against the significant gamble of potentially missing out on even greater future gains. Whatever it decides will shape the global conversation on how governments should manage digital assets born from illicit activity.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413449360445440</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoUK is Sitting On Billions In Bitcoin, But How Will The Government Use It?This week, the United Kingdom made headlines after reports revealed it was considering selling $7.00 billion worth of Bitcoin confiscated during a 2018 law enforcement seizure. The extra cash comes at a cruc</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413449360445440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockmate Establishes Bitcoin Treasury, Pursues &quot;Mine and HODL&quot; StrategyBlockmate Ventures Establishes Dedicated Bitcoin Treasury Division, Complementing Blockmate&apos;s Existing Operations Through its Wholly-Owned Subsidiary, Blockmate Mining, Which is Pursuing a &quot;Mine and HODL&quot; Strategy Aimed at Accumulating Bitcoin on its Balance Sheet as the Business Scales. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948405605806444544</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBlockmate Establishes Bitcoin Treasury, Pursues &quot;Mine and HODL&quot; StrategyBlockmate Ventures Establishes Dedicated Bitcoin Treasury Division, Complementing Blockmate&apos;s Existing Operations Through its Wholly-Owned Subsidiary, Blockmate Mining, Which is Pursuing a &quot;Mine and HODL&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948405605806444544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yi Lihua: ETH is showing strong momentum and is nearing the end of its consolidation. Don&apos;t short in a bull market.LD Capital founder Yi Lihua posted on the X platform, stating, &quot;ETH is strongly approaching the end of its fluctuation. This was originally a huge pressure level, a position where many OGs collectively break even. In a bull market trend, no matter what negative news there is, do not short and try not to short. Adhere to the principle of trend investing.&quot; [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948405580854530048</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyYi Lihua: ETH is showing strong momentum and is nearing the end of its consolidation. Don&apos;t short in a bull market.LD Capital founder Yi Lihua posted on the X platform, stating, &quot;ETH is strongly approaching the end of its fluctuation. This was originally a huge pressure level, a posi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948405580854530048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men suspected in New York cryptocurrency kidnapping torture case released on million-dollar bailTwo suspects, John Woeltz and William Duplessie, accused of kidnapping and abusing a Bitcoin investor in New York, were granted bail on Wednesday for $1.00M each. Despite facing charges that could lead to life imprisonment, the judge stated that the credibility of witnesses and discrepancies in the narratives of both sides in the case led to the decision to grant bail. Prosecutors allege that the two men subjected an Italian businessman to two weeks of violent coercion, including electric shocks, beatings, and death threats, with the aim of obtaining crypto assets. The defense claims that the so-called &quot;victim&quot; was not forcibly detained and submitted videos of him participating in social activities as evidence. Casa Security stated that it has tracked 30 similar incidents in the first half of 2025 alone, calling on crypto holders to strengthen their physical security. [Decrypt]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948403060937658368</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Two men suspected in New York cryptocurrency kidnapping torture case released on million-dollar bailTwo suspects, John Woeltz and William Duplessie, accused of kidnapping and abusing a Bitcoin investor in New York, were granted bail on Wednesday for $1.00M each. Despite facing charges th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948403060937658368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +4.02%, ADA +1.64%, SUI +1.57%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948401221751496704</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +4.02%, ADA +1.64%, SUI +1.57%.$ETH$ADA$SUIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948401221751496704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Announces Integration of INK Token and its Ink Layer 2 Network into Core Product SystemKraken has announced the integration of the INK token and its Ink Layer 2 network into its core product system, opening it up to global users and simultaneously including it in the Kraken Drops airdrop reward program. Officials stated that this move aims to promote the integration of on-chain infrastructure and centralized platforms, and expand scenarios such as liquidity aggregation, on-chain lending, and trading. Ink Network is a member of the Optimism &quot;Superchain&quot; ecosystem, and is in the same expansion system as Base, Uniswap L2, Sony Chain, etc. [TheBlock]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948399647675977728</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Kraken Announces Integration of INK Token and its Ink Layer 2 Network into Core Product SystemKraken has announced the integration of the INK token and its Ink Layer 2 network into its core product system, opening it up to global users and simultaneously including it in the Kraken Drops</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948399647675977728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>