<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:08:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 3.000000M USDC into Hyperliquid and went long ETH 20 timesOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale 0x8F93 deposited 3.000 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened a 20x leveraged ETH long position, holding 7,200 ETH (worth US$26.300 million). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186715428032512</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsA whale deposited 3.000000M USDC into Hyperliquid and went long ETH 20 timesOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale 0x8F93 deposited 3.000 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened a 20x leveraged ETH long position, holding 7,200 ETH (worth US$26.300 million). [P</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186715428032512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law firm Burwick Law expands lawsuit against pump.fun, names Solana and Jito executives as defendants.According to The Block, law firms Burwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against pump.fun to include the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito, and their executives as defendants, including Solana co-founders Anatoly Yakovenko and Raj Gokal, Solana Foundation Executive Director Dan Albert, Chairman Lily Liu, and former Head of Communications Austin Federa. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186400939118592</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNewsLaw firm Burwick Law expands lawsuit against pump.fun, names Solana and Jito executives as defendants.According to The Block, law firms Burwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against pump.fun to include the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186400939118592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pump.fun Co-founder: Airdrop Will Not Happen in the Near Futurepump.fun co-founder Alon was interviewed live today by overseas KOL Thread Guy. When asked about a potential PUMP airdrop, Alon said, &quot;Obviously, we want to give back to the community members who helped build this platform and witnessed its booming development over the past year and a half. That is to say, we want to ensure that this airdrop is substantial and well-executed, and we also know that this is a great opportunity for the platform - to strengthen the existing ecosystem, increase trading volume and user activity, and achieve long-term sustainable growth. This is crucial for us. That&apos;s why we are fully promoting the return of the ecosystem&apos;s popularity. However, it should be noted that the airdrop will not be taking place in the immediate future, and the specific timetable and implementation details will be synchronized with the community as soon as they are determined.&quot; [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186637854380032</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailypump.fun Co-founder: Airdrop Will Not Happen in the Near Futurepump.fun co-founder Alon was interviewed live today by overseas KOL Thread Guy. When asked about a potential PUMP airdrop, Alon said, &quot;Obviously, we want to give back to the community members who helped build this plat</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186637854380032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale transferred 2.12M SPX to CEX again, worth $4.07M.According to OnchainLens monitoring, a certain whale recently transferred another 2.12M SPX to CEX, worth approximately $4.07M at the current price. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186646293319680</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoOdailyA certain whale transferred 2.12M SPX to CEX again, worth $4.07M.According to OnchainLens monitoring, a certain whale recently transferred another 2.12M SPX to CEX, worth approximately $4.07M at the current price. [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186646293319680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machi Big Brother&apos;s PUMP long positions are already showing a floating loss of over $5.80M, and he is still continuing to add to his positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother (@machibigbrother)&apos;s PUMP long position has suffered a floating loss of more than $5.80M, but he is still continuing to increase his long position. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186654744842240</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoOdailyMachi Big Brother&apos;s PUMP long positions are already showing a floating loss of over $5.80M, and he is still continuing to add to his positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother (@machibigbrother)&apos;s PUMP long position ha</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186654744842240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three new addresses have recently purchased approximately $640.0 million worth of ETH in total.According to OnchainLens monitoring, multiple newly created wallets have been continuously accumulating large amounts of ETH, suspected to be the behavior of whales or institutions: Address 0xd47 has withdrawn 32,902 ETH from Kraken in the past 5 days, worth approximately $119.00M; address 0x8eE has cumulatively received 138,345 ETH (worth $501.00M) through FalconX in the past 5 days, with the latest transfer being 32,368 ETH; address 0x4e4 withdrew 5,600 ETH (worth $20.51M) from Coinbase and deposited it into Aave V3 for lending. The three addresses have collectively accumulated approximately 207,000 ETH in the past five days, with a total value of over $640.00M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948184133167026176</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyThree new addresses have recently purchased approximately $640.0 million worth of ETH in total.According to OnchainLens monitoring, multiple newly created wallets have been continuously accumulating large amounts of ETH, suspected to be the behavior of whales or institutions: Add</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948184133167026176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to Conduct Next Round of Fund Distribution on September 30, Disputed Claims Reserve Reduced by $1.90BFTX will conduct its next round of fund distribution on September 30, with the record date set for August 15. This distribution is for customers with allowed claims, holders of general unsecured claims, and holders of convenience claims who have not previously received a distribution. Meanwhile, the bankruptcy court has approved FTX&apos;s reduction of the disputed claims reserve from $6.50B to $4.30B, releasing approximately $1.90B for this round of distribution. The distribution will be conducted through three service providers: BitGo, Kraken, and Payoneer. FTX reminds users to complete KYC verification and submit tax forms, and to be wary of potential phishing scams. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948181308852736000</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoForesightNewsFTX to Conduct Next Round of Fund Distribution on September 30, Disputed Claims Reserve Reduced by $1.90BFTX will conduct its next round of fund distribution on September 30, with the record date set for August 15. This distribution is for customers with allowed claims, ho</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948181308852736000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.30% in the past 1H, down 0.54% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948178801761411072</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.30% in the past 1H, down 0.54% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948178801761411072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Number of stablecoin holders surpasses SOLOn July 24, Decrypt reported that a recent Reown survey shows that the number of stablecoin holders has exceeded the number of SOL holders, accounting for 38% and 37% respectively, indicating that cryptocurrency is shifting from speculation to practical applications. Bitcoin and Ethereum still dominate, each accounting for 48% of users. The survey shows that while trading remains the most popular on-chain activity (36%), payments have jumped to second place (10%), and 14% of users say this is the future application they look forward to the most. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948178563823374336</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoTechFlowData: Number of stablecoin holders surpasses SOLOn July 24, Decrypt reported that a recent Reown survey shows that the number of stablecoin holders has exceeded the number of SOL holders, accounting for 38% and 37% respectively, indicating that cryptocurrency is shifting from s</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948178563823374336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block Joins S&amp;P 500, Square Launches Bitcoin Payment PilotBlock (formerly Square Inc.) officially joined the S&amp;P 500 Index on Wednesday and announced that its payment platform Square has launched a pilot program for Bitcoin payment services. The service is based on Lightning Network technology and supports merchants in achieving low-cost, near-instant Bitcoin payments through Square devices. Block business director Owen Jennings revealed that the company is recruiting the first users of the &quot;native Bitcoin payment experience,&quot; a feature that is an important step in Jack Dorsey&apos;s push to make Bitcoin a mainstream payment tool. [Decrypt]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948178706563928064</link>
      <description>38 minutes ago吴说Block Joins S&amp;P 500, Square Launches Bitcoin Payment PilotBlock (formerly Square Inc.) officially joined the S&amp;P 500 Index on Wednesday and announced that its payment platform Square has launched a pilot program for Bitcoin payment services. The service is based on Lightning Network</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948178706563928064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha fund shuts down after huge losses this yearOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, Joe McCann is gradually closing Asymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha Fund after the fund was accused of a sharp decline in value this year and sparked severe criticism online. Joe McCann said on social media that the fund strategy &quot;clearly no longer serves the interests of LPs&quot; and that the fund was set up for volatile markets and had achieved results. Asymmetric will now &quot;abandon its liquidity trading strategy&quot; and invest in long-term investments in blockchain infrastructure. Investors in the liquidity fund can choose to exit without considering the standard lock-up period, or transfer their funds to a new illiquid investment structure. He also said that the company consists of multiple investment vehicles, and despite the troubles of the Liquid Alpha fund, other business units - especially its venture capital strategy - remain intact, and the venture capital unit will continue to support early blockchain projects. Previously, unconfirmed social media rumors claimed that the liquid fund has fallen 78% this year. Data shows that the volatility of the crypto market has dropped significantly in the past 12 months, which indicates that the digital asset market may be more mature. According to TradingView data, the Cryptocurrency Volatility Index (CVI) has fallen nearly 30%. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948172949298679808</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsAsymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha fund shuts down after huge losses this yearOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, Joe McCann is gradually closing Asymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha Fund after the fund was accused of a sharp decline in value this year and sparked severe criticism online. Joe McCann said</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948172949298679808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House&apos;s First Crypto Policy Report to be Released on July 30Bo Hines stated on the X platform that the Presidential Working Group on Digital Assets has completed its 180-day report, the first White House crypto policy report, which will be publicly released on July 30. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948174074764660736</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyWhite House&apos;s First Crypto Policy Report to be Released on July 30Bo Hines stated on the X platform that the Presidential Working Group on Digital Assets has completed its 180-day report, the first White House crypto policy report, which will be publicly released on July 30. [Odaily]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948174074764660736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LetsBONK commits to using 1% of revenue to buy back top BONK ecosystem tokens.LetsBONK has announced that it will use 1% of its total revenue to repurchase leading tokens within the BONK ecosystem. The funds will come from the team&apos;s marketing fund, and the repurchase operation will be carried out on a weekly basis. Data shows that LetsBONK generated approximately $1.50M in fees in the past 24 hours, which will provide $15,000.00 for this round of repurchases proportionally. Recently, LetsBONK has surpassed its competitor Pump.fun in terms of daily trading volume and the number of tokens issued. Dune data shows that the total market value of tokens issued on its platform has exceeded $1.00B. Among them, Useless Coin is the largest token, followed by ANI, the latter representing the Grok AI companion token launched by xAI. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948174083203600384</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyLetsBONK commits to using 1% of revenue to buy back top BONK ecosystem tokens.LetsBONK has announced that it will use 1% of its total revenue to repurchase leading tokens within the BONK ecosystem. The funds will come from the team&apos;s marketing fund, and the repurchase operation will</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948174083203600384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: In the past 24 hours, $734.00M was liquidated across the entire network, with $631.00M in long positions and $104.00M in short positions.According to Coinglass data, the entire network liquidation in the past 24 hours was $734.00 million, with long orders accounting for $631.00 million and short orders accounting for $104.00 million. Among them, Bitcoin long orders accounted for $53.45 million, Bitcoin short orders accounted for $11.61 million, Ethereum long orders accounted for $130.00 million, and Ethereum short orders accounted for $21.55 million. In addition, in the last 24 hours, 244,517 people were liquidated globally, with the largest single liquidation order occurring on Binance - BTCUSDT with a value of $2.96 million. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948171718622777344</link>
      <description>1 hour agoChainCatcherData: In the past 24 hours, $734.00M was liquidated across the entire network, with $631.00M in long positions and $104.00M in short positions.According to Coinglass data, the entire network liquidation in the past 24 hours was $734.00 million, with long orders accounting for $</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948171718622777344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed company Sixty Six Capital indirectly increased its holdings of 16.02 Bitcoins through ETFsOn July 24 according to newsfilecorp, Canadian listed company Sixty Six Capital Inc. (CSE: SIX) announced an increase of 114,000 units of BTCC.B (Bitcoin ETF), which is equivalent to 16.02 bitcoins, with a total price of US$2,577,850.00. This will bring the company&apos;s current BTC equivalent holdings to 148.8 BTC. The company will convert these BTC equivalents into directly held BTC as soon as reasonably practicable. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948170069955121152</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsListed company Sixty Six Capital indirectly increased its holdings of 16.02 Bitcoins through ETFsOn July 24 according to newsfilecorp, Canadian listed company Sixty Six Capital Inc. (CSE: SIX) announced an increase of 114,000 units of BTCC.B (Bitcoin ETF), which is equivalent to 16.0</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948170069955121152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active loans on Ethereum lending protocols hit $30 billion, up $27 billion from January 2023On July 24, according to Cointelegraph, the scale of active loans on the Ethereum lending protocol reached US$30.00 billion, an increase of US$27.00 billion from January 2023. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948169044565233664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsActive loans on Ethereum lending protocols hit $30 billion, up $27 billion from January 2023On July 24, according to Cointelegraph, the scale of active loans on the Ethereum lending protocol reached US$30.00 billion, an increase of US$27.00 billion from January 2023. [PANews]#DeFi$ET</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948169044565233664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tron Inc. Announces It Will Ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on July 24On July 24, according to Globenewswire, Tron Inc. (NASDAQ: TRON) announced that it will hold an opening bell ceremony at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York on July 24, Eastern Time, hosted by Justin Sun, TRON founder and global advisor of Tron Inc. This marks the company&apos;s official transformation into a technology company focusing on blockchain and digital asset innovation.
The company said that this bell ringing is not only an important milestone in the development of Tron Inc., but also highlights its long-term vision of driving shareholder value growth through innovation and strategic leadership. The company, formerly known as SRM Entertainment, is currently the listed company with the largest number of TRX tokens. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948167955174461440</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsTron Inc. Announces It Will Ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on July 24On July 24, according to Globenewswire, Tron Inc. (NASDAQ: TRON) announced that it will hold an opening bell ceremony at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York on July 24, Eastern Time, hosted by Justin Sun,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948167955174461440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan: $2 trillion stablecoin market forecast is “overly optimistic”On July 24, Bloomberg reported that JPMorgan Chase released a report questioning the $2.00 trillion forecast for the stablecoin market, believing that the figure is &quot;too optimistic.&quot; Analysts pointed out that the current market size of $260.00 billion may only grow by 2-3 times in a few years, far lower than the US Treasury Secretary&apos;s previous expectation of breaking through $2.00 trillion in 2028. The report pointed out that although the GENIUS Act has established a regulatory framework for stablecoins, it will take time to improve the payment infrastructure and ecosystem. Currently, USDT and USDC account for more than 60% of the market share, but stablecoins only account for 1% of global capital flows. Analysts believe that due to investors&apos; conservative attitude towards cash management, it is difficult to use stablecoins as a mainstream liquidity alternative in the short term. JPMorgan Chase emphasized that although stablecoins have the advantage of instant settlement in the field of cross-border payments, merchant acceptance is still higher than that of ordinary consumers. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948161030743461888</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsJPMorgan: $2 trillion stablecoin market forecast is “overly optimistic”On July 24, Bloomberg reported that JPMorgan Chase released a report questioning the $2.00 trillion forecast for the stablecoin market, believing that the figure is &quot;too optimistic.&quot; Analysts pointed out that the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948161030743461888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trialWith the trial of the Tornado Cash co-founder ending its eighth day, a witness testified Roman Storm had control over some of the funds connected to the mixing service.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948144352076828672</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsCrypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trialWith the trial of the Tornado Cash co-founder ending its eighth day, a witness testified Roman Storm had control over some of the funds connected to the mixing service.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948144352076828672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Agent Links Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm to Binance Funds and Offshore DealingsFederal prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm moved millions through Binance and coordinated with co-founders to send funds and buy offshore real estate. IRS-CI Special Agent Stephan George told the jury he traced over $533,000.00 in USDT from a Binance account allegedly controlled by Storm. He said the funds were moved on August 9, 2022, and distributed across three wallet addresses. Storm Allegedly Sent $2.6 Million Each to Co-Founders Prosecutors showed chat logs between Tornado Cash’s founding trio: Roman Storm, Roman Semenov, and Alexey Pertsev. In one message, Storm wrote: “I overloaded 8 million yesterday.” Another message stated: “I sent you guys 2.6 million each.” Agent George said these communications indicated Storm had access to the funds and decision-making power over the wallet in question. In a separate message, Storm reportedly told a colleague to: “Give her a task to f **ing open various offshores… and to buy real estate.” Prosecutors also read a message from Semenov stating: “I will send some TORN later, to avoid getting busted.” The prosecution argued these messages revealed intent to obscure transactions and profit from Tornado Cash’s operations. 96% of Tornado Cash Users Relied on Web Interface Earlier in the day, prosecution expert Philip Werlau of AnChain.AI testified that 96.2% of users accessed Tornado Cash through its user interface (UI), not the command line. He said Lazarus Group shifted to CLI usage only after US sanctions were imposed. Werlau said this behavior suggested a deliberate attempt to avoid detection. During cross-examination, Roman Storm’s defense challenged Werlau’s conclusions. He emphasized that Tornado Cash’s smart contract pools became immutable in May 2020, meaning neither Storm nor the DAO could change them. Klein also clarified that Tornado’s UI did not handle transactions directly. Deposits and withdrawals required interacting with Ethereum’s smart contracts, not any centralized interface. Meanwhile, prosecutors presented an email from an earlier witness, Ms. Lin, addressed to Tornado Cash’s public inbox. Judge Failla warned the jury not to treat its content as fact. The email’s inclusion may relate to the defense’s previously stated mistrial concerns, though no motion was filed. What’s Next in the Tornado Cash Trial The prosecution is expected to rest its case tomorrow morning. A separate hearing on the Chainalysis expert testimony is still pending. Storm’s defense is preparing to present its side, focusing on the immutability of Tornado Cash and Storm’s lack of control after deployment. [Wu Shuo]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948140146783752192</link>
      <description>3 hours agobeincryptoIRS Agent Links Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm to Binance Funds and Offshore DealingsFederal prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm moved millions through Binance and coordinated with co-founders to send funds and buy offshore real estate. IRS-CI</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948140146783752192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 01:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>