<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:44:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cathie Wood sells Coinbase, Roblox shares for Tom Lee’s ETH firm</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544985150967808</link>
      <description>06:30Cathie Wood sells Coinbase, Roblox shares for Tom Lee’s ETH firm</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544985150967808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyShell.AI Launches Application Building Agent ShellAgent 2.0AI consumer layer MyShell.AI tweeted that it has launched the application building agent ShellAgent 2.0. Users can build backends, set up hosting, design UIs, and publish applications by conversing with AI. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947545969059188736</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoForesightNewsMyShell.AI Launches Application Building Agent ShellAgent 2.0AI consumer layer MyShell.AI tweeted that it has launched the application building agent ShellAgent 2.0. Users can build backends, set up hosting, design UIs, and publish applications by conversing with AI. [Fore</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947545969059188736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWF Partner: The Crypto Altcoin Season Has Just BegunDWF Labs Managing Partner Andrei Grachev posted, &quot;The altcoin season in cryptocurrency has just begun, and Nasdaq-listed companies are about to usher in the altcoin season as well.&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544913524838400</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyDWF Partner: The Crypto Altcoin Season Has Just BegunDWF Labs Managing Partner Andrei Grachev posted, &quot;The altcoin season in cryptocurrency has just begun, and Nasdaq-listed companies are about to usher in the altcoin season as well.&quot; [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544913524838400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito announces that its Web3 crowdfunding platform Capital Launchpad is now liveOn July 22, Kaito, an AI-driven Web3 data provider, announced on the X platform that Capital Launchpad is now online and users can register on Yaps. A FAQ page has been added and will be updated based on the feedback and questions received. The financing cycle on Capital Launchpad includes the pre-commitment stage, commitment stage, review stage, optimization stage, and FCFS stage. Currently, the platform only supports USDC on Base, and participants must undergo KYC/AML review, and users in some countries are excluded. Earlier news revealed that Kaito will launch the Web3 crowdfunding platform Capital Launchpad this week. The platform will allow users to participate in private token offerings and new project investments, using an allocation mechanism based on indicators such as social reputation and on-chain holdings to replace the traditional first-come, first-served model. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947543992476651520</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoPANewsKaito announces that its Web3 crowdfunding platform Capital Launchpad is now liveOn July 22, Kaito, an AI-driven Web3 data provider, announced on the X platform that Capital Launchpad is now online and users can register on Yaps. A FAQ page has been added and will be updated base</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947543992476651520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBTC is now supported on the Aptos networkAccording to official sources, the Aptos network now supports WBTC. Users can bridge WBTC to the Aptos network via Stargate. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544921967972352</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoOdailyWBTC is now supported on the Aptos networkAccording to official sources, the Aptos network now supports WBTC. Users can bridge WBTC to the Aptos network via Stargate. [Odaily]#Layer1$WBTC$APTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544921967972352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE eventBinance Wallet announced that users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE event through the Alpha activity page. Participating in this activity will consume 15 points. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544930419494912</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyBinance: Users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE eventBinance Wallet announced that users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE event through the Alpha activity page. Participating in this activity wi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544930419494912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinwatch Launches Track Tool to Help Crypto Projects View Market Maker ActivityCoinwatch has launched Track, a tool to help crypto projects view activity in real-time via market maker API Keys, including buy and sell order depth, spreads, and trading volume, while protecting market maker privacy using a Trusted Execution Environment (TEE). It has currently integrated 12 market makers, including Amber, Ampersan, Auros, CyantArb, Flowdesk, Galaxy, GSR, IMC, Keyrock, LO:TECH, Pulsar, and STS Digital, with more to come. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542193967484928</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoForesightNewsCoinwatch Launches Track Tool to Help Crypto Projects View Market Maker ActivityCoinwatch has launched Track, a tool to help crypto projects view activity in real-time via market maker API Keys, including buy and sell order depth, spreads, and trading volume, while protect</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542193967484928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Advance Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial company strategy. In addition, this operation may be combined with existing operations, allowing the company to acquire an additional approximately 120 BTC, bringing the company&apos;s potential total holdings to 2,075 BTC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541171144511488</link>
      <description>28 minutes ago吴说Publicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Advance Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financia</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541171144511488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Capital B Raises Approximately €10.30M to Advance its Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) has announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial company strategy. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541141926989824</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoChainCatcherPublicly Listed Capital B Raises Approximately €10.30M to Advance its Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) has announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541141926989824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury StrategyOn July 22, according to the official announcement, the European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial company strategy. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540361358626816</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoTechFlowPublicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury StrategyOn July 22, according to the official announcement, the European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540361358626816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin miner Mawson has fired its CEO over alleged fraud and misconductAccording to The Miner Mag, Bitcoin mining company Mawson has fired CEO Rahul Mewawalla for breach of fiduciary duty and alleged fraud, and has filed a lawsuit in Delaware court in the United States. Rahul Mewawalla subsequently stated in a letter to the board of directors on July 17 that he &quot;respectfully but vehemently&quot; opposed the company&apos;s description of the events, noting that the board had publicly praised his leadership earlier this year. Previously, Mawson was sued by NYDIG&apos;s parent company Stone Ridge and its subsidiary Consensus Colocation, accusing it of unauthorized control of $30.00M worth of ASIC miners owned by NYDIG. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542411521839104</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoOdailyBitcoin miner Mawson has fired its CEO over alleged fraud and misconductAccording to The Miner Mag, Bitcoin mining company Mawson has fired CEO Rahul Mewawalla for breach of fiduciary duty and alleged fraud, and has filed a lawsuit in Delaware court in the United States. Rahul Me</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542411521839104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B raises approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin finance company strategyFrench listed company Capital B raised approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy. In addition, the operation may be combined with existing operations to allow the company to acquire an additional approximately 120 BTC, bringing the company&apos;s potential total holdings to 2,075 BTC. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540944639512576</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoForesightNewsCapital B raises approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin finance company strategyFrench listed company Capital B raised approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy. In addition, the operation may be combined with existing operations to allow the com</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540944639512576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B, a listed company, announced a capital increase of approximately €10.3 million to implement its Bitcoin financial strategyOn July 22, according to an official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase in capital of approximately 10.3 million euros to implement its Bitcoin financial company strategy. Earlier yesterday, Blockchain Group announced that it had changed its name to Capital B and announced that it was setting up a subsidiary in Abu Dhabi. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539908608675840</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoPANewsCapital B, a listed company, announced a capital increase of approximately €10.3 million to implement its Bitcoin financial strategyOn July 22, according to an official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase in capita</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539908608675840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B Raises Approximately €10.30M to Advance Bitcoin Treasury StrategyEuropean listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) has announced a capital increase of approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin treasury company strategy. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539885212848128</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoOdailyCapital B Raises Approximately €10.30M to Advance Bitcoin Treasury StrategyEuropean listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) has announced a capital increase of approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin treasury company strategy. [Odaily Planet Daily News]#Bitc</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539885212848128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans propose 7% leaner SEC budget compared to Biden’s eraHouse Republicans have proposed a plan to trim the SEC’s budget and cut enforcement funding for a Biden-era rule requiring public companies to quickly report cyberattacks.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947538976290394112</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsRepublicans propose 7% leaner SEC budget compared to Biden’s eraHouse Republicans have proposed a plan to trim the SEC’s budget and cut enforcement funding for a Biden-era rule requiring public companies to quickly report cyberattacks.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947538976290394112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ether Machine CEO: Ethereum is the Biggest Beneficiary of the &quot;GENIUS Act&quot;According to a post by Cointelegraph, Ether Machine CEO Andrew Keys said, &quot;The biggest beneficiary of the GENIUS Act is Ethereum.&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539893689536512</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoOdailyEther Machine CEO: Ethereum is the Biggest Beneficiary of the &quot;GENIUS Act&quot;According to a post by Cointelegraph, Ether Machine CEO Andrew Keys said, &quot;The biggest beneficiary of the GENIUS Act is Ethereum.&quot; [Odaily]#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539893689536512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>cointelegraph</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange will list ORGO spot trading on July 22.On July 22, according to official news, Hotcoin will list the following trading pairs on July 22: Spot trading pair ORGO/USDT: (July 22 12:00 UTC+8): $ORGO is the native token of the Orgo AI project. Orgo is a desktop infrastructure for AI agents. It launches headless cloud virtual machines that AI models can control and interact with. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947534648326508544</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange will list ORGO spot trading on July 22.On July 22, according to official news, Hotcoin will list the following trading pairs on July 22: Spot trading pair ORGO/USDT: (July 22 12:00 UTC+8): $ORGO is the native token of the Orgo AI project. Orgo is a desktop infr</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947534648326508544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Onchain Trading Lists Grokrooms, ACT B, OPEN, and Other TokensBitget Onchain Trading has launched Solana ecosystem MEME tokens Grokrooms, ACT B, OPEN, and DELULU. Users can start trading in the Onchain Trading section. Bitget Onchain Trading aims to seamlessly connect CEX and DEX, providing users with a more convenient, efficient, and secure on-chain trading experience. Users can directly use their Bitget spot accounts (USDT/USDC) to trade popular on-chain assets. It currently supports popular public chains such as Solana (SOL), BNB Smart Chain (BSC), and Base. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947534844477329408</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoOdailyBitget Onchain Trading Lists Grokrooms, ACT B, OPEN, and Other TokensBitget Onchain Trading has launched Solana ecosystem MEME tokens Grokrooms, ACT B, OPEN, and DELULU. Users can start trading in the Onchain Trading section. Bitget Onchain Trading aims to seamlessly connect CEX</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947534844477329408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Foundation: Purchased $25,000.00 worth of TAG tokensBNB Chain tweeted that it has exchanged 25,000.00 USDT for 40421479.45 TAG at an exchange rate of 0.0006184830526, and that this transaction is part of BNB Chain&apos;s previously announced $100M ecosystem incentive program. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947532581637738496</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说BNB Chain Foundation: Purchased $25,000.00 worth of TAG tokensBNB Chain tweeted that it has exchanged 25,000.00 USDT for 40421479.45 TAG at an exchange rate of 0.0006184830526, and that this transaction is part of BNB Chain&apos;s previously announced $100M ecosystem incentive program. [Wu Bl</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947532581637738496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: US CPI data&apos;s short-term risks still lean upwardAnthony Willis, Senior Economist at Columbia Threadneedle Investments, pointed out that although the U.S. inflation situation is relatively mild, the current level is still significantly higher than the Federal Reserve&apos;s 2% target, and short-term risks still tend to be on the upside. He said: &quot;The current data will keep the Federal Reserve in a &apos;wait-and-see&apos; attitude during the release of the July and August CPI data, until the next interest rate meeting on September 17.&quot; By then, the Federal Reserve should be able to more clearly assess the transmission effect of tariffs on inflation and obtain more corroborating data on the weakening labor market. Willis believes that inflation is likely to move towards 3%, but given the dual mandate, the Federal Reserve may still find it necessary to cut interest rates later this year. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947532333708234752</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyInstitutions: US CPI data&apos;s short-term risks still lean upwardAnthony Willis, Senior Economist at Columbia Threadneedle Investments, pointed out that although the U.S. inflation situation is relatively mild, the current level is still significantly higher than the Federal Reserve&apos;s 2</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947532333708234752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Afternoon News1. Yilihua: The bull market rotation law has begun, and mainstream coins have taken the lead;
2. Yuga Labs co-founder hints at the possible launch of an NFT treasury company;
3. A whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00M;
4. Binance Wallet: Codatta token XNY will start trading on July 23rd at 8 PM;
5. BR: Market volatility has increased after Binance adjusted Alpha rules on July 21st, hoping users will trade rationally;
6. Trader Eugene: Has cut losses on PUMP, as it has been trading sideways for too long without breaking through;
7. Ark Invest reduces its holdings in Coinbase by $90.58M, while also selling Robinhood and Block positions;
8. Trend Research transferred 1.50M FORM to CEX, cashing out a cumulative 6.00M in 3 months, with a profit of approximately $3.90M;
9. Publicly listed company Profusa signs a $100.00M equity credit agreement to launch a Bitcoin treasury strategy;
10. Ethereum spot ETFs had a total net inflow of $297.00M yesterday, continuing for 12 consecutive days of net inflows;
11. Two whales transferred 60.00M ENA to CEX, worth approximately $30.00M.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947529807361495040</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyPlanet Afternoon News1. Yilihua: The bull market rotation law has begun, and mainstream coins have taken the lead;
2. Yuga Labs co-founder hints at the possible launch of an NFT treasury company;
3. A whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position valu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947529807361495040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 06:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>