<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Western Union explores integrating stablecoin services, calling it an important opportunity to accelerate cross-border payments.Western Union CEO Devin McGranahan says the company is actively exploring integrating stablecoin services into its digital wallet and plans to establish relevant on- and off-ramp partnerships to support users in buying and selling stablecoins. He pointed out that stablecoins have significant potential in improving the efficiency of cross-border payments, enhancing the stability of fiat currency exchange, and serving as a store of value in countries with economic turmoil, and the company sees them as an opportunity rather than a threat. This statement was released after the signing of the GENIUS Act, which establishes a federal regulatory framework for stablecoins and promotes their compliance in the global financial system. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947524781721276416</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoOdailyWestern Union explores integrating stablecoin services, calling it an important opportunity to accelerate cross-border payments.Western Union CEO Devin McGranahan says the company is actively exploring integrating stablecoin services into its digital wallet and plans to establish</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947524781721276416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two whales deposited 60.00 million ENA into Binance and Bybit in the early morning, worth $30.00 million.On July 22, according to Lookonchain monitoring, two whale addresses deposited 60.00 million ENA (worth US$30.00 million) into Binance and Bybit 11 hours ago. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947522095537999872</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsTwo whales deposited 60.00 million ENA into Binance and Bybit in the early morning, worth $30.00 million.On July 22, according to Lookonchain monitoring, two whale addresses deposited 60.00 million ENA (worth US$30.00 million) into Binance and Bybit 11 hours ago. [PANews]$ENA$BNB</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 05:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947522095537999872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase Considering Offering Crypto Asset-Backed Loans Starting Next YearJPMorgan Chase is considering allowing clients to use crypto assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum as collateral to apply for loan services, with related plans potentially launching as early as next year. (Cointelegraph) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947522267869368320</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyJPMorgan Chase Considering Offering Crypto Asset-Backed Loans Starting Next YearJPMorgan Chase is considering allowing clients to use crypto assets such as Bitcoin and Ethereum as collateral to apply for loan services, with related plans potentially launching as early as next yea</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947522267869368320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>cointelegraph</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades, a giant whale, has switched from shorting ETH to longing, and currently has a floating loss of nearly $3.00 million.On July 22, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale AguilaTrades has switched from shorting ETH to longing, and is currently suffering losses again, with a loss of nearly $3.00 million. The liquidation price was $3,654.77, which was very close to being liquidated. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947521543286575104</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsAguilaTrades, a giant whale, has switched from shorting ETH to longing, and currently has a floating loss of nearly $3.00 million.On July 22, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale AguilaTrades has switched from shorting ETH to longing, and is currently suffering losses a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947521543286575104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Risks 12% Drop as Long-Term Holders Book ProfitsBitcoin price may be holding above $117,500.00, but under the surface, signs of a potential pullback are mounting. On-chain signals from long-term holders and whale activity are in sync with key price action levels, and if history is any guide, this confluence could trigger a healthy correction in the days ahead. Long-Term Holder SOPR As The Silent Exit Signal The Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) for long-term holders, those holding BTC for more than 155 days, is showing consistent signs of profit-taking. As of July 21, the Long-Term SOPR stood at 1.96, meaning these holders are selling their coins for nearly double their acquisition cost. While that number alone may not sound alarming, context tells the story. For token TA and market updates : Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here . Zooming out on a 1-year chart, SOPR spikes have historically preceded sharp corrections. Consider this: Since July 9, SOPR has seen a series of elevated peaks: Note: The biggest profit-taking day, per the chart, was July 4. The Long-Term SOPR shot past 24.00, but surprisingly, Bitcoin price didn’t correct significantly post that. This delayed reaction builds tension and increases the odds of a catch-up correction soon. Whale-to-Exchange Ratio Quietly Climbing Again Another red flag comes from the Whale-to-Exchange Ratio, which tracks how much BTC whales (large holders) are sending to exchanges compared to overall market activity. Historically, whenever this ratio touches or exceeds the price trendline, a correction tends to follow. Two recent examples: Put simply: When whales move more coins to exchanges, they’re usually getting ready to sell. With the current W2E Ratio again peaking, it suggests distribution pressure is quietly building, even if spot markets seem calm. Bitcoin Price Structure Relies On Key Support Levels From a price structure standpoint , Bitcoin is currently trading around $117,500.00, showing signs of indecision. Since July 12, the price has repeatedly tested and respected the $116,456.00 level, which coincides with the 0.236 Fibonacci retracement of the recent impulse move from $98,230.00 to the $122,086.00 high. This zone has become a key battleground; holding above it signals strength, but a confirmed break below would likely open the door to deeper downside. The strongest support lies at $107,343.00, which marks the 0.618 Fibonacci level; often considered a golden pocket during retracements. If this level fails to hold, the market could enter a steeper correction phase. Since Bitcoin was in price discovery during the run-up to $122,000.00, there are limited structural supports below this level. In such a case, the next viable support rests near $103,355.00, a 12% correction from current prices. (February 9’s SOPR surge led to a similar correction.) However, this short-term bearish thesis would be invalidated if the Bitcoin price manages to break above $122,086.00 and reclaim the previous high near $122,827.00, while moving higher. A move above this zone, particularly if accompanied by a cooling off in SOPR and a drop in the Whale-to-Exchange Ratio, would point toward renewed bullish momentum. [Harsh Notariya]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947520561228042240</link>
      <description>35 minutes agobeincryptoBitcoin (BTC) Price Risks 12% Drop as Long-Term Holders Book ProfitsBitcoin price may be holding above $117,500.00, but under the surface, signs of a potential pullback are mounting. On-chain signals from long-term holders and whale activity are in sync with key price action</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947520561228042240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of England considers shelving digital pound plansOn July 22, foreign media reported that Bank of England officials are considering suspending plans for a digital pound for the public due to growing doubts about the benefits of the project. This reflects the fading enthusiasm for government-backed digital currencies around the world. According to people familiar with the matter, the Bank of England has privately urged the banking industry to accelerate payment innovation in order to achieve similar benefits without launching a central bank digital currency (CBDC). The Bank of England said it still hopes to retain the ability to launch a CBDC if necessary, but if the private sector continues to launch new electronic payment technologies and its staff believe that the benefits of promoting a digital pound are declining, the central bank is willing to step back. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947514065656238080</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsBank of England considers shelving digital pound plansOn July 22, foreign media reported that Bank of England officials are considering suspending plans for a digital pound for the public due to growing doubts about the benefits of the project. This reflects the fading enthusiasm</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947514065656238080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS: Stablecoins will boost net demand for short-term U.S. Treasuries, and there is still room for short-term debt supplyOn July 22, Zhitong Finance reported that UBS had previously anticipated the rapid expansion of short-term U.S. Treasury bonds in tradable debt had passed, but the GENIUS Act may bring a new round of growth. According to the Act, stablecoin issuers must maintain 100% reserve support with short-term, highly liquid, and high-quality assets. Approved reserve assets include: US dollar cash, short-term U.S. Treasury bonds, deposits of insured depository institutions, and short-term Treasury bond repurchase agreements. After the debt ceiling issue was resolved and the government&apos;s money market funds expanded significantly, the current short-term U.S. Treasury market still has ample absorption capacity. If the GENIUS Act stimulates more demand for short-term Treasury bonds, the U.S. Treasury can slightly postpone the time to expand the scale of interest-bearing Treasury bonds, and there is also more room to repurchase old bonds with poor liquidity. In any case, UBS expects the Treasury to continue to keep the relative proportion of short-term Treasury bonds to interest-bearing Treasury bonds stable. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947513857216106496</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoPANewsUBS: Stablecoins will boost net demand for short-term U.S. Treasuries, and there is still room for short-term debt supplyOn July 22, Zhitong Finance reported that UBS had previously anticipated the rapid expansion of short-term U.S. Treasury bonds in tradable debt had passed, but</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947513857216106496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berachain Officially Launches PoL v2 Upgrade, Ushering in an Era of Native Yield for $BERA StakersOn July 22, Berachain officially launched the PoLv2 upgrade. This upgrade allows users to directly stake $BERA to obtain protocol-level收益, which comes from the $BERA repurchase mechanism of PoL incentives. It also sets a 7-day unbinding period to balance long-term ecological development. Non-$BERA incentives will be automatically converted to $BERA and injected into the收益 pool. In the future, it will also support收益 acquisition of liquid staking assets (LST). The收益率 data will be updated every 24 hours on the BeraHub platform. Initially, batch updates will be performed 2-3 times per week, and subsequently, it will gradually transition to daily updates. This upgrade, while maintaining the original logic of the application layer and reward vault, directly transforms ecological growth into staker收益 through protocol-layer design. [Techflow News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947513730116112384</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoTechFlowBerachain Officially Launches PoL v2 Upgrade, Ushering in an Era of Native Yield for $BERA StakersOn July 22, Berachain officially launched the PoLv2 upgrade. This upgrade allows users to directly stake $BERA to obtain protocol-level收益, which comes from the $BERA repurchase mec</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947513730116112384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMart will list ZKWASM (ZKWASM)According to the official announcement, BitMart will list ZKWASM (ZKWASM) at 21:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, opening the ZKWASM/USDT trading pair. Delphinus Lab is the core development team of ZKWASM. ZKWASM is the first open-source virtual machine that supports zero-knowledge proof generation for WebAssembly (WASM). It supports verifiable off-chain computation and a modular Rollup architecture. The ecosystem includes a zk-native Launchpad for deploying verifiable dApps and targets practical use cases such as verifiable mini-games. ZKWASM is supported by top investors such as HashKey Capital, Mirana Ventures, and SevenX, and is positioned as the core zero-knowledge proof infrastructure layer for scalable, trustless Web3 applications. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947514721234341888</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoOdailyBitMart will list ZKWASM (ZKWASM)According to the official announcement, BitMart will list ZKWASM (ZKWASM) at 21:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, opening the ZKWASM/USDT trading pair. Delphinus Lab is the core development team of ZKWASM. ZKWASM is the first open-source virtual machine that</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947514721234341888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Li-Hua Yi: The bull market rotation law has begun, and mainstream coins have taken the lead.Yi Lihua, founder of LD Capital, posted on social media that the current crypto market&apos;s &quot;bull market rotation law&quot; has begun, with XRP, SOL, LTC, UNI and other mainstream currencies taking the lead in rising. He pointed out that as long as the US stock market does not have any surprises, after the crypto bill is implemented, Wall Street may have a large amount of funds entering the market in a concentrated manner. Yi Lihua also mentioned that he had tried to do swing trading in the past, but most of the time he bought high and sold low, resulting in &quot;mental exhaustion and losses&quot;. He said that in a bull market, he should focus on investing in potential targets in order to outperform the market as a whole. He previously stated that the rotation law of the crypto market usually manifests itself as BTC and ETH starting first, followed by medium-cap mainstream currencies, and finally altcoins rotating. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947512210138091520</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoOdailyLi-Hua Yi: The bull market rotation law has begun, and mainstream coins have taken the lead.Yi Lihua, founder of LD Capital, posted on social media that the current crypto market&apos;s &quot;bull market rotation law&quot; has begun, with XRP, SOL, LTC, UNI and other mainstream currencies takin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947512210138091520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet: Codatta token XNY will begin trading on July 23rd at 8 PM.Binance Wallet announced that the Codatta (XNY) token will officially begin circulation on July 23, 2025, at 20:00 Beijing time. Users participating in the Codatta Pre-TGE can trade XNY tokens on the Binance Alpha platform. In addition, winners of the Week 1 and Week 2 Codatta Booster activities can claim and trade XNY tokens within 8 hours of the token&apos;s circulation start. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947512218631557120</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance Wallet: Codatta token XNY will begin trading on July 23rd at 8 PM.Binance Wallet announced that the Codatta (XNY) token will officially begin circulation on July 23, 2025, at 20:00 Beijing time. Users participating in the Codatta Pre-TGE can trade XNY tokens on the Binance Al</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947512218631557120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday, with none of the twelve ETFs experiencing a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 21th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net outflow yesterday was Ark Invest and 21Shares&apos;s ETF ARKB, with a daily net outflow of 77.46M USD, and the total historical net inflow of ARKB currently stands at 2.84B USD.The second highest was Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC, with a daily net outflow of 36.75M USD, and the total historical net outflow of GBTC currently stands at 23.54B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 151.60B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.52%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.62B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947503415871098880</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday, with none of the twelve ETFs experiencing a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 21th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the hi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947503415871098880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate.io Adds USD1 Trading Zone, Launching 9 Popular Trading Pairs Including BTC/USD1 and ETH/USD1 in the First BatchAccording to the official announcement, Gate will officially launch the USD1 trading zone at 14:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, and will initially launch 9 popular currency trading pairs including BTC/USD1, ETH/USD1, SOL/USD1, B/USD1, BNB/USD1, TRX/USD1, DOGE/USD1, SUI/USD1, and EGL1/USD1, to further enrich trading options and enhance user experience. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947504653050859520</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGate.io Adds USD1 Trading Zone, Launching 9 Popular Trading Pairs Including BTC/USD1 and ETH/USD1 in the First BatchAccording to the official announcement, Gate will officially launch the USD1 trading zone at 14:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, and will initially launch 9 popular currency trad</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947504653050859520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit 24-Hour Trading Volume Ranking: XRP, STRIKE, DOGE Top ThreeOn July 22, according to CoinGecko data, Upbit&apos;s trading volume in the past 24 hours reached $6.45B, up 35.40%. The top five tokens by trading volume are:

XRP (12.72% of trading volume, $820.00M in transaction volume)

STRIKE (11.98% of trading volume, $773.00M in transaction volume)

DOGE (7.93% of trading volume, $511.00M in transaction volume)

SOL (6.66% of trading volume, $429.00M in transaction volume)

PENGU (4.84% of trading volume, $312.00M in transaction volume)
 [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502503595888640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowUpbit 24-Hour Trading Volume Ranking: XRP, STRIKE, DOGE Top ThreeOn July 22, according to CoinGecko data, Upbit&apos;s trading volume in the past 24 hours reached $6.45B, up 35.40%. The top five tokens by trading volume are:

XRP (12.72% of trading volume, $820.00M in transaction volume</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502503595888640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraday Future and HabitTrade have reached a strategic partnership to enhance shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial servicesOn July 22, according to Groonghui, Faraday Future announced a strategic partnership with HabitTrade. HabitTrade is a global multi-market broker and digital asset infrastructure platform. FF said it plans to use this partnership to provide its shareholders with exclusive benefits on the HabitTrade platform and further enhance shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial services. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502403410743296</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFaraday Future and HabitTrade have reached a strategic partnership to enhance shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial servicesOn July 22, according to Groonghui, Faraday Future announced a strategic partnership with HabitTrade. HabitTrade is a global multi-market broker a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502403410743296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grupo Murano Plans to Build $10.00B Bitcoin Treasury in Five YearsAccording to Bitcoin Magazine, Mexican-listed real estate company Grupo Murano plans to incorporate Bitcoin into its core strategic assets, with an initial investment of approximately $1.00B and plans to build a $10.00B Bitcoin treasury within five years. Its CEO, Elías Sacal, stated that the company is converting its properties into BTC holdings through asset refinancing and sale-leaseback transactions, and will deploy Bitcoin ATMs in its properties and open up hotel BTC payment scenarios. Its overall capital allocation will allocate 70% to 80% to Bitcoin, with the remainder invested in high-margin real estate projects to improve capital efficiency and mitigate the risks posed by the high-interest rate environment. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947500669359640576</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsGrupo Murano Plans to Build $10.00B Bitcoin Treasury in Five YearsAccording to Bitcoin Magazine, Mexican-listed real estate company Grupo Murano plans to incorporate Bitcoin into its core strategic assets, with an initial investment of approximately $1.00B and plans to build a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947500669359640576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuga Labs Co-founder Posts, Possibly Hinting at the Launch of an NFT Treasury CompanyYuga Labs co-founder Garga.eth tweeted, &quot;The world isn&apos;t ready for NFT treasury companies, but they&apos;re on their way.&quot; The community says this may indicate that it will launch an NFT treasury company. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497840112848896</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsYuga Labs Co-founder Posts, Possibly Hinting at the Launch of an NFT Treasury CompanyYuga Labs co-founder Garga.eth tweeted, &quot;The world isn&apos;t ready for NFT treasury companies, but they&apos;re on their way.&quot; The community says this may indicate that it will launch an NFT treasury c</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497840112848896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00MAccording to crypto analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, a certain whale is currently going long on Bitcoin on both the Aave and Hyperliquid platforms, with a total position value of approximately $91.00M and a current floating profit of over $4.223M. Among them, the address on the Aave platform is cyclically going long on WBTC at an average price of $114,272.00, mortgaging 342.21 WBTC, borrowing $20.00M in stablecoins, with a health factor of 1.57, and a current floating profit of $963,000.00; on the Hyperliquid platform, it is using 10x leverage to go long on BTC, with a position amount of approximately $50.93M, an opening price of $109,655.20, and a floating profit of approximately $3.26M. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497104893300736</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00MAccording to crypto analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, a certain whale is currently going long on Bitcoin on both the Aave and Hyperliquid platforms, with a total position value of</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497104893300736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Diner restaurant has opened to the public, possibly supporting DOGE paymentsTesla Diner is now open to the public. It is equipped with 80 Tesla Supercharger stalls, provides autonomous vehicle pick-up and drop-off for customers, and Tesla humanoid robot waiters. In addition, some community members have revealed that the restaurant may accept DOGE payments. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496919773499392</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsTesla Diner restaurant has opened to the public, possibly supporting DOGE paymentsTesla Diner is now open to the public. It is equipped with 80 Tesla Supercharger stalls, provides autonomous vehicle pick-up and drop-off for customers, and Tesla humanoid robot waiters. In addit</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496919773499392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet Launches Exclusive Point Boost Event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2According to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched an exclusive points bonus event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2. By interacting through linking your OKX Wallet, users can enjoy an additional 10% points bonus. Users can participate in the event via the following link: https://portal.kaia.io/mission/epoch2 It is reported that Kaia is a merger of the Klaytn and Finschia blockchains initially developed by Kakao and LINE, respectively. It has the lowest transaction latency in EVM L1, with a 1-second block time and instant finality, enabling a smooth user experience and opening up possibilities for use cases that require near real-time response. OKX Wallet is a leading one-stop Web3 portal in the industry and supports 130+ popular public chains. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497113336434688</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyOKX Wallet Launches Exclusive Point Boost Event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2According to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched an exclusive points bonus event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2. By interacting through linking your OKX Wallet, users can enjoy an additional 10% points bonus. User</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497113336434688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 05:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>