<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:49:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Arkham: The US government’s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000Arkham stated that the US government has not sold its 170,000 BTC (about $20 billion) in the past four months. Among them, the US Marshals Service (USMS) currently holds about 28,988 BTC (about $3.4 billion), while other agencies such as the FBI, the Department of Justice (DOJ), the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) and local prosecutors&apos; offices hold at least 198,000 BTC (about $23.5 billion) in total. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227735171698688</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsArkham: The US government’s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000Arkham stated that the US government has not sold its 170,000 BTC (about $20 billion) in the past four months. Among them, the US Marshals Service (USMS) currently holds about 28,988 BTC (about $3.4 billion), while</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227735171698688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSR withdrew 2,708 ETH from Binance 2 hours ago, worth approximately $9.87M.According to The Data Nerd, market maker GSR withdrew 2,708 ETH (approximately $98,700.00) from Binance two hours ago and transferred it to a wallet address starting with 0xdE6. Currently, GSR&apos;s 0xdE6-starting address (possibly an ETH storage wallet) holds a total of 103,822 ETH, worth approximately $379.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227705824153600</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsGSR withdrew 2,708 ETH from Binance 2 hours ago, worth approximately $9.87M.According to The Data Nerd, market maker GSR withdrew 2,708 ETH (approximately $98,700.00) from Binance two hours ago and transferred it to a wallet address starting with 0xdE6. Currently, GSR&apos;s 0xd</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227705824153600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller Joins Paradigm TeamParadigm co-founder Matt Huang tweeted that former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller has joined the Paradigm team to help its portfolio design in cutting-edge areas. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227236993241088</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoForesightNewsFormer OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller Joins Paradigm TeamParadigm co-founder Matt Huang tweeted that former OpenAI Head of Design Veit Moeller has joined the Paradigm team to help its portfolio design in cutting-edge areas. [Foresight News]#FundraisingShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948227236993241088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq-listed Lion Group Increases SUI Token Holdings, Portfolio Totals $9.60MAccording to SEC filings, Nasdaq-listed Lion Group has increased its holdings of SUI tokens, with its total purchase amount of Hyperliquid (HYPE), Solana (SOL), and Sui (SUI) tokens reaching approximately $9.60M. As of July 23, 2025, Lion Group&apos;s fiscal reserves include: 128,929 HYPE, 6,629 SOL, and 1,015,680 SUI. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948226916468723712</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoOdailyNasdaq-listed Lion Group Increases SUI Token Holdings, Portfolio Totals $9.60MAccording to SEC filings, Nasdaq-listed Lion Group has increased its holdings of SUI tokens, with its total purchase amount of Hyperliquid (HYPE), Solana (SOL), and Sui (SUI) tokens reaching approximate</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948226916468723712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripple: Beware of XRP-related scams on YouTubeOn July 24, Ripple issued a warning on the X platform, noting that XRP-related scams are increasing on the YouTube platform. After the scammers steal the account, they will update the page content and pretend to be the official Ripple account. Ripple or the company&apos;s executives will never ask users to send them XRP. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948224201592213504</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoPANewsRipple: Beware of XRP-related scams on YouTubeOn July 24, Ripple issued a warning on the X platform, noting that XRP-related scams are increasing on the YouTube platform. After the scammers steal the account, they will update the page content and pretend to be the official Ripple</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948224201592213504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches New VIP Event, Complete Tasks to Unlock 50,000 BGBBitget has launched a new VIP event. During the event, users who complete net deposit, contract, or spot trading volume tasks can receive corresponding BGB airdrop rewards, with a total prize pool of 50,000 BGB. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223766089240576</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Launches New VIP Event, Complete Tasks to Unlock 50,000 BGBBitget has launched a new VIP event. During the event, users who complete net deposit, contract, or spot trading volume tasks can receive corresponding BGB airdrop rewards, with a total prize pool of 50,000</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223766089240576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SIMD-0256 proposal to increase the Solana block limit to 60M CU has been activated on the mainnet.The SIMD-0256 proposal to increase the Solana block limit to 60M CU has been activated on the mainnet. It is understood that Compute Units (CU) capacity is a unit of measurement for transaction computing resources on Solana, similar to Ethereum&apos;s Gas, used to limit transaction complexity and protect network resources. The VP of Core Engineering at Solana ecosystem development company Anza once stated that they would make Solana&apos;s block space reach a block limit of 100M CU by the end of this year. It is worth noting that increasing the block CU limit means that the blocks become larger, which places higher performance requirements on the validation nodes. This is a trade-off between network throughput and stability. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223710078504960</link>
      <description>20 minutes ago吴说The SIMD-0256 proposal to increase the Solana block limit to 60M CU has been activated on the mainnet.The SIMD-0256 proposal to increase the Solana block limit to 60M CU has been activated on the mainnet. It is understood that Compute Units (CU) capacity is a unit of measurement for</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223710078504960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to start next creditor payout on Sep. 30 with $1.9 billion granted by courtFTX announced Wednesday that it is expected to start distributing the next batch of creditor claims on Sep. 30. The record date for claim holders is set for Aug. 15.

Its latest announcement also revealed that the bankruptcy court gave the greenlight to cut down the claims reserve from $6.5 billion to $4.3 billion, which releases $1.9 billion to be distributed to holders in the upcoming disbursement. However, it did not explicitly state how much would be allocated for the Sept. 30 distribution.

FTX has so far handed out approximately $6.2 billion to former customers across two distributions — $1.2 billion in February and $5.0 billion in May this year. The overall repayment plan aims to distribute between $14.7 billion and $16.5 billion, with recoveries varying based on claim type and valuation.

Around 98% of the creditors are expected to receive at least 119% of their claims based on the value at the time of the bankruptcy. Some creditors have criticized the plan, noting that the overall crypto market has significantly appreciated in value since the bankruptcy in 2022.

The payout is expected to be made through BitGo, Kraken and Payoneer. Traders anticipate that these FTX distributions could inject significant liquidity into the crypto market, especially for altcoins.

Meanwhile, the FTX Recovery Trust submitted a motion on July 4 requesting the court to authorize the implementation of new measures to assess creditor claim distributions in restricted jurisdictions overseas.

The motion sought to immediately forfeit and reverse claims in countries designated as &quot;restricted jurisdictions,&quot; where distributions would be deemed illegal. Potentially affected countries included China, Russia, Saudi Arabia, and Pakistan. The proposal drew backlash and formal objections from creditors in those regions.

At a hearing on Tuesday, the court acknowledged the objections to the proposed motion and ordered FTX to revise it —removing the clause that would allow for the &quot;immediate&quot; forfeiture of claims and adding an option for creditors in restricted regions to transfer and receive their claims through a different jurisdiction, according to an X post by FTX Historian. [FTX Historian]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223295937122304</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoThe BlockFTX to start next creditor payout on Sep. 30 with $1.9 billion granted by courtFTX announced Wednesday that it is expected to start distributing the next batch of creditor claims on Sep. 30. The record date for claim holders is set for Aug. 15.

Its latest announcement also re</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948223295937122304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistics: Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated a total of 466,253 ETH, worth 1.7 billion yuanNew wallets have purchased 40,591 ETH (worth 148 million yuan) today. Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated 466,253 ETH (worth 1.7 billion yuan).
 Specific details:
 The 0x8eEa address received 138,345 ETH (worth 505 million yuan) from FalconX in the past 5 days;
 The 0x9684 address received 122,691 ETH (worth 448 million yuan) from FalconX in the past 13 days;
 The 0x35fb address withdrew 103,274 ETH (worth 377 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 15 days;
 The 0x3dF3 address received 43,787 ETH (worth 160 million yuan) from Galaxy Digital in the past 5 days;
 The 0xD479 address withdrew 32,902 ETH (worth 120 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 5 days;
 The 0xf877 address has withdrawn 12,913 ETH (worth 47 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 10 days;
 The 0x6A95 address withdrew 12,341 ETH (worth 45 million yuan) from Kraken in the past 9 days. [Lookonchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221416465305600</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoPANewsStatistics: Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated a total of 466,253 ETH, worth 1.7 billion yuanNew wallets have purchased 40,591 ETH (worth 148 million yuan) today. Recently, 7 new wallets have accumulated 466,253 ETH (worth 1.7 billion yuan).
 Specific details:
 The 0x8eEa a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221416465305600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX launches grid strategy special event, with up to 10,000 USDT strategy position airdrops availableAccording to official sources, OKX will launch a strategy trading special event from 11:00 on July 24, 2025 to 23:59 on August 24, 2025 (UTC+8). The first theme is &quot;grid strategy&quot;. Participating users will have the opportunity to receive a 10,000.00 USDT grid strategy position airdrop and limited peripheral rewards. During the event, users can quickly understand the grid strategy through interesting videos, and start BTC spot grid or contract grid strategy trading with one click. The system defaults to AI intelligent parameters, and users can also choose &quot;custom parameters&quot;. At the same time, you can also participate in the &quot;OKX Chinese&quot; official Twitter original content sharing to win more rewards. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221881844305920</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoOdailyOKX launches grid strategy special event, with up to 10,000 USDT strategy position airdrops availableAccording to official sources, OKX will launch a strategy trading special event from 11:00 on July 24, 2025 to 23:59 on August 24, 2025 (UTC+8). The first theme is &quot;grid strategy&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948221881844305920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb to List LISTA and MERL KRW Trading PairsSouth Korea&apos;s second-largest crypto exchange, Bithumb, will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs. Trading will open at 4:00 PM and 6:00 PM local time, respectively. Lista DAO is a decentralized stablecoin lending protocol powered by LSDfi. Merlin Chain is a Bitcoin Layer 2 powered by Bitmap. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216915113086976</link>
      <description>47 minutes ago吴说Bithumb to List LISTA and MERL KRW Trading PairsSouth Korea&apos;s second-largest crypto exchange, Bithumb, will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs. Trading will open at 4:00 PM and 6:00 PM local time, respectively. Lista DAO is a decentralized stablecoin lending protocol powered by LS</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216915113086976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Momentum Ignites Hong Kong Race for Crypto DominanceIn this week’s Hong Kong Edition, we survey the fizzing stablecoin scene, speak with the man behind Bar Leone and look into the stocks leaving Chinese tech in the dust. For the Review, we visit a new modern Korean restaurant from the chef formerly of Singapore’s famed Odette. To subscribe to this weekly newsletter for free, click here.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948217933922111488</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoBloombergStablecoin Momentum Ignites Hong Kong Race for Crypto DominanceIn this week’s Hong Kong Edition, we survey the fizzing stablecoin scene, speak with the man behind Bar Leone and look into the stocks leaving Chinese tech in the dust. For the Review, we visit a new modern Korean</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948217933922111488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26.According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will launch DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26. Eligible users can go to the Alpha activity page to use Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop after trading opens. Specific rules will be announced separately. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216849795190784</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha will list DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26.According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will launch DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26. Eligible users can go to the Alpha activity page to use Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop after trading opens. Specific</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216849795190784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale has closed their PUMP short position, netting a profit of $2.448M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has closed its PUMP short position on Hyperliquid, with a cumulative profit of $2.448 million. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948214328607444992</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA certain whale has closed their PUMP short position, netting a profit of $2.448M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has closed its PUMP short position on Hyperliquid, with a cumulative profit of $2.448 million. [Odaily Planet Daily]$PUMP$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948214328607444992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget CEO: The next bull market will be driven by application implementation, compliance, and technical value.Bitget CEO Gracy Chen tweeted, &quot;I don&apos;t think the next bull market will be driven by retail investors and meme coins again, nor will it be tied to the halving cycle. Instead, it will depend on how many applications can be implemented, how clear compliance regulations are, and how much real value technology can create.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211919416004608</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitget CEO: The next bull market will be driven by application implementation, compliance, and technical value.Bitget CEO Gracy Chen tweeted, &quot;I don&apos;t think the next bull market will be driven by retail investors and meme coins again, nor will it be tied to the halving cycle.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211919416004608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After School Club NFT Launches Utility Token GEMThe Eclipse ecosystem NFT series After School Club has launched a utility token, GEM. GEM will be rewarded by providing ASC holders with practical uses and long-term benefit alignment within the Eclipse ecosystem. The initial airdrop snapshot was completed on July 21, with each ASC NFT allocated 5 GEM tokens, for a total airdrop of 50,000 GEM (10% of the supply). In addition, monthly airdrops will continue for 45 months, with 1 GEM allocated per ASC NFT each month, for a total allocation of 450,000 GEM (90% of the supply). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211585964642304</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsAfter School Club NFT Launches Utility Token GEMThe Eclipse ecosystem NFT series After School Club has launched a utility token, GEM. GEM will be rewarded by providing ASC holders with practical uses and long-term benefit alignment within the Eclipse ecosystem. The initial air</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211585964642304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist Takashi Murakami will launch NFT collection cards on the chain through Base AppOn July 24, according to The Block, the famous Japanese artist Takashi Murakami announced that he will launch the NFT series &quot;108 Flowers Revised&quot;. The series is based on his iconic &quot;super flat&quot; style of floral images and will be available for minting on the Base App on July 31. This new work continues his creative style of integrating pop culture and anime aesthetics. His past partners include luxury fashion brands such as Louis Vuitton and Supreme. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948210155727949824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsArtist Takashi Murakami will launch NFT collection cards on the chain through Base AppOn July 24, according to The Block, the famous Japanese artist Takashi Murakami announced that he will launch the NFT series &quot;108 Flowers Revised&quot;. The series is based on his iconic &quot;super flat&quot; sty</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948210155727949824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined, over 7.5% has been permanently lostOn July 24, according to Curated Crypto data, only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined. It is estimated that more than 7.5% of the total Bitcoin supply has permanently disappeared from circulation due to lost wallets, forgotten private keys, or being destroyed. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948208958342238208</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowData: Only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined, over 7.5% has been permanently lostOn July 24, according to Curated Crypto data, only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined. It is estimated that more than 7.5% of the total Bitcoin supply has permanently disappeared from circulation du</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948208958342238208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Phase 6: Participant Count Exceeds 120,000 in 12 HoursThe sixth phase of the &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event, jointly launched by Bitget Wallet and Maple Finance, started at 21:00 on July 23, with all 120,000 participation slots snapped up in a short period. The total prize pool for this round is approximately 228,000 SYRUP, with the super lucky prize winner exclusively receiving SYRUP rewards worth $6,666.00. The draw time is 22:00 on July 24 (UTC + 8). Winners must submit their prize collection information within 24 hours after the draw, or it will be invalid. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948209306754682880</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitget Wallet &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Phase 6: Participant Count Exceeds 120,000 in 12 HoursThe sixth phase of the &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event, jointly launched by Bitget Wallet and Maple Finance, started at 21:00 on July 23, with all 120,000 participation slots snapped up in a short period. The t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948209306754682880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch DEBT, NERO, and ELP spot tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Hotcoin will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs
DEBT/USDT (July 24, 12:00 UTC+8): $DEBT is the native token of the DebtCoin project. DebtCoin is the first meme coin with a patriotic mission. Unlike other meme coins that are purely for speculation, DebtCoin directs trading activity to a meaningful cause - reducing the US national debt by purchasing US Treasury bonds.
NERO/USDT (July 24, 17:20 UTC+8): $NERO is the native token of the NeroChain project. NERO Chain is built on a modular blockchain and focuses on providing value to applications, rather than just focusing on the infrastructure layer of storage.
ELP/USDT (July 24, 20:20 UTC+8): $ELP is the native token of the Elympics project. Elympics is a multi-chain entertainment layer designed to attract millions to use cryptocurrency by connecting brands and IPs to web3, and to enable developers to easily build and deploy blockchain-based skill-based games distributed across popular super apps, social platforms, and wallets. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948207963486883840</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch DEBT, NERO, and ELP spot tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Hotcoin will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs
DEBT/USDT (July 24, 12:00 UTC+8): $DEBT is the native token of the DebtCoin project. DebtCoin i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948207963486883840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>