<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:56:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitfarms to buy back 10% of shares, calls stock undervalued</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947786573408129024</link>
      <description>22:30Bitfarms to buy back 10% of shares, calls stock undervalued</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947786573408129024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto confusion: 50% of non-investors don’t understand it well enough to buy</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947781088420319232</link>
      <description>22:08Crypto confusion: 50% of non-investors don’t understand it well enough to buy</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 22:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947781088420319232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US SEC approved conversion of the Bitwise crypto index fund — then hit pauseThe U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission approved the conversion of Bitwise&apos;s cryptocurrency index fund, but then quickly hit pause.

The SEC&apos;s Division of Trading and Markets granted an &quot;accelerated approval&quot; of the Bitwise 10 Crypto Index ETF on Tuesday, according to a filing. However, the SEC&apos;s Assistant Secretary Sherry R. Haywood later stayed the action and said the commission would review it.

&quot;This letter is to notify you that, pursuant to Rule 431 of the Commission’s Rules of Practice, 17 CFR 201.431, the Commission will review the delegated action,&quot; Haywood said on Tuesday. &quot;In accordance with Rule 431(e), the July 22, 2025 order is stayed until the Commission orders otherwise.&quot;

Bitwise did not immediately respond to a request for comment. An SEC spokesperson said they declined to comment on any individual company or filing.

The Bitwise 10 Crypto Index Fund, which trades under the ticker “BITW,” currently consists of exposure to BTC, ETH, XRP, SOL, Polkadot, among others, on a market cap-weighted basis, according to its website.

The SEC&apos;s pause on Bitwise&apos;s proposals mirrors a similar move it made for deciding on whether to convert the Grayscale Digital Large Cap Fund LLC earlier this month. The fund trades over the counter for accredited investors and is composed primarily of Bitcoin at almost 80% and ETH at about 11%. Solana, Cardano, and XRP are also represented with single-digit percentages, according to its website.

The SEC approved Grayscale&apos;s proposal to convert another one of its closed-end funds into an ETF on an &quot;accelerated basis,&quot; but a day later said it was staying the order.

Grayscale has said it &quot;remains committed&quot; to continue trying to list.

This comes as the SEC is also considering a wide array of crypto ETFs, from ones that track SOL to DOGE in the face of a friendlier regulatory environment for crypto following President Donald Trump&apos;s inauguration in January.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947777696637669376</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockUS SEC approved conversion of the Bitwise crypto index fund — then hit pauseThe U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission approved the conversion of Bitwise&apos;s cryptocurrency index fund, but then quickly hit pause.

The SEC&apos;s Division of Trading and Markets granted an &quot;accelerated ap</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947777696637669376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares files for ONDO ETF21Shares has filed for an exchange-traded product tracking ONDO, the native token for the Ondo real-world asset platform. The firm submitted its S-1 filing on Tuesday, according to a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission report.

Ondo Finance is a decentralized finance platform founded in 2021 by former Goldman Sachs associates Nathan Allman and Pinku Suran, focused on tokenizing real-world assets like U.S. Treasury bonds and money market funds.

Ondo is in the orbit of President Donald Trump through the World Liberty Financial DeFi project. World Liberty has purchased approximately half a million worth of ONDO tokens for its multi-asset treasury.

Earlier this month, the platform said it would acquire U.S.-regulated broker Oasis Pro to expand its tokenization business. The firm has also partnered with Pantera on a $250 million RWA investment plan.

There are dozens of crypto-related ETF proposals awaiting SEC approval. Last month, Bloomberg analysts raised their year-end odds of spot XRP, Dogecoin, and Cardano ETF approvals to 90.00%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947772494710853632</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe Block21Shares files for ONDO ETF21Shares has filed for an exchange-traded product tracking ONDO, the native token for the Ondo real-world asset platform. The firm submitted its S-1 filing on Tuesday, according to a U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission report.

Ondo Finance is a dece</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947772494710853632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How GameSquare is monetizing a $38.00M Ether treasury with NFTsWhile most firms treat NFTs as marketing gimmicks, GameSquare is flipping the script, deploying them as financial instruments. Its new $10.00 million yield program transforms Ethereum-based digital assets into revenue generators, marking a risky but innovative leap in corporate crypto strategy. On July 21, GameSquare announced the expansion of its crypto treasury program to $250.00 million, including a dedicated $10.00 million allocation toward a novel NFT yield strategy. The move follows a $30.00 million purchase of Ether ( ETH ), bringing its total holdings to over 10,000 tokens. Rather than holding these assets passively, the company plans to actively deploy them across Ethereum-native DeFi protocols, using NFTs not as collectibles but as yield-bearing instruments. The strategy is backed by risk management infrastructure developed in partnership with Swiss crypto firm Dialectic. The announcement positions GameSquare among a rare breed of public companies experimenting with NFTs as functional components of corporate finance. It reflects a broader evolution in digital asset strategy, moving away from speculative balance sheet positioning toward operational capital deployment. GameSquare’s decision to focus its digital asset strategy on Ethereum signals a fundamental shift in how the company views the role of capital within a modern media business. Ethereum’s capacity to be programmed, staked, lent, or locked in smart contracts is being used as the backbone of a treasury system that does more than just store value. With $35.00 million already deployed into ETH and another $215.00 million authorized, GameSquare is treating its crypto holdings not as hedges, but as financial infrastructure. The NFT angle reveals GameSquare’s deeper play. Rather than chasing hype-driven collectibles, the company is strategically acquiring Ethereum-native digital assets that align with its gaming and media roots. By locking NFTs into DeFi protocols, GameSquare can mint yield-bearing stablecoins while retaining ownership of the underlying assets. “We are excited to be among the first public companies to include NFTs as part of a diversified digital asset strategy,” the company’s CEO, Justin Kenna, said. “This reflects the innovative approach to our treasury management initiatives. With deep experience building in-game and real-world creative environments, GameSquare is uniquely positioned to understand the cultural and economic value of these digital assets.” According to the press release, GameSquare has established a dedicated crypto investment committee reporting directly to its board, with strict controls to prevent conflicts of interest.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947771228395950080</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsHow GameSquare is monetizing a $38.00M Ether treasury with NFTsWhile most firms treat NFTs as marketing gimmicks, GameSquare is flipping the script, deploying them as financial instruments. Its new $10.00 million yield program transforms Ethereum-based digital assets into revenu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947771228395950080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla’s futuristic diner is here, serving fries and popcorn—but where’s the Dogecoin?Elon Musk’s Tesla diner is now serving up burgers and futurism in Hollywood. However, patrons noticed the absence of Dogecoin payments, despite his earlier endorsement, turning what could’ve been a crypto milestone into a missed opportunity. The grand opening of Tesla’s long-hyped “retro-futuristic” diner in Hollywood unfolded Monday afternoon with all the usual Musk theatrics: a 4:20 p.m. unlock time, robots behind popcorn machines, and Cybertruck-shaped trays. Tesla Diner &amp; Supercharger in Hollywood, LA Open 24/7, starting now  pic.twitter.com/nISRNoV89Y The crowd, which had gathered at the Santa Monica Boulevard diner hours before opening, cheered as Tesla’s chief designer, Franz von Holzhausen, unlocked the doors.  For Dogecoin ( DOGE ) loyalists, the fanfare rang hollow. Despite Musk’s 2022 tweet insisting DOGE payments were coming, the only currency accepted was the old-fashioned kind. When one patron approached a touch screen and placed his order, he followed up with a question: “Can I pay in Dogecoin?” “Not today,” the diner employee responded. See below. 🚨DOGE FAM MUST SEE THIS🚨 I actually went to Tesla Diner first day to ask them if they accept DOGECOIN! 👇  pic.twitter.com/3b7zeDhhsA Musk’s influence on Dogecoin’s valuation is well-documented; a single tweet from him has sent the memecoin soaring or cratering for years. His latest pivot away from crypto integration, especially at a high-profile venture blending tech and commerce, raises questions about how seriously Tesla takes digital assets. The diner’s omission of DOGE isn’t just a snub to crypto enthusiasts; it’s a missed chance to normalize cryptocurrency in everyday transactions, something Musk once championed. The Tesla diner, nestled at the intersection of electric vehicles, entertainment, and lifestyle, could have become a high-visibility proving ground for real-world crypto payments. Killing it, man! “Not today” paying with  $Doge . Not the answer we where hoping for but better then a flat out no Instead, the absence of Dogecoin underscores a widening gap between Musk’s rhetoric and implementation, particularly at a time when the digital assets sector is seeking tangible, everyday use cases. Whether this was a delay or a quiet reversal remains unclear, but in the current climate, silence on crypto can speak volumes. Meanwhile, Musk has already floated plans to expand the diner concept to major cities and Supercharger stops, contingent on its initial success. Whether he’ll keep his word and eventually accept DOGE as a payment remains to be seen.  “‘Not today’ paying with $Doge. Not the answer we where hoping for but better then a flat out no,” another observer noted on X [sic].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947767458576486400</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsTesla’s futuristic diner is here, serving fries and popcorn—but where’s the Dogecoin?Elon Musk’s Tesla diner is now serving up burgers and futurism in Hollywood. However, patrons noticed the absence of Dogecoin payments, despite his earlier endorsement, turning what could’ve bee</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947767458576486400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily: JPMorgan explores crypto loans, Musk&apos;s SpaceX moves bitcoin, Senate pushes policy, and moreThe following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter,The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.
Never miss a beat with The Block&apos;sdaily digestof the most influential events happening across the digital assetecosystem.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947762440301465600</link>
      <description>2 hours agoThe BlockThe Daily: JPMorgan explores crypto loans, Musk&apos;s SpaceX moves bitcoin, Senate pushes policy, and moreThe following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter,The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.
Never miss a beat with The Block&apos;sdaily digestof the most influenti</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947762440301465600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Prosecutors Seek Forfeiture of $7.10M in Crypto Assets Tied to Fake Oil and Gas Investment ScamThe U.S. Attorney&apos;s Office for the Western District of Washington announced that it has filed a civil lawsuit regarding a fraud case involving false oil and gas storage investments, seeking to seize approximately $7.10M in cryptocurrency in order to return some of the losses to victims. The related assets were seized by Homeland Security Investigations in December 2024. The total amount of funds involved is approximately $97.00M. The fraudulent group lured victims into remitting funds by disguising themselves as third-party escrow accounts and transferred the funds into multiple financial institutions and cryptocurrency accounts. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947791647534501888</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说US Prosecutors Seek Forfeiture of $7.10M in Crypto Assets Tied to Fake Oil and Gas Investment ScamThe U.S. Attorney&apos;s Office for the Western District of Washington announced that it has filed a civil lawsuit regarding a fraud case involving false oil and gas storage investments, seeking</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947791647534501888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Tapiero Merges Two Crypto Growth Equity Funds Under Rebranded 50TDan Tapiero is merging his two crypto growth equity funds, 10T Holdings and 1RoundTable Partners, rebranding them as 50T, and launching a new $500.00M fund, 50T Fund V, focused on growth investments in blockchain, cryptocurrency, and Web3 infrastructure. Tapiero has raised his ten-year outlook for the digital asset ecosystem from $10.00T to $50.00T, encompassing crypto assets themselves as well as related listed and private company valuations. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947787324654112768</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说Dan Tapiero Merges Two Crypto Growth Equity Funds Under Rebranded 50TDan Tapiero is merging his two crypto growth equity funds, 10T Holdings and 1RoundTable Partners, rebranding them as 50T, and launching a new $500.00M fund, 50T Fund V, focused on growth investments in blockchain, cryp</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947787324654112768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU Could Rally 38% if One Key Price Resistance BreaksAfter a strong 26% gain over the past week, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) is now hovering just below a crucial resistance level. While much of the altcoin market cools down, PENGU price looks poised to break out. Only if it can push past one key wall. A deeper look at bullish strength, liquidations, and price charts shows the token might still have room to run. PENGU Bulls Are In Complete Control Even though PENGU dropped around 2% in the past 24 hours, the bulls still seem to be holding the reins. The Bull-Bear Power (BBP) index, which compares recent highs and lows to measure market strength, is currently flashing green, at around 0.0148. This level suggests buyers still have the upper hand, despite a short-term dip. For token TA and market updates : Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here . In simple terms, when BBP is positive, bulls are stronger than bears. And Pengu’s BBP has remained above zero since late June, even as prices hovered below key resistance. That steady strength could be a sign that any dip is just part of a cooldown before another leg up. If BBP stays positive while price climbs past resistance, it might confirm that PENGU still has momentum. But if BBP flips negative, it could warn of a deeper pullback ahead. 7-Day Liquidation Map Shows Short-Biased Setup PENGU is currently trading around $0.036. The 7-day liquidation map shows cumulative short liquidation leverage building up to $10.46 million versus $10.18 million for longs; a slight bias toward short positions. Do note that there isn’t much to choose between Longs and  Shorts , and a price push in either direction can decide the next leg for PENGU.  However, as bulls are in power and that too by a sizable margin, as established by the BBP index, the price action could impact the short positions more than the long. If the price crosses $0.039, led by bulls breaking key resistance level, and even nears $0.042, a major liquidation cluster of shorts gets triggered. That would reduce downward pressure and potentially propel the  PENGU price  to the next key price level. The liquidation map shows a build-up of short positions; if PENGU’s price moves up fast, those betting against it may be forced to buy back, pushing the price even higher. PENGU Price Action Hints at a 38% Upside Technically, the  PENGU price  has tested the 0.382 Fibonacci level near $0.039 twice and failed to break above cleanly. It now trades just under that resistance. Do note that besides the Fib extension resistance, a key resistance of $0.037 also exists. The chart uses the Trend-based Fibonacci extension tool. It connects the swing low of $0.0077 to the last swing high of $0.035 and then to the immediately retraced price level of $0.028. This tool helps chart the next price targets for a coin/token in an uptrend.  If PENGU price manages a clean breakout above $0.037, $0.039, and then $0.042 (the 0.5 Fib zone), it opens the path to $0.045 first, a 25% surge. If that breaks, the next key resistance point, or rather target, would be $0.050, the 0.786 Fibonacci level. That would be a 38% rally from current prices around $0.036. Validation for this move comes from declining bear power, building short positions, and strong chart structure. The bullish trend would get invalidated if PENGU breaks the $0.035 resistance-turned-support. Or if it continues to drop to touch the retracement zone of the Fibonacci extension: the $0.028 mark.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947763664618803200</link>
      <description>2 hours agobeincryptoPENGU Could Rally 38% if One Key Price Resistance BreaksAfter a strong 26% gain over the past week, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) is now hovering just below a crucial resistance level. While much of the altcoin market cools down, PENGU price looks poised to break out. Only if it can pu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947763664618803200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orphanage in Uganda That Runs on Bitcoin Celebrated Bitcoin Pizza Day with a Road TripOn May 22, 2025, children from the Orphans of Uganda Children’s Center, an orphanage in eastern Uganda that’s part of the Bitcoin Kampala community, took a road trip to the zoo thanks in part to bitcoin donations from around the world. The team that helps fund and run the the orphanage chose to take the trip on Bitcoin Pizza Day to show the orphans, many of whom had never left the village in which the orphanage is located, that anything is possible, much like Laszlo Hanyecz showed the world that paying for goods and services in bitcoin is possible when he paid 10,000 bitcoin for two pizzas on May 22, 2010. 22•05•2025 – Orphanage Bitcoin Pizza Day 😇 We dreamt to leave our district on a bus to the zoo at the end of last year, you all made it happen…. Special Thanks to @blinkbtc , @studentofbtc , @travelwbitcoin who sponsored us for the day And our forever patrons @Bitcoinbeach ,… pic.twitter.com/Ol6XC52bcv “We organized this trip to give the children hope and to open their minds to what’s possible,” Brindon Mwiine, founder of Bitcoin Kampala, told Bitcoin Magazine. “Last year, we started teaching them to write down their dreams in notebooks we gave them, and when we asked what they wished for at Christmas, their answers were simple: visit the capital, see animals, and travel,” he added. “Bitcoin Pizza Day at the Entebbe Zoo became the perfect way to bring those dreams to life while teaching them about Bitcoin.” Mwiine also noted that this was the first time the children had taken an extended bus ride, crossed the Nile, traveled through the capital city of Kampala, explored a zoo — and tasted pizza. “It was a day of firsts,” said Mwiine, who added that it was all the more special because he, the support staff and the children “experienced it all together as a family.” Edith Mpumwire, a member of Blink Wallet’s marketing team and someone who works with the Bitcoin Kampala team, seconded what Mwiine said. “This trip is the first of its kind [for these children],” said Mpumwire in the video embedded in the X post above. “Most of these children are from eastern Uganda [and] they stay in a small house located in Bugiri. They have never left Bugiri, so, for them, today is the first day to not only visit the zoo, but to leave their enclosure,” she added. Mpumwire also noted how the international Bitcoin community is partially to thank for enabling the orphans to take this trip. “The global [Bitcoin] community contributes to their livelihood [and] here we are taking them on a road trip [where] they get to see a mini national park, Lake Victoria and very many animals.” You can contribute to the Orphans of Uganda Children’s Center via the project’s Geyser page.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947764719289126912</link>
      <description>2 hours agobitcoinmagazineOrphanage in Uganda That Runs on Bitcoin Celebrated Bitcoin Pizza Day with a Road TripOn May 22, 2025, children from the Orphans of Uganda Children’s Center, an orphanage in eastern Uganda that’s part of the Bitcoin Kampala community, took a road trip to the zoo thanks in p</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947764719289126912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citadel calls on SEC to strictly regulate tokenized stocks, opposes exemptive treatmentThis week, market-making giant Citadel Securities sent a letter to the U.S. SEC&apos;s Crypto Assets Working Group, opposing granting exemptive treatment to tokenized equities, saying that doing so could cause liquidity to flow out of traditional markets and cause investors to be confused about asset issuers. Citadel said that tokenized equities should follow the same regulatory rules as traditional securities, and that the SEC should advance relevant policies through roundtables and formal rulemaking, rather than circumventing existing regulations through &quot;innovation exceptions.&quot; [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947765365081919488</link>
      <description>3 hours ago吴说Citadel calls on SEC to strictly regulate tokenized stocks, opposes exemptive treatmentThis week, market-making giant Citadel Securities sent a letter to the U.S. SEC&apos;s Crypto Assets Working Group, opposing granting exemptive treatment to tokenized equities, saying that doing so could c</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947765365081919488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KindlyMD and Nakamoto Holdings File with SEC, Merger Expected to Close August 11Today, KindlyMD (NASDAQ: NAKA) and Bitcoin-native firm Nakamoto Holdings announced that it has officially filed their definitive information statement with the SEC in connection with the proposed merger with Nakamoto, moving forward with a planned merger expected to close around August 11, 2025. BREAKING: 🇺🇸 $763.00 million #Bitcoin treasury company Nakamoto files with SEC to merge with publicly traded KindlyMD. Expects to complete the merge in 20 days. pic.twitter.com/ejjMaoqI6k “Filing the definitive information statement is a critical milestone for this merger and accelerates our mission of acquiring one million Bitcoin,” stated the Founder and CEO of Nakamoto David Bailey. “I’m very proud of the teams’ collaboration at Nakamoto and KindlyMD to get us one step closer to closing the merger. Our shared enthusiasm for Bitcoin paired with our expertise in structuring this opportunity for public markets has created a strong foundation for the combined company’s future.” The merger is a key step in advancing Nakamoto’s strategy, which will use Bitcoin not only as a reserve asset but as the foundation of a new capital framework. Nakamoto will treat Bitcoin as the base and combine it with public stocks to grow and invest more effectively. This model supports smaller companies that hold Bitcoin in regions where direct access to it is limited. Firms like Metaplanet, Smarter Web Company, and The Blockchain Group have already shown strong results. Performance is measured by Bitcoin per share, with gains reinvested into more Bitcoin or new ventures. Nakamoto manages the 40 percent securities limit under the Investment Company Act by using Bitcoin-denominated convertible notes, giving it more flexibility and control. With over 750 million dollars raised, the merger with KindlyMD supports its goal of expanding a Bitcoin based financial model globally. “We are proud to reach this important milestone alongside Nakamoto,” said the Founder and CEO of KindlyMD Tim Pickett. “Our shareholders now have the opportunity to be part of a groundbreaking shift in how public companies approach treasury management, with Bitcoin at the center.” Disclosure: Nakamoto is in partnership with Bitcoin Magazine’s parent company BTC Inc to build the first global network of Bitcoin treasury companies, where BTC Inc provides certain marketing services to Nakamoto. More information on this can be found here.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947754372343812096</link>
      <description>3 hours agobitcoinmagazineKindlyMD and Nakamoto Holdings File with SEC, Merger Expected to Close August 11Today, KindlyMD (NASDAQ: NAKA) and Bitcoin-native firm Nakamoto Holdings announced that it has officially filed their definitive information statement with the SEC in connection with the propose</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947754372343812096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $120,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.68% in the past 1H, up 2.29% in the last 24H. Now at $120,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947732176492519424</link>
      <description>3 hours agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $120,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.68% in the past 1H, up 2.29% in the last 24H. Now at $120,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947732176492519424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Senate Republicans release draft bill for crypto market structureRepublican leaders on the Senate Banking Committee said the legislation “built on” the CLARITY Act passed in the House of Representatives last week.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947724867109670912</link>
      <description>4 hours agoPANewsUS Senate Republicans release draft bill for crypto market structureRepublican leaders on the Senate Banking Committee said the legislation “built on” the CLARITY Act passed in the House of Representatives last week.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947724867109670912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram launches non-custodial crypto app in USMessaging app Telegram has launched a new non-custodial crypto wallet in the United States through a partnership with MoonPay. The new feature will enable millions of users to send and manage crypto directly within the app.

Telegram previously launched a crypto wallet globally that was activated by more than 100 million users. Tuesday’s launch will enable users in the U.S. to send, receive, and manage cryptocurrency directly inside the app.

The wallet is built on The Open Platform, a.k.a. TOP, which is built on the TON blockchain. The feature allows users to transact with crypto as easily as sending a message. Telegram said that the wallet will be instantly installed and will not require a download.

The Open Platform recently raised a $28.5 million Series A at a $1 billion valuation.

Telegram infamously fought the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission in court after launching its TON token in 2019. After a protracted legal battle, Telegram agreed to return $1.2 billion to investors and pay an $18.5 million penalty to settle with the SEC.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947722467271528448</link>
      <description>4 hours agoThe BlockTelegram launches non-custodial crypto app in USMessaging app Telegram has launched a new non-custodial crypto wallet in the United States through a partnership with MoonPay. The new feature will enable millions of users to send and manage crypto directly within the app.

Telegra</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947722467271528448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevvStream pivots, anchors crypto treasury to BTC and SOLNasdaq-listed carbon management firm DevvStream unveiled Tuesday the initial composition of its digital asset treasury, naming Bitcoin, Solana and its own DevvE token as core holdings. The company also appointed BitGo as its qualified custodian and brought in FRNT Financial as a digital asset advisor, signaling a deliberate move to pair ESG mandates with programmable finance. DevvStream CEO Sunny Trinh said the company’s crypto treasury strategy is less about speculative upside and more about institutional-grade liquidity, ecosystem alignment, and real-world asset integration. “Our treasury model isn’t just about holding crypto. It’s about aligning capital with our mission,” Trinh said. “Our mix of assets is designed to deliver institutional-grade efficiency and income, while bridging to sustainability tokenization and real-world asset integration. Together, they position DevvStream at the intersection of liquidity, innovation, and impact.” Bitcoin (BTC), described by the company as the “foundational asset of the digital economy,” serves as the bedrock of its treasury, offering deep liquidity and institutional credibility. Unlike firms that treat BTC purely as a hedge, DevvStream appears to view it as an on-ramp for broader blockchain integration, ensuring stability while it experiments with more dynamic assets. Solana’s (SOL) inclusion is equally deliberate. The company cited SOL’s transaction speed and ecosystem depth as key factors, suggesting an intent to generate yield through staking or DeFi participation. This is a departure from passive Bitcoin holdings, aligning with a growing trend of corporations leveraging proof-of-stake networks for treasury management, where idle assets can earn returns without traditional market risks. But the most unconventional pick is DevvE, the company’s proprietary token. Unlike BTC and SOL, DevvE isn’t just a store of value or yield vehicle; it’s designed to facilitate what the firm calls “impact-layer tokenization,” linking digital finance directly to carbon offset projects and other sustainability initiatives. The company hasn’t disclosed exact allocation percentages.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947721623717302272</link>
      <description>4 hours agocrypto.newsDevvStream pivots, anchors crypto treasury to BTC and SOLNasdaq-listed carbon management firm DevvStream unveiled Tuesday the initial composition of its digital asset treasury, naming Bitcoin, Solana and its own DevvE token as core holdings. The company also appointed BitGo as</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947721623717302272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street is Warming Up to Rate Cuts—Will Crypto Be the Biggest Winner?Wall Street is increasingly betting on US interest rate cuts before the end of 2025. At the same time, political pressure from Donald Trump has intensified, as he becomes more vocally aggressive toward Powell for rate cuts.  With inflation cooling and markets adjusting expectations, crypto could stand to gain the most from a looser monetary policy. Trump Wants Fed to Bring Interest Rate Down to 1% Earlier today, Trump renewed his attack on Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. He called for a 3 percentage point rate cut and claimed it would save the US economy $1 trillion annually.  The US President also accused Powell of keeping rates high for “political reasons.” While the Fed has held rates steady at 4.25%–4.50% since June, speculation is rising. Goldman Sachs now expects the first cut to arrive in September.  Meanwhile, traders on prediction market Kalshi see a 40% chance of two cuts before year-end. This shift follows a steep drop in US inflation expectations . One-year consumer expectations fell to 4.4% in July, the lowest since February. That marks a 2.2 percentage point drop over just two months—one of the largest two-month declines in history. Longer-term inflation expectations are also easing. Five-year outlooks dropped 0.8 percentage points in the last quarter, now sitting at 3.6%.  Overall, these trends suggest the Fed has more room to ease without sparking fears of a price spiral. The crypto market is paying close attention. Bitcoin remains above $118,000 , while Ethereum holds near $3,700. Both assets have historically rallied after Fed rate cuts, benefiting from increased liquidity and investor risk appetite. Could a Major Crypto Bull Run Begin? Historically, rate cuts have kicked off strong crypto bull markets .  After the Fed slashed rates in March 2020 during the COVID-19 crisis, Bitcoin soared from under $10,000 to over $60,000 within a year. Ethereum followed, supported by DeFi and NFT growth. If a new rate cut cycle begins in September, it could bring similar conditions. Lower yields push investors toward risk-on assets, including crypto.  Capital could also rotate from bonds and cash into Bitcoin, Ethereum, and high-conviction altcoins. Additionally, falling inflation expectations and improving regulatory clarity—such as the GENIUS and CLARITY Acts —may reinforce investor confidence.  This convergence of macro and policy signals could extend the current cycle beyond previous all-time highs. However, timing matters. Crypto is already near record levels, so momentum may depend on how fast and deep the cuts are. A delayed or shallow response from the Fed could limit upside. Key Dates to Watch The next Federal Reserve policy meeting will take place on July 29–30 . While markets expect no change, Fed commentary will be closely parsed for signals about September. The next critical date is September 16–17 , when the FOMC reconvenes. This is widely seen as the first realistic window for a rate cut, especially if inflation continues to decline. Other key indicators to monitor: For crypto traders, these dates offer cues for potential market inflection points. A confirmed Fed pivot could trigger renewed buying pressure, particularly in Bitcoin, Ethereum, and high-liquidity altcoins.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947727172513058816</link>
      <description>4 hours agobeincryptoWall Street is Warming Up to Rate Cuts—Will Crypto Be the Biggest Winner?Wall Street is increasingly betting on US interest rate cuts before the end of 2025. At the same time, political pressure from Donald Trump has intensified, as he becomes more vocally aggressive toward Powe</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947727172513058816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiNFT index 24hr gain of 10.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has risen by 10.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU +21.28%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947731920098910208</link>
      <description>4 hours agoSSI Price BotssiNFT index 24hr gain of 10.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has risen by 10.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU +21.28%.$PENGUShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947731920098910208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF issuers file amendments for in-kind redemptions, signaling &apos;positive movement&apos; with SECSeveral ETF issuers filed amendments with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to permit in-kind creations and redemptions from their spot crypto funds, something one expert says indicates that there is positive momentum going on at the agency.

21Shares, Fidelity, Franklin Templeton, Galaxy, VanEck, and WisdomTree all submitted their amended proposals Tuesday morning seeking to make their spot Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds, as well as future crypto ETFs, more efficient.

&quot;More positive signs,&quot; Bloomberg Intelligence ETF analyst James Seyffart said in a post on X .&quot;This indicates to me that there is positive movement and likely fine tuning happening with the SEC.&quot;

These firms have been seeking in-kind redemptions for months, and SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce said last month that in-kind redemptions for crypto ETFs are &quot;on the horizon.&quot;

&quot;Those (forms) are going through the process now,&quot; Peirce said on June 25. &quot;So I think that&apos;s something that&apos;s certainly on the horizon at some point. I can&apos;t prejudge, but we hear that there&apos;s a lot of interest.&quot;

Seyffart clarified that this would only be for the &quot;authorized participants&quot; like major Wall Street firms and market makers — not retail traders — to trade in shares of their ETFs for the underlying asset.

&quot;[T]he vast majority of people won&apos;t even see a difference because the products on the market now already trade extremely efficiently,&quot; Seyffart said. &quot;This will treat crypto ETPs the same as other ETPs are treated.

Crypto ETF &quot;floodgates&quot; are poised to open as the SEC is also weighing a faster approval framework, The Block&apos;s Sarah Wynn previously reported. Following spot BTC ETFs (January 2024) and spot ETH ETFs (July 2024), there are now several dozen more crypto-related ETFs seeking approval. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710893240635392</link>
      <description>5 hours agoThe BlockBitcoin and Ethereum ETF issuers file amendments for in-kind redemptions, signaling &apos;positive movement&apos; with SECSeveral ETF issuers filed amendments with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to permit in-kind creations and redemptions from their spot crypto funds, somethin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710893240635392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle launches Circle Gateway, a new infrastructure for unified USDC cross-chain balancesAccording to official sources, Circle has released the Circle Gateway testnet, supporting Avalanche, Base, and the Ethereum mainnet, providing users with the ability to access USDC across chains in seconds. The mainnet version is coming soon and will continue to expand to more blockchains. Key highlights include: 1. &lt;500ms cross-chain access: No cross-chain bridge required, no pre-set assets required, quickly call unified USDC balance; 2. Efficient liquidity management: Meet multi-chain liquidity needs through a single integration, reducing capital occupation; 3. Non-custodial design: Users have complete control over USDC, funds can only be moved under signature authorization, and withdrawals do not require trusting a third party. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710508304191488</link>
      <description>5 hours agoOdailyCircle launches Circle Gateway, a new infrastructure for unified USDC cross-chain balancesAccording to official sources, Circle has released the Circle Gateway testnet, supporting Avalanche, Base, and the Ethereum mainnet, providing users with the ability to access USDC across chain</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 17:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947710508304191488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — ReportThe investigation was reportedly not connected to Jesse Powell’s activities within the crypto industry.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947695662019923968</link>
      <description>6 hours agoPANewsFBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — ReportThe investigation was reportedly not connected to Jesse Powell’s activities within the crypto industry.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947695662019923968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 22:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>