<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:42:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) raises over £100 million to promote AI and Bitcoin deploymentOn July 24, the listed company Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) announced that it had completed the fundraising of over £100 million of convertible bonds and started the third round of financing, with the minimum subscription threshold reduced to $100,000.00, which is expected to end on July 28. The funds will be used to expand the business and promote the construction of Bitcoin and decentralized AI infrastructure. CEO Henry Elder has officially joined the board of directors as executive director. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302120138117120</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsSatsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) raises over £100 million to promote AI and Bitcoin deploymentOn July 24, the listed company Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) announced that it had completed the fundraising of over £100 million of convertible bonds and started the third round of financing,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302120138117120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghana Plans to Issue Licenses to Cryptocurrency PlatformsAccording to Bloomberg, Ghana plans to issue licenses to cryptocurrency platforms as authorities seek to regulate cryptocurrency use while generating revenue. Millions of people in the West African nation already use cryptocurrencies. The Governor of the Bank of Ghana stated that the central bank is finalizing a regulatory framework and plans to submit it to Parliament for consideration in September. The proposed law will enable the country to fully utilize cryptocurrencies, promote cross-border trade, attract strategic investment, and collect financial data. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301655287599104</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsGhana Plans to Issue Licenses to Cryptocurrency PlatformsAccording to Bloomberg, Ghana plans to issue licenses to cryptocurrency platforms as authorities seek to regulate cryptocurrency use while generating revenue. Millions of people in the West African nation already use</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301655287599104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has launched U-margined perpetual contracts.On July 24, according to the official announcement, LBank has launched U-based perpetual contracts on July 24, 2025, at 14:30 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301297815457792</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoTechFlowLBank has launched U-margined perpetual contracts.On July 24, according to the official announcement, LBank has launched U-based perpetual contracts on July 24, 2025, at 14:30 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301297815457792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky Rune continues to use staking rewards to repurchase SKYOn July 24, according to Ember’s monitoring, Rune, the co-founder of Sky (formerly MakerDAO), is using SKY staking rewards for repurchase operations. Half an hour ago, he received staking rewards, including 1,900,000.00 USDS and 10,378,000.000 SPK (total value of about $1,300,000.00), and transferred them to the repurchase address. Currently, Rune is repurchasing SKY tokens by selling SPK. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948300610058653696</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsSky Rune continues to use staking rewards to repurchase SKYOn July 24, according to Ember’s monitoring, Rune, the co-founder of Sky (formerly MakerDAO), is using SKY staking rewards for repurchase operations. Half an hour ago, he received staking rewards, including 1,900,000.00 US</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948300610058653696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satsuma Completes Over $136.00M Private Placement to Accelerate its Bitcoin Funding StrategyUK-listed company Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) has announced the completion of a £100.00M ($136.00M) private placement to accelerate its Bitcoin funding strategy. In addition, the company will launch a short-term third round of financing, which will be limited to individual investors that the company identifies as key strategic qualified investors in the United States, with total financing expected to not exceed £10.00M, which is expected to be completed on or about July 28, 2025. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948300504802594816</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoForesightNewsSatsuma Completes Over $136.00M Private Placement to Accelerate its Bitcoin Funding StrategyUK-listed company Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) has announced the completion of a £100.00M ($136.00M) private placement to accelerate its Bitcoin funding strategy. In addition, the co</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948300504802594816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: The current Bitcoin RSI index is close to 75, and it is expected that the RSI will be greater than 80 for several months during the bull market.PlanB posted that Bitcoin&apos;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently close to 75. In this bull market, it is expected that the RSI will reach above 80 for several months, similar to the bull market performance in 2021, 2017, 2013, and 2011. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948299890806820864</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyAnalyst: The current Bitcoin RSI index is close to 75, and it is expected that the RSI will be greater than 80 for several months during the bull market.PlanB posted that Bitcoin&apos;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently close to 75. In this bull market, it is expected that th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948299890806820864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoPlus launches a 500 million GPS security fund, divided into a token-based reward pool and a token bounty pool.GoPlus announces the launch of a 500 million GPS Security Fund (currently valued at approximately $10.00M USD). There are two ways for users to participate in the fund distribution: users who stake GPS can receive triple benefits (basic annualized + security incident lottery + GoPlus security ecosystem income repurchase); participate in the &quot;Security Bounty List&quot; to participate in obtaining a 100.00M GPS special bounty pool, for example: submit a malicious address / phishing website, with a maximum prize of 10,000 GPS. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948297740588486656</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoForesightNewsGoPlus launches a 500 million GPS security fund, divided into a token-based reward pool and a token bounty pool.GoPlus announces the launch of a 500 million GPS Security Fund (currently valued at approximately $10.00M USD). There are two ways for users to participate in th</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948297740588486656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with App versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function starting July 28Binance Chinese announced, &quot;Starting July 28th, users of the Binance App with versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function. Please upgrade to the latest version in time to ensure normal use.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948296410767626240</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoForesightNewsBinance: Users with App versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function starting July 28Binance Chinese announced, &quot;Starting July 28th, users of the Binance App with versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check func</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948296410767626240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6% in pre-market trading, with Musk saying Tesla may face some difficult quarters.On July 24, according to data from Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network, Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6.00% in pre-market trading. Tesla&apos;s total revenue for the second quarter decreased by 12.00% year-on-year to $22.50B, and Musk said that Tesla may face several difficult quarters next. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294093439832064</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoTechFlowTesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6% in pre-market trading, with Musk saying Tesla may face some difficult quarters.On July 24, according to data from Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network, Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6.00% in pre-market trading. Tesla&apos;s total revenue for the second quarter</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294093439832064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Meme tokens listed on JuCoin chain, expanding the JuCoin Preferred Zone lineupOn July 24, 2025, according to official sources, JuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection Preferred Zone officially launched three popular Memes: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, which are now fully open for trading. Users can enter through the &quot;Trading&quot; - &quot;On-chain Trading&quot; section on the JuCoin App or homepage. It is reported that memecoin emphasizes the community-driven pure Meme spirit; PYTHIA represents a pioneering experiment in the integration of AI and biotechnology; AOL Coin pays tribute to the America Online cultural heritage. This launch will further enrich the JuCoin on-chain ecosystem and meet users&apos; diversified asset allocation needs. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294852696936448</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoOdailyThree Meme tokens listed on JuCoin chain, expanding the JuCoin Preferred Zone lineupOn July 24, 2025, according to official sources, JuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection Preferred Zone officially launched three popular Memes: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, which are now fully open for</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294852696936448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huang Licheng closed his position of 1,229 ETH and lost $80,000. The long positions of ETH, PUMP and HYPE still had a floating loss of about $8.711 million.On July 24, according to Ai Yi’s monitoring, Huang Licheng closed 1,229 ETH positions in the past hour, with a loss of about $80,000. Currently, his long positions in ETH, PUMP and HYPE still have a floating loss of about $8.711 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948293552563359744</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoPANewsHuang Licheng closed his position of 1,229 ETH and lost $80,000. The long positions of ETH, PUMP and HYPE still had a floating loss of about $8.711 million.On July 24, according to Ai Yi’s monitoring, Huang Licheng closed 1,229 ETH positions in the past hour, with a loss of about</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948293552563359744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; has lost over $8.71M on Hyperliquid due to long positions.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi, &quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; closed 1,229 ETH in the past 1 hour and lost $80,000.00, and the remaining ETH, PUMP, and HYPE long positions are still at a floating loss of $8,711,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294861144264704</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdaily&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; has lost over $8.71M on Hyperliquid due to long positions.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi, &quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; closed 1,229 ETH in the past 1 hour and lost $80,000.00, and the remaining ETH, PUMP, and HYPE long positions are still at a floating loss of $8,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294861144264704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast at 8 PM today: How to Learn and Earn through BlumHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast today at 20:00, with the theme &quot;How to Learn and Earn through Blum.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292101573251072</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast at 8 PM today: How to Learn and Earn through BlumHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast today at 20:00, with the theme &quot;How to Learn and Earn through Blum.&quot;$BLUM$HTXShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292101573251072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT platform Pixel Vault may cease operationsAccording to the official announcement, NFT platform Pixel Vault announced that after more than four years of development, the company has begun the process of potentially ceasing operations. The company had attempted to create a profitable and sustainable crypto entertainment business, but was unsuccessful. Currently, Pixel Vault is in discussions with multiple parties regarding the possibility of acquiring the company and its assets in order to continue serving the community. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948291599938686976</link>
      <description>43 minutes ago吴说NFT platform Pixel Vault may cease operationsAccording to the official announcement, NFT platform Pixel Vault announced that after more than four years of development, the company has begun the process of potentially ceasing operations. The company had attempted to create a profitabl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948291599938686976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to 637,500.00.According to the latest information from the validatorqueue website, the number of ETH waiting to be unstaked has increased to 637,450, with net redemptions reaching 316,000. The waiting queue length is 11 days and 2 hours, a record high. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292338601758720</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoOdailyThe number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to 637,500.00.According to the latest information from the validatorqueue website, the number of ETH waiting to be unstaked has increased to 637,450, with net redemptions reaching 316,000. The waiting queue length is 11 days an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292338601758720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch BNKR spot trading
According to official news on July 24, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs


BNKR/USDT (July 24, 17:00 UTC+8): $BNKR is the native token of the Bankr project. Bankr is an advanced AI agent that can help you with swaps, research, and more.


 [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289446029365248</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch BNKR spot trading
According to official news on July 24, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs


BNKR/USDT (July 24, 17:00 UTC+8): $BNKR is the native token of the Bankr project. Bankr is</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289446029365248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT: Ripple co-founder-linked address transferred 50,000,000 XRP, approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchangesAccording to on-chain detective ZachXBT, starting on July 17, 2025, wallet addresses associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen transferred 50,000,000 XRP (approximately $175,000,000.00) to four addresses, of which approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchanges or related service platforms. Some of the funds also flowed into two new addresses, each receiving 5,000,000 XRP. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289501415149568</link>
      <description>52 minutes ago吴说ZachXBT: Ripple co-founder-linked address transferred 50,000,000 XRP, approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchangesAccording to on-chain detective ZachXBT, starting on July 17, 2025, wallet addresses associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen transferred 50,000,000 XRP (app</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289501415149568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet has now added a new encrypted payment channel, supporting mainstream consumer platforms including Hema, Honor of Kings, Sinopec, and JD.com.Bitget Wallet has announced the addition of cryptocurrency payment functionality for a variety of everyday consumption scenarios, covering e-commerce shopping, digital entertainment, game top-ups, global travel, and other areas, allowing users to complete one-stop consumption using crypto assets within the wallet. Currently, the platforms and services supported by this function include Sinopec, Suning.com, JD.com, Hema, Tmall Supermarket, Honor of Kings, Steam, and mobile phone top-ups, among others. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289826477903872</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet has now added a new encrypted payment channel, supporting mainstream consumer platforms including Hema, Honor of Kings, Sinopec, and JD.com.Bitget Wallet has announced the addition of cryptocurrency payment functionality for a variety of everyday consumption scenari</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289826477903872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amended class action calls Pump.fun a ‘slot machine cabinet’ in $5.5B caseAn amended lawsuit accuses Pump.fun and key Solana partners of operating an unlicensed digital casino that funneled billions through deceptive memecoin schemes.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288055307210752</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoPANewsAmended class action calls Pump.fun a ‘slot machine cabinet’ in $5.5B caseAn amended lawsuit accuses Pump.fun and key Solana partners of operating an unlicensed digital casino that funneled billions through deceptive memecoin schemes.#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288055307210752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Congress to Advance Veterans Affairs Blockchain Pilot BillThe U.S. Congress is considering the &quot;Department of Veterans Affairs Distributed Ledger Technology Innovation Act of 2025&quot; (H.R. 3455), which aims to promote the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) to study the application of blockchain technology in the claims process to improve transparency, traceability, and reduce the risk of fraud and abuse. The bill passed a hearing by the House Veterans Affairs Subcommittee on June 11 and is awaiting a full House vote. If passed, the VA will submit a feasibility study and pilot recommendation report within one year. [CryptoSlate]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288300611080192</link>
      <description>58 minutes ago吴说US Congress to Advance Veterans Affairs Blockchain Pilot BillThe U.S. Congress is considering the &quot;Department of Veterans Affairs Distributed Ledger Technology Innovation Act of 2025&quot; (H.R. 3455), which aims to promote the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) to study the application</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288300611080192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 08:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>