<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:55:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold hits $3,420.00On July 22, spot gold continued to climb, reaching $3,420.00 per ounce, its highest level since June 16, and up 0.68% on the day. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947656541276753920</link>
      <description>58seconds agoPANewsSpot gold hits $3,420.00On July 22, spot gold continued to climb, reaching $3,420.00 per ounce, its highest level since June 16, and up 0.68% on the day. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947656541276753920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Senate Republicans Release Draft Crypto Market Structure Bill, Advancing Regulatory ClaritySenator Tim Scott, along with Cynthia Lummis and others, has released a draft regulatory bill for the crypto market, intending to build upon the &quot;Clarity for Digital Assets Act&quot; (the &quot;CLARITY Act&quot;) passed in the House of Representatives. The draft requires the SEC to adjust regulatory rules based on the characteristics of crypto assets and defines &quot;ancillary assets&quot; to clarify the scope of non-security digital assets, with the goal of forming a legislative consensus by September 30. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947655639887269888</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoOdailyUS Senate Republicans Release Draft Crypto Market Structure Bill, Advancing Regulatory ClaritySenator Tim Scott, along with Cynthia Lummis and others, has released a draft regulatory bill for the crypto market, intending to build upon the &quot;Clarity for Digital Assets Act&quot; (the &quot;CLA</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947655639887269888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius Group&apos;s Bitcoin holdings have increased to 200On July 22, according to Cointelegraph, Genius Group has doubled its Bitcoin holdings to 200, and plans to increase it to 1,000 by the end of 2025, with a goal of holding 10,000 Bitcoins in the next two years. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947654858039644160</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsGenius Group&apos;s Bitcoin holdings have increased to 200On July 22, according to Cointelegraph, Genius Group has doubled its Bitcoin holdings to 200, and plans to increase it to 1,000 by the end of 2025, with a goal of holding 10,000 Bitcoins in the next two years. [PANews]#Bitcoin$B</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947654858039644160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale once again transferred more than 314 BTC to Coinbase, with a total value of more than $37.5 million.On July 22, on-chain data showed that at 21:18 Beijing time, Grayscale’s two Bitcoin Trust addresses transferred 235.99 and 78.66 BTC to Coinbase Prime respectively, totaling 314.65 BTC, equivalent to approximately US$37.57 million at the current price. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653594174214144</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsGrayscale once again transferred more than 314 BTC to Coinbase, with a total value of more than $37.5 million.On July 22, on-chain data showed that at 21:18 Beijing time, Grayscale’s two Bitcoin Trust addresses transferred 235.99 and 78.66 BTC to Coinbase Prime respectively, tota</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653594174214144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui ecosystem parallel multi-party computation network Ika will launch its mainnet on July 29.Ika, the Sui ecosystem&apos;s parallel multi-party computation (MPC) network, announced on X that it will launch its mainnet on July 29. In April of this year, Ika announced a strategic investment from the Sui Foundation, bringing its total funding to over $21.00 million. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653240359505920</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoForesightNewsSui ecosystem parallel multi-party computation network Ika will launch its mainnet on July 29.Ika, the Sui ecosystem&apos;s parallel multi-party computation (MPC) network, announced on X that it will launch its mainnet on July 29. In April of this year, Ika announced a strategi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653240359505920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CertiK releases Skynet stablecoin rating report: USDT, USDC, PYUSD, RLUSD lead the packOn July 22, according to the Skynet Stablecoin Panorama Report for the First Half of 2025 released by Web3 security company CertiK, the total global stablecoin supply has exceeded US$250 billion, with a monthly settlement volume of US$1.4 trillion. USDT, USDC, PYUSD, and RLUSD lead in security, market performance, and compliance. The report pointed out that industry risks are shifting from contract vulnerabilities to centralized platform operational errors, and RWA-supported and yield-based stablecoins are developing rapidly, and are expected to account for 8%-10% of the market by the end of the year. The report emphasizes that transparent compliance and risk control will determine the long-term sustainability of the project. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947652124481703936</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoPANewsCertiK releases Skynet stablecoin rating report: USDT, USDC, PYUSD, RLUSD lead the packOn July 22, according to the Skynet Stablecoin Panorama Report for the First Half of 2025 released by Web3 security company CertiK, the total global stablecoin supply has exceeded US$250 billio</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947652124481703936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy has realized 93,191 Bitcoin in book profits this year, worth $11.1 billion.MicroStrategy founder and Executive Chairman Michael Saylor revealed in a post on the X platform that MSTR has generated a book profit of 93,191 Bitcoins so far this year, worth approximately $11.10B. In the first three weeks of July alone, the company realized a book profit of 5,668 Bitcoins, worth $676.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653141197770752</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoOdailyStrategy has realized 93,191 Bitcoin in book profits this year, worth $11.1 billion.MicroStrategy founder and Executive Chairman Michael Saylor revealed in a post on the X platform that MSTR has generated a book profit of 93,191 Bitcoins so far this year, worth approximately $11.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653141197770752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Beast has deactivated its X accountCrypto Beast (@cryptobeastreal) has deactivated its X account. Prior to this, ZachXBT accused Crypto Beast of manipulating the ALT crash, with associated wallets cashing out over $11.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653149691236352</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoOdailyCrypto Beast has deactivated its X accountCrypto Beast (@cryptobeastreal) has deactivated its X account. Prior to this, ZachXBT accused Crypto Beast of manipulating the ALT crash, with associated wallets cashing out over $11.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily]$ALTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653149691236352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks open, Dow down 0.08%, S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, Nasdaq up 0.03%On July 22nd, according to Jinshi Data, the US stock market opened with the Dow down 0.08%, the S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, and the Nasdaq up 0.03%. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947650843964887040</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoTechFlowUS stocks open, Dow down 0.08%, S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, Nasdaq up 0.03%On July 22nd, according to Jinshi Data, the US stock market opened with the Dow down 0.08%, the S&amp;P 500 up 0.01%, and the Nasdaq up 0.03%. [Techflow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947650843964887040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana validator Somos Axolotl launches Web3-powered conservation in Mexico CityA nonprofit called Somos Axolotl has launched a conservation effort that taps into the Solana community. Crypto ecosystem has a long history of charitable and conservation aims. One such project, Solana (SOL) validator Somos Axolotl, has recently started a conservation initiative in Mexico City, aimed at protecting the endangered Axolotl. Centered around the historic area of Xochimilco, the project combines public sculpture, conservation, and community outreach with the crypto community. Its goal is to restore the habitat for the iconic, but endangered, Axolotl amphibian in the Xochimilco canal system. The project will also use its funds to promote regenerative agriculture for local residents and promote economic opportunity. What is more, all of the funds for the project will come from operating a Solana validator node. Supporters among Solana holders can help the project by staking their SOL with the Somos Axolotl validators. They receive staking rewards, just as with any validator, while also contributing to Axolotl conservation. Notably, Somos Axolotl is currently the only non-profit validator on the Solana blockchain. Interestingly, Solana validator nodes offer a unique opportunity for non-profit groups. Specifically, running validator nodes has high fixed costs of operation. However, once the node is set up, it is very scalable, meaning that it can service a large number of stakers. At the same time, revenues for a validator increase linearly with the amount of SOL staked with them. This means that a large validator can operate at high profit margins, while offering the same service as smaller ones. For this reason, if a validator manages to attract users through a charitable or conservation initiative, it gains a competitive edge against for-profit validators. For this reason, it is possible that more and more non-profits will join the Solana ecosystem, helping secure its network and making it more decentralized.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947647620927475712</link>
      <description>36 minutes agocrypto.newsSolana validator Somos Axolotl launches Web3-powered conservation in Mexico CityA nonprofit called Somos Axolotl has launched a conservation effort that taps into the Solana community. Crypto ecosystem has a long history of charitable and conservation aims. One such project,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947647620927475712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western Union plans to integrate stablecoin services and explore cooperation with the crypto industry.According to Cointelegraph, the CEO of Western Union said in an interview with Bloomberg that the company is actively exploring the use of stablecoins for cross-border payments, exchanges, and digital wallets, and sees it as an innovative opportunity. The company has tested related settlement processes in Africa and South America and is seeking to partner with crypto companies to provide stablecoin deposit and withdrawal services. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947650432835014656</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsWestern Union plans to integrate stablecoin services and explore cooperation with the crypto industry.According to Cointelegraph, the CEO of Western Union said in an interview with Bloomberg that the company is actively exploring the use of stablecoins for cross-border pay</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947650432835014656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram Crypto Wallet Now Available to 87.00 Million US UsersAccording to CNBC, US users can now send, receive, and manage cryptocurrencies directly within the Telegram app, without the need for additional downloads, browser plugins, or separate logins. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653455380500480</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoForesightNewsTelegram Crypto Wallet Now Available to 87.00 Million US UsersAccording to CNBC, US users can now send, receive, and manage cryptocurrencies directly within the Telegram app, without the need for additional downloads, browser plugins, or separate logins. [Foresight News]Sh</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947653455380500480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell said nothing about monetary policy in his latest meeting speechFederal Reserve Chairman Powell delivered a welcome speech at a regulatory conference today, but as expected, he did not make any controversial or news-making remarks. Powell did not give any monetary policy hints in his brief pre-prepared speech, nor did he mention the pressure from the Trump administration. This is not surprising, as Federal Reserve officials are in a &quot;quiet period&quot; before the July 29-30 meeting and are not allowed to make public comments on interest rates and the economy. However, he said he welcomed comments on bank regulatory rules and capital issues. &quot;The Federal Reserve is a dynamic institution,&quot; Powell said. &quot;We are willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework for large banks, and I look forward to hearing from today&apos;s participants.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947644441078812672</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoPANewsPowell said nothing about monetary policy in his latest meeting speechFederal Reserve Chairman Powell delivered a welcome speech at a regulatory conference today, but as expected, he did not make any controversial or news-making remarks. Powell did not give any monetary policy hi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947644441078812672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soluna Holdings Completes $20 Million Financing to Advance Green Data Center Project in Kati, TexasOn July 22, according to Business Wire, Soluna Holdings, a Nasdaq-listed company that develops green data centers for intensive computing applications such as Bitcoin mining and artificial intelligence, announced the completion of a new round of financing of US$20.00 million, with Spring Lane Capital participating. The new funds will be used to expand the Kati green data center project in Texas and further expand its Bitcoin hosting business. The project is scheduled to start construction in the third quarter of 2025 and achieve initial power supply and business start-up in the first quarter of 2026. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947642389548257280</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoPANewsSoluna Holdings Completes $20 Million Financing to Advance Green Data Center Project in Kati, TexasOn July 22, according to Business Wire, Soluna Holdings, a Nasdaq-listed company that develops green data centers for intensive computing applications such as Bitcoin mining and art</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947642389548257280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Customs Detects HK$1.15 Billion Money Laundering Case Involving Virtual Assets and Cash SmugglingAccording to Sing Tao Daily, Hong Kong Customs has cracked a suspected money laundering case involving approximately HK$1.15B through cash smuggling and virtual assets, arresting a 37-year-old local man and a 50-year-old non-local man. Customs stated that the two are suspected of smuggling cash out of the country and frequently using funds of unknown origin to conduct large stablecoin and fiat currency transactions, with the amounts inconsistent with their financial situation. Customs raided multiple locations today, seizing items such as phones and bank cards, and arrested the two under the Organized and Serious Crimes Ordinance. The case is still under investigation. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947639528273760256</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Hong Kong Customs Detects HK$1.15 Billion Money Laundering Case Involving Virtual Assets and Cash SmugglingAccording to Sing Tao Daily, Hong Kong Customs has cracked a suspected money laundering case involving approximately HK$1.15B through cash smuggling and virtual assets, arresting a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947639528273760256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessant: There is no reason to let Powell step down as Fed chairmanOn July 22, U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson publicly supported Federal Reserve Chairman Powell amid frequent attacks from Trump administration officials, saying he saw no reason to let him step down at this time. &quot;There is no indication that he should resign now, and his term will end in May next year,&quot; Benson said in an interview with Fox Business Channel on Tuesday. &quot;If he wants to stick to it, I think he should do it. If he wants to leave early, I think he can.&quot; For months, Powell has been criticized by Trump because he led the Federal Reserve to keep interest rates unchanged, worried about the inflationary impact of the government&apos;s tariff hikes. This month, some Republicans also raised objections to Bernanke over a costly plan to renovate the Federal Reserve building. On Monday, Benson called for an internal review of the Fed&apos;s non-monetary activities, including renovation projects. &quot;There is a real opportunity for him now, and that&apos;s where his legacy lies - to rationalize the Fed&apos;s non-monetary policy functions,&quot; Benson said. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947637767181979648</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBessant: There is no reason to let Powell step down as Fed chairmanOn July 22, U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson publicly supported Federal Reserve Chairman Powell amid frequent attacks from Trump administration officials, saying he saw no reason to let him step down at this time. &quot;Ther</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947637767181979648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Will List Alliance Games (COA) for Spot TradingBitget will list Alliance Games (COA) in the Innovation Zone and GameFi Zone. The deposit channel is now open, and the trading channel will open on July 23, 18:00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947639071937679360</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitget Will List Alliance Games (COA) for Spot TradingBitget will list Alliance Games (COA) in the Innovation Zone and GameFi Zone. The deposit channel is now open, and the trading channel will open on July 23, 18:00. [Foresight News]#GameFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947639071937679360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: The Fed is willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework for large banksFederal Reserve Chairman Powell: The Federal Reserve is a dynamic institution that is willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework for large banks. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947638029292425216</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyPowell: The Fed is willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework for large banksFederal Reserve Chairman Powell: The Federal Reserve is a dynamic institution that is willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framew</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947638029292425216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citadel Securities Warns SEC Not to Rush Tokenized Securities RulesCitadel Securities has sent a letter to the SEC&apos;s crypto task force, warning that advancing tokenized securities in the absence of a clear regulatory framework could disrupt the market, mislead investors, and weaken the liquidity of traditional stock markets. The company is calling for financial innovation to be promoted through formal legislative processes and opposes regulatory arbitrage. (CoinDesk) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947638037773307904</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyCitadel Securities Warns SEC Not to Rush Tokenized Securities RulesCitadel Securities has sent a letter to the SEC&apos;s crypto task force, warning that advancing tokenized securities in the absence of a clear regulatory framework could disrupt the market, mislead investors, and weaken t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947638037773307904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>coindesk</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic opens first season airdrop claim, users can now claim 25% shareSonic has announced the official launch of its Season 1 airdrop, where users can now claim 25% of their allocated share. The remaining 75% will be released linearly in NFT form and gradually opened via the PaintSwap order book. The official announcement clarifies that this airdrop is based on the Sonic mainnet whitelist event and is not related to pre-sales or TGE. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947635517567029248</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySonic opens first season airdrop claim, users can now claim 25% shareSonic has announced the official launch of its Season 1 airdrop, where users can now claim 25% of their allocated share. The remaining 75% will be released linearly in NFT form and gradually opened via the PaintSwap</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947635517567029248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>