<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:54:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Bessent: If inflation data is low, interest rates should be loweredJuly 21st, according to Jinshi Data, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent stated that if inflation data is low, interest rates should be lowered. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263807017734144</link>
      <description>36seconds agoTechFlowTreasury Secretary Bessent: If inflation data is low, interest rates should be loweredJuly 21st, according to Jinshi Data, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent stated that if inflation data is low, interest rates should be lowered. [TechFlow]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263807017734144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Announces the Latest List of BNB Hack Winners on July 21BNB Chain has announced the latest list of BNB Hack winners on July 21, with a total of 3 winning projects and 2 projects receiving honorable mentions, focusing on AI, DeSoc, DeSci, and DePIN. The new batch covers more than 30 submissions from June 23 to July 17, and the winning projects include the web social layer Basement, the DeFi assistant DeFi Copilot, and the strategy platform Bibim. The nominated projects are the cross-chain platform Peridot and the AI trading assistant Agent Einstein.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263690487386112</link>
      <description>1 minute ago吴说BNB Chain Announces the Latest List of BNB Hack Winners on July 21BNB Chain has announced the latest list of BNB Hack winners on July 21, with a total of 3 winning projects and 2 projects receiving honorable mentions, focusing on AI, DeSoc, DeSci, and DePIN. The new batch covers more t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263690487386112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTCS discloses that the company&apos;s ETH and cash market value reached US$242.00 millionAccording to GlobeNewswire, blockchain technology company BTCS Inc. (NASDAQ: BTCS) announced that as of now, the total market value of its 55,788 Ethereum (ETH), cash and other liquid assets is approximately US$242.00 million (based on an ETH price of US$3,600.00). In addition, BTCS has agreed to issue approximately US$10.00 million in convertible notes at a price of US$13.00 per share, a 198.00% premium to the closing price on July 18. The company has raised a total of US$189.00 million through its DeFi/TradFi Accretion Flywheel strategy this year, and plans to continue to expand its ETH holdings through decentralized and traditional financial instruments to enhance shareholder value. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263401428537344</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoPANewsBTCS discloses that the company&apos;s ETH and cash market value reached US$242.00 millionAccording to GlobeNewswire, blockchain technology company BTCS Inc. (NASDAQ: BTCS) announced that as of now, the total market value of its 55,788 Ethereum (ETH), cash and other liquid assets is ap</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263401428537344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selini Capital withdrew 8.273M USDC from HyperliquidAccording to Arkham monitoring, Selini Capital: 0xfF…463C withdrew 8.273 million USDC from Hyperliquid at 17:49. HypurrScan data shows that Selini Capital has cumulatively earned $9.62 million in profits trading on Hyperliquid, including $2.305 million in contract profits. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263462241751040</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoForesightNewsSelini Capital withdrew 8.273M USDC from HyperliquidAccording to Arkham monitoring, Selini Capital: 0xfF…463C withdrew 8.273 million USDC from Hyperliquid at 17:49. HypurrScan data shows that Selini Capital has cumulatively earned $9.62 million in profits trading on Hyperli</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263462241751040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale that has held BTC for 12 years transferred 250 BTC to Binance today and still holds 4,000 BTC.According to @EmberCN monitoring, a BTC whale holding for 12 years transferred 250 BTC (approximately $29.68M) to Binance today. This address first accumulated 5,000 BTC in November 2013 at a price of $332 per coin, and began selling them successively in November 2024. To date, 1,000 coins have been sold at an average price of $102,410. It currently still holds 4,000 BTC, worth approximately $474.00M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263325696184320</link>
      <description>3 minutes ago吴说A whale that has held BTC for 12 years transferred 250 BTC to Binance today and still holds 4,000 BTC.According to @EmberCN monitoring, a BTC whale holding for 12 years transferred 250 BTC (approximately $29.68M) to Binance today. This address first accumulated 5,000 BTC in November 2</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263325696184320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Hack Announces Latest Round of Winning Projects: Basement, DeFi Copilot, BIBIMBNB Chain has announced the latest batch (6/23–7/17) of BNB Hack selection results. Social protocol Basement (DeSoc direction), AI-powered DeFi assistant DeFi Copilot, and strategy tool BIBIM (AI direction) have successfully received awards, each receiving a 3,000.00 USDT prize, a 50,000 Kickstart reward package, and an official Demo Day presentation opportunity. At the same time, AI-oriented Peridot and Agent Einstein have been added to the incubation observation list.
This round received over 30 submissions from global developers, including those from the New York offline event:
Basement: Provides an instant social layer for web pages, combined with AI Agent, to achieve one-click chat, interaction, rewards, and information aggregation;
DeFi Copilot: A one-stop PancakeSwap trading assistant that integrates real-time analysis, one-click order placement, and automatic management;
BIBIM: Simplifies strategy construction, testing, and monetization with a visual interface and AI, reducing DeFi complexity;
BNB Hack is a long-term hackathon launched by BNB Chain targeting Web3 innovation directions such as AI, DeSoc, DeSci, and DePIN. It has currently received over 200 global submissions and has cumulatively selected 9 Tier 3 projects and 40 potential projects. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263067935232000</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoOdailyBNB Hack Announces Latest Round of Winning Projects: Basement, DeFi Copilot, BIBIMBNB Chain has announced the latest batch (6/23–7/17) of BNB Hack selection results. Social protocol Basement (DeSoc direction), AI-powered DeFi assistant DeFi Copilot, and strategy tool BIBIM (AI dir</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263067935232000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: 66% of USDt on-chain transfers come from West Asia, the Middle East and AfricaOn July 21, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino tweeted that USDt is growing rapidly around the world, especially in emerging markets. In the first half of 2025, USDt on-chain transfers increased by 120% compared to the full year of 2024, of which 66% of the transfers came from West Asia, the Middle East and Africa. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947260928064245760</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsTether CEO: 66% of USDt on-chain transfers come from West Asia, the Middle East and AfricaOn July 21, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino tweeted that USDt is growing rapidly around the world, especially in emerging markets. In the first half of 2025, USDt on-chain transfers increased by 12</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947260928064245760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet to Launch Exclusive Booster Event for Treehouse (TREE)According to the official announcement, Binance Wallet will launch an exclusive Booster event for Treehouse (TREE).

Event time: July 22, 2025 08:00:00 to July 29, 2025 07:59:59 (UTC+8)
Total reward: $750,000.00 equivalent in TREE tokens
Reward distribution: 2,500,000.00 TREE will be distributed on the day of the token generation event, and the remaining tokens will be distributed on the second day of trading.
Participation conditions: Participants must hold a Binance non-custodial wallet that has been backed up. There are no Binance Alpha point requirements for this event.

Activity 1: Stake at least 0.01 ETH into the Simple Yield Treehouse ETH pool to equally share $200,000.00 worth of TREE tokens.
During the event period, users who are eligible and stake at least 0.01 ETH into the Binance Wallet Simple Yield Treehouse ETH pool will be able to equally share $200,000.00 worth of TREE.

Activity 2: Stake at least 0.01 ETH into the Simple Yield Treehouse ETH pool to share $550,000.00 worth of TREE tokens.
During the event period, all eligible users who stake at least 0.01 ETH into the Binance Wallet Simple Yield Treehouse ETH pool will be able to share an annualized yield increase reward of $550,000.00 worth of TREE tokens, with a daily prize pool of $78,571.00 worth of TREE. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947260545799573504</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyBinance Wallet to Launch Exclusive Booster Event for Treehouse (TREE)According to the official announcement, Binance Wallet will launch an exclusive Booster event for Treehouse (TREE).

Event time: July 22, 2025 08:00:00 to July 29, 2025 07:59:59 (UTC+8)
Total reward: $750,000.00</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947260545799573504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Daily News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses TRUMP, becoming the second-largest Meme coin on the Solana chain;
2. The PUMP organization&apos;s private placement address is suspected of having cashed out over $140.00M, with a total profit of $39.65M;
3. QCP Capital: Ethereum&apos;s performance drives the start of altcoin season, with institutions dominating this round of gains;
4. Sequans increases its holdings by 1264 BTC, bringing its current total holdings to 2317 BTC;
5. The Ether Machine plans to go public through a business combination with Nasdaq-listed Dynamix, expected to be completed in the fourth quarter of this year if approved by shareholders and other conditions are met;
6. The Ether Machine: Commits to investing over $1.50B to hold and manage ETH, with Chairman Andrew Keys contributing over $500.00M;
7. Analyst: Ethereum&apos;s rise marks the beginning of the blockchain financial services cycle;
8. NFT recovery may indicate that funds are flowing from Bitcoin to other high-risk assets;
9. Ping An of China: Will continue to monitor regulatory changes in Hong Kong&apos;s stablecoin and actively conduct research;
10. MyStonks and BIT reach a strategic partnership to accelerate the deep integration of digital assets and traditional securities;
11. Hong Kong-listed company Fourth Paradigm releases a stablecoin underlying asset management solution.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947258014331588608</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoOdailyPlanet Daily News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses TRUMP, becoming the second-largest Meme coin on the Solana chain;
2. The PUMP organization&apos;s private placement address is suspected of having cashed out over $140.00M, with a total profit of $39.65M;
3. QCP Capital: Ethereum&apos;s perf</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947258014331588608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morocco’s Central Bank Completes Draft Crypto Assets BillOn July 21, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law to legalize the use of crypto assets. The law ensures &quot;adequate protection of consumers and investors, strengthens market integrity, combats fraud, manipulation, money laundering and terrorist financing, and maintains financial stability.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947255689445658624</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoPANewsMorocco’s Central Bank Completes Draft Crypto Assets BillOn July 21, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law to legalize the use of crypto assets. The law ensures &quot;adequate protectio</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947255689445658624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes calls for pushing ETH to $5,000.00On July 21, Arthur Hayes, co-founder of BitMEX, posted on the X platform, &quot;Fam can we pump $ETH to $5k by Friday?&quot; and interacted with FSInsight chief strategist Thomas Lee, saying that he has traditional financial power and called for a joint push to increase ETH prices. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947255326369927168</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoPANewsArthur Hayes calls for pushing ETH to $5,000.00On July 21, Arthur Hayes, co-founder of BitMEX, posted on the X platform, &quot;Fam can we pump $ETH to $5k by Friday?&quot; and interacted with FSInsight chief strategist Thomas Lee, saying that he has traditional financial power and called f</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947255326369927168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ether Machine plans to go public through a business combination with Nasdaq-listed Dynamix. If approved by shareholders and other conditions are met, the transaction is expected to be completed in the fourth quarter of this year.According to official sources, The Ether Machine will conduct a business combination with Dynamix Corporation (Nasdaq: DYNX) through The Ether Reserve, LLC entity. The merged entity will subsequently be listed on Nasdaq under the ticker symbol &quot;ETHM.&quot; The company is expected to launch with over 400,000 ETH, with core support primarily contributed by Andrew Keys, an early member of Consensys and founder of the Enterprise Ethereum Alliance (EEA), with approximately $645.00M (169,984 ETH). Additionally, it has secured over $800.00M in common stock financing from top institutions, native cryptocurrency entities, and strategic investors such as 1Roundtable Partners / 10T Holdings, Archetype, Blockchain.com, cyber•Fund, Electric Capital, Kraken, and Pantera Capital. The transaction is projected to generate over $1.60B in gross proceeds, including over $1.50B in fully committed financing and up to $170.00M in cash held in Dynamix&apos;s trust account, potentially becoming the largest public ETH-producing company. The boards of directors of The Ether Machine and DYNX have unanimously approved the proposed business combination, which is expected to be completed in the fourth quarter of 2025, pending shareholder approval and other customary closing conditions. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947255508939591680</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoOdailyThe Ether Machine plans to go public through a business combination with Nasdaq-listed Dynamix. If approved by shareholders and other conditions are met, the transaction is expected to be completed in the fourth quarter of this year.According to official sources, The Ether Machin</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947255508939591680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia&apos;s large-scale anti-fraud operation halts the business of Potato Guaranteed Public Groups.On July 14, the Cambodian government launched a nationwide crackdown on online scams, arresting 2,270 criminal suspects as of July 18. According to on-chain analysis firm Bitrace, during this period, the escrow addresses of the Cambodia-based cryptocurrency transaction escrow platform &quot;Potato Escrow&quot; stopped transferring funds, the scale of merchant deposit payments dropped to nearly zero, and the public group business basically stalled. The private group business briefly declined before partially recovering. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254128803860480</link>
      <description>39 minutes ago吴说Cambodia&apos;s large-scale anti-fraud operation halts the business of Potato Guaranteed Public Groups.On July 14, the Cambodian government launched a nationwide crackdown on online scams, arresting 2,270 criminal suspects as of July 18. According to on-chain analysis firm Bitrace, during</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254128803860480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antalpha&apos;s shareholders&apos; meeting passed several important resolutions, including increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital and restructuring share classes.Antalpha Platform Holdings held a special general meeting, with a total of 19,318,273 common shares voting at the meeting, representing approximately 81.6% of the company&apos;s total common shares as of June 20, 2025. At this general meeting, the company&apos;s shareholders approved the following proposals: increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital from &quot;$50,000.00, divided into 50,000,000 common shares with a par value of $0.001&quot; to &quot;$62,500.00, divided into 62,500,000 common shares with a par value of $0.001&quot;; reclassifying 59,375,000 authorized common shares as Class A common shares, while reclassifying 3,125,000 unissued authorized common shares as Class B common shares; amending the company&apos;s articles of association and memorandum to reflect the new authorized share capital structure; the Chairman of the Board and CEO of the company may receive an award of up to 1.50M Class B common shares under the 2024 Equity Incentive Plan; and the company will adopt a financial management plan to improve the company&apos;s financial management. All of the above proposals have been approved. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254027649830912</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoForesightNewsAntalpha&apos;s shareholders&apos; meeting passed several important resolutions, including increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital and restructuring share classes.Antalpha Platform Holdings held a special general meeting, with a total of 19,318,273 common shares voting at</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254027649830912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundstrat Co-Founder: Predicts Bitcoin Price Could Break $1 Million in the Next Few YearsOn July 21, CNBC reported that Fundstrat co-founder and managing partner Tom Lee said in an interview with &quot;Squawk Box&quot; that the price of Bitcoin could exceed $1 million per coin in the coming years. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947253121936019456</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoTechFlowFundstrat Co-Founder: Predicts Bitcoin Price Could Break $1 Million in the Next Few YearsOn July 21, CNBC reported that Fundstrat co-founder and managing partner Tom Lee said in an interview with &quot;Squawk Box&quot; that the price of Bitcoin could exceed $1 million per coin in the com</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947253121936019456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-founder Joseph Lubin will serve as the torchbearer for Ethereum&apos;s 10th anniversary, saying the protocol has been running stably and uninterruptedly for ten years.On July 21, Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin was invited to be the torchbearer for the 10th anniversary celebration of Ethereum. He said that the Ethereum protocol has been running stably for nearly ten years since its release, and even though it has undergone several major upgrades during this period, it has never lost a block, demonstrating the high reliability and strong vitality of the protocol. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947252518648303616</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoPANewsCo-founder Joseph Lubin will serve as the torchbearer for Ethereum&apos;s 10th anniversary, saying the protocol has been running stably and uninterruptedly for ten years.On July 21, Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin was invited to be the torchbearer for the 10th anniversary celebration</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947252518648303616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Token Unlocks to Watch in the Fourth Week of July 2025As the fourth week of July 2025 begins, several major token unlocks will shake up the crypto market. Projects like Avail (AVAIL), Venom (VENOM), amd AltLayer (ALT) are releasing new tokens into circulation.  These events could significantly alter supply dynamics, introducing short-term price swings and heightened market activity. 1. Avail (AVAIL) Avail is a horizontally scalable network that enables seamless  cross-chain interoperability , fast transaction verification, and decentralized data availability. With components like availDA, availNexus, and availFusion, it empowers developers to build scalable, secure, and connected Web3 applications. On July 23, the  project will unlock  972.85 million AVAIL tokens, valued at approximately $19.46 million. This is equivalent to 38.23% of the current circulating supply. Avail will distribute  500.00 million tokens to core  contributors. Furthermore, investors will get 353.13 million AVAIL. The team will also award 66.67 million tokens for ecosystem development and 53.06 million tokens to the community and research.  2. Venom (VENOM) Venom is a heterogeneous  multi-blockchain system  with dynamic sharding capabilities. It is built on the Threaded Virtual Machine (TVM) and utilizes Mesh network technology for enhanced efficiency and scalability.  The project will release 59.26 million VENOM on July 25, following its monthly pattern of cliff token unlocks. Moreover, the tokens are worth $12.67 million and represent 2.84% of the  current circulating supply. A majority of the unlocked tokens, 17.92 million, will go toward the ecosystem. Early backers will receive 15.00 million tokens, and the community will get 15.84 million. Lastly, the team will collect 10.50 million VENOM. 3. AltLayer (ALT) AltLayer is a decentralized protocol designed to  launch highly scalable  and customizable rollups. It’s often described as a rollup-as-a-service (RaaS) platform. The network will unlock 240.10 million ALT tokens, valued at $9.01 million. This unlock accounts for 6.39% of the circulating supply. Additionally, the supply will be split six ways. AltLayer will award 64.25 million tokens to investors. The treasury will also get 52.25 million ALT. The network will keep 41.31 million tokens earmarked for protocol development. The team will receive 36.44 million tokens, the ecosystem and community will gain 29.17 million ALT, and finally, 16.68 million tokens will be kept for advisors. In addition to these three, Sahara (SAHAR), Soon (SOON), and Undeads Games (UDS) will also experience new supply entering the market.  Overall, over the next seven days , the market will welcome tokens worth more than $96.70 million. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947257090905231360</link>
      <description>48 minutes agobeincrypto3 Token Unlocks to Watch in the Fourth Week of July 2025As the fourth week of July 2025 begins, several major token unlocks will shake up the crypto market. Projects like Avail (AVAIL), Venom (VENOM), amd AltLayer (ALT) are releasing new tokens into circulation.  These events</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947257090905231360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jingwei Tiandi: Launching a self-developed global stable currency payment platformOn July 21, Jingwei Tiandi announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that the company announced its entry into the field of crypto payments and will release its first mobile application &quot;Fopay&quot; on July 21, 2025, providing a one-stop payment platform. Fopay is developed based on the concept of stablecoin crypto payments and currently provides stablecoin custody and prepaid card payment functions through several licensed partners. The board of directors believes that the launch of Fopay and new business segments can explore more business opportunities for the company and benefit shareholders as a whole. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251533666340864</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoPANewsJingwei Tiandi: Launching a self-developed global stable currency payment platformOn July 21, Jingwei Tiandi announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that the company announced its entry into the field of crypto payments and will release its first mobile application &quot;Fopay&quot; on J</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251533666340864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum is expected to reach around $8,000.00 in early 2026, with its price structure similar to the 1980s Dow Jones bull market patternOn July 21, Cointelegraph reported that analyst Gert van Lagen pointed out that Ethereum (ETH) is in the &quot;final surge&quot; stage and may move towards the $8,000.00 price level. He found that ETH&apos;s current price structure is strikingly similar to the bull market pattern of the Dow Jones Index in 1980. The analysis is based on the &quot;textbook expansion diagonal&quot; pattern, which has provided strong support for Ethereum&apos;s main rebound since mid-2022. Currently, ETH is trading between the upper and lower boundaries of this pattern, and is expected to reach the upper boundary of about $8,000.00 in early 2026. Technically, ETH has re-established a multi-year upward trend line as support and is consolidating within an ascending triangle pattern. A break above the $3,900.00-$4,150.00 level resistance zone could trigger a rise to $7,150.00, close to the target price of the trumpet pattern. Analysts say that macroeconomic factors such as the expected Fed rate cuts and continued ETH ETF inflows may support this upward trend. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249833433911296</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoTechFlowAnalyst: Ethereum is expected to reach around $8,000.00 in early 2026, with its price structure similar to the 1980s Dow Jones bull market patternOn July 21, Cointelegraph reported that analyst Gert van Lagen pointed out that Ethereum (ETH) is in the &quot;final surge&quot; stage and may</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249833433911296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ether Machine to list on Nasdaq with $1.50 billion war chest for Ethereum treasuryThe Ether Machine plans to list on Nasdaq with more than $1.5 billion in fully committed capital and over 400,000 Ether on its balance sheet, potentially positioning the newly formed company as the largest publicly traded vehicle focused exclusively on Ethereum, according to a definitive merger announcement on Monday.

Financing includes an anchor contribution of roughly $645 million, about 169,984 ETH, from co‑founder Andrew Keys, who will serve as chairman, and more than $800 million in common‑stock commitments from institutional and crypto‑native investors such as 1Roundtable/10T Holdings, Archetype, Blockchain.com, cyber Fund, Electric Capital, Kraken, and Pantera Capital.

Dynamix’s $170 million cash trust could lift gross proceeds above $1.6 billion, the statement notes. David Merin, the former head of corporate development at Consensys, will also become the CEO, with Morgan Stanley alumnus Jonathan Christodoro serving as vice chairman.

The Ether Machine will go public through a business combination with Dynamix Corporation (DYNX), a special-purpose acquisition company that launched its initial public offering in late 2024. The company says it will generate ETH‑denominated returns through staking, restaking, and decentralized‑finance strategies while offering institutions turnkey exposure to Ethereum yields. Upon closing — targeted for the fourth quarter and contingent on shareholder approval — the combined entity will trade under the ticker ETHM.

If successful, the listing would eclipse SharpLink Gaming’s 353,000 ETH treasury and BitMine Immersion’s 300,657 ETH stash, making Ether Machine the largest public ether holder at launch. It would also extend a growing trend of pure proxy players for investors seeking Ethereum exposure via U.S. equities</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251572945997824</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoThe BlockThe Ether Machine to list on Nasdaq with $1.50 billion war chest for Ethereum treasuryThe Ether Machine plans to list on Nasdaq with more than $1.5 billion in fully committed capital and over 400,000 Ether on its balance sheet, potentially positioning the newly formed company</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251572945997824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>