<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:37:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Powell: Fed is a dynamic institution, willing to listen to new ideasOn July 22, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell said: The Federal Reserve is a dynamic institution that is willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework of large banks. Large banks must be able to compete freely, including with non-bank institutions and banks in other jurisdictions. Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell did not comment on the economic or monetary policy outlook in his speech. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947636602742525952</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsPowell: Fed is a dynamic institution, willing to listen to new ideasOn July 22, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell said: The Federal Reserve is a dynamic institution that is willing to listen to new ideas and feedback on how to improve the capital framework of large banks. Large banks</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947636602742525952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will deliver welcome remarks at a regulatory conference in ten minutes.Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will deliver a welcome speech at a regulatory meeting in ten minutes. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947635509119700992</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailyFederal Reserve Chairman Powell will deliver welcome remarks at a regulatory conference in ten minutes.Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will deliver a welcome speech at a regulatory meeting in ten minutes. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947635509119700992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic opens first season airdrop claim, users can now claim 25% shareSonic has announced the official launch of its Season 1 airdrop, where users can now claim 25% of their allocated share. The remaining 75% will be released linearly in NFT form and gradually opened via the PaintSwap order book. The official announcement clarifies that this airdrop is based on the Sonic mainnet whitelist event and is not related to pre-sales or TGE. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947635517567029248</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailySonic opens first season airdrop claim, users can now claim 25% shareSonic has announced the official launch of its Season 1 airdrop, where users can now claim 25% of their allocated share. The remaining 75% will be released linearly in NFT form and gradually opened via the PaintS</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947635517567029248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US State Department: US will withdraw from UNESCOOn July 22, the US State Department said the US will withdraw from UNESCO. US Treasury Secretary Benson said there is no indication that Powell should resign now. If he wants to leave early, he should do so. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947631778827358208</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoPANewsUS State Department: US will withdraw from UNESCOOn July 22, the US State Department said the US will withdraw from UNESCO. US Treasury Secretary Benson said there is no indication that Powell should resign now. If he wants to leave early, he should do so. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947631778827358208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soluna Holdings Completes $20.00M Financing Round with Participation from Spring Lane CapitalNasdaq-listed Soluna Holdings, which develops green data centers for intensive computing applications such as Bitcoin mining and artificial intelligence, has announced the completion of a new $20.00M funding round with participation from Spring Lane Capital. The new funds are intended to expand its Kati green data center project in Texas to further expand its Bitcoin hosting business. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947630569504657408</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoForesightNewsSoluna Holdings Completes $20.00M Financing Round with Participation from Spring Lane CapitalNasdaq-listed Soluna Holdings, which develops green data centers for intensive computing applications such as Bitcoin mining and artificial intelligence, has announced the completi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947630569504657408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharplink Gaming increased its holdings by 79,949 ETH last week, investing approximately $258 millionOn July 22, according to Aggr News, Sharplink purchased 79,949 Ethereums at an average price of US$3,238.00 per ether between July 14 and July 20, with a total amount of US$258.00 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947629499399294976</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoPANewsSharplink Gaming increased its holdings by 79,949 ETH last week, investing approximately $258 millionOn July 22, according to Aggr News, Sharplink purchased 79,949 Ethereums at an average price of US$3,238.00 per ether between July 14 and July 20, with a total amount of US$258.00</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947629499399294976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Now Lists YALAAccording to the official page, Binance Alpha has launched YALA. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947628341792362496</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoChainCatcherBinance Alpha Now Lists YALAAccording to the official page, Binance Alpha has launched YALA. [ChainCatcher]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947628341792362496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent: Calls for Internal Review of the Federal ReserveU.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Calls for an internal review of the Federal Reserve. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627952036663296</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdailyU.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent: Calls for Internal Review of the Federal ReserveU.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Calls for an internal review of the Federal Reserve. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627952036663296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese textile company Kitabo plans to purchase approximately $5.40M worth of BitcoinAccording to the official announcement, Japanese textile materials company Kitabo Co has announced the official launch of its Bitcoin purchase plan. The company has been approved by the shareholders&apos; meeting to purchase Bitcoin in batches through Japanese crypto asset exchanges using a dollar-cost averaging (DCA) strategy with a maximum of 800.00 million yen (approximately $5.43 million USD), and plans to use some of it for lending business to obtain stable income. Kitabo stated that it will position Bitcoin as the basic asset for carrying out cross-border services and diversified business strategies in the future. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627204997566464</link>
      <description>39 minutes ago吴说Japanese textile company Kitabo plans to purchase approximately $5.40M worth of BitcoinAccording to the official announcement, Japanese textile materials company Kitabo Co has announced the official launch of its Bitcoin purchase plan. The company has been approved by the shareholder</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627204997566464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs Increases BNB Strategic Reserve to $90.00M, Plans to Upgrade Reserve StrategyWeb 3.0 infrastructure and product solution provider Nano Labs Ltd (Nasdaq: NA) announced that the company has significantly increased its BNB holdings to 120,000, with a current total value of approximately $90.00M. Recently, Nano Labs added 45,684.9862 BNB through over-the-counter transactions, with an average purchase price of approximately $764 per BNB. Currently, the company&apos;s average purchase cost of BNB is $707. Nano Labs stated that it will further strengthen its BNB strategic reserve in the future through various methods such as continuously increasing its BNB holdings, acquiring controlling stakes in entities with BNB as a core reserve asset, and investing in companies focused on holding BNB. (Globe Newswire) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627969027788800</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoOdailyNano Labs Increases BNB Strategic Reserve to $90.00M, Plans to Upgrade Reserve StrategyWeb 3.0 infrastructure and product solution provider Nano Labs Ltd (Nasdaq: NA) announced that the company has significantly increased its BNB holdings to 120,000, with a current total value of</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627969027788800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hut 8 Announces Subsidiary Receives Dubai DIFC License to Explore Derivatives MarketNasdaq-listed BTC mining company Hut 8 announced that its subsidiary, Hut 8 Investment Ltd, has obtained a commercial license from the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC), authorizing it to conduct proprietary investment and other commercial activities under the legal and regulatory framework of the DIFC based on international standards and common law principles, including direct access to global derivatives markets and access to institutional-grade products and counterparties. It is reported that Hut 8 is the main shareholder of American Bitcoin, a cryptocurrency company supported by Eric Trump, son of former U.S. President Donald Trump, and has previously transferred its mining equipment to American Bitcoin in exchange for 80% of the equity. (Globenewswire) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627977563197440</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyHut 8 Announces Subsidiary Receives Dubai DIFC License to Explore Derivatives MarketNasdaq-listed BTC mining company Hut 8 announced that its subsidiary, Hut 8 Investment Ltd, has obtained a commercial license from the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC), authorizing it t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627977563197440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Bessent: Tariff revenue could reach $2.8 trillion over the next decade.US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Tariff revenue could reach $2.8 trillion over the next decade. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627986027302912</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyUS Treasury Secretary Bessent: Tariff revenue could reach $2.8 trillion over the next decade.US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Tariff revenue could reach $2.8 trillion over the next decade. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627986027302912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish company SMX plans to include crypto assets such as Bitcoin in its treasury reserves to increase asset value and hedge against inflation.According to the official announcement, the Irish company Security Matters (SMX) plans to start using Bitcoin and other crypto assets as treasury reserves to increase asset value and hedge against inflation. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627994520768512</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyIrish company SMX plans to include crypto assets such as Bitcoin in its treasury reserves to increase asset value and hedge against inflation.According to the official announcement, the Irish company Security Matters (SMX) plans to start using Bitcoin and other crypto assets as t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947627994520768512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Labs Increases Holdings by 45,684 BNB via OTC, Approximately $34.90MU.S. listed company Nano Labs Ltd (Nasdaq: NA) today announced that its BNB holdings have significantly increased to 120,000, with a current total value of approximately $90.00M. Nano Labs has newly purchased 45,684.9862 BNB through over-the-counter (OTC) transactions, with an average purchase price of approximately $764.00 per BNB. As of now, the company holds a total of approximately 120,000 BNB, with an average purchase cost of $707.00 per BNB and a current market value of approximately $90.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947626484634243072</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsNano Labs Increases Holdings by 45,684 BNB via OTC, Approximately $34.90MU.S. listed company Nano Labs Ltd (Nasdaq: NA) today announced that its BNB holdings have significantly increased to 120,000, with a current total value of approximately $90.00M. Nano Labs has newly p</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947626484634243072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Bitcoin dominance drops 2.98 percentage points in one week, funds are flowing into altcoinsGlassnode posted on X that Bitcoin&apos;s market capitalization dominance fell from 63.76% to 60.78% over the past week, a drop of 2.98 percentage points, one of the largest single-week declines this year, with funds flowing into altcoins. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947626484755877888</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoForesightNewsGlassnode: Bitcoin dominance drops 2.98 percentage points in one week, funds are flowing into altcoinsGlassnode posted on X that Bitcoin&apos;s market capitalization dominance fell from 63.76% to 60.78% over the past week, a drop of 2.98 percentage points, one of the largest si</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947626484755877888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The second phase of the Gate &quot;Red Bull Racing Tour&quot; is in full swing, with transaction volume exceeding $10.00B and more than 21,000 participantsOn July 22, according to official news, the second phase of the &quot;Red Bull Racing Tour&quot; launched by Gate on July 12 has continued to gain popularity. Before the deadline, the total transaction volume has exceeded $10.00B, the number of participants has exceeded 21,000, and 1,000 GT rewards have been successfully unlocked. The total prize pool for this phase is as high as 20,000 GT. Participants can impact the rankings by completing spot and contract tasks, and not only have the opportunity to share generous rewards, but also have the opportunity to win tickets to watch the F1 Grand Prix worth tens of thousands of dollars.
 Join the Red Bull Racing Tour now to start a speed feast where the world of crypto meets the passion of top racing, and chase the peak of glory together. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947624019348180992</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsThe second phase of the Gate &quot;Red Bull Racing Tour&quot; is in full swing, with transaction volume exceeding $10.00B and more than 21,000 participantsOn July 22, according to official news, the second phase of the &quot;Red Bull Racing Tour&quot; launched by Gate on July 12 has continued to gai</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947624019348180992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-chain wallet TokenPocket now supports using USDD to pay transaction feesMulti-chain self-custody wallet TokenPocket announced that after previously adding support for USDT as a transfer &quot;network fee&quot; on TRON, it now supports the decentralized stablecoin USDD as a Gas Fee payment method. When users transfer via the TRON network, they can directly use USDD to pay transaction fees and enjoy limited-time transaction fee subsidies, achieving &quot;more savings with every transaction.&quot; Currently, TokenPocket serves over 25.00 million users worldwide, with over 3.50 million monthly active users, and its business covers more than 200 countries and regions. The new support for USDD to pay transaction fees will inevitably further enrich the application scenarios of USDD 2.0. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947620414960455680</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMulti-chain wallet TokenPocket now supports using USDD to pay transaction feesMulti-chain self-custody wallet TokenPocket announced that after previously adding support for USDT as a transfer &quot;network fee&quot; on TRON, it now supports the decentralized stablecoin USDD as a Gas Fee paymen</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947620414960455680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archax Acquires German Digital Asset Firm DDA to Expand European Crypto ETP FootprintUK-based digital asset exchange Archax will acquire Deutsche Digital Assets (DDA), a regulated German crypto asset management company, to strengthen its business presence in major European financial markets such as the UK, Germany, and France. DDA currently manages approximately $70.00M in assets and focuses on distributing crypto exchange-traded products (ETPs) through European banks and asset management institutions. This acquisition will bring new licenses to Archax, including portfolio management and investment advisory under German BaFin regulation, enabling it to better serve EU institutional clients. (CoinDesk) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947617899678289920</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyArchax Acquires German Digital Asset Firm DDA to Expand European Crypto ETP FootprintUK-based digital asset exchange Archax will acquire Deutsche Digital Assets (DDA), a regulated German crypto asset management company, to strengthen its business presence in major European financial</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947617899678289920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>coindesk</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.44% in the past 1H, up 0.24% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947613988454883328</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.44% in the past 1H, up 0.24% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947613988454883328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 300 BTC to Binance again, worth approximately $35.61M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale once again deposited 300 BTC into Binance, worth approximately $35.61M. Currently, the whale address still holds 800 BTC, worth approximately $95.00M, with a profit of $93.33M. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947615393116082176</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA whale deposited 300 BTC to Binance again, worth approximately $35.61M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale once again deposited 300 BTC into Binance, worth approximately $35.61M. Currently, the whale address still holds 800 BTC, worth approximately $95.00M, with a profit o</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947615393116082176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>