<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:29:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ETH core developer testifies in Roman Storm defense as gov’t rests case</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948477160959840256</link>
      <description>20:14ETH core developer testifies in Roman Storm defense as gov’t rests case</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948477160959840256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH core developer testifies in Roman Storm defense as gov’t rests caseAfter about two weeks of hearing from US government witnesses, Roman Storm’s legal team called Preston Van Loon to the stand to kick off its defense case.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948479322100142080</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoPANewsETH core developer testifies in Roman Storm defense as gov’t rests caseAfter about two weeks of hearing from US government witnesses, Roman Storm’s legal team called Preston Van Loon to the stand to kick off its defense case.#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948479322100142080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey&apos;s Solana staking ETF to pass on 100% of rewards to shareholders as it integrates JitoSOLREX-Osprey’s Solana staking exchange-traded fund has integrated staking rewards through a partnership with JitoSOL, the leading liquid staking token on Solana. This makes it the first and only crypto ETF to offer staking rewards to U.S. investors, according to an announcement on Thursday.

According to the announcement, 100% of the fund’s staking rewards will be “passed through to shareholders, with neither REX nor Osprey retaining any portion.”

The REX-Osprey Solana + Staking ETF went live on July 2 as the first approved fund to stake its assets. The fund has accrued at least $222 million in cumulative trading volume and over $100 million in net assets under management since its debut, according to The Block Research.

“Now by integrating the capability for liquid staking through JitoSOL, we’re enhancing liquidity while continuing to deliver native Solana rewards within a U.S. ETF structure,” Greg King, CEO of REX Financial &amp; Osprey Funds, said in a statement.

JitoSOL, a liquid staking token, is a tokenized version of staked SOL that enables users to continue trading the value of their staked assets while still earning on-chain rewards. There is approximately $3 billion worth of JitoSOL in circulation, according to The Block’s data.

The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has clarified that it does not believe most staking activities fall under its remit. However, the agency has been hesitant to approve staking ETFs. REX-Osprey’s fund was approved under a more stringent regulatory model called the Investment Company Act of 1940, which requires a qualified custodian to hold the assets.

REX-Osprey tapped Anchorage Digital as its custodian and staking partner. Staking represents an increasingly fast-growing part of crypto custodians like Anchorage and BitGo’s business model.

“JitoSOL becoming the first liquid staking token included in a U.S. ETF is a landmark moment — not just for Jito, but for the future of staked assets in traditional financial products,&quot; Thomas Uhm, Jito Foundation chief commercial officer, said in a statement. [The Block Research]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948476776715456512</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoThe BlockREX-Osprey&apos;s Solana staking ETF to pass on 100% of rewards to shareholders as it integrates JitoSOLREX-Osprey’s Solana staking exchange-traded fund has integrated staking rewards through a partnership with JitoSOL, the leading liquid staking token on Solana. This makes it the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948476776715456512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s Grok AI integrates with Kalshi, Paradigm-backed prediction marketxAI, the artificial‑intelligence startup founded by Elon Musk, will integrate its Grok conversational model into Kalshi, the only CFTC‑regulated exchange for event‑based contracts, bringing real‑time AI analysis to retail traders wagering on everything from Fed decisions to Oscar winners.

The tie‑up is effective immediately, the companies said on X. Kalshi users will be able to query Grok’s large‑language model for onchain data, historical odds, and breaking headlines before placing trades, while xAI gains a live environment to stress‑test Grok’s reasoning and probability outputs.

Kalshi operates a federally regulated prediction market where traders buy shares of “yes” or “no” contracts on future events, with stakes settling at $1 per share if correct and zero if wrong. The venue accepts crypto deposits in Bitcoin, SOL, USDC, and WLD, but settles all wagers in U.S. dollars. Founded in 2018 by MIT alumni Tarek Mansour and Luana Lopes Lara, the New York‑based firm processed $1.4 billion in trades over 11 days for election-related contracts, a November 2024 report from the FIA Expo stated.

xAI builds Grok, an LLM positioned as a challenger to OpenAI’s ChatGPT and embedded inside Musk‑owned social platform X.

The partnership follows Kalshi’s $185.00 million Series B round in June 2025, led by crypto VC firm Paradigm, that valued the platform at $2.00 billion. Musk’s AI studio was valued on paper at $80.00 billion after an all-stock acquisition of X, Axios reported. “Two of the fastest-growing companies in America are now on the same team,” the official xAI account posted on X.

Kalshi’s collaboration with xAI occurs amid ongoing debates in Washington about expanding retail access to event contracts. The CFTC reopened public comments on political-election markets in June 2025 after a contentious debate sparked by Kalshi’s legal victory in 2024, which allowed it to offer election-related contracts after a federal appeals court ruling overturned a CFTC ban.

Meanwhile, prediction market rival Polymarket plans to re-enter the U.S. by acquiring derivatives exchange QCEX. [Axios]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948468647051202560</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoThe BlockElon Musk’s Grok AI integrates with Kalshi, Paradigm-backed prediction marketxAI, the artificial‑intelligence startup founded by Elon Musk, will integrate its Grok conversational model into Kalshi, the only CFTC‑regulated exchange for event‑based contracts, bringing real‑time</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948468647051202560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injective lists SharpLink stocks, launches first Ethereum vault tokenized assetInjective has announced the on-chain listing of SharpLink (SBET) shares, making it the first &quot;Digital Asset Treasury&quot; (DAT) tokenized product. Injective stated that the SBET DAT is developed based on its iAssets framework and has features such as native programmability, mechanism interfaces accessible to on-chain governance, and cross-protocol composability, which can be used in scenarios such as lending, collateralization, and derivatives design. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948468266258731008</link>
      <description>48 minutes ago吴说Injective lists SharpLink stocks, launches first Ethereum vault tokenized assetInjective has announced the on-chain listing of SharpLink (SBET) shares, making it the first &quot;Digital Asset Treasury&quot; (DAT) tokenized product. Injective stated that the SBET DAT is developed based on its i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948468266258731008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy upsizes preferred &apos;Stretch&apos; stock offering to $2.00 billion to buy more bitcoinBitcoin treasury firm Strategy plans to quadruple the size of its recently announced Series A Perpetual Stretch Preferred Stock offer to $2.00 billion from $500.00 million after strong demand for bitcoin‑focused shares, Morgan Stanley, Barclays, Moelis, and TD Securities are bookrunners on the latest Stretch sale.

Proceeds from Strategy’s expanded facility are earmarked to fund additional Bitcoin purchases. Last week, the company spent $739.90 million generated from share sales on 6,220 BTC, increasing its holdings to 607,770, The Block’s data shows. That’s currently valued at over $72.00 billion and roughly 3% of Bitcoin’s total supply of 21 million.

The company, formerly known as MicroStrategy, will offer Stretch shares at a price of $90 per share, a 10% discount to face value and the low end of a marketed range of $100. The securities carry an initial 9% annual dividend that Strategy can reset monthly.

Stretch, the company’s fourth preferred stock program, reportedly ranks senior to the firm’s Strike (STRK) and Stride (STRD) preferred stock and its common shares, but subordinate to its Strife (STRF) preferred series and outstanding convertible notes.

Earlier this week, TD Cowen said the company’s preferred‑stock arsenal could help Strategy lift its holdings to nearly 900,000 BTC by 2027, arguing each share controls more Bitcoin today than 18 months ago despite aggressive issuance. Strategy’s net asset value premium, the percentage by which its market cap surpasses its BTC holdings, is justified since the company can effectively borrow at low rates and stockpile crypto’s largest asset, the brokerage stated.

Strategy’s common stock is trading around $414, giving the firm a market capitalization of $124.00 billion, according to The Block’s data dashboard. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948442129080061952</link>
      <description>2 hours agoThe BlockStrategy upsizes preferred &apos;Stretch&apos; stock offering to $2.00 billion to buy more bitcoinBitcoin treasury firm Strategy plans to quadruple the size of its recently announced Series A Perpetual Stretch Preferred Stock offer to $2.00 billion from $500.00 million after strong demand</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948442129080061952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolv Enables Protocol Fee Mechanism, Returns Will Reward Stakers and Drive Ecosystem ExpansionResolv has announced the official launch of a protocol fee mechanism starting in July 2025, where a portion of the daily revenue will be used for long-term value accumulation and distributed to RESOLV stakers. The protocol fee will gradually increase to 10% of daily profits over 4 weeks and will only be charged when there is a positive return, without affecting the principal or days with zero returns. Protocol revenue will be used to expand DeFi and institutional integration, fund ecosystem development, promote token buybacks, and usage will be made public through a transparent dashboard. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948441027974598656</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说Resolv Enables Protocol Fee Mechanism, Returns Will Reward Stakers and Drive Ecosystem ExpansionResolv has announced the official launch of a protocol fee mechanism starting in July 2025, where a portion of the daily revenue will be used for long-term value accumulation and distributed</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948441027974598656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized exchange WOO X investigates &apos;contained incident&apos; resulting in estimated $14 million lossWOO X, a little-known centralized crypto trading platform, said it is investigating “a contained incident” impacting nine customer accounts on Thursday. The company noted that “unauthorized withdrawals were placed,” totalling an estimated $14 million.

“The incident was quickly detected and as a precaution, withdrawals were paused and many of the withdrawals were blocked,” WOO X said. “We&apos;ve already contacted the affected users, and all unauthorized withdrawals will be covered.”

The firm said it is working with external security teams and other exchanges to halt the flow of funds. WOO X trading volumes have spiked 264.8% over the past 24-hours, according to CoinGecko data.

Crypto security firm Cyvers has begun tracking funds as they move along the Arbitrum, Bitcoin, BNB Chain, Ethereum, and Tron networks. The firm said about $1 million worth of USDT was swapped into ETH with an additional $7.3 million worth of funds later sent to a new address.

An additional five wrapped BTC tokens on the BNB Chain were swapped into BNB tokens and sent to a new address, Cyvers said.

Crypto hacks are not an uncommon occurrence in the industry. Chainalysis estimates there were losses totaling at least $2.2 billion in 2024 across centralized and decentralized blockchain platforms. This represents a 21.07% year-over-year increase during a year that saw rising crypto prices, which is typically a driving factor in increasing crypto crime.

WOO X is a Seychelles-registered centralized exchange established in 2019. The firm most recently raised $9 million in a 2024 funding round with participation from Wintermute, Selini Capital, among others.

Notably, in 2023, WOO X temporarily paused trading activity after its largest market maker and incubator, Kronos Research, experienced a $25 million hack, in a move that caused it to revamp its market mechanisms. [WOO X]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948434193335259136</link>
      <description>3 hours agoThe BlockCentralized exchange WOO X investigates &apos;contained incident&apos; resulting in estimated $14 million lossWOO X, a little-known centralized crypto trading platform, said it is investigating “a contained incident” impacting nine customer accounts on Thursday. The company noted that “una</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948434193335259136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPTO Miner launches smart, secure mobile platform for cloud-based crypto miningDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. OPTO Miner launches mobile-first cloud mining app amid rising DeFi growth and renewed crypto utility focus. The first half of 2025 marked a shift in crypto, with Ethereum’s Dencun upgrade boosting DeFi growth and SEC rulings restoring momentum to projects like XRP. At the same time, speculations that Elon Musk’s plans to integrate DOGE into X have renewed interest in utility-driven crypto use, as digital assets gain real value in unstable economies. OPTO Miner has launched a mobile-first cloud mining platform, enabling users worldwide to mine crypto easily and securely — anytime, anywhere — through smart tech, clean energy, and regulatory alignment. Key advantages of OPTO Miner No Hardware, No Hassle Forget costly mining rigs and complex setups. All that’s needed is a smartphone or computer to begin mining with just one click. Global Access with Real-Time Transparency The dashboard is always on, allowing users to track their mining progress and earnings 24/7 from anywhere in the world. Support for Leading Mineable Asset Mine major cryptocurrencies include Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Dogecoin (DOGE), and more. Smart Allocation Meets Green Energy Leveraging an intelligent distributed compute model, OPTO Miner routes operations through clean energy-powered facilities — reducing environmental impact while enhancing efficiency. Flexible Settlements in Top Digital Assets Earnings can be received in BTC, ETH, USDT (ERC20 &amp; TRC20), USDC, XRP, SOL, DOGE, BCH, LTC, and more. Whether someone’s seeking short-term income or building long-term crypto reserves, OPTO adapts to their strategy. Enterprise-Grade Security Infrastructure is protected by Cloudflare® and McAfee®, ensuring account safety and data integrity. The platform guarantees 100% uptime and provides live technical support 24/7. OPTO Miner’s cloud contracts are powered by renewable energy sources like solar and hydro, providing not only stable returns but also a low-carbon mining footprint. Choose OPTO Miner as a provider; OPTO Miner offers a $15 free mining plan, where users can earn $0.60 in passive income per day for free. The platform has launched a variety of stable income contract packages, which can be viewed on the official website. OPTO Miner isn’t just a tool for crypto enthusiasts. It’s a frictionless entry point into the evolving blockchain ecosystem, at a time when accessibility, sustainability, and transparency matter more than ever. OPTO Miner gives users the ability to grow their digital wealth with minimal effort. Participate in the crypto economy without expensive hardware. Diversify across top digital assets in a secure, compliant environment. Whether the goal is portfolio growth, cross-border diversification, or early positioning in the next wave of decentralized finance, OPTO Miner offers the simplicity and scalability to help investors get there. Founded in 2010 and headquartered in the UK, OPTO Miner is a legally registered entity operating under internationally recognized regulatory frameworks. Since launching its cloud computing service in 2018, the company has expanded across more than 180 countries and regions, delivering high-performance, reliable mining infrastructure to users worldwide. For more information, visit the official website and download the mobile app. Disclosure: This content is provided by a third party. Neither crypto.news nor the author of this article endorses any product mentioned on this page. Users should conduct their own research before taking any action related to the company.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948433065486913536</link>
      <description>3 hours agocrypto.newsOPTO Miner launches smart, secure mobile platform for cloud-based crypto miningDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. OPTO Miner launches mobile-first cloud mining app ami</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948433065486913536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Private Equity Managers Will Win 401(k) Race, Blackstone’s Gray SaysThe alternative asset industry’s biggest players will likely come out on top once the US paves the way for Americans’ 401(k)s to go beyond stocks and bonds, Blackstone Inc. President Jon Gray said. The White House has been readying an executive order to provide legal assurances to 401(k) plan managers to offer private markets funds, crypto and other alternatives as investment options.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948449453014323200</link>
      <description>3 hours agoBloombergBig Private Equity Managers Will Win 401(k) Race, Blackstone’s Gray SaysThe alternative asset industry’s biggest players will likely come out on top once the US paves the way for Americans’ 401(k)s to go beyond stocks and bonds, Blackstone Inc. President Jon Gray said. The White</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948449453014323200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Digital announces stablecoin issuance platform on GENIUS&apos; heelsThe digital asset service company joins a growing list of firms making stablecoin moves following the GENIUS bill&apos;s passage into law.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948428512754470912</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsAnchorage Digital announces stablecoin issuance platform on GENIUS&apos; heelsThe digital asset service company joins a growing list of firms making stablecoin moves following the GENIUS bill&apos;s passage into law.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948428512754470912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Stock Fever Can Cool as Quickly as It BeginsMeme stock mania returned in full force this week, but for some names, the gains are vanishing quickly. I’m Claire Ballentine filling in for my colleague Charlie Wells this week. I’ve been following meme stocks for a while now, and I remember when this was brand-new back in 2021 (check out the time I spent 11 hours on Reddit for a story).This time, hordes of everyday investors piled into heavily shorted companies like Kohl’s and Opendoor, along with GoPro, Krispy Kreme and Beyond Meat.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948449499776618496</link>
      <description>3 hours agoBloombergMeme Stock Fever Can Cool as Quickly as It BeginsMeme stock mania returned in full force this week, but for some names, the gains are vanishing quickly. I’m Claire Ballentine filling in for my colleague Charlie Wells this week. I’ve been following meme stocks for a while now, and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948449499776618496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum holding company GameSquare purchases CryptoPunk NFT as treasury asset for $5.15 million in preferred sharesIn something of a novel move for the increasingly saturated crypto treasury space, Ethereum holding company GameSquare (ticker GAME) has acquired a CryptoPunk NFT. The firm says it will now hold the “iconic” piece as a “strategic treasury asset.”

GameSquare purchased the token — Punk #5577, one of just 24 “Ape Punks” — for $5.15 million in an equity trade with its previous owner, DeFi OG Robert Leshner. The preferred stock will be convertible into common shares at $1.50 per share.

Leshner, the founder of Superstate and Compound, appears to have purchased CryptoPunk #5577 in February 2022 for 2,501 ETH, equivalent to approximately $7.7 million at the time. The asset is distinguished by its cowboy hat.

The 10,000 token CryptoPunks series was one of the earliest experiments with non-fungible tokens when launched in 2017. Yuga Labs, which bought the CryptoPunks IP from creator Larva Labs in March 2022, sold the project to the nonprofit Infinite Node Foundation in May of this year.

“This isn’t just our first grail NFT, it’s a signal of how we’re thinking differently and expanding our existing footprint in digital culture by building a next-generation media company with crypto in its DNA,” Justin Kenna, CEO of GameSquare, said in a statement.

GameSquare is one of many newly emerging Ethereum treasury firms. Early this month, the firm’s board approved a $100 million ETH treasury authorization, which was later expanded to $250 million. The firm has acquired approximately 10,170.74 ETH, now worth $52 million, as of July 21.

Unlike other ETH balance sheet plays that typically stake their holdings for yield, GameSquare said it will pursue higher returns through DeFi deployments, namely Dialectic’s institutional Medici platform. The board also approved an initial $10 million allocation to an NFT yield strategy, targeting 6%–10% annualized returns.

According to the announcement on Thursday, Leshner has joined the firm as an advisor and will help it tokenize its GAME shares on the Superstate platform.

Recently, Leshner’s attempt at a hostile takeover of a “low market cap” liquor firm to start a crypto treasury was thwarted after its executives diluted his ownership.

[Unknown]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948427168882692096</link>
      <description>3 hours agoThe BlockEthereum holding company GameSquare purchases CryptoPunk NFT as treasury asset for $5.15 million in preferred sharesIn something of a novel move for the increasingly saturated crypto treasury space, Ethereum holding company GameSquare (ticker GAME) has acquired a CryptoPunk NFT.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948427168882692096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; is long on PUMP and is currently down more than $9.00M in unrealized losses.hypurrscan data shows that &quot;Machi Big Brother&apos;s&quot; 5x leveraged long PUMP position and spot position have a total floating loss of over $9.00M. In addition, he also holds a 5x leveraged HYPE long position with a floating loss of $1.00M, and a 25x leveraged ETH long position with a floating profit of $850,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948425726591569920</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdaily&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; is long on PUMP and is currently down more than $9.00M in unrealized losses.hypurrscan data shows that &quot;Machi Big Brother&apos;s&quot; 5x leveraged long PUMP position and spot position have a total floating loss of over $9.00M. In addition, he also holds a 5x leveraged HYP</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948425726591569920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroStrategy Increases Senior Note Offering to $2.00 Billion, Plans to Use STRC Proceeds to Increase Bitcoin HoldingsMicroStrategy has increased its latest round of preferred stock issuance from $500 million to $2.00 billion, intending to price its Series A perpetual preferred stock &quot;Stretch&quot; at $90 per share. This round of issuance is led by Morgan Stanley, Barclays, Moelis &amp; Co., and TD Securities, with plans to issue 5.00 million shares. The funds raised will be used for purposes including the purchase of Bitcoin. To date, MicroStrategy holds a total of 607,770 Bitcoin, with a market value of approximately $72.40 billion. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948422535078547456</link>
      <description>3 hours ago吴说MicroStrategy Increases Senior Note Offering to $2.00 Billion, Plans to Use STRC Proceeds to Increase Bitcoin HoldingsMicroStrategy has increased its latest round of preferred stock issuance from $500 million to $2.00 billion, intending to price its Series A perpetual preferred stock &quot;S</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948422535078547456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase: Crypto market inflows have reached $60.00B so far this year, with investors&apos; interest in altcoins on the riseJPMorgan Chase analysts estimate that $600.00B in capital has flowed into digital assets since the beginning of the year, mainly driven by inflows into crypto funds, active trading in CME futures, and venture capital fundraising activities. Analysts point out that inflows have grown by nearly 50.00% since the end of May and are on track to easily surpass last year&apos;s historical record. Analysts say that the increasingly friendly regulatory environment in the United States is one of the key drivers. Investor interest in altcoins is also on the rise. Among them, Ethereum is the biggest beneficiary due to its dominance in decentralized finance (DeFi) and smart contracts, and its increasing inclusion in corporate treasury allocations along with Bitcoin. More and more asset management companies intend to launch crypto ETFs based on altcoins and introduce staking mechanisms. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948423189821984768</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyJPMorgan Chase: Crypto market inflows have reached $60.00B so far this year, with investors&apos; interest in altcoins on the riseJPMorgan Chase analysts estimate that $600.00B in capital has flowed into digital assets since the beginning of the year, mainly driven by inflows into crypto</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948423189821984768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 1.96M FARTCOIN from Kraken and exchanged it for $2.72M USDCAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale address withdrew approximately 1.96M FARTCOIN from the Kraken exchange and exchanged them for $2.72M USDC at a price of approximately $1.39 per coin. The relevant address is: HL6s4Nr9hKG2Nz7RjpaJbhnRPgKSCrPRppTJyQm1C5zU. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948420702540992512</link>
      <description>4 hours agoOdailyA whale withdrew 1.96M FARTCOIN from Kraken and exchanged it for $2.72M USDCAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale address withdrew approximately 1.96M FARTCOIN from the Kraken exchange and exchanged them for $2.72M USDC at a price of approximately $1.39 per coin. The relevan</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948420702540992512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celestia buys back over 43 million TIA held by Polychain, plans to transfer them to new investors and unlock them in batchesThe Celestia Foundation has announced an agreement with Polychain Capital to purchase 43,451,616.09 TIA from the latter for $62.50M. To complete this transaction, Polychain will unstake all of its staked TIA. The Foundation will allocate these TIA to new investors and use a staggered unlocking method, with the unlocking period starting on August 16 and ending on November 14. According to previous disclosures, Polychain invested approximately $20.00M in the Celestia project. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948414232592191488</link>
      <description>4 hours ago吴说Celestia buys back over 43 million TIA held by Polychain, plans to transfer them to new investors and unlock them in batchesThe Celestia Foundation has announced an agreement with Polychain Capital to purchase 43,451,616.09 TIA from the latter for $62.50M. To complete this transaction,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948414232592191488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today&apos;s on-chain fund flow: Arbitrum net inflow of $25.00M, Base net outflow of $44.90MOn July 24, according to Artemis data, Arbitrum saw a net inflow of $25.00M today, and Ethereum saw a net inflow of $14.30M; Base saw a net outflow of $44.90M, and Starknet saw a net outflow of $5.90M. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413262491619328</link>
      <description>4 hours agoTechFlowToday&apos;s on-chain fund flow: Arbitrum net inflow of $25.00M, Base net outflow of $44.90MOn July 24, according to Artemis data, Arbitrum saw a net inflow of $25.00M today, and Ethereum saw a net inflow of $14.30M; Base saw a net outflow of $44.90M, and Starknet saw a net outflow of</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413262491619328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. House of Representatives promotes the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, emphasizing its non-partisan natureOn July 24, according to Eleanor Terrett, at a press conference before the House of Representatives&apos; August recess, House Majority Whip Tom Emmer said he would work hard to win more Senate Democrats&apos; support for his Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act. The bill aims to make it clear that blockchain developers and infrastructure providers (such as miners, validators, and node operators) are not considered money transmitters as long as they do not host funds. Emmer called the bill a &quot;non-partisan issue,&quot; emphasizing that there are clear rules to protect Americans and innovators, and said he welcomes the Senate&apos;s adjustments and improvements to the bill during the review process. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948411763346706432</link>
      <description>4 hours agoPANewsU.S. House of Representatives promotes the Blockchain Regulatory Certainty Act, emphasizing its non-partisan natureOn July 24, according to Eleanor Terrett, at a press conference before the House of Representatives&apos; August recess, House Majority Whip Tom Emmer said he would work har</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948411763346706432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two new wallets accumulate $388.00M worth of ETHAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, two newly created wallets have accumulated ETH worth $388.00M, of which: wallet 0x3dF received 87,275 ETH worth $326.00M from Galaxy OTC; wallet 0x286 received 16,472 ETH worth $61.43M from FalconX. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413148486242304</link>
      <description>4 hours agoOdailyTwo new wallets accumulate $388.00M worth of ETHAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, two newly created wallets have accumulated ETH worth $388.00M, of which: wallet 0x3dF received 87,275 ETH worth $326.00M from Galaxy OTC; wallet 0x286 received 16,472 ETH worth $61.43M from FalconX</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948413148486242304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>