<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:44:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise is &apos;actively evaluating&apos; the SEC&apos;s pause on its initially approved crypto index fundBitwise says it&apos;s &quot;actively evaluating&quot; the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&apos;s recent move to pause the conversion of its cryptocurrency index fund after initially approving it to list and trade.

In a statement, a Bitwise spokesperson said the crypto index fund manager was &quot;thrilled by the SEC&apos;s accelerated approval,&quot; and noted they&apos;re assessing the pause.

&quot;The subsequent stay is a new development that we’re actively evaluating,&quot; the spokesperson said in an email on Wednesday. &quot;We’ve been encouraged by the constructive engagement with the SEC under the new administration and remain committed to working productively to expand access to crypto — just as we’ve done over the last seven years.”

On Tuesday, the SEC&apos;s Division of Trading and Markets granted an &quot;accelerated approval&quot; of the Bitwise 10 Crypto Index ETF, according to a filing. However, SEC Assistant Secretary Sherry R. Haywood later stayed the action and said the commission would review it.

The Bitwise 10 Crypto Index Fund, which trades under the ticker “BITW,” currently consists of exposure to BTC, ETH, XRP, SOL, Polkadot, among others, on a market cap-weighted basis, according to its website.

This marks the second instance the SEC has hit pause on an initial approval to convert a fund to an ETF. A similar scenario occurred with Grayscale&apos;s proposed conversion of its Digital Large Cap Fund, which was initially approved and later put under review. Grayscale has said it &quot;remains committed&quot; to continue trying to list the fund.

This comes amid a broader shift as the SEC is also considering a wide array of crypto ETFs, from ones that track SOL to DOGE in the face of a friendlier regulatory environment for crypto following President Donald Trump&apos;s inauguration in January. [Bitwise]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948102244129378304</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoThe BlockBitwise is &apos;actively evaluating&apos; the SEC&apos;s pause on its initially approved crypto index fundBitwise says it&apos;s &quot;actively evaluating&quot; the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&apos;s recent move to pause the conversion of its cryptocurrency index fund after initially approving it t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948102244129378304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burwick Law Expands RICO Lawsuit Against Pump, Listing Solana and Jito Executives as Co-ConspiratorsBurwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against memecoin platform Pump, naming the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito Labs, and their executives as co-conspirators. The lawsuit alleges illegal gambling, wire fraud, securities fraud, intellectual property theft, and unlicensed money transmission, and invokes the Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO). [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948101169599025152</link>
      <description>23 minutes ago吴说Burwick Law Expands RICO Lawsuit Against Pump, Listing Solana and Jito Executives as Co-ConspiratorsBurwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against memecoin platform Pump, naming the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito Labs, and their executives as co-co</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948101169599025152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric Adjusts Fund Strategy, Liquid Alpha Fund Shifts to Illiquid InvestmentsAsymmetric founder and CEO Joe McCann stated that the company will adjust its fund structure, with its Liquid Alpha Fund exiting liquidity trading strategies and allowing investors to opt out regardless of the lock-up period or transfer funds to specific illiquid investments. He emphasized that all valid redemption requests have been fulfilled since the fund&apos;s inception. Despite the fund&apos;s poor performance this year, Asymmetric&apos;s other investment vehicles are still operating, the venture capital strategy remains unchanged, and the company will continue to support the development of the blockchain space. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948098518685650944</link>
      <description>34 minutes ago吴说Asymmetric Adjusts Fund Strategy, Liquid Alpha Fund Shifts to Illiquid InvestmentsAsymmetric founder and CEO Joe McCann stated that the company will adjust its fund structure, with its Liquid Alpha Fund exiting liquidity trading strategies and allowing investors to opt out regardless</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948098518685650944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first crypto policy report will be released to the public on July 30.Bo Hines, Executive Director of the Presidential Digital Assets Advisory Council, stated that the Presidential Digital Assets Working Group has completed its 180-day report and is expected to release it to the public on July 30. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948087647477501952</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说The first crypto policy report will be released to the public on July 30.Bo Hines, Executive Director of the Presidential Digital Assets Advisory Council, stated that the Presidential Digital Assets Working Group has completed its 180-day report and is expected to release it to the publi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948087647477501952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s AI plan eases data center rules, strips federal DEI guidelinesThe White House on Wednesday released its plan to make the United States a global leader in artificial intelligence research and development.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948085881256087552</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsTrump&apos;s AI plan eases data center rules, strips federal DEI guidelinesThe White House on Wednesday released its plan to make the United States a global leader in artificial intelligence research and development.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948085881256087552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Custody joins Ondo’s Global Markets AllianceZodia Custody, a digital assets custody platform backed by Standard Chartered, has joined the Global Markets Alliance, an initiative by Ondo Finance aimed at promoting interoperability across the tokenized assets market. As the Global Markets Alliance’s newest member, Zodia Custody adds to a group of industry players that include Solana Foundation, LayerZero, BitGo, Fireblocks, Jupiter, Trust Wallet, 1inch, Alpaca, and Bitget. Ondo Finance announced the Zodia Custody move via X. Like the other members, Zodia Custody will leverage its infrastructure, security and compliance features to help advance the tokenization of capital markets. The on-chain efforts aligns with the institution-first digital assets custodian’s traction across the ecosystem, efforts that include the support for institutional decentralized finance on the TON blockchain, Berachain and RWA platform Polymesh. The Global Markets Alliance’s areas of focus across the real-world assets on-chain ecosystem includes tokenized stocks, exchange-traded funds, money market funds and private credit. RWA on-chain is a rapidly expanding market, with major players, including BlackRock, Franklin Templeton, and Fidelity Investments, driving adoption to the next level. The key to growing tokenization lies in its feature that enables the bridging of traditional finance and blockchain, with real-world assets wrapped into tokens issued on the blockchain. Investors taking positions with these assets benefit from 24/7 trading, fractional ownership and on-chain transparency and accessibility. With institutional clients eyeing the tokenization opportunity, major Wall Street banks have had no option but to consider launching their own tokenized assets initiatives. Zodia, which also offers a staking solution, counts asset managers, banks, crypto natives, governments, hedge funds, and private wealth firms among its partners.  The platform recently launched Zodia Rewards, its opt-in token rewards program targeted for institutional clients. Clients can enjoy rewards on supported stablecoins, including USDC ( USDC ), Ethena USDe ( USDE ) and the Global Dollar Network. “Stablecoins are being adopted far beyond crypto capital markets, emerging as a tool to complement traditional financial rails for cross-border payments. We see this value, and as a custodian, we want to play our part to help unlock further capital efficiencies,” Anoosh Arevshatian, chief product officer at Zodia Custody, said at the time. [Ondo Finance]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948086047681875968</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsStandard Chartered-backed Zodia Custody joins Ondo’s Global Markets AllianceZodia Custody, a digital assets custody platform backed by Standard Chartered, has joined the Global Markets Alliance, an initiative by Ondo Finance aimed at promoting interoperability across the tokeniz</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948086047681875968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: XRP is now at $3.16009According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 10.13% in the past 24h. Now at $3.16009.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948070918004629504</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: XRP is now at $3.16009According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 10.13% in the past 24h. Now at $3.16009.$XRPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948070918004629504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil’s VERT launches private credit solution on the XRP LedgerVERT, a Brazil-based capital markets firm, has joined the growing trend of companies looking to tap into tokenization with a new solution on XRP Ledger. The fund management firm’s move comes as Wall Street giants such as Goldman Sachs, BNY and JPMorgan a tokenized assets market that has attracted products from fund behemoths like BlackRock, Fidelity and Franklin Templeton. XRP Ledger is powered by the XRP ( XRP ) token. VERT’s blockchain-based platform on the XRPL will focus on the issuance and management of private credit operations. Ripple expands its reach in LATAM with this initiative. According to the details, the on-chain venture goes live with the issuance of an Agribusiness Receivables Certificate. The RCA is a regulated credit instrument managed across a sector that accounts for over 20% of Brazil ’s gross domestic product. “Agribusiness plays an essential role in Brazil’s economy, and improving how credit is structured and tracked in this sector is a meaningful advancement,” said Silvio Pegado, managing director of Ripple in Latin America. The first CRA transaction will be valued at 700 million Brazilian real, or approximately $130 million. Recently, Token Relations revealed the total tokenized real-world assets on XRPL had grown by more than 2,260% in six months — from $5 million at the start of the year to over $118 million at the beginning of July. Mercado Bitcoin, Latin America’s largest cryptocurrency exchange and alternative asset investment platform, announced on July 4 that it will bring over $200 million in tokenized RWAs to the XRPL. The assets the platform plans to tokenize on the blockchain include fixed income and equity instruments. Guggenheim Capital is also tapping into the XRP Ledger. Its subsidiary, Guggenheim Treasury Services, issued U.S. Treasury-backed digital commercial paper on the Ripple blockchain platform. June also saw tokenized assets platform Ondo Finance unveil its short-term Treasuries bill OUSG , while Circle added native USDC ( USDC ) to XRP Ledger. VERT’s initiative will add to this traction as it helps Brazil’s capital markets come on-chain. The company aims to generate $500 million in value that will be on-chain. Benefits will include increased operational efficiency, transparency, and accessibility. As well as issuing private credit on the XRPL, VERT is integrating Ripple’s Ethereum-compatible protocol XRPL EVM Sidechain to leverage smart contracts for programmable automation among other functionality. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948069413860741120</link>
      <description>2 hours agocrypto.newsBrazil’s VERT launches private credit solution on the XRP LedgerVERT, a Brazil-based capital markets firm, has joined the growing trend of companies looking to tap into tokenization with a new solution on XRP Ledger. The fund management firm’s move comes as Wall Street giants s</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948069413860741120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNC Bank Partners with Coinbase to Launch Customer Crypto Trading ServicesAccording to Reuters, PNC Bank, the eighth-largest bank in the U.S., is partnering with Coinbase to roll out cryptocurrency trading services for its customers. PNC will leverage Coinbase&apos;s institutional-grade &quot;crypto-as-a-service&quot; platform to enable customers to buy, sell, and hold crypto assets, and will provide some banking services to Coinbase. [Reuters]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948059670664515584</link>
      <description>3 hours ago吴说PNC Bank Partners with Coinbase to Launch Customer Crypto Trading ServicesAccording to Reuters, PNC Bank, the eighth-largest bank in the U.S., is partnering with Coinbase to roll out cryptocurrency trading services for its customers. PNC will leverage Coinbase&apos;s institutional-grade &quot;cry</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948059670664515584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU diplomat: EU and US moving towards possible trade deal, with US benchmark tariffs on EU goods at 15%EU diplomat: The EU and the US are moving towards a possible trade agreement, with the US benchmark tariff on EU goods at 15.00%. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948058298900615168</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyEU diplomat: EU and US moving towards possible trade deal, with US benchmark tariffs on EU goods at 15%EU diplomat: The EU and the US are moving towards a possible trade agreement, with the US benchmark tariff on EU goods at 15.00%. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948058298900615168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tron Inc. to Ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on July 24Tron Inc. (Nasdaq: TRON) has announced that it will hold an opening bell ceremony at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York on July 24th, US Eastern Time, hosted by Justin Sun, founder of TRON and Global Advisor of Tron Inc. This marks the company&apos;s official transformation into a technology company focused on blockchain and digital asset innovation. The company stated that the bell-ringing is not only an important milestone in the development of Tron Inc., but also highlights its long-term vision of driving shareholder value growth through innovation and strategic leadership. Formerly known as SRM Entertainment, the company is currently the listed company holding the most TRON (TRX) tokens. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948055775972233216</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyTron Inc. to Ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on July 24Tron Inc. (Nasdaq: TRON) has announced that it will hold an opening bell ceremony at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York on July 24th, US Eastern Time, hosted by Justin Sun, founder of TRON and Global Advisor of Tron In</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948055775972233216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase to List JITOSOL and MPLXCoinbase has announced the listing of Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL) and Metaplex (MPLX) on the Solana network, with plans to enable JITOSOL/USD and MPLX/USD trading pairs in phases starting July 24, 2025, at 9:00 AM (PT), pending liquidity conditions. The official reminder is not to send assets through other networks to prevent fund loss. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948053257041022976</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyCoinbase to List JITOSOL and MPLXCoinbase has announced the listing of Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL) and Metaplex (MPLX) on the Solana network, with plans to enable JITOSOL/USD and MPLX/USD trading pairs in phases starting July 24, 2025, at 9:00 AM (PT), pending liquidity conditions. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948053257041022976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the dayOn July 23, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the day. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948050492361347072</link>
      <description>3 hours agoTechFlowSpot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the dayOn July 23, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the day. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948050492361347072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US government&apos;s AI.Gov official website is officially launched, focusing on Trump&apos;s AI strategyOn July 23, the US government launched a new AI.Gov official website today, systematically launching the &quot;American AI Action Plan&quot;, proposing three pillar strategies of &quot;accelerating innovation, building AI infrastructure, and leading international AI diplomacy and security&quot;. The plan was led by President Donald Trump in the early days of his second term, emphasizing the improvement of national AI competitiveness by reducing regulation, supporting open source AI, strengthening infrastructure and international cooperation, and promoting the application of AI in key areas such as medicine, manufacturing, and national defense, in order to consolidate the United States&apos; global AI leadership. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948049419613573120</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsThe US government&apos;s AI.Gov official website is officially launched, focusing on Trump&apos;s AI strategyOn July 23, the US government launched a new AI.Gov official website today, systematically launching the &quot;American AI Action Plan&quot;, proposing three pillar strategies of &quot;accelerating i</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948049419613573120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today&apos;s on-chain fund flows: Polygon PoS net inflow of $58.00M, Ethereum net outflow of $72.90MOn July 23, according to Artemis data, Polygon PoS saw a net inflow of $58.00M today, and OP Mainnet saw a net inflow of $16.70M; Ethereum saw a net outflow of $72.90M, and Base saw a net outflow of $18.40M. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948047984687648768</link>
      <description>3 hours agoTechFlowToday&apos;s on-chain fund flows: Polygon PoS net inflow of $58.00M, Ethereum net outflow of $72.90MOn July 23, according to Artemis data, Polygon PoS saw a net inflow of $58.00M today, and OP Mainnet saw a net inflow of $16.70M; Ethereum saw a net outflow of $72.90M, and Base saw a ne</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948047984687648768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payment giant Block added to S&amp;P 500 index today, holding 8,584 BitcoinsPayment giant Block will officially join the S&amp;P 500 index today. Block currently holds 8,584 Bitcoin on its balance sheet. (CNBC) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948045730173751296</link>
      <description>4 hours agoOdailyPayment giant Block added to S&amp;P 500 index today, holding 8,584 BitcoinsPayment giant Block will officially join the S&amp;P 500 index today. Block currently holds 8,584 Bitcoin on its balance sheet. (CNBC) [Odaily]#Crypto Stocks$BTC$BLOCK$XYZShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948045730173751296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the entire network liquidation was $501.00M, mainly liquidating long positions.On July 23, according to Coinglass data, the total liquidation amount in the cryptocurrency market in the past 24 hours reached $501.00 million, of which $384.00 million were long liquidations and $117.00 million were short liquidations. The liquidation amount of ETH reached $107.00 million, BTC liquidated $50.61 million, and XRP liquidated $49.20 million. In the past 24 hours, 176,047 people were liquidated, and the largest single liquidation occurred on Binance&apos;s ETH-USDT trading pair, worth $3.97 million.  [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948043931521978368</link>
      <description>4 hours agoTechFlowIn the past 24 hours, the entire network liquidation was $501.00M, mainly liquidating long positions.On July 23, according to Coinglass data, the total liquidation amount in the cryptocurrency market in the past 24 hours reached $501.00 million, of which $384.00 million were long</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948043931521978368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Launches BMNR Options Trading on NYSE, Plans to Acquire 5% of Ethereum SupplyAccording to The Block, BitMine, an Ethereum vault and crypto mining company backed by Peter Thiel and ARK, launched options trading for its common stock BMNR on the New York Stock Exchange on Wednesday. BitMine plans to acquire 5% of the global Ethereum (ETH) supply. The company&apos;s stock price has risen sharply since announcing its shift to ETH accumulation, with Founders Fund now being the largest shareholder, and ARK Invest also purchasing $182.00M worth of shares this week to invest in ETH. As of July 17, the total value of ETH held by BitMine has exceeded $1.00B. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041435298729984</link>
      <description>4 hours agoForesightNewsBitMine Launches BMNR Options Trading on NYSE, Plans to Acquire 5% of Ethereum SupplyAccording to The Block, BitMine, an Ethereum vault and crypto mining company backed by Peter Thiel and ARK, launched options trading for its common stock BMNR on the New York Stock Exchange o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041435298729984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark launches SPK farm and other new features to optimize user revenue experienceOn July 23, the Spark platform recently launched a number of practical functions, including SPK farm (supply USDS to earn SPK), Overdrive (increase airdrop rewards), USDS (SPK farm) pool (stake SPK to enjoy SPK annualized income), and earning USDS points through Pendle. Users can increase their income by providing USDS, staking SPK, or participating in Overdrive activities, with no lock-up period and no additional threshold, further enriching the way to participate in DeFi. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948040730047483904</link>
      <description>4 hours agoPANewsSpark launches SPK farm and other new features to optimize user revenue experienceOn July 23, the Spark platform recently launched a number of practical functions, including SPK farm (supply USDS to earn SPK), Overdrive (increase airdrop rewards), USDS (SPK farm) pool (stake SPK to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948040730047483904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun May Be the Cause of Most Ethereum Withdrawal EventsOver the past week, people have withdrawn as much as $1.7 billion worth of Ethereum from the lending protocol Aave. The reduction in available liquidity has caused the protocol to charge borrowers interest rates exceeding 10%. Aave contributor Marc Zeller told DL News that Justin Sun may be the cause of most of the Ethereum withdrawals, as he regularly moves large sums of money in and out of the lending protocol, &quot;He&apos;s so unpredictable, he moves billions of dollars like I go to the supermarket to buy something.&quot; Over the past three days, wallets on Arkham that users have tagged as belonging to Justin Sun have withdrawn over $646.00 million worth of Ethereum from Aave. [DLNEWS]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041040732164096</link>
      <description>4 hours ago吴说Justin Sun May Be the Cause of Most Ethereum Withdrawal EventsOver the past week, people have withdrawn as much as $1.7 billion worth of Ethereum from the lending protocol Aave. The reduction in available liquidity has caused the protocol to charge borrowers interest rates exceeding 10%</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041040732164096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 19:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>