<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:59:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC: Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon to launch tokenized money market fundsAccording to CNBC, as cited by Jinshi, Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon will launch tokenized money market funds. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947985715131912192</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoForesightNewsCNBC: Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon to launch tokenized money market fundsAccording to CNBC, as cited by Jinshi, Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon will launch tokenized money market funds. [Foresight News]#ETFShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947985715131912192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Russia is using Kyrgyzstan’s crypto market to bypass sanctions: reportHas Russia turned Kyrgyzstan’s booming crypto market into a backdoor for moving funds? A new report sheds light on how Kyrgyz-registered exchanges are helping Russian networks evade sanctions. According to TRM Labs, Kyrgyzstan’s crypto industry has exploded from near-zero to billions in activity since passing its “On Virtual Assets” law back in 2022. By October 2024, authorities had issued 126 virtual asset service provider (VASP) licenses, with licensed platforms recording $4.2 billion in transactions in the first seven months of 2024 alone. But with the region’s relatively weak oversight on the local industry, the rapid growth has made it an attractive base for entities seeking to bypass sanctions. TRM Labs’ report points to crypto exchanges Grinex and Meer, which sprang up in Kyrgyzstan shortly after U.S. law enforcement disrupted Russia’s Garantex in March 2025. On-chain analysis suggests both firms, suspected to be successors, used similar wallet infrastructure and transaction patterns as Garantex, helping Russian users move funds through A7A5, a Russian ruble-tied stablecoin that has long come under scrutiny. Crypto.news reported earlier in June that an FT research revealed that the A7A5 stablecoin has quietly moved billions since launch, and has ties to sanctioned entities that suggest it may be part of broader efforts to bypass Western sanctions and enable cross-border payments for Russian entities. Another exchange, Envoys Vision Digital Exchange (EVDE), was found to have ties to wallets linked to the Rusich Group, a sanctioned Russian paramilitary organization. Many of these platforms also display signs of being shell companies, including identical registration addresses, shared founders, and recycled contact information, suggesting coordinated or shared illicit control. TRM Labs warns that while Kyrgyzstan may be exploited rather than complicit, weak oversight leaves the door wide open. Without tighter controls on VASP registrations, clearer ownership rules, and stronger checks on shell companies, Russia’s financial networks will keep exploiting the country’s crypto infrastructure. If left unaddressed, similar tactics could also spread to neighboring Kazakhstan and Uzbekistan, which are already rolling out crypto-friendly regulations, undermining international sanctions. [TRM Labs]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983858556801024</link>
      <description>23 minutes agocrypto.newsHow Russia is using Kyrgyzstan’s crypto market to bypass sanctions: reportHas Russia turned Kyrgyzstan’s booming crypto market into a backdoor for moving funds? A new report sheds light on how Kyrgyz-registered exchanges are helping Russian networks evade sanctions. Accordin</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983858556801024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARA Announces $850.0M Convertible Notes Offering to Purchase Additional BTCMARA Holdings has announced plans for a private placement of zero-coupon convertible senior notes with an aggregate principal amount of $850.0M, due in 2032. MARA expects to grant the initial purchasers an option to purchase up to an additional $150.0M of notes within 13 days. MARA expects to use no more than $50.00M of the net proceeds from the offering to repurchase a portion of its 1.00% convertible notes due 2026 in privately negotiated transactions. The remaining funds will be used to acquire more Bitcoin, etc. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983664444411904</link>
      <description>24 minutes ago吴说MARA Announces $850.0M Convertible Notes Offering to Purchase Additional BTCMARA Holdings has announced plans for a private placement of zero-coupon convertible senior notes with an aggregate principal amount of $850.0M, due in 2032. MARA expects to grant the initial purchasers an op</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983664444411904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Benson: Trump said he would not fire PowellJuly 23 news, according to Jinshi, US Treasury Secretary Bessant said: We are not in a hurry to nominate the chairman of the Federal Reserve. The Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a little wrong&quot;. (Talking about interest rate decisions) I don&apos;t know what the Fed is thinking. The review of the Federal Reserve may be to set up a committee. The Bank of England has done a good job in reviewing its past monetary policy. The frustration of the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. Trump has said that he will not fire Powell. Economist El-Erian said that Powell should resign, which is a bit surprising. My regular talks with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell are still continuing. (Talking about Bowman as a candidate for Federal Reserve Chairman) Reluctant to reveal the name of the candidate. Powell has not yet indicated that he will leave his position on the board. Since the global financial crisis, regulation has been too strict. Trump always has a plan, it&apos;s just not always obvious. Trump has created the biggest negotiating leverage on tariffs. The selection of a successor to Governor Kugler is being carried out simultaneously. US Treasury Secretary Bessant (talking about Trump&apos;s tariff plan) The market reaction was relatively calm. U.S. Treasury Secretary Benson also said that he believes regional banks are strong contenders for the Federal Reserve chairmanship. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983109521215488</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoPANewsUS Treasury Secretary Benson: Trump said he would not fire PowellJuly 23 news, according to Jinshi, US Treasury Secretary Bessant said: We are not in a hurry to nominate the chairman of the Federal Reserve. The Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a little wrong&quot;. (Talking about interest ra</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947983109521215488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Evening News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses BONK, becoming the largest Solana ecosystem Meme coin by market cap;
2. Analyst: Ethereum faces short-term pullback risk, but the current increase is still relatively small from a large cycle perspective;
3. Matrixport: The crypto market faces short-term volatility, but the overall upward trend is not over;
4. Merlin Founder: 2.0 upgrade officially released, aiming to create a &quot;yield-generating, tradable&quot; BTC;
5. Tether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits;
6. Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks will outperform Ethereum this cycle;
7. Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach a $15.80M financing agreement to increase Bitcoin holdings;
8. Crypto mining company MARA to issue $850.00M in convertible notes to purchase more Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982797888622592</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailyPlanet Evening News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses BONK, becoming the largest Solana ecosystem Meme coin by market cap;
2. Analyst: Ethereum faces short-term pullback risk, but the current increase is still relatively small from a large cycle perspective;
3. Matrixport: The crypt</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982797888622592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Trump says he will not fire PowellAccording to Jinshi, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent said, &quot;We are not in a hurry to nominate the Federal Reserve Chairman. Frustration with the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. Trump has said he will not fire Powell. Powell has also not indicated that he will leave his board position.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981973129072640</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoForesightNewsUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Trump says he will not fire PowellAccording to Jinshi, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent said, &quot;We are not in a hurry to nominate the Federal Reserve Chairman. Frustration with the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981973129072640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Bessent: Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off&quot;US Treasury Secretary Bessent says the Federal Reserve&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off,&quot; and (regarding interest rate decisions) he doesn&apos;t know what the Federal Reserve is considering. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982806327562240</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoOdailyTreasury Secretary Bessent: Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off&quot;US Treasury Secretary Bessent says the Federal Reserve&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off,&quot; and (regarding interest rate decisions) he doesn&apos;t know what the Federal Reserve is considering. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982806327562240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate launches the second round of VIP financial carnival, complete the task and win a box of MaotaiOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch the second phase of the &quot;VIP Financial Management Summer Carnival&quot; for a limited time. The registration period is from 18:00 on July 22 to 18:00 on August 5 (UTC+8). After VIP users complete the registration, participate in Yubibao Financial Management and complete the challenge to win a whole box of Feitian Moutai. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981438208512000</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoPANewsGate launches the second round of VIP financial carnival, complete the task and win a box of MaotaiOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch the second phase of the &quot;VIP Financial Management Summer Carnival&quot; for a limited time. The registration period i</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981438208512000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) on Binance Smart Chain (BSC), causing losses of more than $600,000. Since the contract is not open source, investigations show that the vulnerability stems from the lack of slippage protection, and the attacker used a fake liquidity pool to harvest TA tokens (0x539ae81a166e5e80aed211731563e549c411b140) and sold them in a legitimate pool for profit. BlockSec Phalcon strongly recommends that users who have authorized the contract immediately revoke permissions to prevent further losses. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoPANewsSecurity agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly impose a 30% tariff on US products worth about 100.00 billion euros (about 117.00 billion US dollars). A spokesman for the European Commission said on Wednesday that as part of the first wave of countermeasures, the EU will combine the already approved tariff list for 21.00 billion euros of US goods and the previously proposed tariff list for another 72.00 billion euros of US products into a package. According to people familiar with the matter, US exports, including Boeing aircraft, US-made cars and industrial products such as bourbon whiskey, will face tariffs matching Trump&apos;s threat of 30%. These people said that the tariffs will be ready to take effect next month, but only if the negotiations break down and the United States implements its tax measures after the August deadline. An unnamed government official said that in the absence of an agreement, Berlin is even willing to support the activation of the EU&apos;s &quot;anti-coercion tool&quot; (ACI). This tool will only be activated if an agreement cannot be reached. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoPANewsEU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly imp</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+8) on July 23. At the same time, the relevant tokens will no longer support Simple Earn and flexible lending services. (This news was generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoOdailyOKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar (XLM) Risks a 40% Drop as Bearish Divergence ReturnsStellar’s (XLM) price trades near $0.47 after a 103% month-on-month. The rally has stalled into small daily candles (mostly indecisive Doji candles) . And two daily signals now lean lower: a heavy block of leveraged longs sits under price, and slipping momentum. Key support levels might be at risk. Leverage Pocket Below $0.40 Raises Cascade Risk Price is hovering above $0.45, but Bitget’s 30‑day XLM/USDT liquidation map shows roughly $79.8 million of long exposure compared with about $42.1 million in shorts , with the cumulative cluster highlighted under $0.40. Each step down would trigger smaller pockets first, then the dense area under $0.40 can amplify selling as forced closures hit the order book. A liquidation map plots where leveraged positions get auto-closed; when the largest clusters sit below spot, even a modest drop can snowball. Daily RSI Divergence Mirrors December Slide Since July 14, the price has held near the highs while the Relative Strength Index ( RSI ) on the daily chart has made lower highs. The last time XLM showed this pattern, in late December, the price fell over 40%. RSI measures the strength of recent price movements on a 0–100 scale. When price is steady or rising but RSI eases, momentum is not confirming the move, and pullback risk increases. With leverage and liquidation risks waiting below, that loss of momentum becomes more dangerous, supporting the “ XLM price correction ” logic. Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here . XLM Price Now Eyes Key Support Levels A Fibonacci retracement drawn from the $0.21 low to the $0.52 high frames the likely supports if selling starts: $0.44 (0.236) being the strongest level will multiple support hits. Fibonacci levels mark common pullback areas, and when they overlap with liquidation clusters, reactions tend to be sharper. XLM is currently sitting above $0.44. A daily close beneath that level would put $0.40 in focus. Below $0.40, the liquidation hypothesis wins, so a break there could speed a move toward $0.33. A 40% decline (inspired by the December 2024 pattern) from the $0.52 high lands under $0.33. Under $0.28 (if the $0.33 level breaks), the entire XLM price structure could turn bearish in the short term. Invalidation is straightforward: a firm daily close back above $0.52, with RSI turning up and liquidation risk thinning out, would neutralize this bearish setup and restore the upside case.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947980641638879232</link>
      <description>58 minutes agobeincryptoStellar (XLM) Risks a 40% Drop as Bearish Divergence ReturnsStellar’s (XLM) price trades near $0.47 after a 103% month-on-month. The rally has stalled into small daily candles (mostly indecisive Doji candles) . And two daily signals now lean lower: a heavy block of leveraged</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947980641638879232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares secures MiCA license in France to cement EU presenceIn addition to its leadership in the EU, CoinShares has been actively expanding in the US market since officially entering in 2023, aiming to compete with major industry peers.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974271371907072</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCoinShares secures MiCA license in France to cement EU presenceIn addition to its leadership in the EU, CoinShares has been actively expanding in the US market since officially entering in 2023, aiming to compete with major industry peers.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974271371907072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Pastor Couple Charged in $3.40M Crypto Token ScamProsecutors in Denver, Colorado, have announced that online pastor Eli Regalado and his wife, Kaitlyn, have been indicted on a total of 40 counts for allegedly orchestrating a fraud involving the INDXcoin crypto token. The couple is accused of raising over $3.40 million between 2022 and 2023 by promoting the token to religious communities through their self-built Kingdom Wealth Exchange platform. At least $1.30 million of this amount was allegedly used for personal expenses, including home renovations. The indictment states that approximately 300 investors suffered total losses as a result. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974177159450624</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Colorado Pastor Couple Charged in $3.40M Crypto Token ScamProsecutors in Denver, Colorado, have announced that online pastor Eli Regalado and his wife, Kaitlyn, have been indicted on a total of 40 counts for allegedly orchestrating a fraud involving the INDXcoin crypto token. The couple</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974177159450624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a &quot;buy&quot; rating with a target price of $35.00.According to CoinDesk, Jefferies initiated coverage of Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a &quot;buy&quot; rating and a price target of $35.00 in its latest research report. The report noted that the passage of the GENIUS Act in the United States has improved the crypto regulatory environment, providing a favorable market structure for Galaxy. Galaxy is also expected to benefit from the growing demand for AI data centers by leasing a 393 megawatt data center in Texas. Currently, approximately two-thirds of its company value comes from its data center business. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947973963057008640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a &quot;buy&quot; rating with a target price of $35.00.According to CoinDesk, Jefferies initiated coverage of Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a &quot;buy&quot; rating and a price target of $35.00 in its latest research report. The report noted that the passage of the GEN</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947973963057008640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $1.9 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $1.3 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to join.Data shows that the Ethereum validator exit queue has surged in the past week, with approximately 521,000 ETH (worth approximately $1.9 billion at current prices) waiting to exit the Ethereum network. The number of ETH requested to exit has increased significantly since July 16, and the exit waiting time has been extended to 8 to 9 days, the longest waiting time since the beginning of 2024. At the same time, more than 359,500 ETH are queued to join the network, worth approximately $1.3 billion, with an expected activation delay of approximately 6 days. This situation reflects two opposing forces in the market: on the one hand, some stakers may be choosing to take profits after Ethereum rebounded 162.00% from its April low, leading to a surge in the exit queue; on the other hand, new deposits driven by regulatory benefits and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue, such as listed companies like SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion increasing their ETH holdings and staking. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947972733899444224</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyApproximately $1.9 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $1.3 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to join.Data shows that the Ethereum validator exit queue has surged in the past week, with approximately 521,000 ETH (worth approxima</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947972733899444224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value foundation of the ecosystem, Giants Protocol will advance its originally scheduled phased lock-up plan, locking 90% of the circulating tokens through smart contracts to ensure market stability and token value support. Giants Protocol stated that several international listed luxury goods groups have recently taken the initiative to contact the project team, intending to obtain priority access to its RWA asset on-chain services by holding G tokens. The official statement said: &quot;As traditional luxury assets accelerate on-chain, G is gradually becoming a key bridge connecting Web2 luxury assets and the Web3 protocol layer.&quot; [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGiants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value foundation</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been partially liquidated, and there is still a floating loss of $266,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyJames Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been parti</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Capital to support its Bitcoin funding strategy. The ATM-style financing tool allows Hilbert Group to flexibly withdraw funds in the next 36 months to purchase more Bitcoin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsHilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Capital</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadian dollars, with funds coming from the company&apos;s existing cash reserves. As of July 22, 2025, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings increased to 28.89, equivalent to 2,889,000,000.00 satoshis. Based on the company&apos;s 206 million outstanding shares, the number of bitcoins held per share increased to 14.01 satoshis, an increase of more than 8.49 times from 1.65 satoshis / share on June 26, an increase of 750.00%. The company&apos;s cumulative investment in bitcoins reached 4.5 million Canadian dollars, with an average holding cost of 155,800.00 Canadian dollars per coin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCanadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadian do</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>