<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:19:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades opened a 40x long position on BTC, worth approximately $100.00MAccording to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, AguilaTrades has turned to BTC after losing money on ETH long positions. It has now opened a 40x leverage BTC long position, holding 840 BTC (approximately $100.00M), with an opening price of $118,033.30. The trader&apos;s current two positions are still being increased or decreased through TWAP accordingly. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947555813858234368</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoForesightNewsAguilaTrades opened a 40x long position on BTC, worth approximately $100.00MAccording to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, AguilaTrades has turned to BTC after losing money on ETH long positions. It has now opened a 40x leverage BTC long position, holding 840 BTC (approximately $100</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947555813858234368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources: Bank of Japan expected to stick to gradual rate hike stance after Ishiba&apos;s Upper House election lossAccording to sources, Bank of Japan officials believe there is little need to change their stance on gradually raising interest rates after Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba&apos;s setback in the Upper House election. Although officials will continue to closely monitor the government&apos;s fiscal policy, they still believe that continuing to raise the benchmark interest rate is appropriate if the economic outlook is as expected. Sources said the Policy Board, led by Bank of Japan Governor Kazuo Ueda, is likely to keep the interest rate unchanged at 0.50% at its meeting next week. Given that trade negotiations between Japan and the United States are still ongoing, officials want to assess the impact of the agreement on inflation trends and the economic outlook before raising interest rates again. Sources said that while the election results will not change the Bank of Japan&apos;s policy path at present, some officials believe that it is necessary to be wary of the upside risks to inflation that may result from a significant easing of fiscal policy. Officials have noted that inflation risks are rising as soaring food prices such as rice push up price increases more than expected. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947554977191055360</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailySources: Bank of Japan expected to stick to gradual rate hike stance after Ishiba&apos;s Upper House election lossAccording to sources, Bank of Japan officials believe there is little need to change their stance on gradually raising interest rates after Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947554977191055360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase explores lending secured by clients’ cryptocurrencies: FTJPMorgan Chase is exploring plans to offer loans secured by customers’ cryptocurrency holdings, signaling a broader embrace of crypto assets by traditional financial institutions.

FT reported on Tuesday, citing sources familiar with the matter, that the bank is weighing plans to allow clients to borrow against crypto assets such as Bitcoin and Ether as early as next year, though the details remain subject to change.

Jamie Dimon, chief executive of JPMorgan Chase, has consistently expressed skepticism toward Bitcoin, but in May he acknowledged that the bank would facilitate client access to the cryptocurrency — though it does not plan to offer custody services.

According to the FT article, JPMorgan has already taken preliminary steps into the crypto sector, including plans to offer loans against crypto exchange-traded funds.

Jamie Dimon, chief executive of JPMorgan Chase, has repeatedly reaffirmed his negative stance on Bitcoin but acknowledged in May that the bank would work to allow clients to buy Bitcoin. In May, — but it will not keep custody.

The Block has reached out to JPMorgan for further comment.

The bank&apos;s move comes amid crypto-friendly regulatory shifts in the U.S., with President Donald Trump signing the GENIUS Act, a landmark stablecoin bill, last week.

The GENIUS bill would establish a federal regulatory framework for stablecoins, requiring them to be fully backed by U.S. dollars or other highly liquid assets. It would also mandate annual audits for issuers with a market capitalization exceeding $50 billion and establish rules for issuance by foreign entities. [Financial Times]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947554903526494208</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoThe BlockJPMorgan Chase explores lending secured by clients’ cryptocurrencies: FTJPMorgan Chase is exploring plans to offer loans secured by customers’ cryptocurrency holdings, signaling a broader embrace of crypto assets by traditional financial institutions.

FT reported on Tuesday,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947554903526494208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 2,143 ETH from Binance and transferred it to TreehouseFi to earn yield.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,143 ETH, worth approximately $7.93M, from Binance and transferred it to TreehouseFi to earn yield. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947554820139536384</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoForesightNewsA whale withdrew 2,143 ETH from Binance and transferred it to TreehouseFi to earn yield.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,143 ETH, worth approximately $7.93M, from Binance and transferred it to TreehouseFi to earn yield. [Foresight News]#DeFi$ETH$MAG</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947554820139536384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Wall Street Crypto IPO Craze May Extend Bitcoin Bull Market CycleOn July 22, according to a recent report by independent analyst Markus Thielen, as several crypto companies prepare to go public, Wall Street investment banks intend to keep Bitcoin at a high level to create a favorable market environment for the upcoming IPOs. Currently, several companies, including Circle, have submitted prospectuses, and new projects are lining up to go public almost every week. At the same time, the stock prices of crypto-related listed companies have risen sharply, with MicroStrategy up 47.00%, Coinbase up 67.00%, Robinhood up 180.00%, and Circle up as much as 597.00%. This upsurge has not only boosted market sentiment and sustained investor profits, but also rapidly increased attention and enthusiasm for crypto company IPOs, which is expected to extend Bitcoin&apos;s current bull market cycle. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947552419877769216</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoTechFlowMatrixport: Wall Street Crypto IPO Craze May Extend Bitcoin Bull Market CycleOn July 22, according to a recent report by independent analyst Markus Thielen, as several crypto companies prepare to go public, Wall Street investment banks intend to keep Bitcoin at a high level to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947552419877769216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet has integrated the Plasma public chain and supports stablecoin payments.Bitget Wallet has announced the integration of the Layer 1 blockchain network Plasma, allowing users to directly connect to the Plasma testnet through Bitget Wallet and experience the network&apos;s low-cost, high-speed stablecoin payment environment. Bitget Wallet has a built-in &quot;Faucet,&quot; supporting the free collection of XPL test tokens for exploring the Plasma network ecosystem and interactions. XPL is the native token of the Plasma network, used to pay transaction fees and priority processing fees. During the testnet phase, XPL will be used to simulate real transactions and encourage user participation in network interaction. Officials stated that Bitget Wallet will also launch incentive activities in conjunction with Plasma ecosystem partners to further promote user growth and ecosystem expansion. Plasma is a Layer 1 blockchain designed specifically for stablecoin payments, supporting zero Gas USDT transfers and allowing the use of USDT or BTC as network fees, while being compatible with the Ethereum development framework. The project is invested in by institutions such as Tether and is expected to become an important infrastructure for global stablecoin payments in the future. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947552475603292160</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet has integrated the Plasma public chain and supports stablecoin payments.Bitget Wallet has announced the integration of the Layer 1 blockchain network Plasma, allowing users to directly connect to the Plasma testnet through Bitget Wallet and experience the network&apos;s</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947552475603292160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derive Research Head: The gap between Solana&apos;s 30-day realized volatility and implied volatility is wideningSean Dawson, Head of Research at options trading platform Derive, said that the gap between Solana&apos;s 30-day realized volatility and implied volatility is widening. Implied volatility has more than tripled, from 4% to 14%. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947549726820028416</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoForesightNewsDerive Research Head: The gap between Solana&apos;s 30-day realized volatility and implied volatility is wideningSean Dawson, Head of Research at options trading platform Derive, said that the gap between Solana&apos;s 30-day realized volatility and implied volatility is widening. I</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947549726820028416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital Rush into NFT Tokens Puts PENGU’s Rally at RiskPudgy Penguins (PENGU) faces pressure amid a surge in interest in NFTs (non-fungible tokens). This move could pull capital away from the trending meme coin, potentially influencing its price. Meanwhile, investors hope for a PENGU ETF (exchange-traded fund) following Canary Capital’s March filing. PENGU Faces New Competition as NFT Tokens Attract Growing Investment Pudgy Penguins meme coin has been the center of attention for months, since Canary Capital filed for a PENGU ETF. Hype around the PENGU meme coin invigorated in late June, following Justin Sun’s move to join the huddle. Amidst the frenzy and hopes for a PENGU ETF, the token soared, with analysts projecting even more gains. However, the optimism may no longer be sustainable amid renewed interest in NFT tokens. Over the weekend, Ethereum ignited renewed interest in non-fungible tokens, unveiling the NFT Torch ahead of its 10th anniversary. With it came a frenzy of NFT buying, with a single wallet scooping 48 CryptoPunk NFTs for $8.5 million. Analysts also noted an acceleration in the purchases, causing a surge in the CryptoPunk NFT floor price. According to Shotgun, a popular user on X (Twitter), whales are showing conviction with legacy collections outperforming, suggesting the market may be rotating back to quality NFTs. Legacy NFT projects are getting heavy buys and pumps. According to data on Artemis, the NFT sector is already outperforming the broader market, rising by over 200% in the last month. Notably, the NFT sector has more than tripled the Ethereum market. Despite the euphoria around PENGU and Pudgy Penguins NFTs, CryptoPunks are leading the sector in market capitalization metrics. However, on 24-hour sales metrics, BAYC (Bored Ape Yacht Club) and Mutant Ape Yacht Club face stiff competition. Capital Flows Signal Appetite for Other NFT Projects Beyond PENGU Analysts are looking for PENGU-like opportunities, with ANIME as a prospective choice. Tommy, a trader and popular user on X, highlights ANIME as the best liquid NFT beta after the token bottomed out recently. The interest in the ANIME token may be ascribed to Animecoin’s recent announcement involving a Burger King and Naruto collaboration coming to the US. While Animecoin does not have any direct affiliations with either party in the prospective partnership, it may be leveraging Burger King and Naruto to target anime fans. Meanwhile, other analysts have also highlighted DOOD as a possible next PENGU. Despite no ETF prospects for the DOOD coin, which is associated with the Doodles NFT project, analysts say it also has strong fundamentals. Notably, both DOOD and PENGU are Solana meme coins. PENGU benefits from the ETF buzz and whale buys. It also has a supply of 76.7 billion. On the other hand, its RSI (Relative Strength Index) above 80 suggests the token may be overbought. Meanwhile, DOOD’s smaller supply of 10 billion could mean bigger price potential, with its RSI suggesting still more room for further upside. Another NFT trader highlighted that Doodles NFT outperformed the DOOD token, which could bode well for the meme coin’s price.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947550500014804992</link>
      <description>47 minutes agobeincryptoCapital Rush into NFT Tokens Puts PENGU’s Rally at RiskPudgy Penguins (PENGU) faces pressure amid a surge in interest in NFTs (non-fungible tokens). This move could pull capital away from the trending meme coin, potentially influencing its price. Meanwhile, investors hope for</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947550500014804992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyShell.AI Launches Application Building Agent ShellAgent 2.0AI consumer layer MyShell.AI tweeted that it has launched the application building agent ShellAgent 2.0. Users can build backends, set up hosting, design UIs, and publish applications by conversing with AI. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947545969059188736</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoForesightNewsMyShell.AI Launches Application Building Agent ShellAgent 2.0AI consumer layer MyShell.AI tweeted that it has launched the application building agent ShellAgent 2.0. Users can build backends, set up hosting, design UIs, and publish applications by conversing with AI. [Fore</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947545969059188736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWF Partner: The Crypto Altcoin Season Has Just BegunDWF Labs Managing Partner Andrei Grachev posted, &quot;The altcoin season in cryptocurrency has just begun, and Nasdaq-listed companies are about to usher in the altcoin season as well.&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544913524838400</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoOdailyDWF Partner: The Crypto Altcoin Season Has Just BegunDWF Labs Managing Partner Andrei Grachev posted, &quot;The altcoin season in cryptocurrency has just begun, and Nasdaq-listed companies are about to usher in the altcoin season as well.&quot; [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544913524838400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito announces that its Web3 crowdfunding platform Capital Launchpad is now liveOn July 22, Kaito, an AI-driven Web3 data provider, announced on the X platform that Capital Launchpad is now online and users can register on Yaps. A FAQ page has been added and will be updated based on the feedback and questions received. The financing cycle on Capital Launchpad includes the pre-commitment stage, commitment stage, review stage, optimization stage, and FCFS stage. Currently, the platform only supports USDC on Base, and participants must undergo KYC/AML review, and users in some countries are excluded. Earlier news revealed that Kaito will launch the Web3 crowdfunding platform Capital Launchpad this week. The platform will allow users to participate in private token offerings and new project investments, using an allocation mechanism based on indicators such as social reputation and on-chain holdings to replace the traditional first-come, first-served model. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947543992476651520</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsKaito announces that its Web3 crowdfunding platform Capital Launchpad is now liveOn July 22, Kaito, an AI-driven Web3 data provider, announced on the X platform that Capital Launchpad is now online and users can register on Yaps. A FAQ page has been added and will be updated base</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947543992476651520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBTC is now supported on the Aptos networkAccording to official sources, the Aptos network now supports WBTC. Users can bridge WBTC to the Aptos network via Stargate. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544921967972352</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoOdailyWBTC is now supported on the Aptos networkAccording to official sources, the Aptos network now supports WBTC. Users can bridge WBTC to the Aptos network via Stargate. [Odaily]#Layer1$WBTC$APTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544921967972352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE eventBinance Wallet announced that users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE event through the Alpha activity page. Participating in this activity will consume 15 points. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544930419494912</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoOdailyBinance: Users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE eventBinance Wallet announced that users with no less than 225 Alpha points can participate in the Delphinus Lab TGE event through the Alpha activity page. Participating in this activity wi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947544930419494912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinwatch Launches Track Tool to Help Crypto Projects View Market Maker ActivityCoinwatch has launched Track, a tool to help crypto projects view activity in real-time via market maker API Keys, including buy and sell order depth, spreads, and trading volume, while protecting market maker privacy using a Trusted Execution Environment (TEE). It has currently integrated 12 market makers, including Amber, Ampersan, Auros, CyantArb, Flowdesk, Galaxy, GSR, IMC, Keyrock, LO:TECH, Pulsar, and STS Digital, with more to come. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542193967484928</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoForesightNewsCoinwatch Launches Track Tool to Help Crypto Projects View Market Maker ActivityCoinwatch has launched Track, a tool to help crypto projects view activity in real-time via market maker API Keys, including buy and sell order depth, spreads, and trading volume, while protect</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542193967484928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Advance Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial company strategy. In addition, this operation may be combined with existing operations, allowing the company to acquire an additional approximately 120 BTC, bringing the company&apos;s potential total holdings to 2,075 BTC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541171144511488</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Publicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Advance Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial co</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541171144511488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Capital B Raises Approximately €10.30M to Advance its Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) has announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial company strategy. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541141926989824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoChainCatcherPublicly Listed Capital B Raises Approximately €10.30M to Advance its Bitcoin Treasury StrategyAccording to the official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) has announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin fin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947541141926989824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury StrategyOn July 22, according to the official announcement, the European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its Bitcoin financial company strategy. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540361358626816</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowPublicly Listed Capital B Announces Approximately €10.30M Raise to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury StrategyOn July 22, according to the official announcement, the European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase of approximately €10.30M to promote its</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540361358626816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin miner Mawson has fired its CEO over alleged fraud and misconductAccording to The Miner Mag, Bitcoin mining company Mawson has fired CEO Rahul Mewawalla for breach of fiduciary duty and alleged fraud, and has filed a lawsuit in Delaware court in the United States. Rahul Mewawalla subsequently stated in a letter to the board of directors on July 17 that he &quot;respectfully but vehemently&quot; opposed the company&apos;s description of the events, noting that the board had publicly praised his leadership earlier this year. Previously, Mawson was sued by NYDIG&apos;s parent company Stone Ridge and its subsidiary Consensus Colocation, accusing it of unauthorized control of $30.00M worth of ASIC miners owned by NYDIG. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542411521839104</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitcoin miner Mawson has fired its CEO over alleged fraud and misconductAccording to The Miner Mag, Bitcoin mining company Mawson has fired CEO Rahul Mewawalla for breach of fiduciary duty and alleged fraud, and has filed a lawsuit in Delaware court in the United States. Rahul Mewawa</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947542411521839104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B raises approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin finance company strategyFrench listed company Capital B raised approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy. In addition, the operation may be combined with existing operations to allow the company to acquire an additional approximately 120 BTC, bringing the company&apos;s potential total holdings to 2,075 BTC. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540944639512576</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsCapital B raises approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin finance company strategyFrench listed company Capital B raised approximately €10.30M to advance its Bitcoin treasury strategy. In addition, the operation may be combined with existing operations to allow the company</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947540944639512576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capital B, a listed company, announced a capital increase of approximately €10.3 million to implement its Bitcoin financial strategyOn July 22, according to an official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase in capital of approximately 10.3 million euros to implement its Bitcoin financial company strategy. Earlier yesterday, Blockchain Group announced that it had changed its name to Capital B and announced that it was setting up a subsidiary in Abu Dhabi. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539908608675840</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCapital B, a listed company, announced a capital increase of approximately €10.3 million to implement its Bitcoin financial strategyOn July 22, according to an official announcement, European listed company Capital B (formerly The Blockchain Group) announced an increase in capital of</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 06:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947539908608675840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>