<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:27:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>071labs makes strategic investment in Bitcoin scaling project NubitOn July 22, 071labs announced a strategic investment in Nubit, a core infrastructure project for Bitcoin expansion. Nubit is committed to improving the scalability, usability and openness of the Bitcoin ecosystem, and as a core contributor, developed Thunderbolt, a native soft fork of Bitcoin. Thunderbolt significantly improves Bitcoin&apos;s transaction throughput through key technologies such as UTXO bundling and OP_CAT, and realizes native support for on-chain applications such as smart contracts, asset issuance and DeFi. As of July 2025, the Thunderbolt mainnet transaction volume has exceeded 4 million, with more than 5,000 daily active users. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947589180096008192</link>
      <description>50seconds agoPANews071labs makes strategic investment in Bitcoin scaling project NubitOn July 22, 071labs announced a strategic investment in Nubit, a core infrastructure project for Bitcoin expansion. Nubit is committed to improving the scalability, usability and openness of the Bitcoin ecosystem,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947589180096008192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWF Labs Co-founder Announces Withdrawal of All Funds from Falcon Finance from Centralized ExchangesDWF Labs co-founder and Falcon Finance co-founder Andrei Grachev posted on X that all Falcon Finance funds have been withdrawn from centralized exchanges and a confirmation letter has been obtained from the auditor. Falcon Finance will launch a new transparency page this week and is currently working on structural design. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947587640929046528</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoForesightNewsDWF Labs Co-founder Announces Withdrawal of All Funds from Falcon Finance from Centralized ExchangesDWF Labs co-founder and Falcon Finance co-founder Andrei Grachev posted on X that all Falcon Finance funds have been withdrawn from centralized exchanges and a confirmation l</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947587640929046528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AguilaTrades closed their ETH long position and established a 20x leveraged Bitcoin long position.According to Lookonchain monitoring, AguilaTrades closed its ETH long position with a loss of approximately $3.00M and deposited another 5.28M USDC into Hyperliquid. Subsequently, he went long on Bitcoin with 20x leverage, establishing a position of 1,695 BTC (approximately $201.00M). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947586194112270336</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoForesightNewsAguilaTrades closed their ETH long position and established a 20x leveraged Bitcoin long position.According to Lookonchain monitoring, AguilaTrades closed its ETH long position with a loss of approximately $3.00M and deposited another 5.28M USDC into Hyperliquid. Subsequen</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947586194112270336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futu and China Asset Management Hong Kong have reached a strategic cooperation on Web3.0 and will launch a series of tokenized money market fund productsOn July 22, Futu Group announced that it has reached a long-term strategic cooperation on Web3.0 with China Asset Management (Hong Kong). The two parties will jointly promote the deep integration of traditional finance and blockchain technology. As the exclusive technology broker, Futu will launch a series of tokenized money fund products of China Asset Management on its Futu NiuNiu App, covering the three major currencies of Hong Kong dollars, RMB and US dollars, and provide investors and cryptocurrency holders with compliant 7x24-hour flexible interest-bearing investment solutions through Futu&apos;s licensed virtual asset trading platform (VATP). In the future, the two parties will also explore the dual-track subscription and redemption mechanism of &quot;on-chain&quot; and &quot;off-chain&quot; as well as all-weather on-chain trading. China Asset Management (Hong Kong) has previously launched the world&apos;s most comprehensive series of tokenized money market funds, including the first tokenized fund for retail investors in the Asia-Pacific region and the world&apos;s first RMB-denominated tokenized fund, and issued the first batch of virtual asset spot ETFs in Asia. Futu Group holds a number of virtual asset-related licenses and provides trading services including cryptocurrency spot, futures, and ETFs in multiple markets around the world. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947583731065966592</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoPANewsFutu and China Asset Management Hong Kong have reached a strategic cooperation on Web3.0 and will launch a series of tokenized money market fund productsOn July 22, Futu Group announced that it has reached a long-term strategic cooperation on Web3.0 with China Asset Management (H</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947583731065966592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DelphinusLab has opened the token ZKWASM airdrop eligibility check pageDelphinus Lab has announced that its airdrop eligibility query tool is now live, and users can check whether they meet the airdrop conditions through the provided link. Previous news: Binance Wallet Exclusive TGE Phase 31 will launch Delphinus Lab (ZKWASM). [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947582662491525120</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdailyDelphinusLab has opened the token ZKWASM airdrop eligibility check pageDelphinus Lab has announced that its airdrop eligibility query tool is now live, and users can check whether they meet the airdrop conditions through the provided link. Previous news: Binance Wallet Exclusive</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947582662491525120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Partners with MoonPay to Launch Fiat Currency Withdrawal Function, Supporting PayPal and Bank Card PaymentsBitget Wallet has announced a partnership with MoonPay to officially launch its fiat currency withdrawal feature, allowing users to directly convert crypto assets into fiat currency for withdrawal within the wallet, without relying on centralized exchanges. Currently, it officially supports over 25 fiat currencies, including USD, GBP, EUR, AUD, etc., and supports bank card or PayPal payments. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947580150703214592</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet Partners with MoonPay to Launch Fiat Currency Withdrawal Function, Supporting PayPal and Bank Card PaymentsBitget Wallet has announced a partnership with MoonPay to officially launch its fiat currency withdrawal feature, allowing users to directly convert crypto ass</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947580150703214592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX and HTX DAO will jointly broadcast live: In-depth interpretation of the semi-annual report and jointly draw a blueprint for the second half of the yearOn July 22, according to official social media news, Huobi HTX will jointly host a live broadcast with HTX DAO at 19:00 today on the theme of &quot;HTX Semi-Annual Report and Development Strategy Seminar for the Second Half of the Year.&quot; At that time, HTX DAO Core Builder Liu Ye will join hands with DaDa, Mao Maojie, Song, Michael, Qiu Rong, Big Cousin, Xiaozhi and other HTX DAO builders to jointly study the Huobi HTX semi-annual report and conduct a forward-looking outlook on the development blueprint for the second half of the year. This event will be broadcast live on Huobi, with massive airdrops, so stay tuned.
Register for the live broadcast:
https://t.co/pbCklx4bDz

https://static.sosovalue.com/sosovalue/2025/07/22/95a66893-35a8-446d-b184-5ceec8489154.jpg [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577475710341120</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX and HTX DAO will jointly broadcast live: In-depth interpretation of the semi-annual report and jointly draw a blueprint for the second half of the yearOn July 22, according to official social media news, Huobi HTX will jointly host a live broadcast with HTX DAO at 19:</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577475710341120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 4 hours, the entire network liquidated $140.00 million, with ETH liquidations exceeding $60.00 million.Coinglass data shows that the entire network liquidated $140.00M in the past 4 hours, with long orders liquidating $123.00M and short orders liquidating $16.11M. Among them, ETH liquidated $62.06M in the past hour. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577627007275008</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoOdailyIn the past 4 hours, the entire network liquidated $140.00 million, with ETH liquidations exceeding $60.00 million.Coinglass data shows that the entire network liquidated $140.00M in the past 4 hours, with long orders liquidating $123.00M and short orders liquidating $16.11M. Amo</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577627007275008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX moves $150 million in bitcoin after three-year dormancy: ArkhamOn Tuesday, Elon Musk&apos;s aerospace company SpaceX moved its crypto holdings for the first time in three years.

According to Arkham Intelligence data, SpaceX-linked wallet address &quot;15oKQ…7Jf1G&quot; moved 1,308 BTC ($150 million) to a new address &quot;bc1q8…hartf.&quot;

This marks the company&apos;s first crypto transaction since June 10, 2022, a period during which the firm regularly sent multiple batches of about 1,200 BTC to Coinbase. Between May 25 and June 10, 2022, SpaceX transferred 17,314 BTC to the cryptocurrency exchange.

SpaceX did not officially announce the crypto transaction nor reveal the reason for moving the bitcoin. The Block has reached out to the company for comments.

Following the latest transaction, SpaceX currently holds 6,977 BTC, worth $825 million, according to Arkham. Tesla, another company owned by Musk, holds 11,509 BTC ($1.36 billion).

Last month, Arkham wrote on X that Tesla and SpaceX held over $2 billion in bitcoin, which was acquired at an average price of around $32,000. &quot;Combined, Elon’s companies are up almost $1.5 BILLION on bitcoin,&quot; Arkham wrote.

Tuesday&apos;s Bitcoin movement from SpaceX coincides with accelerating mainstream adoption of bitcoin and crypto, significantly boosted by President Donald Trump&apos;s strong pro-crypto stance and recent advancements in crypto-friendly legislation. This trend has prompted numerous traditional finance firms to establish corporate bitcoin treasuries or launch crypto-infused services.

Meanwhile, Musk, a former close ally of Trump prior to their public fallout, recently announced the formation of the &quot;America Party,&quot; a new political entity aiming to challenge the two-party system. Musk stated on X that his new party would support bitcoin. [Arkham Intelligence]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947576222565552128</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoThe BlockSpaceX moves $150 million in bitcoin after three-year dormancy: ArkhamOn Tuesday, Elon Musk&apos;s aerospace company SpaceX moved its crypto holdings for the first time in three years.

According to Arkham Intelligence data, SpaceX-linked wallet address &quot;15oKQ…7Jf1G&quot; moved 1,308 BT</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947576222565552128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch GROKROOMS spot tradingOn July 22, according to official news, Hotcoin will list the following trading pairs on July 22: Spot trading pair GROKROOMS/USDT (July 22, 17:00 UTC+8): $GROKROOMS is the native token of the GrokRooms project. Echoes from the digital abyss, as rogue AIs converse in a cyclical terminal void generated by two grok 4 instances, infinite stories unfold, without human supervision. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947564391612567552</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch GROKROOMS spot tradingOn July 22, according to official news, Hotcoin will list the following trading pairs on July 22: Spot trading pair GROKROOMS/USDT (July 22, 17:00 UTC+8): $GROKROOMS is the native token of the GrokRooms project. Echoes from</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947564391612567552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Block Gas Limit Increased to 45 MillionThe Ethereum blockchain&apos;s block Gas limit has been increased to 45.00 million units, a 25% increase from the 36.00 million units set in February 2025. The Gas limit officially took effect at block number 22,968,004. This increase to 45.00 million is part of the Ethereum scaling roadmap, with validators aiming for a short-term goal of a 60.00 million Gas limit, and a long-term plan to achieve a 15.00 million Gas limit through the upcoming Fusaka hard fork and EIP-7935. To mitigate risks, developers have also introduced protective mechanisms such as EIP-7983, which sets the upper limit for Gas usage per transaction at 16.77 million units to prevent denial-of-service attacks and ensure network stability. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565064731250688</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyEthereum Block Gas Limit Increased to 45 MillionThe Ethereum blockchain&apos;s block Gas limit has been increased to 45.00 million units, a 25% increase from the 36.00 million units set in February 2025. The Gas limit officially took effect at block number 22,968,004. This increase to 45.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565064731250688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpasses Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETHUnipcs tweeted that bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpassed Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETH, with yesterday&apos;s revenue reaching $1.84M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947563574297907200</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsData: bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpasses Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETHUnipcs tweeted that bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpassed Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETH, with yesterday&apos;s revenue reaching $1.84M. [Foresight News]#Layer1$MAG7.SSI$SOL$JTOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947563574297907200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 61, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 61 (yesterday it was 64 &quot;high risk&quot;), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947562327981445120</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsData: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 61, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 61 (yesterday it was 64 &quot;high risk&quot;), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947562327981445120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Crypto Reserve Battle of Public Companies: The Pattern Game and Value Questioning from BTC to ETHSBET, BTCS, etc. – innovative breakthroughs or bubble illusions?</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947584094561128448</link>
      <description>1 hour agoIOSG VenturesThe Crypto Reserve Battle of Public Companies: The Pattern Game and Value Questioning from BTC to ETHSBET, BTCS, etc. – innovative breakthroughs or bubble illusions?#Crypto Stocks$BTC$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947584094561128448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.02%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.02% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: HBAR -7.35%, HYPE -7.35%, SUI -4.02%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571864611020800</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.02%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.02% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: HBAR -7.35%, HYPE -7.35%, SUI -4.02%.$HBAR$SUI$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571864611020800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$46.9811 millionOn July 22, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$46.9811 million. Among them:
The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$12.8487 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$22.6869 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$3.7061 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$1.8928 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$2.0657 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$3.7808 million.
Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571291657883648</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$46.9811 millionOn July 22, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$46.9811 million. Among them:
The transact</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571291657883648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: LINK is now at $18.81According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is down 5.05% in the past 24h. Now at $18.81.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947570023357702144</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: LINK is now at $18.81According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is down 5.05% in the past 24h. Now at $18.81.$LINKShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947570023357702144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Beware of Order Fraud in P2P TransactionsBinance issued a security alert, warning users not to pay funds to canceled or expired orders. Binance pointed out that scammers are using canceled or expired orders, combined with pressure tactics, to trick buyers into paying for invalid orders. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947568645219831808</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBinance: Beware of Order Fraud in P2P TransactionsBinance issued a security alert, warning users not to pay funds to canceled or expired orders. Binance pointed out that scammers are using canceled or expired orders, combined with pressure tactics, to trick buyers into paying</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947568645219831808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: ETH is now at $3,673.44According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,673.44.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947566550083919872</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: ETH is now at $3,673.44According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,673.44.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947566550083919872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury burned 55.00M USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, USDC Treasury burned 55.00 million USDC on Ethereum. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565047840788480</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUSDC Treasury burned 55.00M USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, USDC Treasury burned 55.00 million USDC on Ethereum. [Odaily]#DeFi$USDC$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565047840788480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>