<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:28:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ping An of China: Actively Studying Industry Regulatory Changes Related to Stablecoins in the Hong Kong MarketAccording to Cailian Press, Ping An of China stated on the interactive platform that the company has noticed industry regulatory changes related to stablecoins in the Hong Kong market. Ping An has a deep accumulation in blockchain technology and will continue to pay close attention and actively research it. [Cailian Press]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210540837523456</link>
      <description>6 minutes ago吴说Ping An of China: Actively Studying Industry Regulatory Changes Related to Stablecoins in the Hong Kong MarketAccording to Cailian Press, Ping An of China stated on the interactive platform that the company has noticed industry regulatory changes related to stablecoins in the Hong Kon</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210540837523456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares: Ethereum Drives Record $4.39 Billion in Global Inflows Last WeekCoinShares released its latest weekly report showing that weekly inflows into digital asset products hit a record high of $4.39B, bringing year-to-date inflows to $27.0B and pushing assets under management to a record $220.0B. Ethereum set several important new records, with 2025 inflows now exceeding the total for 2024, reaching $6.20B, and weekly inflows nearly double that of any other week on record, reaching $2.12B. The United States accounted for the vast majority of the flow ($4.36B), while global ETP trading volume hit a record $39.2B, driven by Bitcoin and Ethereum. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947209991585026048</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsCoinShares: Ethereum Drives Record $4.39 Billion in Global Inflows Last WeekCoinShares released its latest weekly report showing that weekly inflows into digital asset products hit a record high of $4.39B, bringing year-to-date inflows to $27.0B and pushing assets under man</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947209991585026048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.11%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.11% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: SOL +6.69%, ADA +5.17%, HBAR +5.07%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947209661064110080</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.11%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.11% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: SOL +6.69%, ADA +5.17%, HBAR +5.07%.$ADA$SOL$HBARShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947209661064110080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$55.7922 millionOn July 21, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$55.7922 million. Among them: The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$17.0465 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$27.77655 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$1.2222 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$2.3379 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$2.2717 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$5.1413 million. Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947208587025862656</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$55.7922 millionOn July 21, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$55.7922 million. Among them: The tran</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947208587025862656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTFS 4.0 Introduces the Storage Provider RoleThe BTFS 4.0 network officially introduces the new role of &quot;Storage Provider&quot; to enhance the performance of the BTFS network, including reliability and long-term scalability. As core infrastructure nodes of the network, storage providers must meet stricter standards in terms of hardware configuration, online rate, and service quality, and must be certified by BTTC verification nodes. The plan aims to build a high-performance distributed storage network and promote the sustainable development of the BitTorrent ecosystem. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210224557641728</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoOdailyBTFS 4.0 Introduces the Storage Provider RoleThe BTFS 4.0 network officially introduces the new role of &quot;Storage Provider&quot; to enhance the performance of the BTFS network, including reliability and long-term scalability. As core infrastructure nodes of the network, storage provide</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210224557641728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aster Introduces Active Staking Model, asBNB Staking Can Earn Yield, Collateralize Transactions, and Participate in MiningAster, a decentralized trading platform, has announced that the staking strategy for asBNB has been upgraded from traditional &quot;passive income&quot; to &quot;active participation.&quot; Users can enjoy the following features after minting asBNB:
1: Earn up to 30% APR in BNB ecosystem rewards by holding;
2: Use as trading collateral for Aster Pro;
3: Earn funding rate收益 while hedging BNB holdings.
Aster stated that asBNB&apos;s multi-use model as a staking asset improves staking efficiency and flexibility. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210232996581376</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoOdailyAster Introduces Active Staking Model, asBNB Staking Can Earn Yield, Collateralize Transactions, and Participate in MiningAster, a decentralized trading platform, has announced that the staking strategy for asBNB has been upgraded from traditional &quot;passive income&quot; to &quot;active part</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210232996581376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand SEC proposes relaxing rules for testing crypto ICO investorsOn July 21, the Securities and Exchange Commission of Thailand (SEC) proposed to relax the knowledge testing requirements for retail crypto investors, allowing investors who have passed the test to be exempted from repeated testing, and changing the current quarterly retesting regulations to a suitability assessment every two years. The new rules require ICO portals to conduct comprehensive suitability testing on all digital token investors to ensure that investment risks match product risks. The proposal aims to reduce the burden on investors and ICO portals while being consistent with existing securities regulatory standards. The SEC is now open for public comments, with a deadline of August 1. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205827186413568</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsThailand SEC proposes relaxing rules for testing crypto ICO investorsOn July 21, the Securities and Exchange Commission of Thailand (SEC) proposed to relax the knowledge testing requirements for retail crypto investors, allowing investors who have passed the test to be exempted f</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205827186413568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23.Binance Alpha will launch Alliance Games (COA) on July 23. Eligible users can visit the Alpha activity page to claim the airdrop using Binance Alpha points after trading opens. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207693962072064</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23.Binance Alpha will launch Alliance Games (COA) on July 23. Eligible users can visit the Alpha activity page to claim the airdrop using Binance Alpha points after trading opens. [Odaily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207693962072064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruida Futures: No R&amp;D on stablecoin trading clearing systemAccording to Zhitong Finance, Ruida Futures stated on the interactive platform that the company has not conducted research and development of a stablecoin transaction clearing system. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947206203943964672</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoForesightNewsRuida Futures: No R&amp;D on stablecoin trading clearing systemAccording to Zhitong Finance, Ruida Futures stated on the interactive platform that the company has not conducted research and development of a stablecoin transaction clearing system. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947206203943964672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Will List ETC/USDC and Other Spot Trading Pairs and Open Trading Bots ServicesAccording to the official announcement, Binance will launch the ETC/USDC, GRT/USDC, and ROSE/USDC spot trading pairs on July 22, 2025, at 08:00 (UTC). In addition, Binance will open trading bot services for the following trading pairs at the same time: Spot algorithmic orders (ETC/USDC, GRT/USDC, ROSE/USDC); Spot Grid and Spot DCA (PENGU/USDC, XLM/USDC). (This news flash is generated with AI assistance) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207702405206016</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoOdailyBinance Will List ETC/USDC and Other Spot Trading Pairs and Open Trading Bots ServicesAccording to the official announcement, Binance will launch the ETC/USDC, GRT/USDC, and ROSE/USDC spot trading pairs on July 22, 2025, at 08:00 (UTC). In addition, Binance will open trading bot</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207702405206016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: NFT rebound suggests traders are rotating out of Bitcoin and exploring other speculative plays in the crypto marketThe total market capitalization of NFTs has now exceeded $6.3 billion, nearly doubling from $3.2 billion less than a month ago. At the same time, Bitcoin&apos;s market share has fallen by 6.6% to around 61%. Market analysis suggests that the return of NFTs provides a signal that traders are cycling out of Bitcoin and re-exploring speculative investments in the crypto market. This means that once Bitcoin consolidates and investors begin to shift capital to higher-risk assets, altcoins tend to see more aggressive movements. (DL News) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205175731310592</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyAnalysis: NFT rebound suggests traders are rotating out of Bitcoin and exploring other speculative plays in the crypto marketThe total market capitalization of NFTs has now exceeded $6.3 billion, nearly doubling from $3.2 billion less than a month ago. At the same time, Bitcoin&apos;s</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205175731310592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: ETH is now at $3,786According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.08% in the past 24h. Now at $3,786.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202446030757888</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: ETH is now at $3,786According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.08% in the past 24h. Now at $3,786.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202446030757888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave community vote approves ARFC proposal to deploy a white-label version of Aave V3 on the Ink chainThe Aave community has passed a proposal authorizing the Ink Foundation to deploy a white-label version of the Aave V3 lending platform on the Ink chain. The platform will be centrally governed by the Ink Foundation, branded as &quot;Powered by Aave,&quot; and will not have a governance token. The Aave DAO will receive no less than 5% of the platform&apos;s lending revenue as a share. Aave ecosystem service providers (such as ACI, Chaos Labs, etc.) will assist in operation and maintenance for the first 6 months, and Ink will arrange its own commercial support thereafter. Ink has committed to injecting over $250.00M in initial liquidity and reserving 4% of future governance tokens for incentives. The platform is not included in the Aave DAO insurance system, and Ink will exclusively operate the lending protocol for 12 months after deployment. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202459332268032</link>
      <description>41 minutes ago吴说Aave community vote approves ARFC proposal to deploy a white-label version of Aave V3 on the Ink chainThe Aave community has passed a proposal authorizing the Ink Foundation to deploy a white-label version of the Aave V3 lending platform on the Ink chain. The platform will be central</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202459332268032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian publicly traded company Jetking&apos;s board of directors approves the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares to further expand its Bitcoin strategy.The board of directors of Indian listed company Jetking has approved the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares (approximately $1.30M at most) to further expand its Bitcoin strategy. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202428940341248</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoForesightNewsIndian publicly traded company Jetking&apos;s board of directors approves the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares to further expand its Bitcoin strategy.The board of directors of Indian listed company Jetking has approved the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares (approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202428940341248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale is currently shorting altcoins with a floating loss of $12.48M.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, the wallet address that &quot;once leveraged $2.82M to arbitrage 14.81M USDe&quot; recently opened mixed long and short positions on Hyperliquid. The long positions only include BTC and AAVE, while the remaining 26 currencies are short positions. Currently, only 38% are in a floating profit state, with a cumulative floating loss of $12.48M, of which XRP alone has a loss of $9.00M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200152184049664</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoOdailyA certain whale is currently shorting altcoins with a floating loss of $12.48M.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, the wallet address that &quot;once leveraged $2.82M to arbitrage 14.81M USDe&quot; recently opened mixed long and short positions on Hyperliquid. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200152184049664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale with over $24.00M in long position profits has opened multiple short positions.According to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited $5.00M USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple leveraged short positions, including: SOL (20x), DOGE, FARTCOIN, BONK, LTC, PEPE (all 10x), and PENGU, SPX (both 5x). In addition, the whale holds multiple long positions in another address, with current unrealized profits exceeding $24.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200160639766528</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoOdailyA whale with over $24.00M in long position profits has opened multiple short positions.According to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited $5.00M USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple leveraged short positions, including: SOL (20x), DOGE, FARTCOIN, BONK, LTC, PEPE (all 10x</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200160639766528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch CSKY spot tradingOn July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will list the following trading pairs on July 21: Spot trading pair CSKY/USDT (July 21, 20:20 UTC+8): $CSKY is the native token of the CoreSky project. Coresky is a new generation Web3 meme incubation platform that aims to discover, empower, and launch community-driven meme projects. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195954121953280</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch CSKY spot tradingOn July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will list the following trading pairs on July 21: Spot trading pair CSKY/USDT (July 21, 20:20 UTC+8): $CSKY is the native token of the CoreSky project. Coresky is a new</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195954121953280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX-sponsored ChainCatcher &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party in Hanoi, Vietnam will be held on July 31.The &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party, sponsored by HTX and hosted by ChainCatcher, will be grandly held in Hanoi, Vietnam on July 31st from 19:30 - 22:30 (GMT+7). As the third time this brand event has been held in Vietnam, previous events have successfully brought together leading local Vietnamese Web3 project teams, top investors, well-known KOLs, and core community members, creating a highly influential communication platform in the industry. This event will further promote in-depth cooperation and resource docking within the Vietnamese Web3 ecosystem. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195150010961920</link>
      <description>1 hour agoChainCatcherHTX-sponsored ChainCatcher &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party in Hanoi, Vietnam will be held on July 31.The &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party, sponsored by HTX and hosted by ChainCatcher, will be grandly held in Hanoi, Vietnam on July 31st from 19:30 - 22:30 (GMT</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195150010961920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinTax Founder: Web3-related crypto income may become a focus of taxation in the futureIn recent years, the data analysis capabilities of tax authorities have significantly improved, and tax bureaus have begun to proactively analyze CRS data. As a Chinese tax resident, if your overseas assets and income are conspicuous enough, you are likely to come into the view of the tax bureau. In the long run, these overseas assets will sooner or later face the attention and management of tax authorities. This reflects the upgrading of the collection and management mechanism—based on specific risk indicators, using internal &quot;five-step work method&quot; and other means to conduct a systematic assessment of the overseas income of natural persons. Currently, common targets of verification include those who invest in Hong Kong and US stocks, and those who realize overseas equity in Internet companies. However, Web3-related crypto income may become one of the focuses in the future. [Securities Times]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947189008828485632</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说FinTax Founder: Web3-related crypto income may become a focus of taxation in the futureIn recent years, the data analysis capabilities of tax authorities have significantly improved, and tax bureaus have begun to proactively analyze CRS data. As a Chinese tax resident, if your overseas a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947189008828485632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish listed company H100 Group plans to raise $1.50M to increase its holdings of BitcoinPublicly listed company H100 Group announced that its board of directors has decided to conduct a directed issue of up to 1,523,089 new shares to certain qualified investors at a price of SEK 9.30 per share, with total proceeds expected to be approximately SEK 14.10 million (approximately $1.50 million). The announcement stated that the net proceeds from this fundraising will be used to seek new investment opportunities within its Bitcoin reserve strategy framework. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947190076857667584</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySwedish listed company H100 Group plans to raise $1.50M to increase its holdings of BitcoinPublicly listed company H100 Group announced that its board of directors has decided to conduct a directed issue of up to 1,523,089 new shares to certain qualified investors at a price of SEK 9</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947190076857667584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 08:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>