<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:58:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes purchased $1.00M ENA in the past 7 hours.According to Ember Monitoring, BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes has once again purchased $1.00M worth of ENA through various channels in the past 7 hours. He transferred 500,000.00 USDC to Binance and withdrew 1.08M ENA; transferred 250,000.00 USDC to Galaxy Digital and withdrew 560,000.00 ENA; and transferred 250,000.00 USDC to Flowdesk and withdrew 520,000.00 ENA. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948562062589890560</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoForesightNewsBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes purchased $1.00M ENA in the past 7 hours.According to Ember Monitoring, BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes has once again purchased $1.00M worth of ENA through various channels in the past 7 hours. He transferred 500,000.00 USDC to Binance and wit</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948562062589890560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtuals Protocol: veVIRTUAL Holder Airdrop Eligibility to be ResetVirtuals Protocol tweeted that the one-time airdrop eligibility for veVIRTUAL holders will be reset. All veVIRTUAL holders are eligible to receive a full allocation in the next airdrop, and no action is required. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948560655484784640</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoForesightNewsVirtuals Protocol: veVIRTUAL Holder Airdrop Eligibility to be ResetVirtuals Protocol tweeted that the one-time airdrop eligibility for veVIRTUAL holders will be reset. All veVIRTUAL holders are eligible to receive a full allocation in the next airdrop, and no action is req</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948560655484784640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: White House to Allow 401(k) Investments in Crypto, Blackstone Expects Large Private Equity Firms to Dominate MarketChainCatcher News, according to Bloomberg, the White House is preparing an executive order that will provide legal protection for 401(k) retirement plan managers, allowing them to include private market funds, cryptocurrencies, and other alternative assets in their investment options. Blackstone Inc. President Jon Gray said that once the U.S. paves the way for 401(k) plans to expand into investment areas beyond stocks and bonds, leading institutions in the alternative asset industry will be the most likely to benefit. This move will bring significant changes to the U.S. retirement savings market, providing ordinary investors with more diversified investment channels, and may also create new business growth opportunities for large private equity management companies. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948560852235390976</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoChainCatcherBloomberg: White House to Allow 401(k) Investments in Crypto, Blackstone Expects Large Private Equity Firms to Dominate MarketChainCatcher News, according to Bloomberg, the White House is preparing an executive order that will provide legal protection for 401(k) retirement</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948560852235390976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machibigbrother continues to increase his long positions in PUMP tokens, with losses exceeding $10.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, Machi Big Brother is still increasing his long positions in PUMP tokens. His losses on PUMP have now exceeded $10.00M, including spot losses of $2.17M and contract losses of $8.14M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948558271882792960</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoForesightNewsMachibigbrother continues to increase his long positions in PUMP tokens, with losses exceeding $10.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, Machi Big Brother is still increasing his long positions in PUMP tokens. His losses on PUMP have now exceeded $10.00M, including spot</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948558271882792960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale reduced its holdings by 3,459 ETH 11 hours ago, with a loss of $35,000.0.On July 25, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa)&apos;s monitoring, swing trading whale 0x54d...e6029 reduced its holdings by 3,459 ETH (approximately $12.58M) 11 hours ago. This whale established a position of 5,557 ETH (worth $20.27M) on 07.23 at an average price of $3,648.50; this reduction in holdings resulted in a slight loss of $35,000.00, and the remaining portion is still staked in ether.fi. The win rate for the two swing trading operations since June 20 has remained at 100.00%. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948558335690739712</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoTechFlowA certain whale reduced its holdings by 3,459 ETH 11 hours ago, with a loss of $35,000.0.On July 25, according to on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa)&apos;s monitoring, swing trading whale 0x54d...e6029 reduced its holdings by 3,459 ETH (approximately $12.58M) 11 hours ago. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948558335690739712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christie&apos;s International Real Estate Launches New Division to Handle Real Estate Transactions with CryptocurrencyAccording to The New York Times, Christie&apos;s International Real Estate will establish a new department to handle real estate transactions using cryptocurrencies. The team consists of lawyers, analysts, and cryptocurrency experts, specializing in transactions where both buyers and sellers use only digital currencies and do not rely on banks at all. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948557060379054080</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoForesightNewsChristie&apos;s International Real Estate Launches New Division to Handle Real Estate Transactions with CryptocurrencyAccording to The New York Times, Christie&apos;s International Real Estate will establish a new department to handle real estate transactions using cryptocurrencies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948557060379054080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Truth Collective&quot; reappears after six months, transferring $7.24M worth of ZEREBRO and FARTCOINAccording to Arkham monitoring, after six months, truth terminal: Squads Vault &quot;truth collective&quot; transferred 40,000,000 ZEREBRO and 4,300,000 FARTCOIN out at 5:11 UTC+8 today, totaling $7,240,000.00; currently stored in the new address: Co7xwX…BTv9TN. In January of this year, truth terminal: Squads Vault &quot;truth collective&quot; transferred 6,750,000 FARTCOIN and 8,250,000 FARTCOIN to Wintermute Deposit and Fireblock Custody, respectively, with a total value of $24,600,000.00 at that time. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948556322118635520</link>
      <description>29 minutes ago吴说&quot;Truth Collective&quot; reappears after six months, transferring $7.24M worth of ZEREBRO and FARTCOINAccording to Arkham monitoring, after six months, truth terminal: Squads Vault &quot;truth collective&quot; transferred 40,000,000 ZEREBRO and 4,300,000 FARTCOIN out at 5:11 UTC+8 today, totaling $7</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948556322118635520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injective announces tokenization and on-chain listing of Ethereum treasury company SharpLink&apos;s stock (SBET)On July 25, according to The Block, the blockchain project Injective announced that it will tokenize and put on-chain the shares (SBET) of Ethereum vault company SharpLink, founded by Joe Lubin, to create the &quot;first tokenized digital asset vault&quot; (DAT). The project utilizes Injective&apos;s iAssets framework to transform static company Ethereum reserves into yield-generating on-chain tools, supporting functions such as lending markets, collateral, and derivatives. SharpLink currently holds approximately $1.30B worth of Ethereum (360,807 ETH) and is the second-largest Ethereum vault company. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948555097369284608</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoTechFlowInjective announces tokenization and on-chain listing of Ethereum treasury company SharpLink&apos;s stock (SBET)On July 25, according to The Block, the blockchain project Injective announced that it will tokenize and put on-chain the shares (SBET) of Ethereum vault company SharpLink</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948555097369284608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Treasury minted 2.00B USDT on Ethereum in the early hours of today.According to Whale Alert monitoring, Tether Treasury minted a total of 2.00B USDT in two transactions on Ethereum in the early hours of today. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948554740689866752</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoForesightNewsTether Treasury minted 2.00B USDT on Ethereum in the early hours of today.According to Whale Alert monitoring, Tether Treasury minted a total of 2.00B USDT in two transactions on Ethereum in the early hours of today. [Foresight News]#DeFi$USDT$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948554740689866752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xAI to Integrate its Grok Conversational Model into Prediction Market KalshiElon Musk&apos;s xAI will integrate its Grok conversational model into the prediction market Kalshi. Before making predictions, Kalshi users can query the Grok large language model to obtain on-chain data, historical odds, and the latest headline information. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948553580385996800</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoForesightNewsxAI to Integrate its Grok Conversational Model into Prediction Market KalshiElon Musk&apos;s xAI will integrate its Grok conversational model into the prediction market Kalshi. Before making predictions, Kalshi users can query the Grok large language model to obtain on-chain da</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948553580385996800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Haidian District Financial Administration: Beware of illegal fundraising in the name of stablecoins, etc.The Haidian District Local Financial Supervision and Administration Bureau of Beijing issued an announcement stating that digital currencies, represented by stablecoins, have recently received widespread attention in the market. Some illegal institutions use &quot;financial innovation,&quot; &quot;digital assets,&quot; and other gimmicks, taking advantage of the public&apos;s lack of understanding of stablecoins, to absorb funds by issuing so-called &quot;virtual currencies,&quot; &quot;virtual assets,&quot; and &quot;digital assets,&quot; inducing the public to participate in trading and speculation, disrupting economic and financial order, and breeding illegal fundraising, gambling, fraud, pyramid schemes, money laundering, and other illegal and criminal activities, which seriously endanger the safety of the public&apos;s property. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948551964362608640</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoForesightNewsBeijing Haidian District Financial Administration: Beware of illegal fundraising in the name of stablecoins, etc.The Haidian District Local Financial Supervision and Administration Bureau of Beijing issued an announcement stating that digital currencies, represented by sta</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948551964362608640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CICC: Stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructureAccording to Zhitong Finance, a research report by CICC states that stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructure. By analyzing the incentive compatibility mechanisms of various participants in stablecoins, the report envisions the potential impact of stablecoins on financial markets and the international monetary system, and further explores China&apos;s response. We believe that the nascent stage of infrastructure is an important development opportunity, and issuing offshore RMB stablecoins may be China&apos;s preferred choice for participating in stablecoin development. However, it should be noted that stablecoins are only a &quot;technique&quot; for promoting the internationalization of the RMB. Whether the RMB can become a widely trusted international currency ultimately depends on the &quot;principles,&quot; namely the &quot;legal anchor&quot; and &quot;functional anchor&quot; of the RMB. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948549091427946496</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoForesightNewsCICC: Stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructureAccording to Zhitong Finance, a research report by CICC states that stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructure. By analyzing the incentive compatibility mechanisms of vari</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948549091427946496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>510 billion BONK Transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase, Approximately $18.75 millionAccording to @EmberCN monitoring, half an hour after the Bonk project team tweeted that it had repurchased and burned 500.00B BONK (approximately $18.47M), 510.00B BONK (approximately $18.75M) was transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548771264139264</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说510 billion BONK Transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase, Approximately $18.75 millionAccording to @EmberCN monitoring, half an hour after the Bonk project team tweeted that it had repurchased and burned 500.00B BONK (approximately $18.47M), 510.00B BONK (approximately $1</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548771264139264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripple co-founder-related addresses transferred approximately $140.00M worth of XRP to trading platforms in the past 7 days.According to on-chain investigator ZachXBT, since July 17, an address long associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen has transferred 50,000,000 XRP. The wallet appears to have transferred approximately $140,000,000.00 worth of tokens into three addresses associated with trading platforms, while another 10,000,000 XRP were deposited into two newly created wallets. Addresses controlled by Chris Larsen still hold approximately 2,810,000,000 XRP, worth about $9,000,000,000.00. Previously, the SEC accused Ripple&apos;s CEO Brad Garlinghouse of personally cashing out $150,000,000.00 worth of XRP over three years when it sued Ripple in 2020. In addition, Larsen and his spouse sold $450,000,000.00 worth of tokens between 2017 and 2020. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548137433501696</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsRipple co-founder-related addresses transferred approximately $140.00M worth of XRP to trading platforms in the past 7 days.According to on-chain investigator ZachXBT, since July 17, an address long associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen has transferred 50,000,000 XRP.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548137433501696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinmarketcap: Monad will launch on September 30th, with a total token supply of 100,000,000,000.00On July 25th, according to Coinmarketcap&apos;s Monad token page, Monad will be launched on September 30, 2025 (North American time September 29) Beijing time, with a total token supply of 100.00B.

[Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948547285012516864</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowCoinmarketcap: Monad will launch on September 30th, with a total token supply of 100,000,000,000.00On July 25th, according to Coinmarketcap&apos;s Monad token page, Monad will be launched on September 30, 2025 (North American time September 29) Beijing time, with a total token supply of</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948547285012516864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s second son forwards the view that &quot;ETH is undervalued&quot; and expresses his agreement.Trump&apos;s second son, Eric Trump, retweeted, &quot;Ethereum is catching up with global liquidity. If compared to M2 money supply growth, the price of ETH should already be over $8,000.00. This suggests that ETH is currently undervalued and may be one of the best trades right now,&quot; and said, &quot;Totally agree.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948545787805372416</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsTrump&apos;s second son forwards the view that &quot;ETH is undervalued&quot; and expresses his agreement.Trump&apos;s second son, Eric Trump, retweeted, &quot;Ethereum is catching up with global liquidity. If compared to M2 money supply growth, the price of ETH should already be over $8,000.00. This</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948545787805372416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSL Group plans to raise approximately HK$2.355B through a rights issue for strategic acquisitions, stablecoin business, etc.According to Jiemian News, OSL Group entered into a placing and subscription agreement, a general mandate subscription agreement, and a special mandate subscription agreement on July 25, 2025 (before the trading session). The total estimated proceeds from the transactions contemplated under these agreements are approximately HK$2,355.03M, and the estimated net proceeds are approximately HK$2,336.10M. The placing price is HK$14.90 per placing share, representing a discount of approximately 15.34% to the closing price of the shares as quoted on the Stock Exchange on the last trading day. The Company intends to use the total net proceeds for the following: approximately 50% to support the Company&apos;s strategic acquisition initiatives; approximately 30% for the development of global business and new business initiatives (including payment and stablecoin initiatives); and approximately 20% for the general corporate purposes of the Group. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948543627420045312</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsOSL Group plans to raise approximately HK$2.355B through a rights issue for strategic acquisitions, stablecoin business, etc.According to Jiemian News, OSL Group entered into a placing and subscription agreement, a general mandate subscription agreement, and a special mandate</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948543627420045312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: SOL is now at $181.26According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 5.01% in the past 24h. Now at $181.26.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948542128647790592</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: SOL is now at $181.26According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 5.01% in the past 24h. Now at $181.26.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948542128647790592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant Founder: Bitcoin Cycle Theory Has Become InvalidOn July 25, CryptoQuant founder Ki Young Ju posted that the cyclical theory of &quot;buy when whales accumulate, sell when retail investors enter&quot; no longer applies to Bitcoin. In previous cycles, whales would sell chips to retail investors, but now old whales are selling to new long-term whales, with institutional participation far exceeding expectations, and the number of holders exceeding the number of traders. Ki Young Ju apologized for his previous misjudgment that &quot;the bull market cycle is over&quot; and said that he will be more cautious in the future and focus on data-driven analysis. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948540004162146304</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowCryptoQuant Founder: Bitcoin Cycle Theory Has Become InvalidOn July 25, CryptoQuant founder Ki Young Ju posted that the cyclical theory of &quot;buy when whales accumulate, sell when retail investors enter&quot; no longer applies to Bitcoin. In previous cycles, whales would sell chips to ret</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948540004162146304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US crypto legislation drives $4B surge in stablecoin supplyRegulatory clarity is opening the door for banks, asset managers, and crypto firms to roll out new stablecoin products.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948534676737560576</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUS crypto legislation drives $4B surge in stablecoin supplyRegulatory clarity is opening the door for banks, asset managers, and crypto firms to roll out new stablecoin products.#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948534676737560576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>