<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>FBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — Report</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694986539847680</link>
      <description>16:26FBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — Report</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694986539847680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — ReportThe investigation was reportedly not connected to Jesse Powell’s activities within the crypto industry.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947695662019923968</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoPANewsFBI ends probe of Kraken co-founder, returns confiscated devices — ReportThe investigation was reportedly not connected to Jesse Powell’s activities within the crypto industry.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947695662019923968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun to Become Youngest Chinese Commercial Astronaut with Blue Origin’s New ShepardGeneva, Switzerland - July 22, 2025 - Justin Sun, founder of TRON and one of the most recognizable figures in crypto, is set to make history as the youngest Chinese-born commercial astronaut and the first Forbes-cover crypto entrepreneur to travel to space aboard Blue Origin’s New Shepard. This mission is the 14th human flight for the New Shepard program and the 34th in its history. The flight date will be announced soon. The live webcast on launch day will start 30 minutes before liftoff.

In 2021, Sun placed the winning bid for the first seat on New Shepard. The $28 million in proceeds were donated to Blue Origin’s foundation, Club for the Future, which selected 19 space-focused non-profits to each receive a $1 million grant to inspire future generations to pursue careers in STEAM (science, technology, engineering, arts, and math) for the benefit of Earth and help invent the future of life in space.

“We are witnessing the beginning of a new chapter in human exploration, where space is no longer reserved for governments or institutions but is becoming a frontier for innovators, dreamers, and builders from all walks of life,” said Sun. “Blue Origin’s commitment to expanding access to space, along with Club for the Future’s mission to inspire young people worldwide, reflects a powerful vision. I am proud to support this effort and help advance the belief that space is a place for everyone, not just a select few.”

Sun’s upcoming flight is more than a personal milestone. It highlights the growing international presence in commercial space travel and the increasing connection between blockchain and scientific innovation. As a leading voice in the digital economy and a strong advocate for decentralized technology, his journey reflects the broader potential for global collaboration and progress at the frontier of space exploration.

About TRON DAO

TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.

Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON blockchain has experienced significant growth since its MainNet launch in May 2018. TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin, exceeding $81 billion. As of July 2025, the TRON blockchain has recorded over 320 million in total user accounts, more than 10 billion in total transactions, and over $25 billion in total value locked (TVL), based on TRONSCAN.

TRONNetwork | TRONDAO | X | YouTube | Telegram | Discord | Reddit | GitHub | Medium | Forum

Media Contact

Yeweon Park

[email protected]

This post is commissioned by TRON and does not serve as a testimonial or endorsement by The Block. This post is for informational purposes only and should not be relied upon as a basis for investment, tax, legal or other advice. You should conduct your own research and consult independent counsel and advisors on the matters discussed within this post. Past performance of any asset is not indicative of future results. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947693515320610816</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoThe BlockJustin Sun to Become Youngest Chinese Commercial Astronaut with Blue Origin’s New ShepardGeneva, Switzerland - July 22, 2025 - Justin Sun, founder of TRON and one of the most recognizable figures in crypto, is set to make history as the youngest Chinese-born commercial astrona</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947693515320610816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance CEO Joins The Digital Chamber Advisory BoardAccording to the official announcement, Binance CEO Richard Teng has officially joined its advisory board. This move aims to assist the organization in promoting the collaborative development of the global digital asset industry in terms of compliance, transparency, and innovation. The Digital Chamber is the world&apos;s largest blockchain and digital asset industry association, and its advisory members also include executives from institutions such as Chainlink and Custodia Bank. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694544774778880</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoOdailyBinance CEO Joins The Digital Chamber Advisory BoardAccording to the official announcement, Binance CEO Richard Teng has officially joined its advisory board. This move aims to assist the organization in promoting the collaborative development of the global digital asset industry</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694544774778880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Zohran Mamdani’s Crypto Position Ahead of the New York Mayoral Election?New York’s viral mayoral candidate Zohran Mamdani has caused a social media storm with his ‘social democratic’ political ideology and engaging campaign approach. However, his crypto stance still remains in the grey. Meanwhile, Mamdani’s opposition is already turning to the crypto industry to swing public opinion. Zohran Mamdani’s Silence on Crypto New York City, a major cryptocurrency industry hub, is scheduled to hold a mayoral election on November 4, 2025. Current Mayor Eric Adams, elected as a Democrat, is seeking re-election as an independent candidate. Andrew Cuomo, the former governor of New York State, is also running. The two men, who formerly ran for offices on Democratic party tickets, are up against a rising newcomer in the NYC mayoral race. That would be 33-year-old New York assemblyman Zohran Mamdani, who is running as a Democrat, winning the party’s nomination over Cuomo, who now plans to run as an independent. Already, Mamdani is quite popular, even to those outside of New York’s five boroughs. On July 16, Mamdani was in Washington. He was meeting with leading Democrats such as Senator Bernie Sanders and Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, who both endorsed Mamdani in his party’s successful primary run against Cuomo. Sanders posted on Twitter/X on that day about Mamdami, saying he was “deeply impressed by the grassroots campaign he is running”. But Mamdani has never talked about crypto. BeInCrypto reached out to Mamdani, both his campaign and council office, for comments on the blockchain industry. There was no response as of press time. Though his following is largely a younger demographic, he hasn’t yet addressed policy regarding blockchain and cryptocurrency in a city well-known for the industry. Some in crypto might be concerned. Leading Democrats have been critical of cryptocurrency, mainly due to consumer protection issues. Will Mamdani’s Political Ideology Hamper New York’s Crypto Progress? The most outspoken Democrat member of the crypto opposition is Elizabeth Warren, who told CNBC on July 17 that Mamdani is “willing to try new ideas”. That might not be enough to convince cryptocurrency advocates Mamdani is the right person to push blockchain technology forward in NYC, where companies like Uniswap, OpenSea and ConsenSys are headquartered. “Not bullish,” said Brian Mahoney, based in NYC as vice president of business development for Thesis, a Bitcoin startup accelerator. Influential Democrats like Warren have been outspoken critics of the cryptocurrency industry. And Mamdani’s position as a “socialist” Democrat may not align with the free market ideals of blockchain and cryptocurrency. It’s hard to tell when Mamdani’s positioning is not yet clear. It may take some time before that positioning crystallizes ahead of the election in November. Many cryptocurrency companies that would rather have less regulation, especially in light of New York State’s onerous BitLicense requirements, could be concerned if Mamdani starts to criticize the industry. Yet the majority of crypto companies concerned about tougher regulations in New York may have some fear of a very left-leaning mayoral candidate like Mamdani. This is largely because Mamdani plans to make busing in NYC free and freeze rents for citizens. Already, opponent and incumbent Eric Adams is busy courting cryptocurrency, seeing it as an opportunity for fundraising. Empower NYC, a super PAC, is raising up to $10 million for Adams, largely from the crypto and banking industry. It will be interesting to see what Mamdani’s views and positioning will be about crypto. To him, is it a world-changing good for the people? Or does he view it as harmful for the people of New York City, despite it being an industry epicenter? Only time and Mamdani’s positioning will truly tell. [BeInCrypto]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947696231220531200</link>
      <description>39 minutes agobeincryptoWhat is Zohran Mamdani’s Crypto Position Ahead of the New York Mayoral Election?New York’s viral mayoral candidate Zohran Mamdani has caused a social media storm with his ‘social democratic’ political ideology and engaging campaign approach. However, his crypto stance still r</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947696231220531200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase International Exchange to List ERA and SUSHI Perpetual ContractsAccording to the official announcement, Coinbase International Exchange will list ERA and SUSHI perpetual contracts. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694565352034304</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyCoinbase International Exchange to List ERA and SUSHI Perpetual ContractsAccording to the official announcement, Coinbase International Exchange will list ERA and SUSHI perpetual contracts. [Odaily]#Crypto Stocks$ERA$SUSHI$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947694565352034304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI data layer startup Poseidon completes $15.00M seed round led by a16zAI data layer startup Poseidon completes $15.00M seed round led by a16z. Built on Story Protocol, Poseidon aims to unlock high-quality training data for the &quot;next generation of physical AI.&quot; Reportedly, Poseidon was incubated by the Story team and is committed to solving the problem of obtaining high-quality, usable, and legally authorized training data in the AI field. a16z Crypto founder Chris Dixon stated that Poseidon&apos;s decentralized data layer will establish a new economic foundation for the internet, incentivizing creators and suppliers to provide diverse data inputs for the next generation of intelligent systems. The project will provide AI developers with IP-safe, legally compliant training data access through Story Protocol&apos;s programmable intellectual property layer and immutable registry. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947690882656653312</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoOdailyAI data layer startup Poseidon completes $15.00M seed round led by a16zAI data layer startup Poseidon completes $15.00M seed round led by a16z. Built on Story Protocol, Poseidon aims to unlock high-quality training data for the &quot;next generation of physical AI.&quot; Reportedly, Poseid</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947690882656653312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign media: Musk&apos;s allies are raising up to $12 billion to support the xAI chip projectOn July 23, according to the Wall Street Journal: Musk&apos;s allies are raising up to $12 billion to support the xAI chip project as the startup is rapidly consuming funds. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947689701431595008</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoPANewsForeign media: Musk&apos;s allies are raising up to $12 billion to support the xAI chip projectOn July 23, according to the Wall Street Journal: Musk&apos;s allies are raising up to $12 billion to support the xAI chip project as the startup is rapidly consuming funds. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947689701431595008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Interest rates should be lowered by 3 percentage points, or even moreUS President Trump: Interest rates should be lowered by 3 percentage points, or even lower. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947688360340639744</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrump: Interest rates should be lowered by 3 percentage points, or even moreUS President Trump: Interest rates should be lowered by 3 percentage points, or even lower. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947688360340639744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the US GENIUS Act mean for stablecoins?The Genius Act is a US law aimed at establishing federal oversight for stablecoin issuers, setting rules for reserves, redemption rights, and licensing requirements.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684746545090560</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsWhat does the US GENIUS Act mean for stablecoins?The Genius Act is a US law aimed at establishing federal oversight for stablecoin issuers, setting rules for reserves, redemption rights, and licensing requirements.#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684746545090560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump on Powell: Anyway, he&apos;ll be out soonPresident Trump on Powell: Anyway, he will be out soon. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947685838259507200</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrump on Powell: Anyway, he&apos;ll be out soonPresident Trump on Powell: Anyway, he will be out soon. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947685838259507200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former AWS CEO Adam Selipsky Officially Joins Circle&apos;s Board of DirectorsCircle CEO Jeremy Allaire tweeted that former Amazon Web Services (AWS) CEO Adam Selipsky has officially joined Circle&apos;s board of directors. Allaire said Selipsky will provide important support for Circle&apos;s efforts to promote global on-chain operations and financial system construction. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684246198177792</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Former AWS CEO Adam Selipsky Officially Joins Circle&apos;s Board of DirectorsCircle CEO Jeremy Allaire tweeted that former Amazon Web Services (AWS) CEO Adam Selipsky has officially joined Circle&apos;s board of directors. Allaire said Selipsky will provide important support for Circle&apos;s efforts</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684246198177792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources: Apple is expected to get EU antitrust approval for its App Store fees and rulesOn July 22, Apple (AAPL.O) is expected to receive approval from the European Union&apos;s antitrust agency for its App Store fees and rules, which will help Apple avoid daily fines. A decision is expected to be made in the coming weeks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683511305785344</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSources: Apple is expected to get EU antitrust approval for its App Store fees and rulesOn July 22, Apple (AAPL.O) is expected to receive approval from the European Union&apos;s antitrust agency for its App Store fees and rules, which will help Apple avoid daily fines. A decision is expec</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683511305785344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local timeOn July 22, the White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local time. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683241972748288</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsThe White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local timeOn July 22, the White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local time. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683241972748288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TON Wallet Announces Launch in the United StatesTON Wallet announces that it is now live in the United States. U.S. users can now use TON Wallet directly in Telegram, supporting the purchase and trading of USDT, TON and other tokens, private message transfers, 0% fee fiat currency exchange, credit card withdrawals, and token holding benefits. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680359261163520</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说TON Wallet Announces Launch in the United StatesTON Wallet announces that it is now live in the United States. U.S. users can now use TON Wallet directly in Telegram, supporting the purchase and trading of USDT, TON and other tokens, private message transfers, 0% fee fiat currency exchan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680359261163520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitalik: The paradox of utilitarianism is that the setting of &quot;utility is infinite&quot; does not match the upper limit of human emotionsOn July 22, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin wrote on a social media platform that the reason why many paradoxes of utilitarianism are confusing is that its &quot;unlimited utility&quot; setting conflicts with human emotional mechanisms. He pointed out that humans actually have an upper limit to their positive and negative emotional experience of a situation, so the &quot;unlimited utility&quot; assumption in theoretical models is often contrary to intuition. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947679409423273984</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsVitalik: The paradox of utilitarianism is that the setting of &quot;utility is infinite&quot; does not match the upper limit of human emotionsOn July 22, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin wrote on a social media platform that the reason why many paradoxes of utilitarianism are confusing is t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947679409423273984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneFootball to Launch Token Sale on CoinList on July 24According to the official announcement from CoinList, the OneFootball (OFC) token sale will officially begin on July 24th at 17:00 UTC. The fully diluted valuation (FDV) for this token sale is $50.00M, the token price is $0.05, 25% will be released at TGE, and the remaining portion will be released linearly over 12 months, with a minimum purchase amount of $100.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680819560861696</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyOneFootball to Launch Token Sale on CoinList on July 24According to the official announcement from CoinList, the OneFootball (OFC) token sale will officially begin on July 24th at 17:00 UTC. The fully diluted valuation (FDV) for this token sale is $50.00M, the token price is $0.05, 2</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680819560861696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs announces the launch of the first season of airdrops, 25% of the shares are now availableOn July 22, Sonic Labs published a post on the X platform saying that the first season of Sonic airdrop has officially started. Users can now claim 25% of the allocated shares, and the remaining 75% will be released linearly in the form of NFTs and gradually opened through the PaintSwap order book. The official specially reminded that this airdrop is based on the Sonic mainnet whitelist event and has nothing to do with pre-sales or TGE. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678554049499136</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsSonic Labs announces the launch of the first season of airdrops, 25% of the shares are now availableOn July 22, Sonic Labs published a post on the X platform saying that the first season of Sonic airdrop has officially started. Users can now claim 25% of the allocated shares, and the</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678554049499136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machi Big Brother has accumulated losses of over $5.50M on PUMP spot and contracts, but continues to add to long positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother Huang Licheng (@machibigbrother) has lost more than $1.50M on PUMP spot and more than $3.90M on contracts. However, he continues to add to his PUMP long position. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678290018062336</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMachi Big Brother has accumulated losses of over $5.50M on PUMP spot and contracts, but continues to add to long positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother Huang Licheng (@machibigbrother) has lost more than $1.50M on PUMP</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678290018062336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US DOJ drops probe into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell over nonprofit allegations: FortuneThe U.S. Justice Department has dropped its investigation into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell tied to a nonprofit group, according to reporting from Fortune.

Authorities searched Powell&apos;s Los Angeles home and took electronic devices in 2023 as part of an investigation into claims he hacked and cyber-stalked a nonprofit arts group, The New York Times previously reported.

In 2023, the nonprofit alleged that Powell interfered with its computer accounts, including blocking access to emails and other messages, according to people with knowledge of the matter who spoke to The New York Times.

Powell has said he did not stalk or hack anyone and alleged that the nonprofit Verge Center for the Arts executives tried to remove him from the board, Fortune reported on Tuesday.

The DOJ did not immediately respond to a request for comment. Powell told Fortune that the Federal Bureau of Investigation&apos;s raid was &quot;devastating both personally and professionally.&quot;

Powell, who co-founded the Kraken exchange, stepped down as CEO in 2022 and he is currently the chair of its board of directors.

The Justice Department&apos;s probe happened as crypto firms were being sued by federal regulators over charges related to not registering properly and fraud. A Kraken spokeswoman told the New York Times in 2023 that the investigation into Powell has nothing to do with the company and that it had no reason to believe that prosecutors were looking into other potential issues. [Fortune]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947676994187841536</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockUS DOJ drops probe into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell over nonprofit allegations: FortuneThe U.S. Justice Department has dropped its investigation into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell tied to a nonprofit group, according to reporting from Fortune.

Authorities searched Powell&apos;s Lo</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947676994187841536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fogo Launches High-Performance Layer 1 SVM Chain Public Testnet with 40 Millisecond Block TimeFogo, a Layer 1 blockchain created by former Wall Street executives, announced on Tuesday the official launch of its public testnet. Fogo aims to bring the execution speed of traditional finance to the decentralized finance space without sacrificing decentralization and composability. The team says the Fogo network can achieve 40 milliseconds block times and provide unique advantages for on-chain trading products through native infrastructure and vertical integration. Other innovations include reduced MEV risk, a co-located node architecture for real-time transaction execution, and an enhanced session-based account management experience. Fogo plans to be the first to fully deploy the Firedancer validator client, and has already adopted the Frankendancer hybrid client and will gradually transition to Firedancer. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678298461196288</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyFogo Launches High-Performance Layer 1 SVM Chain Public Testnet with 40 Millisecond Block TimeFogo, a Layer 1 blockchain created by former Wall Street executives, announced on Tuesday the official launch of its public testnet. Fogo aims to bring the execution speed of traditional fin</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678298461196288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>