<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:14:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Announces Partnership with Anchorage, Transitioning USDtb from Offshore Model to Federally Regulated StablecoinEthena has announced that it will partner with Anchorage, a U.S. federally chartered crypto bank, to transition USDtb from an offshore model to a payment stablecoin under federal regulation. Ethena claims that its USDtb is expected to be the first stablecoin with a clear path to full compliance with the U.S. GENIUS Act. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369827164393472</link>
      <description>5 minutes ago吴说Ethena Announces Partnership with Anchorage, Transitioning USDtb from Offshore Model to Federally Regulated StablecoinEthena has announced that it will partner with Anchorage, a U.S. federally chartered crypto bank, to transition USDtb from an offshore model to a payment stablecoin un</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369827164393472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement), supporting 1-20 times leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369608704069632</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoPANewsGate has launched ASP perpetual contract tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement), supporting 1-20 times leverage. [PANews]$USDT$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369608704069632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK AI firm Satsuma Technology raises $135 million to build a Bitcoin vaultReported on July 24 that according to Cointelegraph, British artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology announced that it had successfully raised $135.00 million to build one of the largest Bitcoin vaults in the UK. The company said that all the promised funds are expected to arrive in the next two weeks. This financing is expected to make Satsuma the second largest corporate Bitcoin holder in the UK, second only to The Smarter Web Company. At the same time, this may also become the largest single Bitcoin purchase record for a British company. Satsuma completed this financing through convertible bonds, aiming to accelerate business growth and promote the deep integration of Bitcoin and artificial intelligence. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369519503806464</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoPANewsUK AI firm Satsuma Technology raises $135 million to build a Bitcoin vaultReported on July 24 that according to Cointelegraph, British artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology announced that it had successfully raised $135.00 million to build one of the largest Bitcoin v</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369519503806464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks.live: The English-speaking community is showing clear bearish sentiment, with key discussions revolving around the 30% volatility level.On July 24th, Greeks.live macro researcher Adam released a brief report to the English community stating that the group showed a clear bearish sentiment, with traders holding put option positions despite significant losses. Most traders are focused on potential declines, with key discussions revolving around a 30% volatility level. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367969196773376</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoTechFlowGreeks.live: The English-speaking community is showing clear bearish sentiment, with key discussions revolving around the 30% volatility level.On July 24th, Greeks.live macro researcher Adam released a brief report to the English community stating that the group showed a clear</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367969196773376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine updates ETH holdings: Holds a total of 566,776 ETH, worth over $2.0 billionBitmine officially updated its ETH holdings on the X platform. As of 11:59 PM Eastern Time on July 23, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing time today), Bitmine holds a total of 566,776 ETH, worth over $2.00B. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948370345290960896</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyBitmine updates ETH holdings: Holds a total of 566,776 ETH, worth over $2.0 billionBitmine officially updated its ETH holdings on the X platform. As of 11:59 PM Eastern Time on July 23, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing time today), Bitmine holds a total of 566,776 ETH, worth over $2.00B. [</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948370345290960896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sei Network Launches Native USDC and CCTP V2Native USDC and CCTP V2 are now live on the Sei Network. Circle Mint now fully supports native USDC on Sei. Sei&apos;s USDC (issued via Noble, i.e. USDC.n) will continue to exist after launch. Circle and the Sei Development Foundation have partnered with the ecosystem to develop a migration plan to help move liquidity from USDC.n to native USDC on Sei. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948368309602291712</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoForesightNewsSei Network Launches Native USDC and CCTP V2Native USDC and CCTP V2 are now live on the Sei Network. Circle Mint now fully supports native USDC on Sei. Sei&apos;s USDC (issued via Noble, i.e. USDC.n) will continue to exist after launch. Circle and the Sei Development Foundation</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948368309602291712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet and BASCAN.io jointly launch an exclusive booster pack event, Alpha points 61 and above can be claimedOn July 24, Binance Wallet announced that the exclusive booster pack event in cooperation with BASCAN.io is now live. Users can participate in the second week of the event to share 44.00 million BAS rewards. Binance users with 61 or more Binance Alpha points can participate. Please note that the event reward tokens will be subject to the lock-up period set by the project party. Please understand the relevant regulations in detail before participating. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367155514380288</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoPANewsBinance Wallet and BASCAN.io jointly launch an exclusive booster pack event, Alpha points 61 and above can be claimedOn July 24, Binance Wallet announced that the exclusive booster pack event in cooperation with BASCAN.io is now live. Users can participate in the second week of t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367155514380288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Blockchain Capital Forms New Entity SpiritReserve Group and Plans to Raise Up to $500.00MCanadian digital asset management and investment public company Spirit Blockchain Capital announced the launch of the Spirit Blockchain 2.0 strategy, which plans to integrate a multi-token portfolio into its yield strategy, and expects to expand its yield program to three cryptocurrencies, BTC, ETH and SOL, in the fourth quarter of this year. In addition, Spirit Blockchain Capital also announced the formal establishment of a new entity, SpiritReserve Group, and the phased raising of up to $500.00M in funds, aimed at creating shareholder value through strategic investments in the digital asset space. (Globe Newswire)</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367846236557312</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailySpirit Blockchain Capital Forms New Entity SpiritReserve Group and Plans to Raise Up to $500.00MCanadian digital asset management and investment public company Spirit Blockchain Capital announced the launch of the Spirit Blockchain 2.0 strategy, which plans to integrate a multi-t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367846236557312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: XRP is now at $3.1505According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 6.65% in the past 24h. Now at $3.1505.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366601563627520</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: XRP is now at $3.1505According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 6.65% in the past 24h. Now at $3.1505.$XRPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366601563627520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Foundation Q2 Grants Totaled Approximately $8.374MThe Ethereum Foundation has released its grant data for Q2 2025, with total funding of approximately $8.374 million. The funded project categories include Community and Education, Consensus Layer, Cryptography and Zero-Knowledge Proofs, Developer Experience and Tools, Execution Layer, Overall Growth and Support, Layer 2, etc. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366129713451008</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoForesightNewsEthereum Foundation Q2 Grants Totaled Approximately $8.374MThe Ethereum Foundation has released its grant data for Q2 2025, with total funding of approximately $8.374 million. The funded project categories include Community and Education, Consensus Layer, Cryptography and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366129713451008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAgentAI ecosystem product CorrAI and Blave reach strategic cooperation to promote the democratization of quantitative tradingOn July 24, CorrAI, the core product of the DeAgentAI ecosystem, announced a strategic partnership with the institutional-level data platform Blave. The two parties will integrate institutional-level derivatives data and code-free quantitative strategy building capabilities to provide users with a one-stop solution from data insights to executable trading strategies. The position concentration analysis, advanced filters and real-time warning functions provided by the Blave platform will be directly imported into CorrAI&apos;s visual strategy builder. With the guidance of the AI assistant Corr-GPT, users can quickly create strategies using key data such as whale behavior, long and short positions, and optimize them through indicators such as Sharpe ratio and maximum drawdown. The whole process does not require programming knowledge. The cooperation will also bring cross-platform benefits to users of both platforms: Blave users can access CorrAI&apos;s backtesting function through API, and CorrAI subscribers can unlock Blave&apos;s enhanced data layer. CorrAI is a quantitative trading product in the DeAgentAI ecosystem that focuses on de-FAI. It provides users with verifiable on-chain insights and intelligent strategy development capabilities through DeAgentAI&apos;s advanced multi-agent infrastructure. The product is committed to making quantitative trading more accessible to both novices and professional users, and helps users avoid common pitfalls such as overfitting through an integrated large language model. DeAgentAI is an AI Agent network infrastructure project built on multiple chain ecosystems such as Sui, BSC and BTC, with the core vision of &quot;Make AI Smarter&quot;. It is committed to empowering on-chain transactions through AI prediction and feedback mechanisms, and has currently supported more than 190 million on-chain interactions, providing a smarter and more reliable AI-driven solution for the Web3 ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364632405643264</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoPANewsDeAgentAI ecosystem product CorrAI and Blave reach strategic cooperation to promote the democratization of quantitative tradingOn July 24, CorrAI, the core product of the DeAgentAI ecosystem, announced a strategic partnership with the institutional-level data platform Blave. The</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364632405643264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Innovation Council Appoints Ji Hun Kim as CEO, Adds SoFi as MemberOn July 24, the Cryptocurrency Innovation Council (CCI) announced today that the board of directors has appointed Ji Hun Kim as its chief executive officer (CEO). Kim has served as president and acting CEO of CCI since January 2025. He previously served as the organization&apos;s chief legal and policy officer. At the same time, SoFi, as an innovative company in the field of fintech and banking, officially joined the Crypto Innovation Council. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364466982293504</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoPANewsCrypto Innovation Council Appoints Ji Hun Kim as CEO, Adds SoFi as MemberOn July 24, the Cryptocurrency Innovation Council (CCI) announced today that the board of directors has appointed Ji Hun Kim as its chief executive officer (CEO). Kim has served as president and acting CEO o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364466982293504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Now Supports USYC and cUSDO as OTC CollateralAccording to official sources, Binance is now officially expanding its institutional OTC settlement services, adding support for two tokenized real-world assets (RWA) as collateral: USYC and cUSDO. Institutional users can now use these yield-bearing tokenized stable assets as collateral through Banking Triparty custody and MirrorRSV, to trade securely on the Binance platform while maintaining off-exchange custody and optimizing capital efficiency. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365325002674176</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailyBinance Now Supports USYC and cUSDO as OTC CollateralAccording to official sources, Binance is now officially expanding its institutional OTC settlement services, adding support for two tokenized real-world assets (RWA) as collateral: USYC and cUSDO. Institutional users can now u</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365325002674176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOOFi Pro has enabled multi-collateral margin, adding ETH and USDT as collateral.WOOFi Pro now supports multi-collateral margin, allowing users to trade with ETH, USDT, or USDC without the need for swaps. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360274519592960</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoForesightNewsWOOFi Pro has enabled multi-collateral margin, adding ETH and USDT as collateral.WOOFi Pro now supports multi-collateral margin, allowing users to trade with ETH, USDT, or USDC without the need for swaps. [Foresight News]#DeFi$ETH$MAG7.SSI$USDTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360274519592960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: We will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligenceElon Musk stated on the X platform that we will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligence. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360287639375872</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoOdailyMusk: We will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligenceElon Musk stated on the X platform that we will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligence. [Odaily星球日报]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360287639375872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Societe Generale to make markets in 21Shares Bitcoin, Ether ETPsSociete Generale will provide liquidity for 21Shares’ Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, expanding access for institutional crypto investors in Europe.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948356453256990720</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoPANewsSociete Generale to make markets in 21Shares Bitcoin, Ether ETPsSociete Generale will provide liquidity for 21Shares’ Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, expanding access for institutional crypto investors in Europe.#ETF$ETH$MAG7.SSI$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948356453256990720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether: XAUT token is backed by over 7.66 tons of gold stored in SwitzerlandTether stated that as of Q2 2025, the number of XAUT tokens, Tether&apos;s gold token, issued was 246,524.330, with each token pegged to an equivalent amount of physical gold at a 1:1 ratio, backed by over 7.66 tons (246,524.380 troy ounces) of gold stored in Switzerland. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948354800466333696</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsTether: XAUT token is backed by over 7.66 tons of gold stored in SwitzerlandTether stated that as of Q2 2025, the number of XAUT tokens, Tether&apos;s gold token, issued was 246,524.330, with each token pegged to an equivalent amount of physical gold at a 1:1 ratio, backed by over</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948354800466333696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deBridge Foundation Launches Reserve Fund, Repurchasing DBR Tokens with All Protocol RevenueThe deBridge Foundation has launched a reserve fund that allocates 100% of protocol revenue to repurchase its native DBR token on the open market. As of July 24, the fund has acquired 1.3% of the total DBR supply since its launch in June, worth nearly $3.00M. deBridge&apos;s overall treasury now holds $30.10M in assets, covering DBR, USDC, SOL, and ETH. In addition, the fund is exploring yield strategies and has launched a public dashboard to track assets and yields in real time. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948355264826118144</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailydeBridge Foundation Launches Reserve Fund, Repurchasing DBR Tokens with All Protocol RevenueThe deBridge Foundation has launched a reserve fund that allocates 100% of protocol revenue to repurchase its native DBR token on the open market. As of July 24, the fund has acquired 1.3% of</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948355264826118144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoSoValue Podcast Upgrade: Enhanced Market Insights DeliveryAI-driven investment research platform SoSoValue has announced a significant upgrade to its daily podcast feature.   This enhancement focuses on optimizing content delivery methodology to facilitate efficient absorption of critical market intelligence.Key Improvements:Streamlined Narration: Complex market analysis translated into accessible insightsCut through chaos. Focus on what drives the crypto market.Listen Now: SoSoValue remains committed to building a professional, transparent, open, and intelligent crypto data platform, delivering real-time, in-depth market analysis to empower investors and democratize market intelligence.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353255068880896</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSoValueSoSoValue Podcast Upgrade: Enhanced Market Insights DeliveryAI-driven investment research platform SoSoValue has announced a significant upgrade to its daily podcast feature.   This enhancement focuses on optimizing content delivery methodology to facilitate efficient absorption o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353255068880896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to begin $1.9B payouts in September as claims no longer disputedFTX’s next $1.9 billion distribution would unlikely include repayments to jurisdictions questioned in an earlier motion, which is currently being rewritten, according to creditors.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353017945853952</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFTX to begin $1.9B payouts in September as claims no longer disputedFTX’s next $1.9 billion distribution would unlikely include repayments to jurisdictions questioned in an earlier motion, which is currently being rewritten, according to creditors.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353017945853952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>