<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Codatta’s XNY token will begin circulating on July 23 at 20:00On July 22, Binance Wallet stated on the X platform that Codatta&apos;s XNY tokens will begin to circulate at 20:00 Beijing time on July 23. Users who participated in Codatta Pre-TGE can trade XNY tokens on the Binance Alpha platform. Winners of Codatta&apos;s first and second week Booster activities can claim and trade their XNY tokens within 8 hours after the tokens begin to circulate. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947509496834445312</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsBinance: Codatta’s XNY token will begin circulating on July 23 at 20:00On July 22, Binance Wallet stated on the X platform that Codatta&apos;s XNY tokens will begin to circulate at 20:00 Beijing time on July 23. Users who participated in Codatta Pre-TGE can trade XNY tokens on the Binan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947509496834445312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet: XNY Token Circulation to Launch on July 23 at 20:00Binance Wallet tweeted that Codatta (XNY) token circulation will start on July 23 at 20:00. Users participating in Codatta Pre-TGE can trade XNY tokens on Binance Alpha. Winners of the Week 1 and Week 2 Codatta Booster activities can claim and trade XNY tokens within 8 hours of the token circulation start. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947509492698861568</link>
      <description>1 minute agoForesightNewsBinance Wallet: XNY Token Circulation to Launch on July 23 at 20:00Binance Wallet tweeted that Codatta (XNY) token circulation will start on July 23 at 20:00. Users participating in Codatta Pre-TGE can trade XNY tokens on Binance Alpha. Winners of the Week 1 and Week 2 Codat</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 04:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947509492698861568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday, with none of the twelve ETFs experiencing a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 21th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net outflow yesterday was Ark Invest and 21Shares&apos;s ETF ARKB, with a daily net outflow of 77.46M USD, and the total historical net inflow of ARKB currently stands at 2.84B USD.The second highest was Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC, with a daily net outflow of 36.75M USD, and the total historical net outflow of GBTC currently stands at 23.54B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 151.60B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.52%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.62B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947503415871098880</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday, with none of the twelve ETFs experiencing a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 131.35M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 21th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with th</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947503415871098880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate.io Adds USD1 Trading Zone, Launching 9 Popular Trading Pairs Including BTC/USD1 and ETH/USD1 in the First BatchAccording to the official announcement, Gate will officially launch the USD1 trading zone at 14:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, and will initially launch 9 popular currency trading pairs including BTC/USD1, ETH/USD1, SOL/USD1, B/USD1, BNB/USD1, TRX/USD1, DOGE/USD1, SUI/USD1, and EGL1/USD1, to further enrich trading options and enhance user experience. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947504653050859520</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyGate.io Adds USD1 Trading Zone, Launching 9 Popular Trading Pairs Including BTC/USD1 and ETH/USD1 in the First BatchAccording to the official announcement, Gate will officially launch the USD1 trading zone at 14:00 (UTC+8) on July 22, and will initially launch 9 popular currency</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947504653050859520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upbit 24-Hour Trading Volume Ranking: XRP, STRIKE, DOGE Top ThreeOn July 22, according to CoinGecko data, Upbit&apos;s trading volume in the past 24 hours reached $6.45B, up 35.40%. The top five tokens by trading volume are:

XRP (12.72% of trading volume, $820.00M in transaction volume)

STRIKE (11.98% of trading volume, $773.00M in transaction volume)

DOGE (7.93% of trading volume, $511.00M in transaction volume)

SOL (6.66% of trading volume, $429.00M in transaction volume)

PENGU (4.84% of trading volume, $312.00M in transaction volume)
 [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502503595888640</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoTechFlowUpbit 24-Hour Trading Volume Ranking: XRP, STRIKE, DOGE Top ThreeOn July 22, according to CoinGecko data, Upbit&apos;s trading volume in the past 24 hours reached $6.45B, up 35.40%. The top five tokens by trading volume are:

XRP (12.72% of trading volume, $820.00M in transaction vo</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502503595888640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faraday Future and HabitTrade have reached a strategic partnership to enhance shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial servicesOn July 22, according to Groonghui, Faraday Future announced a strategic partnership with HabitTrade. HabitTrade is a global multi-market broker and digital asset infrastructure platform. FF said it plans to use this partnership to provide its shareholders with exclusive benefits on the HabitTrade platform and further enhance shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial services. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502403410743296</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoPANewsFaraday Future and HabitTrade have reached a strategic partnership to enhance shareholder value through innovative Web3 financial servicesOn July 22, according to Groonghui, Faraday Future announced a strategic partnership with HabitTrade. HabitTrade is a global multi-market brok</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947502403410743296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grupo Murano Plans to Build $10.00B Bitcoin Treasury in Five YearsAccording to Bitcoin Magazine, Mexican-listed real estate company Grupo Murano plans to incorporate Bitcoin into its core strategic assets, with an initial investment of approximately $1.00B and plans to build a $10.00B Bitcoin treasury within five years. Its CEO, Elías Sacal, stated that the company is converting its properties into BTC holdings through asset refinancing and sale-leaseback transactions, and will deploy Bitcoin ATMs in its properties and open up hotel BTC payment scenarios. Its overall capital allocation will allocate 70% to 80% to Bitcoin, with the remainder invested in high-margin real estate projects to improve capital efficiency and mitigate the risks posed by the high-interest rate environment. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947500669359640576</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoForesightNewsGrupo Murano Plans to Build $10.00B Bitcoin Treasury in Five YearsAccording to Bitcoin Magazine, Mexican-listed real estate company Grupo Murano plans to incorporate Bitcoin into its core strategic assets, with an initial investment of approximately $1.00B and plans to bui</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947500669359640576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuga Labs Co-founder Posts, Possibly Hinting at the Launch of an NFT Treasury CompanyYuga Labs co-founder Garga.eth tweeted, &quot;The world isn&apos;t ready for NFT treasury companies, but they&apos;re on their way.&quot; The community says this may indicate that it will launch an NFT treasury company. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497840112848896</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoForesightNewsYuga Labs Co-founder Posts, Possibly Hinting at the Launch of an NFT Treasury CompanyYuga Labs co-founder Garga.eth tweeted, &quot;The world isn&apos;t ready for NFT treasury companies, but they&apos;re on their way.&quot; The community says this may indicate that it will launch an NFT treasu</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497840112848896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Diner restaurant has opened to the public, possibly supporting DOGE paymentsTesla Diner is now open to the public. It is equipped with 80 Tesla Supercharger stalls, provides autonomous vehicle pick-up and drop-off for customers, and Tesla humanoid robot waiters. In addition, some community members have revealed that the restaurant may accept DOGE payments. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496919773499392</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoForesightNewsTesla Diner restaurant has opened to the public, possibly supporting DOGE paymentsTesla Diner is now open to the public. It is equipped with 80 Tesla Supercharger stalls, provides autonomous vehicle pick-up and drop-off for customers, and Tesla humanoid robot waiters. In a</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947496919773499392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00MAccording to crypto analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, a certain whale is currently going long on Bitcoin on both the Aave and Hyperliquid platforms, with a total position value of approximately $91.00M and a current floating profit of over $4.223M. Among them, the address on the Aave platform is cyclically going long on WBTC at an average price of $114,272.00, mortgaging 342.21 WBTC, borrowing $20.00M in stablecoins, with a health factor of 1.57, and a current floating profit of $963,000.00; on the Hyperliquid platform, it is using 10x leverage to go long on BTC, with a position amount of approximately $50.93M, an opening price of $109,655.20, and a floating profit of approximately $3.26M. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497104893300736</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailyA whale is going long on BTC on both Aave and Hyperliquid, with a total position value of $91.00MAccording to crypto analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, a certain whale is currently going long on Bitcoin on both the Aave and Hyperliquid platforms, with a total position value</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497104893300736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet Launches Exclusive Point Boost Event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2According to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched an exclusive points bonus event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2. By interacting through linking your OKX Wallet, users can enjoy an additional 10% points bonus. Users can participate in the event via the following link: https://portal.kaia.io/mission/epoch2 It is reported that Kaia is a merger of the Klaytn and Finschia blockchains initially developed by Kakao and LINE, respectively. It has the lowest transaction latency in EVM L1, with a 1-second block time and instant finality, enabling a smooth user experience and opening up possibilities for use cases that require near real-time response. OKX Wallet is a leading one-stop Web3 portal in the industry and supports 130+ popular public chains. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497113336434688</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoOdailyOKX Wallet Launches Exclusive Point Boost Event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2According to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched an exclusive points bonus event for Kaia Portal Epoch 2. By interacting through linking your OKX Wallet, users can enjoy an additional 10% points bonus. U</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947497113336434688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: SOL is now at $202.45According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 8.91% in the past 24h. Now at $202.45.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947493444191477760</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: SOL is now at $202.45According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 8.91% in the past 24h. Now at $202.45.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947493444191477760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changpeng Zhao: Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today.According to Business Daily, Changpeng Zhao stated that Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today. &quot;Giggle is small, but it focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947491851171024896</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsChangpeng Zhao: Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today.According to Business Daily, Changpeng Zhao stated that Giggle Academy focuses on building schools in impoverished areas that no one wants to go to today. &quot;Giggle</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947491851171024896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito AI to Launch on Capital Launchpad This WeekKaito AI has announced that it will launch Capital Launchpad this week, providing a fundraising platform for community projects. Project teams can combine social reputation and on-chain holdings for distribution. After eligible users subscribe, the remaining quota can enter the FCFS stage. Platform fees will be returned to the community through the gKAITO mechanism. In addition, the official said that KYC is only a regulatory requirement and will be fully managed by Persona. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947490196438405120</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Kaito AI to Launch on Capital Launchpad This WeekKaito AI has announced that it will launch Capital Launchpad this week, providing a fundraising platform for community projects. Project teams can combine social reputation and on-chain holdings for distribution. After eligible users subsc</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947490196438405120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea to Advance &quot;Virtual Currency Short Selling&quot; Legislation, Planning to Introduce Stock Market-Level RegulationAccording to Edaily, South Korean financial regulators plan to introduce regulatory standards equivalent to those in the stock market for token lending services offered by the country&apos;s crypto exchanges. Currently, Bithumb offers token lending services up to 400% of the collateral value, while Upbit offers Bitcoin lending services up to 80% of the collateral. Financial authorities believe that such services are essentially equivalent to short selling transactions and are considering introducing corresponding regulatory measures in the ongoing second phase of virtual asset legislation. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488457840676864</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说South Korea to Advance &quot;Virtual Currency Short Selling&quot; Legislation, Planning to Introduce Stock Market-Level RegulationAccording to Edaily, South Korean financial regulators plan to introduce regulatory standards equivalent to those in the stock market for token lending services offered</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488457840676864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain game developer Delabs Games completes $5.20M Series A funding round, led by Hashed and othersAccording to GamesBeat, blockchain game developer Delabs Games has completed a $5.20M Series A funding round led by Hashed, TON Ventures, and Kilo Fund, with participation from IVC, Taisu Ventures, Arche Fund (Coin98), YGG, Everyrealm, and Jets Capital. The funds raised will be used to promote the continued development of AI-driven Web3 games through the AI game creation platform Verse8, and to support Delabs Games&apos; upcoming game releases. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488053623017472</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBlockchain game developer Delabs Games completes $5.20M Series A funding round, led by Hashed and othersAccording to GamesBeat, blockchain game developer Delabs Games has completed a $5.20M Series A funding round led by Hashed, TON Ventures, and Kilo Fund, with participation f</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947488053623017472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institutional investor withdrew 550.0M PUMP and transferred it to Bybit, worth approximately $2.28MAccording to Solscan data, a pre-sale institutional investor: HmKrZg…G8BkKt removed 550.00M PUMP and 2.344M USDC from Pumpfun AMM between 3:46-4:36 UTC+8 today, and then transferred all 550.00M PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $2.285M [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947485294265913344</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说An institutional investor withdrew 550.0M PUMP and transferred it to Bybit, worth approximately $2.28MAccording to Solscan data, a pre-sale institutional investor: HmKrZg…G8BkKt removed 550.00M PUMP and 2.344M USDC from Pumpfun AMM between 3:46-4:36 UTC+8 today, and then transferred all</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947485294265913344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western Union plans to integrate stablecoins into its digital wallet productsOn July 22, according to Cryptobriefing, Devin McGranahan, CEO of Western Union, said in an interview with Bloomberg&apos;s &quot;The Close&quot; column on Monday that Western Union sees stablecoins as an opportunity and the company is actively adjusting its infrastructure and expanding partnerships to integrate related technologies into its global payment network. McGranahan pointed out that Western Union, which has a 175-year history, faces three key opportunities: fast cross-border remittances, stablecoin and fiat currency exchange, and providing customers with value storage tools. He added: &quot;We believe that stablecoins are indeed an opportunity, not a threat.&quot; McGranahan revealed that the company has tested new settlement systems in South America and Africa to speed up the remittance process, while exploring the provision of stablecoin services in its digital wallets through cooperation. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484174625820672</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsWestern Union plans to integrate stablecoins into its digital wallet productsOn July 22, according to Cryptobriefing, Devin McGranahan, CEO of Western Union, said in an interview with Bloomberg&apos;s &quot;The Close&quot; column on Monday that Western Union sees stablecoins as an opportunity and t</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484174625820672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Police Seize 7 Illegal Crypto ATMs, Arrest Two SuspectsThe UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and the London Metropolitan Police have jointly seized 7 illegal crypto ATMs and arrested two people on suspicion of money laundering and operating an illegal crypto exchange. Therese Chambers, Executive Director of Enforcement and Market Oversight at the FCA, said, &quot;If users operate crypto ATMs or exchanges illegally, they should be prepared to face serious consequences. There are currently no legally operating crypto ATMs in the UK, so using such devices only fuels crime. We will continue to work with law enforcement to combat financial crime and protect consumers.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947483058597023744</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsUK Police Seize 7 Illegal Crypto ATMs, Arrest Two SuspectsThe UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and the London Metropolitan Police have jointly seized 7 illegal crypto ATMs and arrested two people on suspicion of money laundering and operating an illegal crypto exchange. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947483058597023744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader Eugene: Cut losses on PUMP, sideways trading for too long without a breakoutTrader Eugene stated in his personal channel that he has cleared his PUMP position. He pointed out that PUMP has been trading sideways in the 0.004 range for too long and has failed to break upwards. His personal trading logic is no longer valid, so he chose to stop the loss and leave the market. He emphasized that now is not the time to hold stagnant targets. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484521498955776</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrader Eugene: Cut losses on PUMP, sideways trading for too long without a breakoutTrader Eugene stated in his personal channel that he has cleared his PUMP position. He pointed out that PUMP has been trading sideways in the 0.004 range for too long and has failed to break upwards. H</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 03:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947484521498955776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>