<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>90-Day Correlation Between Bitcoin Volatility Index and S&amp;P 500 VIX Hits All-Time HighOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, data showed that the 90-day correlation coefficient between the Bitcoin 30-day Implied Volatility Index (BVIV/DVOL) and the S&amp;P 500 Volatility Index (VIX) hit a record high of 0.88, indicating that the linkage between the cryptocurrency market and the volatility of US stocks has significantly increased. The current correlation coefficient remains at a high level of 0.75. Analysts pointed out that this phenomenon reflects that Wall Street institutions are dominating this round of crypto market cycle. Markus Thielen, founder of 10x Research, said that institutional investors have compressed volatility by selling a large number of call options, making Bitcoin price movements increasingly affected by the risk appetite of traditional markets. Since the beginning of this year, the BVIV index has dropped from 67% to 42%, while the price of Bitcoin has risen by 26% during the same period, breaking the historical pattern of the two fluctuating in the same direction. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948266788579512320</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoPANews90-Day Correlation Between Bitcoin Volatility Index and S&amp;P 500 VIX Hits All-Time HighOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, data showed that the 90-day correlation coefficient between the Bitcoin 30-day Implied Volatility Index (BVIV/DVOL) and the S&amp;P 500 Volatility Index (VIX) hit a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948266788579512320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US judge denies brothers&apos; motion to dismiss $25.00 million crypto fraud chargesOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. District Judge Jessica Clarke rejected the motion of the Peraire-Bueno brothers, MIT graduates, to dismiss the $25.00 million cryptocurrency fraud charges. Prosecutors accused the brothers of exploiting a vulnerability in the Ethereum network in May 2024 to conduct arbitrage attacks by manipulating the MEV robot. Court documents show that the two developed a four-step plan of &quot;bait-blocking-search-propagation&quot;, using 16 Ethereum verification nodes and 529.50 ETH as bait to intercept the trading profits of the MEV robot within 12 seconds. The judge determined that his actions met the requirements of wire fraud, although the defendant argued that &quot;the system code allows such operations.&quot; The case is expected to go to trial in October 2025, and the brothers face felony charges such as wire fraud and conspiracy to launder money. The prosecutor has dropped one of the charges of conspiracy to receive stolen property, but the remaining charges will still go to trial. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948265564467695616</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsUS judge denies brothers&apos; motion to dismiss $25.00 million crypto fraud chargesOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. District Judge Jessica Clarke rejected the motion of the Peraire-Bueno brothers, MIT graduates, to dismiss the $25.00 million cryptocurrency fraud charges. P</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948265564467695616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PancakeSwap’s Infinity hits Base chain. Will CAKE price follow and hit new highs?PancakeSwap Infinity DEX has just launched on Base, bringing its advanced DeFi features to the Ethereum L2 as PancakeSwap’s CAKE token price tests key resistance, eyeing $4. PancakeSwap’s decentralized exchange, PancakeSwap Infinity, has officially launched on Base, bringing Infinity’s powerful features — including dynamic fee structures via customizable Hooks, dual pool types, and major gas-saving optimizations — to one of the fastest-growing Ethereum Layer 2 ecosystems. The rollout also aligns with PancakeSwap’s broader goal of delivering scalable, low-cost DeFi across chains. The rollout on Base follows closely on the heels of Infinity’s debut on BNB Chain in late April and comes amid a surge in activity on the Base network, which recently hit record highs in both total value locked and DEX volume. It also follows the launch of PancakeSwap’s one-click cross-chain swaps via the Across Protocol, which already supports asset transfers between BNB Chain, Arbitrum, and Base. CAKE price has recently tested the key horizontal resistance in the $2.80–$3.00 range. This level has acted as a significant barrier, having been tested multiple times since early January. This was accompanied by a series of higher lows, forming a well-defined ascending triangle — a bullish continuation pattern that suggests increasing buying pressure at progressively higher levels. Although the price has pulled back from the local peak of $3.00 to $2.65 at the time of writing, CAKE remains technically strong — holding above both the 20-day EMA and the ascending trendline that defines the pattern’s support. Notably, volume also spiked during the recent breakout attempt, signaling growing market interest. This, combined with CAKE’s consistent pattern of higher lows converging toward the key resistance zone, points to mounting bullish pressure that soon culminate in a breakout. A confirmed close above the $3.00 level would validate the ascending triangle breakout, setting the stage for a potential rally toward the $4.00 region, a target derived from the measured move of the triangle’s height. On the downside, the immediate support lies around $2.30, followed by the psychological $2.00 level, which forms the triangle’s base. A breakdown below these levels could invalidate the bullish setup and expose CAKE price to further downside risk toward $1.75 or lower. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948264996252749824</link>
      <description>10 minutes agocrypto.newsPancakeSwap’s Infinity hits Base chain. Will CAKE price follow and hit new highs?PancakeSwap Infinity DEX has just launched on Base, bringing its advanced DeFi features to the Ethereum L2 as PancakeSwap’s CAKE token price tests key resistance, eyeing $4. PancakeSwap’s decent</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948264996252749824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale sold multiple Base ecosystem tokens in the past 48 hours, with a cumulative loss of US$5.00 millionOn July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, in the past 48 hours, a whale sold multiple Base ecosystem tokens, with a cumulative loss of US$5.00 million:
 Sold 1.08 million VIRTUAL in exchange for 1.87 million USDC, with a loss of $1.73 million (original purchase price of $3.59 million);
 Sold 5.75 million AIXBT in exchange for 951,000 USDC, with a loss of $1.70 million (original purchase price of $2.655 million);
 Sold 4.47 million GAME in exchange for 188,000 USDC, with a loss of $1.19 million (original purchase price of $1.375 million);
 Sold 38,443.75 VVVs in exchange for 123,000 USDC, with a loss of US$379,000.00 (original purchase price US$502,000.00).
 Note: These tokens were purchased between December 2024 and January 2025. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948263289066164224</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsA whale sold multiple Base ecosystem tokens in the past 48 hours, with a cumulative loss of US$5.00 millionOn July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, in the past 48 hours, a whale sold multiple Base ecosystem tokens, with a cumulative loss of US$5.00 million:
 Sold 1.08 mi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948263289066164224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European investment app Lightyear completes $23.00M funding round, led by NordicNinjaAccording to CNBC, European investment app Lightyear has completed a $23.00M funding round led by NordicNinja, with participation from Bolt co-founder Markus Villig, Wise co-founder Taavet Hinrikus, former Checkout.com CTO Ott Kaukver, and Skype founding engineer Jaan Tallinn. The startup hopes to become the &quot;European version of Robinhood,&quot; entering the commission-free trading market. In addition to the new funding, Lightyear will also launch a new artificial intelligence feature. Furthermore, Lightyear plans to launch its own cryptocurrency product within two months, focusing on a &quot;more long-term perspective&quot; investment experience. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948262683811319808</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoForesightNewsEuropean investment app Lightyear completes $23.00M funding round, led by NordicNinjaAccording to CNBC, European investment app Lightyear has completed a $23.00M funding round led by NordicNinja, with participation from Bolt co-founder Markus Villig, Wise co-founder Taavet</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948262683811319808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: SOL is now at $181.33According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 10.05% in the past 24h. Now at $181.33.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948261529970237440</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: SOL is now at $181.33According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 10.05% in the past 24h. Now at $181.33.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948261529970237440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiRWA index 24hr loss of 10.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiRWA has fallen by 10.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OM -12.88%, PENDLE -11.58%, ONDO -11.26%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948261249174167552</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiRWA index 24hr loss of 10.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiRWA has fallen by 10.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OM -12.88%, PENDLE -11.58%, ONDO -11.26%.$PENDLE$OM$ONDOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948261249174167552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: LINK is now at $17.53According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is down 10.01% in the past 24h. Now at $17.53.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948261147604901888</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: LINK is now at $17.53According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is down 10.01% in the past 24h. Now at $17.53.$LINKShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948261147604901888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: SUI is now at $3.60849According to SoSoValue, SUI (Sui) is down 10.04% in the past 24h. Now at $3.60849.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948260894038253568</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: SUI is now at $3.60849According to SoSoValue, SUI (Sui) is down 10.04% in the past 24h. Now at $3.60849.$SUIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948260894038253568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zircuit launches Hyperliquid for AI Trading, an AI engine that supports real-time cross-chain crypto tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Zircuit announced the launch of &quot;Hyperliquid for AI Trading,&quot; an AI engine that supports real-time cross-chain crypto trading, with one-click execution and enterprise-level security. The platform now supports both passive income generation and active AI strategy trading, and will be launched in phases starting in July 2025, open to the world in August, and launch an ecological incentive plan in Q4 (a total of 10.00 million ZRC will be allocated for the community to build AI models). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948257607294193664</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoPANewsZircuit launches Hyperliquid for AI Trading, an AI engine that supports real-time cross-chain crypto tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Zircuit announced the launch of &quot;Hyperliquid for AI Trading,&quot; an AI engine that supports real-time cross-chain crypto trading, with</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948257607294193664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized computing network Spheron Network&apos;s annual recurring revenue has exceeded $10.00M.Decentralized computing network Spheron Network posted on X that its annual recurring revenue (ARR) has exceeded $10.00M. Spheron is building a global community-driven computing power infrastructure network by integrating data center-grade and retail-grade GPUs/CPUs. Spheron&apos;s native token SPON will be launched on the Base L2 mainnet in Q3 2025 and will be used for computing power payment, node staking, governance and other scenarios. According to official introduction, Spheron will focus on promoting Agent Marketplace, DePIN lending module, inference/model market and serverless computing product lines in the future. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948259623923945472</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoOdailyDecentralized computing network Spheron Network&apos;s annual recurring revenue has exceeded $10.00M.Decentralized computing network Spheron Network posted on X that its annual recurring revenue (ARR) has exceeded $10.00M. Spheron is building a global community-driven computing power</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948259623923945472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini adds more tokenized stock assets and launches Solana staking serviceReported on July 24 that according to Crowdfundinsider, the crypto exchange Gemini announced that it has added 14 new U.S. stock tokenized assets for EU investors, including Broadcom, Nike, Starbucks, etc., bringing the total to 37. These assets issued through the Arbitrum chain are managed by the Malta-regulated entity Gemini Intergalactic EU Artemis, which supports 24/7 trading and fragmented holdings, but does not grant voting rights. Gemini Custody simultaneously launched the Solana pledge service for ETFs and corporate clients. Canada&apos;s Purpose Investments has connected its SOLL ETF to the service, and the pledge income is directly attributed to the fund. Listed company DeFi Development Corp (DFDV) also uses the service to manage its SOL holdings and expand the scale of pledges in combination with a $5.00B credit line. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948256917612204032</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoPANewsGemini adds more tokenized stock assets and launches Solana staking serviceReported on July 24 that according to Crowdfundinsider, the crypto exchange Gemini announced that it has added 14 new U.S. stock tokenized assets for EU investors, including Broadcom, Nike, Starbucks, etc.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948256917612204032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Onchain Trading Lists Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, and Other TokensBitget Onchain Trading has launched MEME tokens Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, ORGO, ZKWASM, TRUST, COA, and DEBT from the Solana, Base, and BNB Smart Chain ecosystems. Users can start trading in the Onchain Trading section. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948255223381823488</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Onchain Trading Lists Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, and Other TokensBitget Onchain Trading has launched MEME tokens Totakeke, Billy, memecoin, ORGO, ZKWASM, TRUST, COA, and DEBT from the Solana, Base, and BNB Smart Chain ecosystems. Users can start trading in the Oncha</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948255223381823488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dexari self-custody trading app officially launched on iOS and Android, no invitation code required, supports up to 40x leverage tradingDexari has announced the official launch of its self-custody trading app on iOS and Android platforms, with no invitation code required for user registration. The platform is powered by Hyperliquid and supports spot and perpetual contract trading with up to 40x leverage, featuring advanced orders, TradingView charts, no KYC, no blocking, and a MoonPay fiat gateway. Currently, Dexari is in the preliminary stage of points accumulation, with snapshots to be completed soon. Users can earn points and USDC rewards through trading, inviting friends (25% profit sharing + 10% commission discount), and participating in social tasks. In addition, Dexari has launched a content creation reward campaign (UGC Campaign), announcing winners weekly with a total prize pool of over $5,000.00, and participants can receive up to 80% commission discounts, Discord identity badges, and additional points rewards. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254596715057152</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoOdailyDexari self-custody trading app officially launched on iOS and Android, no invitation code required, supports up to 40x leverage tradingDexari has announced the official launch of its self-custody trading app on iOS and Android platforms, with no invitation code required for user</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254596715057152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Afternoon News1. Trump will visit the Federal Reserve on Thursday;
2. Azuki partners with OpenSea to release Mizuki short film ERC-1155 collectibles;
3. Nasdaq-listed Lion Group increases its holdings of SUI tokens, bringing the total investment portfolio to $9.60M;
4. GSR withdrew approximately $9.87M worth of ETH from Binance 2 hours ago and transferred it to an associated wallet;
5. Faraday Future, under Jia Yueting, announces a strategic partnership with digital asset infrastructure platform HabitTrade;
6. Arkham: The U.S. government&apos;s total BTC holdings are at least 198,000;
7. Bithumb will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs;
8. A whale has closed its PUMP short position, profiting a total of $2.45M;
9. Bitcoin spot ETFs had a total net outflow of $85.96M yesterday, continuing the net outflow for 3 consecutive days;
10. Ethereum spot ETFs had a total net inflow of $332.00M yesterday, continuing the net inflow for 14 consecutive days.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254605149802496</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoOdailyPlanet Afternoon News1. Trump will visit the Federal Reserve on Thursday;
2. Azuki partners with OpenSea to release Mizuki short film ERC-1155 collectibles;
3. Nasdaq-listed Lion Group increases its holdings of SUI tokens, bringing the total investment portfolio to $9.60M;
4. GSR</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948254605149802496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Proposes Increasing Block Limit to 100M CU via SIMD-0286 ProposalAccording to Cointelegraph, Solana plans to increase block capacity by 66% from 60.00M CU to 100.00M CU through the SIMD-0286 proposal. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948253509324967936</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoForesightNewsSolana Proposes Increasing Block Limit to 100M CU via SIMD-0286 ProposalAccording to Cointelegraph, Solana plans to increase block capacity by 66% from 60.00M CU to 100.00M CU through the SIMD-0286 proposal. [Foresight News]#Layer1$MAG7.SSI$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948253509324967936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale withdrew 76,000 SOL again and staked them, with cumulative withdrawals reaching 164,000 SOL.According to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale today again withdrew 76,000 SOL from Kraken, worth approximately $14.50M. Since July 8, the address has cumulatively withdrawn 164,000 SOL (approximately $30.14M) from Kraken and used them for staking. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948239496893501440</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA certain whale withdrew 76,000 SOL again and staked them, with cumulative withdrawals reaching 164,000 SOL.According to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale today again withdrew 76,000 SOL from Kraken, worth approximately $14.50M. Since July 8, the address has cumulatively withdrawn 164,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948239496893501440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiNFT index 24hr loss of 10.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has fallen by 10.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU -11.35%, APE -10.12%, SUPER -9.98%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948248825549250560</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiNFT index 24hr loss of 10.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has fallen by 10.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: PENGU -11.35%, APE -10.12%, SUPER -9.98%.$APE$SUPER$PENGUShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948248825549250560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority: It is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the public from August 1.The Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, Eddie Yue, reminded the public that there have recently been fraudulent activities involving the promotion of digital assets and stablecoins, causing losses to the public. The &quot;Stablecoin Ordinance&quot; came into effect on August 1st, and according to the ordinance, it is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the Hong Kong public from the effective date. Eddie Yue revealed that the greater focus of central banks and financial regulatory authorities in various countries recently is on how to prevent stablecoins from being used as money laundering tools by criminals, especially in cross-border use scenarios. The Bank for International Settlements devoted considerable space in its latest annual economic report to emphasizing the importance of preventing stablecoin money laundering risks. Eddie Yue believes that a balance between strictness and flexibility is an art of regulation. After all, the regulated stablecoin business is in its initial stage. It is obviously more conducive to the sustainable and healthy development of the market and issuing institutions to be strict and stable first, and then moderately relax according to practical experience, rather than starting too loosely and then cleaning up the chaos. [Securities Times]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948247042186350592</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyHong Kong Monetary Authority: It is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the public from August 1.The Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, Eddie Yue, reminded the public that there have recently been fraudulent activities involving the promotion of digital</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948247042186350592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azuki Announces Collaboration with OpenSea to Release &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts&quot; NFT CollectionAzuki has announced a collaboration with OpenSea to release an ERC-1155 collectible, &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts,&quot; based on the &quot;Mizuki&quot; animated short film. The proceeds will be used to support the production of the short film and creators&apos; work. The first round of Mint will be open for 1 week, followed by a regular Mint that will last for 6 months, priced at 0.0014 ETH, with no wallet or whitelist restrictions. In the last cycle, Azuki raised over 20,000 ETH through the Elemental Beans series. After the reveal, the works were criticized for lacking originality and resembling old works, which triggered strong dissatisfaction in the community. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948241940276908032</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Azuki Announces Collaboration with OpenSea to Release &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts&quot; NFT CollectionAzuki has announced a collaboration with OpenSea to release an ERC-1155 collectible, &quot;Azuki Mizuki Anime Shorts,&quot; based on the &quot;Mizuki&quot; animated short film. The proceeds will be used to suppor</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 05:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948241940276908032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>