<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5Yahoo Finance quotes show that Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377912905895936</link>
      <description>1 minute agoOdailyTesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5Yahoo Finance quotes show that Tesla (TSLA.O) fell 8.7%, hitting $303.00, the biggest drop since June 5. [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377912905895936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;U.S. President Trump denies he wants to &quot;destroy Musk&apos;s company.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377921361612800</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoOdailyTrump Denies He Wants to &quot;Destroy Musk&apos;s Company&quot;U.S. President Trump denies he wants to &quot;destroy Musk&apos;s company.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377921361612800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Digital Partners with Ethena Labs to Launch First GENIUS Compliant, Federally Regulated Stablecoin USDtbAnchorage Digital Announces Strategic Collaboration with Ethena Labs to Launch the First GENIUS Act Compliant Stablecoin, USDtb, in the United States. As the only federally chartered crypto bank in the U.S., Anchorage Digital will issue USDtb in the U.S. through its stablecoin issuance platform, helping institutional clients access digital dollars in a compliant and secure manner. [Business Wire]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377929808941056</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailyAnchorage Digital Partners with Ethena Labs to Launch First GENIUS Compliant, Federally Regulated Stablecoin USDtbAnchorage Digital Announces Strategic Collaboration with Ethena Labs to Launch the First GENIUS Act Compliant Stablecoin, USDtb, in the United States. As the only fede</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948377929808941056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito: Capital Launchpad&apos;s first products, Theoriq and Espresso, will be launched tomorrow.Kaito Al announces that the first products of its Capital Launchpad will officially launch tomorrow, with Theoriq and Espresso conducting their community initial distribution on Capital Launchpad on July 25 at 20:00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376297218052096</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNewsKaito: Capital Launchpad&apos;s first products, Theoriq and Espresso, will be launched tomorrow.Kaito Al announces that the first products of its Capital Launchpad will officially launch tomorrow, with Theoriq and Espresso conducting their community initial distribution on Capit</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376297218052096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$TRUMP Goes Live On TRON NetworkJuly 24, 2025 - Geneva, Switzerland - TRON DAO, a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps, announced today the official deployment of $TRUMP on the TRON blockchain. The token expansion is enabled by LayerZero’s Omnichain Fungible Token (OFT) standard and Stargate Finance’s user interface and liquidity transport protocol. Together, they provide a framework for cross-chain transfers of $TRUMP while maintaining a unified supply. This development positions TRON at the forefront of the evolving digital asset landscape, where real-world value transfer, speed, and accessibility are critical to mainstream growth.

The deployment of $TRUMP on TRON introduces the token to one of the most actively used blockchain networks in the world. TRON hosts over 321 million user accounts and over $20 billion in daily transfer volume, with a circulating supply of more than $80 billion in USDT on the network. Its infrastructure is optimized for high-speed and low-cost transactions, making it an ideal blockchain for a token like $TRUMP that seeks to scale across everyday use cases—from DeFi engagement to community activations and potentially real-world payments.

“TRON is built to support scale, inclusion, and real-world use,” said Justin Sun, Founder of TRON. “The launch of $TRUMP on TRON reflects our belief in giving community-powered assets a network that can help them thrive globally.”

LayerZero’s integration plays a critical role in this launch, offering secure and seamless cross-chain functionality through its Omnichain Fungible Token (OFT) standard. This allows $TRUMP to move across supported blockchains without relying on traditional bridges or wrapped assets, reducing fragmentation and increasing accessibility. Stargate Finance, a liquidity network for cross-chain transfer for assets built on top of LayerZero protocol, supports $TRUMP bridging to and from TRON, further strengthening its liquidity and multichain utility.

By bringing $TRUMP into the TRON ecosystem, TRON DAO plans to explore DeFi and payment utility to the token as they continue to champion a vision of open, scalable blockchain infrastructure that supports emerging digital assets and unlocks new channels for community and financial participation. The commitment reinforces TRON DAO’s commitment to expanding its reach through innovative, user-centric initiatives that align with the decentralized ethos of the crypto space. With the addition of $TRUMP, TRON continues to prove itself as a dynamic technology for the next generation of token-based innovation.

About TRON DAO

TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.

Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON blockchain has experienced significant growth since its MainNet launch in May 2018. TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin, exceeding $80 billion. As of July 2025, the TRON blockchain has recorded over 321 million in total user accounts, more than 10 billion in total transactions, and over $25 billion in total value locked (TVL), based on TRONSCAN.

TRONNetwork | TRONDAO | X | YouTube | Telegram | Discord | Reddit | GitHub | Medium | Forum

Media Contact

Yeweon Park

[emailprotected]

This post is commissioned by TRON and does not serve as a testimonial or endorsement by The Block. This post is for informational purposes only and should not be relied upon as a basis for investment, tax, legal or other advice. You should conduct your own research and consult independent counsel and advisors on the matters discussed within this post. Past performance of any asset is not indicative of future results.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376149897318400</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoThe Block$TRUMP Goes Live On TRON NetworkJuly 24, 2025 - Geneva, Switzerland - TRON DAO, a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps, announced today the official deployment of $TRUMP on the TRON blockchain.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948376149897318400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum’s daily gas usage hits a record highOn July 24, according to everstake.eth, on July 21, 2025, Ethereum&apos;s daily Gas usage reached 149,673,860,000, setting a record high. Analysis pointed out that this milestone shows that the Ethereum ecosystem continues to prosper, with on-chain applications, users, and actual value growing continuously. The continued rise in Gas usage reflects real market demand and adoption. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375739375620096</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoPANewsEthereum’s daily gas usage hits a record highOn July 24, according to everstake.eth, on July 21, 2025, Ethereum&apos;s daily Gas usage reached 149,673,860,000, setting a record high. Analysis pointed out that this milestone shows that the Ethereum ecosystem continues to prosper, with</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375739375620096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine’s Ethereum holdings exceed $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETHOn July 24, according to PR Newswire, BitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE AMERICAN: BMNR) announced that its Ethereum (ETH) holdings have exceeded $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETH, far exceeding the $250 million in the first private placement completed on July 8. Thomas &quot;Tom&quot; Lee, chairman of the company&apos;s board of directors, said that BitMine is one step closer to achieving its goal of holding and staking 5% of the world&apos;s total ETH. CEO Jonathan Bates said that the company will continue to advance the Ethereum treasury strategy to help the development of the Ethereum ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375281416343552</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsBitMine’s Ethereum holdings exceed $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETHOn July 24, according to PR Newswire, BitMine Immersion Technologies (NYSE AMERICAN: BMNR) announced that its Ethereum (ETH) holdings have exceeded $2 billion, with a total of 566,776 ETH, far exceeding the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948375281416343552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USYC interest-bearing stablecoin will be issued natively on BNB ChainOn July 24, according to BNB Chain Chinese, Circle&apos;s interest-bearing stablecoin USYC (with U.S. Treasury bonds as the underlying asset) will soon be natively issued on BNB Chain. This move will significantly improve the capital efficiency of global users, achieve income acquisition, maintain liquidity, and increase transaction speed, and can be operated on the entire chain. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372368744845312</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoPANewsUSYC interest-bearing stablecoin will be issued natively on BNB ChainOn July 24, according to BNB Chain Chinese, Circle&apos;s interest-bearing stablecoin USYC (with U.S. Treasury bonds as the underlying asset) will soon be natively issued on BNB Chain. This move will significantly im</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372368744845312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMGE Technology Group: Accelerating the layout of IP RWA, WEB3 aggregated payment, and WEB3 e-sports game platformsCMGE announced that the company is accelerating a series of strategic initiatives, including accelerating the RWA (Real World Assets) on-chain plan for the &quot;The Legend of Sword and Fairy&quot; IP, launching a Web3 aggregated payment tool, and self-developing and self-operating a decentralized Web3 e-sports game platform. The company believes that breakthroughs in key areas such as RWA and stablecoins are strongly promoting Web3 to cross the conceptual gap and move towards large-scale commercial applications, demonstrating its great potential to reshape asset value and technological landscape. (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372861525233664</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoOdailyCMGE Technology Group: Accelerating the layout of IP RWA, WEB3 aggregated payment, and WEB3 e-sports game platformsCMGE announced that the company is accelerating a series of strategic initiatives, including accelerating the RWA (Real World Assets) on-chain plan for the &quot;The Lege</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372861525233664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sei Network has launched native USDC and CCTP V2According to the official announcement, native USDC and CCTP V2 are now live on the Sei Network. Circle Mint now fully supports native USDC on Sei. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372869976756224</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailySei Network has launched native USDC and CCTP V2According to the official announcement, native USDC and CCTP V2 are now live on the Sei Network. Circle Mint now fully supports native USDC on Sei. [Odaily Planet Daily News]#Crypto Stocks$USDC$SEI$CRCLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948372869976756224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement), supporting 1-20 times leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369608704069632</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoPANewsGate has launched ASP perpetual contract tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Gate has launched ASP perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement), supporting 1-20 times leverage. [PANews]$USDT$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369608704069632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK AI firm Satsuma Technology raises $135 million to build a Bitcoin vaultReported on July 24 that according to Cointelegraph, British artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology announced that it had successfully raised $135.00 million to build one of the largest Bitcoin vaults in the UK. The company said that all the promised funds are expected to arrive in the next two weeks. This financing is expected to make Satsuma the second largest corporate Bitcoin holder in the UK, second only to The Smarter Web Company. At the same time, this may also become the largest single Bitcoin purchase record for a British company. Satsuma completed this financing through convertible bonds, aiming to accelerate business growth and promote the deep integration of Bitcoin and artificial intelligence. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369519503806464</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoPANewsUK AI firm Satsuma Technology raises $135 million to build a Bitcoin vaultReported on July 24 that according to Cointelegraph, British artificial intelligence company Satsuma Technology announced that it had successfully raised $135.00 million to build one of the largest Bitcoin</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948369519503806464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks.live: The English-speaking community is showing clear bearish sentiment, with key discussions revolving around the 30% volatility level.On July 24th, Greeks.live macro researcher Adam released a brief report to the English community stating that the group showed a clear bearish sentiment, with traders holding put option positions despite significant losses. Most traders are focused on potential declines, with key discussions revolving around a 30% volatility level. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367969196773376</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoTechFlowGreeks.live: The English-speaking community is showing clear bearish sentiment, with key discussions revolving around the 30% volatility level.On July 24th, Greeks.live macro researcher Adam released a brief report to the English community stating that the group showed a clear</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367969196773376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Wallet and BASCAN.io jointly launch an exclusive booster pack event, Alpha points 61 and above can be claimedOn July 24, Binance Wallet announced that the exclusive booster pack event in cooperation with BASCAN.io is now live. Users can participate in the second week of the event to share 44.00 million BAS rewards. Binance users with 61 or more Binance Alpha points can participate. Please note that the event reward tokens will be subject to the lock-up period set by the project party. Please understand the relevant regulations in detail before participating. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367155514380288</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoPANewsBinance Wallet and BASCAN.io jointly launch an exclusive booster pack event, Alpha points 61 and above can be claimedOn July 24, Binance Wallet announced that the exclusive booster pack event in cooperation with BASCAN.io is now live. Users can participate in the second week of t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367155514380288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Blockchain Capital Forms New Entity SpiritReserve Group and Plans to Raise Up to $500.00MCanadian digital asset management and investment public company Spirit Blockchain Capital announced the launch of the Spirit Blockchain 2.0 strategy, which plans to integrate a multi-token portfolio into its yield strategy, and expects to expand its yield program to three cryptocurrencies, BTC, ETH and SOL, in the fourth quarter of this year. In addition, Spirit Blockchain Capital also announced the formal establishment of a new entity, SpiritReserve Group, and the phased raising of up to $500.00M in funds, aimed at creating shareholder value through strategic investments in the digital asset space. (Globe Newswire)</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367846236557312</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoOdailySpirit Blockchain Capital Forms New Entity SpiritReserve Group and Plans to Raise Up to $500.00MCanadian digital asset management and investment public company Spirit Blockchain Capital announced the launch of the Spirit Blockchain 2.0 strategy, which plans to integrate a multi-t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948367846236557312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: XRP is now at $3.1505According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 6.65% in the past 24h. Now at $3.1505.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366601563627520</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: XRP is now at $3.1505According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 6.65% in the past 24h. Now at $3.1505.$XRPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366601563627520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Foundation Q2 Grants Totaled Approximately $8.374MThe Ethereum Foundation has released its grant data for Q2 2025, with total funding of approximately $8.374 million. The funded project categories include Community and Education, Consensus Layer, Cryptography and Zero-Knowledge Proofs, Developer Experience and Tools, Execution Layer, Overall Growth and Support, Layer 2, etc. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366129713451008</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoForesightNewsEthereum Foundation Q2 Grants Totaled Approximately $8.374MThe Ethereum Foundation has released its grant data for Q2 2025, with total funding of approximately $8.374 million. The funded project categories include Community and Education, Consensus Layer, Cryptography and</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948366129713451008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAgentAI ecosystem product CorrAI and Blave reach strategic cooperation to promote the democratization of quantitative tradingOn July 24, CorrAI, the core product of the DeAgentAI ecosystem, announced a strategic partnership with the institutional-level data platform Blave. The two parties will integrate institutional-level derivatives data and code-free quantitative strategy building capabilities to provide users with a one-stop solution from data insights to executable trading strategies. The position concentration analysis, advanced filters and real-time warning functions provided by the Blave platform will be directly imported into CorrAI&apos;s visual strategy builder. With the guidance of the AI assistant Corr-GPT, users can quickly create strategies using key data such as whale behavior, long and short positions, and optimize them through indicators such as Sharpe ratio and maximum drawdown. The whole process does not require programming knowledge. The cooperation will also bring cross-platform benefits to users of both platforms: Blave users can access CorrAI&apos;s backtesting function through API, and CorrAI subscribers can unlock Blave&apos;s enhanced data layer. CorrAI is a quantitative trading product in the DeAgentAI ecosystem that focuses on de-FAI. It provides users with verifiable on-chain insights and intelligent strategy development capabilities through DeAgentAI&apos;s advanced multi-agent infrastructure. The product is committed to making quantitative trading more accessible to both novices and professional users, and helps users avoid common pitfalls such as overfitting through an integrated large language model. DeAgentAI is an AI Agent network infrastructure project built on multiple chain ecosystems such as Sui, BSC and BTC, with the core vision of &quot;Make AI Smarter&quot;. It is committed to empowering on-chain transactions through AI prediction and feedback mechanisms, and has currently supported more than 190 million on-chain interactions, providing a smarter and more reliable AI-driven solution for the Web3 ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364632405643264</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoPANewsDeAgentAI ecosystem product CorrAI and Blave reach strategic cooperation to promote the democratization of quantitative tradingOn July 24, CorrAI, the core product of the DeAgentAI ecosystem, announced a strategic partnership with the institutional-level data platform Blave. The</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364632405643264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Innovation Council Appoints Ji Hun Kim as CEO, Adds SoFi as MemberOn July 24, the Cryptocurrency Innovation Council (CCI) announced today that the board of directors has appointed Ji Hun Kim as its chief executive officer (CEO). Kim has served as president and acting CEO of CCI since January 2025. He previously served as the organization&apos;s chief legal and policy officer. At the same time, SoFi, as an innovative company in the field of fintech and banking, officially joined the Crypto Innovation Council. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364466982293504</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoPANewsCrypto Innovation Council Appoints Ji Hun Kim as CEO, Adds SoFi as MemberOn July 24, the Cryptocurrency Innovation Council (CCI) announced today that the board of directors has appointed Ji Hun Kim as its chief executive officer (CEO). Kim has served as president and acting CEO o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364466982293504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoins Surpass SOL in Adoption as Crypto Shifts Toward UtilityThe number of wallets holding stablecoins has officially surpassed the number of wallets holding Solana’s SOL token. The rise of stablecoins is not just a matter of statistics—it is a sign that crypto is gradually “maturing.” Why Stablecoins Are Winning as Crypto Matures After years of being viewed as speculative tools or “toys for tech enthusiasts,” the crypto market is undergoing a structural shift. The latest data shows that the number of wallets holding stablecoins has officially exceeded those holding Solana’s SOL token. Specifically, stablecoin now accounts for 38% of all wallets, while SOL represents only 37%. This appears to signal a shift in investor priorities, from holding highly volatile digital assets to using more stable digital assets. In other words, crypto is entering a phase of practical application. Stablecoin has become an essential part of the Web3 ecosystem. Unlike other narratives, stablecoins don’t rely on market cycles. They prove to be a real product-market fit and are easy to use for mainstream users. They enhance cross-border payments, e-commerce, and DeFi and dominate value storage in the expanding digital economy. A key factor fueling the rapid growth of stablecoins is the shifting regulatory environment, particularly in the US. The Genius Act has triggered a new wave of stablecoin issuance from banks, asset funds, and even major tech firms. Chainlink stated that a new “stablecoin issuance boom” is being launched, driven by regulatory momentum and growing interest from traditional finance. However, not everyone is fully optimistic. JPMorgan recently argued that the forecast of a $2 trillion stablecoin market by 2028 is “overly optimistic”, with a more realistic figure closer to $500 billion. However, a survey of 295 global institutions shows 49% use stablecoins for payments, with 41% in testing or planning phases. Although more Layer-1 platforms like Solana, Tron, and BNB Chain are joining the stablecoin race, Ethereum remains the dominant “home” in terms of both volume and transaction value. Still, high gas fees and limited scalability remain major barriers. This opens the door for high-performance blockchains to gain market share ahead.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948373451403759616</link>
      <description>59 minutes agobeincryptoStablecoins Surpass SOL in Adoption as Crypto Shifts Toward UtilityThe number of wallets holding stablecoins has officially surpassed the number of wallets holding Solana’s SOL token. The rise of stablecoins is not just a matter of statistics—it is a sign that crypto is gradu</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948373451403759616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>