<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:55:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Soneium Head Meme PCAT Officially Launched on BNB ChainOn-chain data shows that Soneium&apos;s first Meme token, PACT, has been officially deployed to BNB Chain. The PACT token donation event ended yesterday, raising over $3.50M with over 26,000 on-chain addresses. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947278164862717952</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoOdailySoneium Head Meme PCAT Officially Launched on BNB ChainOn-chain data shows that Soneium&apos;s first Meme token, PACT, has been officially deployed to BNB Chain. The PACT token donation event ended yesterday, raising over $3.50M with over 26,000 on-chain addresses. [Odaily Planet Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947278164862717952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cumberland deposited 31,000 ETH, worth approximately $118.00M, to Coinbase PrimeAccording to The Data Nerd, Cumberland deposited 31,000 ETH, worth approximately $118.00 million, to Coinbase Prime 15 minutes ago. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947277955185266688</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsCumberland deposited 31,000 ETH, worth approximately $118.00M, to Coinbase PrimeAccording to The Data Nerd, Cumberland deposited 31,000 ETH, worth approximately $118.00 million, to Coinbase Prime 15 minutes ago. [Foresight News]#Crypto Stocks$ETH$MAG7.SSI$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947277955185266688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COINS Act model law offers blueprint for crypto regulation in IndiaHashed Emergent’s Vishal Achanta told Cointelegraph that COINS Act aims to turn India from a “regulatory minefield” to a destination of choice for the crypto community.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276110362595328</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoPANewsCOINS Act model law offers blueprint for crypto regulation in IndiaHashed Emergent’s Vishal Achanta told Cointelegraph that COINS Act aims to turn India from a “regulatory minefield” to a destination of choice for the crypto community.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276110362595328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yapper Leaderboard to Introduce Reputation Threshold MechanismKaito AI founder Yu Hu announced that the Yapper Leaderboard will launch a reputation threshold mechanism to reduce leaderboard manipulation and improve content quality. The mechanism draws on creator thresholds from platforms such as X, TikTok, and YouTube, and will be launched in the coming weeks. At the same time, Kaito will also introduce the community incentive mechanism gKAITO, allowing users with different levels of contribution to participate in platform revenue distribution. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677495410688</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoForesightNewsYapper Leaderboard to Introduce Reputation Threshold MechanismKaito AI founder Yu Hu announced that the Yapper Leaderboard will launch a reputation threshold mechanism to reduce leaderboard manipulation and improve content quality. The mechanism draws on creator thresholds</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677495410688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orders to buy BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX can enjoy 4x trading volume counted towards Alpha pointsBinance has announced that starting from 08:00 on July 22, 2025, orders to purchase BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX will enjoy 4x trading volume counted towards Binance Alpha points. The end date of the promotion will be announced separately. Previously, Binance announced that purchasing BSC Alpha tokens or using the Alpha 2.0 limit order function to purchase other Alpha tokens would earn 2x trading volume Alpha points. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947275961783570432</link>
      <description>13 minutes ago吴说Orders to buy BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX can enjoy 4x trading volume counted towards Alpha pointsBinance has announced that starting from 08:00 on July 22, 2025, orders to purchase BSC chain Alpha tokens with limit orders on Binance Alpha CEX will e</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947275961783570432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bit Origin Acquires Over 40.00 Million Dogecoins (DOGE), Advancing Financial StrategyNasdaq-listed mining company Bit Origin announces its first purchase of approximately 40.50 million Dogecoins (DOGE). This is the company&apos;s first strategic acquisition under its digital asset treasury program, following a previously announced capital commitment of up to $500.00 million. As of July 21, 2025, the company holds 40,543,745 DOGE at an average price of $0.2466. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677646405632</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoForesightNewsBit Origin Acquires Over 40.00 Million Dogecoins (DOGE), Advancing Financial StrategyNasdaq-listed mining company Bit Origin announces its first purchase of approximately 40.50 million Dogecoins (DOGE). This is the company&apos;s first strategic acquisition under its digital as</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677646405632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Announces Bitcoin Holdings Reach $2.00BTrump Media announced that its Bitcoin assets have reached approximately $2.00B, accounting for two-thirds of the company&apos;s approximately $3.00B in liquid assets. The strategy is supported by $3.00B in liquid funds, with an additional $300.00M used for Bitcoin-related options operations, which may be converted into spot Bitcoin in the future. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677700931584</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoForesightNewsTrump Media &amp; Technology Group Announces Bitcoin Holdings Reach $2.00BTrump Media announced that its Bitcoin assets have reached approximately $2.00B, accounting for two-thirds of the company&apos;s approximately $3.00B in liquid assets. The strategy is supported by $3.00B in l</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947276677700931584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks Profusa signs $100.00M equity credit agreement, launches Bitcoin treasury strategyCommercial-stage digital health company Profusa (Nasdaq: PFSA) announced today that it has entered into a securities purchase agreement (equity credit agreement) with Ascent Partners Fund LLC (&quot;Ascent&quot;) to raise up to $100 million through the issuance of common stock, and will use the net proceeds in full to purchase Bitcoin (which can be used for debt repayment), provided that the company&apos;s cash balance at the time of the equity sale is higher than $5.00 million. Under the terms of the agreement, Profusa has the right to sell common stock to Ascent at a price per share equal to 97% of the lowest volume-weighted average price (VWAP) within 5 trading days after each sale. The upper limit for a single sale is $5.00 million or 100% of the average daily trading volume for the 5 trading days prior to the sale date (whichever is lower). If the company&apos;s cash balance is less than $5.00 million, the net proceeds will be used to first replenish that amount, and the remaining funds will be used to allocate Bitcoin as a core reserve asset. (Business Insider) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947273130993274880</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoOdailyUS stocks Profusa signs $100.00M equity credit agreement, launches Bitcoin treasury strategyCommercial-stage digital health company Profusa (Nasdaq: PFSA) announced today that it has entered into a securities purchase agreement (equity credit agreement) with Ascent Partners Fund</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947273130993274880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercurity Fintech Holding Signs $200.00M Equity Credit Line Agreement with Solana VenturesMercurity Fintech Holding (Nasdaq: MFH) has announced a $200.00M equity credit line agreement with Solana Ventures to launch its Solana-based digital asset treasury strategy. MFH stated that it will become a long-term institutional participant in the Solana ecosystem by accumulating SOL assets, running validation nodes, participating in DeFi protocols, and investing in Solana projects. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947271109544267776</link>
      <description>32 minutes ago吴说Mercurity Fintech Holding Signs $200.00M Equity Credit Line Agreement with Solana VenturesMercurity Fintech Holding (Nasdaq: MFH) has announced a $200.00M equity credit line agreement with Solana Ventures to launch its Solana-based digital asset treasury strategy. MFH stated that it</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947271109544267776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created address today accumulated withdrawals of 8357 ETH from Binance, equivalent to approximately $31.84M.According to on-chain data analyst Ember, a newly created address has been continuously withdrawing ETH from Binance today, and has so far withdrawn a total of 8,357 ETH (approximately $31.84 million), at an average price of $3,810. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947273139432214528</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoOdailyA newly created address today accumulated withdrawals of 8357 ETH from Binance, equivalent to approximately $31.84M.According to on-chain data analyst Ember, a newly created address has been continuously withdrawing ETH from Binance today, and has so far withdrawn a total of 8,35</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947273139432214528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gong Green Hydrogen: Promoting the &quot;New Energy +RWA&quot; strategy, planning to connect 100,000 devices to the RWA system in the next 5 years.According to the Securities Times, a reporter learned from Xingong Green Hydrogen, a subsidiary of Sichuan Jin Ding, that Xingong Green Hydrogen is exploring the transformation of its three core products into divisible and tradable RWA targets through dynamic asset on-chain technology. These products include mobile energy storage and charging robots, skid-mounted hydrogen production and refueling integrated stations, and hydrogen power plants. Taking Tianqing No. 1 TGHD01 as an example, the on-chain confirmation of power generation allows for the automatic settlement of electricity revenue into stablecoins, achieving the real-time conversion of &quot;green electricity into revenue.&quot; It is reported that Xingong Green Hydrogen is promoting three strategic upgrades: In the next 5 years, it plans to connect 100,000 sets of equipment to the RWA system, with an estimated securitizable asset scale of several billion yuan; jointly build a &quot;Hydrogen Energy Industry RWA Alliance&quot; with companies such as Bosch Hydrogen Power, Junrui Green Hydrogen, Sinopec, and China Power Construction to open up cross-border hydrogen energy carbon sink trading channels; and launch the &quot;Green Hydrogen Revenue Pass&quot; standardized contract in conjunction with partners, and apply to the local financial regulatory bureau for the first batch of pilots. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947271854511378432</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoForesightNewsNew Gong Green Hydrogen: Promoting the &quot;New Energy +RWA&quot; strategy, planning to connect 100,000 devices to the RWA system in the next 5 years.According to the Securities Times, a reporter learned from Xingong Green Hydrogen, a subsidiary of Sichuan Jin Ding, that Xingong Gr</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947271854511378432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese blockchain Conflux to launch offshore yuan-backed stablecoinChinese blockchain Conflux has launched Conflux 3.0 and unveiled a new offshore yuan-backed stablecoin targeting “Belt and Road” cross-border payments.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947266688278089728</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoPANewsChinese blockchain Conflux to launch offshore yuan-backed stablecoinChinese blockchain Conflux has launched Conflux 3.0 and unveiled a new offshore yuan-backed stablecoin targeting “Belt and Road” cross-border payments.#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947266688278089728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Bessent: The quality of signing a trade agreement is more important than the timing of signing itU.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent stated that trade negotiations are currently underway, and he is more concerned with reaching a high-quality agreement than completing an agreement before August 1. Bessent said that they are not in a hurry, but he can imagine that the EU would like to negotiate faster, but at least the EU is now more engaged. His top priority is to secure the best deal for the United States (on the Japan issue). Some analysts say that Bessent&apos;s remarks indicate that &quot;delaying tactics&quot; are likely to occur again by August 1, so people can wait and see. At the same time, Bessent said on the issue of Powell, &quot;Ultimately, this is Trump&apos;s decision on Powell.&quot; He then added that they need to examine the Federal Reserve as a whole institution. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947265596148436992</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoOdailyUS Treasury Secretary Bessent: The quality of signing a trade agreement is more important than the timing of signing itU.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent stated that trade negotiations are currently underway, and he is more concerned with reaching a high-quality agreement than</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947265596148436992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Hack’s Latest Winners Announced: Basement, DeFi Copilot, BIBIMOn July 21, BNB Chain announced the results of the latest batch of BNB Hack (6/23–7/17). The social protocol Basement (DeSoc direction), AI-driven DeFi assistant DeFi Copilot, and strategy tool BIBIM (AI direction) successfully won awards, all of which can receive $3,000.00 USDT bonus, $50,000.00 Kickstart reward package, and official Demo Day display opportunities. At the same time, Peridot and Agent Einstein in the AI direction entered the incubation observation list.
 This round received 30+ submissions from developers around the world, including from the offline event in New York:
 Basement: Provides an instant social layer for web pages, combined with AI Agents to achieve one-click chat, interaction, rewards and information aggregation
 DeFi Copilot: A one-stop PancakeSwap trading assistant that integrates real-time analysis, one-click ordering, and automatic management
 BIBIM: Using visual interfaces and AI to simplify strategy building, testing, and monetization, reducing the complexity of DeFi
 BNB Hack is a long-term hackathon launched by BNB Chain for Web3 innovation directions such as AI, DeSoc, DeSci, and DePIN. It has received more than 200 global submissions and has selected 9 Tier 3 projects and 40 potential projects. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947264309780566016</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoPANewsBNB Hack’s Latest Winners Announced: Basement, DeFi Copilot, BIBIMOn July 21, BNB Chain announced the results of the latest batch of BNB Hack (6/23–7/17). The social protocol Basement (DeSoc direction), AI-driven DeFi assistant DeFi Copilot, and strategy tool BIBIM (AI direction)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947264309780566016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTCS Discloses Company ETH and Cash Market Value of $242.00 millionBlockchain technology company BTCS Inc. (Nasdaq: BTCS) announced that, as of now, its holdings of 55,788 Ethereum (ETH), cash, and other liquid assets have a total market value of approximately $242.00 million (calculated at an ETH price of $3,600.00). In addition, BTCS has agreed to issue approximately $10.00 million in convertible notes at a price of $13.00 per share, a 198.00% premium to the closing price on July 18. The company has accumulated $189.00 million in financing this year through its DeFi/TradFi Accretion Flywheel strategy and plans to continue expanding its ETH holdings and increasing shareholder value through decentralized and traditional financial instruments. (GlobeNewswire) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947265604591570944</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoOdailyBTCS Discloses Company ETH and Cash Market Value of $242.00 millionBlockchain technology company BTCS Inc. (Nasdaq: BTCS) announced that, as of now, its holdings of 55,788 Ethereum (ETH), cash, and other liquid assets have a total market value of approximately $242.00 million (ca</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947265604591570944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selini Capital withdrew 8.273M USDC from HyperliquidAccording to Arkham monitoring, Selini Capital: 0xfF…463C withdrew 8.273 million USDC from Hyperliquid at 17:49. HypurrScan data shows that Selini Capital has cumulatively earned $9.62 million in profits trading on Hyperliquid, including $2.305 million in contract profits. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263462241751040</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsSelini Capital withdrew 8.273M USDC from HyperliquidAccording to Arkham monitoring, Selini Capital: 0xfF…463C withdrew 8.273 million USDC from Hyperliquid at 17:49. HypurrScan data shows that Selini Capital has cumulatively earned $9.62 million in profits trading on Hyperliqui</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263462241751040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Fresh Capital Fueling XRP’s Next Move? 3 Key Signs From JulyAlongside XRP’s strong price rally in July, its ecosystem also set several noteworthy records. These records may signal a turning point for XRP. They also reinforce the altcoin’s fundamental growth drivers. What are those factors? This article breaks them down in detail. XRP Ecosystem Sets New Records in July The first and most obvious sign of XRP’s growth is the number of new accounts activated on XRPL. According to data from XRPScan, the number of new accounts surpassed 10,000 on July 18, marking the highest daily total since February. Although this number hasn’t broken the all-time daily record—over 30,000 in December 2024—it has steadily increased throughout July. This trend shows that XRP is attracting new investors. Many of them may become long-term holders. In addition, the number of daily active wallet addresses surpassed 50,500. That’s a 100% increase from the previous month and the highest since February. Another notable record is the total value locked (TVL) on XRPL. It recently hit an all-time high (ATH), exceeding $92.00 million. Most of this growth came from XRPL’s decentralized exchange (DEX). This number remains modest compared to TVLs on other blockchains. However, it marks the first breakout after nearly a year of stagnation. Moreover, Ripple’s official XRPL EVM Sidechain Mainnet launch in early July created new opportunities to lock value in liquidity pools. This directly helped boost the DEX’s TVL. XRP Dominance Rises Above 5% Lastly, the XRP Dominance (XRP.D) index has climbed above 5%. It is now near its 2025 high and may rise even further. This index reflects how much investors prioritize XRP relative to the total crypto market cap. Some investors expect XRP.D to reach 15%. in 2025. Others hope it could climb to 30%, as it did in 2017. All these indicators point to one thing: new capital is flowing into XRP. With a market cap of over $211.00 billion, XRP now ranks #78 globally by market capitalization, surpassing Shell, Blackstone, and Siemens. However, recent analysis from BeInCrypto warns that XRP futures have reached an all-time high . At the same time, signs of short-term profit-taking have emerged. These could pose short-term liquidation risks for over-leveraged positions.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947268670413885440</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoIs Fresh Capital Fueling XRP’s Next Move? 3 Key Signs From JulyAlongside XRP’s strong price rally in July, its ecosystem also set several noteworthy records. These records may signal a turning point for XRP. They also reinforce the altcoin’s fundamental growth drivers. What are t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947268670413885440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Bessent: If inflation data is low, interest rates should be loweredU.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent says that if inflation data is low, interest rates should be lowered. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947265621511393280</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTreasury Secretary Bessent: If inflation data is low, interest rates should be loweredU.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent says that if inflation data is low, interest rates should be lowered. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947265621511393280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale that has held BTC for 12 years transferred 250 BTC to Binance today and still holds 4,000 BTC.According to @EmberCN monitoring, a BTC whale holding for 12 years transferred 250 BTC (approximately $29.68M) to Binance today. This address first accumulated 5,000 BTC in November 2013 at a price of $332 per coin, and began selling them successively in November 2024. To date, 1,000 coins have been sold at an average price of $102,410. It currently still holds 4,000 BTC, worth approximately $474.00M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263325696184320</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说A whale that has held BTC for 12 years transferred 250 BTC to Binance today and still holds 4,000 BTC.According to @EmberCN monitoring, a BTC whale holding for 12 years transferred 250 BTC (approximately $29.68M) to Binance today. This address first accumulated 5,000 BTC in November 2013</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947263325696184320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: 66% of USDt on-chain transfers come from West Asia, the Middle East and AfricaOn July 21, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino tweeted that USDt is growing rapidly around the world, especially in emerging markets. In the first half of 2025, USDt on-chain transfers increased by 120% compared to the full year of 2024, of which 66% of the transfers came from West Asia, the Middle East and Africa. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947260928064245760</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsTether CEO: 66% of USDt on-chain transfers come from West Asia, the Middle East and AfricaOn July 21, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino tweeted that USDt is growing rapidly around the world, especially in emerging markets. In the first half of 2025, USDt on-chain transfers increased by 120% c</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947260928064245760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>