<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:18:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sequans buys 1,264 more bitcoins for $150 millionOn July 21, according to Bitcoin Magazine, French listed company Sequans purchased 1,264 bitcoins for US$150.00 million, and its total bitcoin holdings have now reached 2,317. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947238311387222016</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoPANewsSequans buys 1,264 more bitcoins for $150 millionOn July 21, according to Bitcoin Magazine, French listed company Sequans purchased 1,264 bitcoins for US$150.00 million, and its total bitcoin holdings have now reached 2,317. [PANews]#Bitcoin$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947238311387222016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merlin Chain Releases Merlin 2.0 - &quot;Hold, Earn, Invest&quot; Reshaping BTCMerlin Chain has announced its new Merlin 2.0, proposing a development direction of &quot;Reinvent Bitcoin: Hold, Earn, Invest,&quot; aiming to expand Bitcoin from a &quot;store of value&quot; to a &quot;yield-generating, deployable core asset.&quot; Merlin 2.0 focuses on three major areas: BTCFi expansion, chain abstraction technology, and AI applications (such as Merlin Wizard), further enhancing the liquidity and utility of BTC in multi-chain ecosystems. It also lowers the barrier to entry for BTC, allowing users to participate in various investment opportunities across chains without having to exchange other assets, conveniently realizing BTC holding, yield acquisition, and liquidity participation. According to previous reports, since the mainnet launch in February 2024, Merlin Chain has promoted the rise of BTCFi, giving rise to several representative projects including Solv, Bedrock, Avalon, and Babylon, with over $3.80B in BTC cumulatively staked on the chain. Currently, the Merlin-related ecosystem contributes approximately $2.00B in BTCFi TVL, accounting for over 20.00%. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237887540219904</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoOdailyMerlin Chain Releases Merlin 2.0 - &quot;Hold, Earn, Invest&quot; Reshaping BTCMerlin Chain has announced its new Merlin 2.0, proposing a development direction of &quot;Reinvent Bitcoin: Hold, Earn, Invest,&quot; aiming to expand Bitcoin from a &quot;store of value&quot; to a &quot;yield-generating, deployable cor</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237887540219904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Central Bank of Morocco Completes Draft Law on Crypto AssetsAccording to Zhitong Finance, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law that would legalize the use of crypto assets. The law ensures &quot;adequate protection for consumers and investors, strengthens market integrity, combats fraud, manipulation, money laundering and terrorist financing, and maintains financial stability.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236660978929664</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoForesightNewsThe Central Bank of Morocco Completes Draft Law on Crypto AssetsAccording to Zhitong Finance, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law that would legalize the use of crypto ass</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236660978929664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX will delist 3 perpetual contracts including BADGER on July 25.According to the official announcement, OKX will delist BADGERUSDT, BALUSDT, and NILUSDT perpetual contracts on July 25, 2025, at 4:00 PM (UTC+8). Trading will be suspended and all pending orders will be canceled at the time of delisting, and delivery will be made based on the average index price one hour before the delisting. (This news flash is generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237895979159552</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyOKX will delist 3 perpetual contracts including BADGER on July 25.According to the official announcement, OKX will delist BADGERUSDT, BALUSDT, and NILUSDT perpetual contracts on July 25, 2025, at 4:00 PM (UTC+8). Trading will be suspended and all pending orders will be canceled a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237895979159552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn closed positions in various assets, making a profit of approximately $178,000.00 in 6 daysAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, James Wynn has closed his 10x long positions in DOGE and PEPE, as well as his 40x short position in BTC, with a loss of $625,222.00. In the past 6 days, James deposited 1.25M USDC into HyperLiquid and made a profit of $177,675.00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236412231536640</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoForesightNewsJames Wynn closed positions in various assets, making a profit of approximately $178,000.00 in 6 daysAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, James Wynn has closed his 10x long positions in DOGE and PEPE, as well as his 40x short position in BTC, with a loss of $625,222.00. I</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236412231536640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain compliance tools can slash TradFi costs — Chainlink co-founderInstitutional investors will increasingly adopt blockchain-based compliance solutions and tokenized RWAs, Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov told Cointelegraph. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234608521433088</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoPANewsBlockchain compliance tools can slash TradFi costs — Chainlink co-founderInstitutional investors will increasingly adopt blockchain-based compliance solutions and tokenized RWAs, Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov told Cointelegraph. [Cointelegraph]#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234608521433088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory releases ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutionOn July 21, according to Xinhua Finance, Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory released DeepLink ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutions, which supports cross-domain long-term stable mixed training of large models with hundreds of billions of parameters in multiple intelligent computing centers over a thousand kilometers, such as connecting the intelligent computing centers between Shanghai and Jinan over 1,500 kilometers, and realizing the interconnection and large-model mixed training of intelligent computing centers in Beijing, Shanghai, Guizhou and other places. At present, the DeepLink open computing system of Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory has been deeply integrated into intelligent computing platforms such as China Unicom, China Telecom, SenseTime, and Yidian, achieving stable operation of &quot;1 platform + N chips + X regions&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234435628027904</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoPANewsShanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory releases ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutionOn July 21, according to Xinhua Finance, Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory released DeepLink ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology so</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234435628027904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum NFT marketplace weekly trading volume reaches $84.03M, highest since mid-to-late February this year.According to @hildobby&apos;s data panel, in the past week (July 14 to 20), the weekly trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market reached $84,029,000.00, the highest point since mid-to-late February this year. Among them, OpenSea reached $40,143,000.00, and Blur reached $25,552,000.00. In addition, on July 21, with the support of CryptoPunks whales&apos; purchases, the daily trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market has exceeded $25,900,000.00, the highest point since February 18 this year. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947232369966862336</link>
      <description>30 minutes ago吴说Ethereum NFT marketplace weekly trading volume reaches $84.03M, highest since mid-to-late February this year.According to @hildobby&apos;s data panel, in the past week (July 14 to 20), the weekly trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market reached $84,029,000.00, the highest point since mid</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947232369966862336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC explores Ethereum token standard for compliant securitiesERC-3643 Association president Dennis O’Connell told Cointelegraph the SEC showed “a noticeable shift in tone” and openness to blockchain standards.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230186244427776</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoPANewsSEC explores Ethereum token standard for compliant securitiesERC-3643 Association president Dennis O’Connell told Cointelegraph the SEC showed “a noticeable shift in tone” and openness to blockchain standards.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230186244427776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Exchange Lists ESPORTS, GP, ERA and Other Perpetual ContractsOn July 21st, WEEX Exchange announced that it has launched Yooldo (ESPORTS), Graphite Protocol (GP), Caldera (ERA), Taker (TAKER), Pump.fun (PUMP), and Eclipse (ES) perpetual contracts. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229440153243648</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoTechFlowWEEX Exchange Lists ESPORTS, GP, ERA and Other Perpetual ContractsOn July 21st, WEEX Exchange announced that it has launched Yooldo (ESPORTS), Graphite Protocol (GP), Caldera (ERA), Taker (TAKER), Pump.fun (PUMP), and Eclipse (ES) perpetual contracts. [TechFlow]$ERA$ES$PUMPShar</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229440153243648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two institutional addresses sold 25.5 billion PUMPs in one week and made a profit of nearly $40 million USD.On July 21, according to Ember, two addresses that participated in the institutional private placement of pump.fun recently made a total profit of $39.65 million in one week by selling 25.5 billion PUMP (about $141 million). Among them, the D6ar…Lazd address participated in the private placement with $100 million USDC and obtained 25 billion PUMP. In the past week, 13 billion PUMP (about $71.46 million) was transferred to FalconX and flowed to multiple exchanges, making a profit of $19.50 million; the 58WQ…v33E address obtained 12.5 billion PUMP with $50 million USDC, which has been transferred to the exchange, making a profit of $20.15 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229455345012736</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoPANewsTwo institutional addresses sold 25.5 billion PUMPs in one week and made a profit of nearly $40 million USD.On July 21, according to Ember, two addresses that participated in the institutional private placement of pump.fun recently made a total profit of $39.65 million in one wee</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947229455345012736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QCP Capital: Ethereum&apos;s performance drives the start of altcoin season, with institutions leading this round of gainsIn its market weekly report released on July 21, QCP Capital stated that multiple altcoin season indicators have exceeded 50, reaching their highest level since December of last year. Coupled with the open interest in ETH perpetual contracts jumping from $18.00B to $28.00B in a week, this marks the potential official start of altcoin season. QCP pointed out that the dominant force in this round of the cycle is institutional investors. Benefiting from the clarity in stablecoin regulatory frameworks brought about by the GENIUS Act, corporate finance departments have begun to increase their holdings of L1 public chain tokens such as ETH, SOL, XRP, and ADA, similar to the role of BTC in the fiscal allocations of Strategy and Metaplanet. If ETH obtains SEC approval for its staking spot ETF in the coming months, it may attract funds to shift from BTC ETFs to ETH, further unlocking yield potential. In fact, the daily net inflow of ETH spot ETFs last week has exceeded that of BTC for two consecutive days, showing a surge in institutional interest in ETH, and BlackRock is also confident in its staking ETH ETF. In addition, bullish call spread trading is active in the ETH options market, with large volumes of call spread positions being established for September and December expirations, highlighting the market&apos;s optimism for the fourth quarter. The current BTC market dominance has fallen from 64% to 60%, while ETH&apos;s market share has risen from 9.7% to 11.6%. If the trend continues, a new round of altcoin season may have begun. QCP stated that it will continue to monitor relevant signals and update developments as soon as possible. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230335943331840</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyQCP Capital: Ethereum&apos;s performance drives the start of altcoin season, with institutions leading this round of gainsIn its market weekly report released on July 21, QCP Capital stated that multiple altcoin season indicators have exceeded 50, reaching their highest level since De</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947230335943331840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamix to merge with cryptocurrency firm to form Ether MachineOn July 21, according to the Wall Street Journal, blank check company Dynamix is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company, Ether Machine. Sources said the merged company plans to hold more than $1.5 billion in Ethereum. Ether Machine co-founder Andrew Keys will serve as chairman. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947228416285888512</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoPANewsDynamix to merge with cryptocurrency firm to form Ether MachineOn July 21, according to the Wall Street Journal, blank check company Dynamix is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company, Ether Machine. Sources said the merged company plans to hold more than $1.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947228416285888512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigONE launches $8.1 million hacker bounty programOn July 21, according to BigONE’s announcement, in response to the recent theft of encrypted assets, BigONE has officially launched a hacker bounty program with a total amount of US$8.10M, calling on white hat hackers around the world to help track down the stolen funds and identify the attackers. BigONE said that it welcomes security experts to participate in promoting the recovery of stolen assets and the detection of cases. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223567464943616</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBigONE launches $8.1 million hacker bounty programOn July 21, according to BigONE’s announcement, in response to the recent theft of encrypted assets, BigONE has officially launched a hacker bounty program with a total amount of US$8.10M, calling on white hat hackers around the world</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223567464943616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto investment products see record $4.4 billion in weekly inflows, pushing year-to-date total to $27B: CoinSharesGlobal crypto investment products attracted a record $4.39 billion of inflows last week, their strongest tally since CoinShares began tracking the data in 2014, and more than the previous $4.27 billion peak logged last December after the U.S. general election, the firm&apos;s head of research, James Butterfill, wrote on Monday.

The surge — the 14th consecutive week of net buying — lifted year‑to‑date inflows to $27 billion and pushed assets under management to a new all‑time high of $220 billion. Trading activity in exchange‑traded products also hit a peak, with turnover jumping to $39.2 billion.

Market leader Bitcoin was a primary driver of last week’s flows, but Ethereum was the star and notched a 13th consecutive week of capital allocations, according to Butterfill. Funds linked to the world’s second‑largest cryptocurrency pulled in $2.12 billion, nearly double their prior weekly record of $1.2 billion and taking 2025 inflows to $6.2 billion, already eclipsing last year’s total. Bitcoin products gathered $2.2 billion, down from $2.7 billion the previous week, but still sizable enough to keep overall flows at historic levels.

The United States unsurprisingly dominated geographically with $4.36 billion of inflows to funds offered by firms like BlackRock, Grayscale, and Bitwise, while Switzerland, Hong Kong, and Australia contributed a combined $78.7 million. Brazil and Germany logged modest outflows of $28.1 million and $15.5 million, respectively.

Among other altcoins, Solana, XRP, and Sui products attracted $39 million, $36 million, and $9.3 million, respectively, signaling risk appetite beyond the crypto’s two top heavyweights.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222623654268928</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockCrypto investment products see record $4.4 billion in weekly inflows, pushing year-to-date total to $27B: CoinSharesGlobal crypto investment products attracted a record $4.39 billion of inflows last week, their strongest tally since CoinShares began tracking the data in 2014, and</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222623654268928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address holding 50 WBTC is likely to profit approximately $2.404 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, the address starting with 0x2Be is suspected of clearing 50 WBTC purchased in April last year at a cost of only $65,135. If sold, it will profit approximately $2.404M, with a return rate of approximately 83% for holding the position for 15 months. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947221156860022784</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsAn address holding 50 WBTC is likely to profit approximately $2.404 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, the address starting with 0x2Be is suspected of clearing 50 WBTC purchased in April last year at a cost of only $65,135. If sold, it will profit approximately $2.4</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947221156860022784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degen adjusts liquidity mining rewards, Beefy rewards reduced to 1.25M, Aerodrome increased to 1.75MThe Degen token on the Base network will adjust the distribution of liquidity provider rewards: The daily distribution of Degen tokens on the Beefy platform will decrease from 1.50M to 1.25M; at the same time, an additional 1.75M Degen token rewards will be added to the Aerodrome platform each week to better balance the incentive mechanisms between the two platforms. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070854053888</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsDegen adjusts liquidity mining rewards, Beefy rewards reduced to 1.25M, Aerodrome increased to 1.75MThe Degen token on the Base network will adjust the distribution of liquidity provider rewards: The daily distribution of Degen tokens on the Beefy platform will decrease from 1</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070854053888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Launches BEP-593, Introducing Weekly Incremental Snapshots to Improve Node EfficiencyBNB Chain is advancing the construction of more efficient node infrastructure. According to the BEP-593 proposal, BNB Chain will introduce a weekly incremental snapshot function to simplify the node synchronization process. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070937939968</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBNB Chain Launches BEP-593, Introducing Weekly Incremental Snapshots to Improve Node EfficiencyBNB Chain is advancing the construction of more efficient node infrastructure. According to the BEP-593 proposal, BNB Chain will introduce a weekly incremental snapshot function to s</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070937939968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet Launches PUMP Trading Arena with a Total Prize Pool of 18.00 Million PUMP TokensAccording to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched the PUMP Trading Arena, with the event running from July 21, 2025, 13:30 to July 28, 2025, 13:30 (UTC+8). During the event, users who complete specified trading, invitation, and sharing tasks will have the opportunity to receive rewards. The top 300 users by trading volume will share 12,000,000 PUMP tokens. The total prize pool for the event is 18,000,000 PUMP tokens. It is reported that Pump.Fun is a platform for creating and trading tokens, and PUMP is its official token. OKX Wallet is a leading one-stop Web3 portal in the industry, supporting 130+ popular public chains. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947217749633945600</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyOKX Wallet Launches PUMP Trading Arena with a Total Prize Pool of 18.00 Million PUMP TokensAccording to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched the PUMP Trading Arena, with the event running from July 21, 2025, 13:30 to July 28, 2025, 13:30 (UTC+8). During the event, users who comp</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947217749633945600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ping An of China: Actively Studying Industry Regulatory Changes Related to Stablecoins in the Hong Kong MarketAccording to Cailian Press, Ping An of China stated on the interactive platform that the company has noticed industry regulatory changes related to stablecoins in the Hong Kong market. Ping An has a deep accumulation in blockchain technology and will continue to pay close attention and actively research it. [Cailian Press]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210540837523456</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Ping An of China: Actively Studying Industry Regulatory Changes Related to Stablecoins in the Hong Kong MarketAccording to Cailian Press, Ping An of China stated on the interactive platform that the company has noticed industry regulatory changes related to stablecoins in the Hong Kong m</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210540837523456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 10:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>