<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:14:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bithumb to List LISTA and MERL KRW Trading PairsSouth Korea&apos;s second-largest crypto exchange, Bithumb, will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs. Trading will open at 4:00 PM and 6:00 PM local time, respectively. Lista DAO is a decentralized stablecoin lending protocol powered by LSDfi. Merlin Chain is a Bitcoin Layer 2 powered by Bitmap. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216915113086976</link>
      <description>12 minutes ago吴说Bithumb to List LISTA and MERL KRW Trading PairsSouth Korea&apos;s second-largest crypto exchange, Bithumb, will list LISTA and MERL KRW trading pairs. Trading will open at 4:00 PM and 6:00 PM local time, respectively. Lista DAO is a decentralized stablecoin lending protocol powered by LS</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216915113086976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Momentum Ignites Hong Kong Race for Crypto DominanceIn this week’s Hong Kong Edition, we survey the fizzing stablecoin scene, speak with the man behind Bar Leone and look into the stocks leaving Chinese tech in the dust. For the Review, we visit a new modern Korean restaurant from the chef formerly of Singapore’s famed Odette. To subscribe to this weekly newsletter for free, click here.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948217933922111488</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoBloombergStablecoin Momentum Ignites Hong Kong Race for Crypto DominanceIn this week’s Hong Kong Edition, we survey the fizzing stablecoin scene, speak with the man behind Bar Leone and look into the stocks leaving Chinese tech in the dust. For the Review, we visit a new modern Korean</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948217933922111488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26.According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will launch DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26. Eligible users can go to the Alpha activity page to use Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop after trading opens. Specific rules will be announced separately. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216849795190784</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha will list DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26.According to the official announcement, Binance Alpha will launch DePHY Network (PHY) on July 26. Eligible users can go to the Alpha activity page to use Binance Alpha points to claim the airdrop after trading opens. Specific</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948216849795190784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale has closed their PUMP short position, netting a profit of $2.448M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has closed its PUMP short position on Hyperliquid, with a cumulative profit of $2.448 million. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948214328607444992</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoOdailyA certain whale has closed their PUMP short position, netting a profit of $2.448M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has closed its PUMP short position on Hyperliquid, with a cumulative profit of $2.448 million. [Odaily Planet Daily]$PUMP$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948214328607444992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget CEO: The next bull market will be driven by application implementation, compliance, and technical value.Bitget CEO Gracy Chen tweeted, &quot;I don&apos;t think the next bull market will be driven by retail investors and meme coins again, nor will it be tied to the halving cycle. Instead, it will depend on how many applications can be implemented, how clear compliance regulations are, and how much real value technology can create.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211919416004608</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget CEO: The next bull market will be driven by application implementation, compliance, and technical value.Bitget CEO Gracy Chen tweeted, &quot;I don&apos;t think the next bull market will be driven by retail investors and meme coins again, nor will it be tied to the halving cyc</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211919416004608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After School Club NFT Launches Utility Token GEMThe Eclipse ecosystem NFT series After School Club has launched a utility token, GEM. GEM will be rewarded by providing ASC holders with practical uses and long-term benefit alignment within the Eclipse ecosystem. The initial airdrop snapshot was completed on July 21, with each ASC NFT allocated 5 GEM tokens, for a total airdrop of 50,000 GEM (10% of the supply). In addition, monthly airdrops will continue for 45 months, with 1 GEM allocated per ASC NFT each month, for a total allocation of 450,000 GEM (90% of the supply). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211585964642304</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoForesightNewsAfter School Club NFT Launches Utility Token GEMThe Eclipse ecosystem NFT series After School Club has launched a utility token, GEM. GEM will be rewarded by providing ASC holders with practical uses and long-term benefit alignment within the Eclipse ecosystem. The initial</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948211585964642304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist Takashi Murakami will launch NFT collection cards on the chain through Base AppOn July 24, according to The Block, the famous Japanese artist Takashi Murakami announced that he will launch the NFT series &quot;108 Flowers Revised&quot;. The series is based on his iconic &quot;super flat&quot; style of floral images and will be available for minting on the Base App on July 31. This new work continues his creative style of integrating pop culture and anime aesthetics. His past partners include luxury fashion brands such as Louis Vuitton and Supreme. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948210155727949824</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoPANewsArtist Takashi Murakami will launch NFT collection cards on the chain through Base AppOn July 24, according to The Block, the famous Japanese artist Takashi Murakami announced that he will launch the NFT series &quot;108 Flowers Revised&quot;. The series is based on his iconic &quot;super flat&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948210155727949824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined, over 7.5% has been permanently lostOn July 24, according to Curated Crypto data, only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined. It is estimated that more than 7.5% of the total Bitcoin supply has permanently disappeared from circulation due to lost wallets, forgotten private keys, or being destroyed. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948208958342238208</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoTechFlowData: Only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined, over 7.5% has been permanently lostOn July 24, according to Curated Crypto data, only 5.3% of Bitcoin remains to be mined. It is estimated that more than 7.5% of the total Bitcoin supply has permanently disappeared from circulatio</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948208958342238208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Phase 6: Participant Count Exceeds 120,000 in 12 HoursThe sixth phase of the &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event, jointly launched by Bitget Wallet and Maple Finance, started at 21:00 on July 23, with all 120,000 participation slots snapped up in a short period. The total prize pool for this round is approximately 228,000 SYRUP, with the super lucky prize winner exclusively receiving SYRUP rewards worth $6,666.00. The draw time is 22:00 on July 24 (UTC + 8). Winners must submit their prize collection information within 24 hours after the draw, or it will be invalid. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948209306754682880</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Phase 6: Participant Count Exceeds 120,000 in 12 HoursThe sixth phase of the &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event, jointly launched by Bitget Wallet and Maple Finance, started at 21:00 on July 23, with all 120,000 participation slots snapped up in a short period. T</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948209306754682880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch DEBT, NERO, and ELP spot tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Hotcoin will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs
DEBT/USDT (July 24, 12:00 UTC+8): $DEBT is the native token of the DebtCoin project. DebtCoin is the first meme coin with a patriotic mission. Unlike other meme coins that are purely for speculation, DebtCoin directs trading activity to a meaningful cause - reducing the US national debt by purchasing US Treasury bonds.
NERO/USDT (July 24, 17:20 UTC+8): $NERO is the native token of the NeroChain project. NERO Chain is built on a modular blockchain and focuses on providing value to applications, rather than just focusing on the infrastructure layer of storage.
ELP/USDT (July 24, 20:20 UTC+8): $ELP is the native token of the Elympics project. Elympics is a multi-chain entertainment layer designed to attract millions to use cryptocurrency by connecting brands and IPs to web3, and to enable developers to easily build and deploy blockchain-based skill-based games distributed across popular super apps, social platforms, and wallets. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948207963486883840</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch DEBT, NERO, and ELP spot tradingOn July 24, according to official news, Hotcoin will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs
DEBT/USDT (July 24, 12:00 UTC+8): $DEBT is the native token of the DebtCoin project. DebtCo</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948207963486883840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 巨鲸 deposited 7.51 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple short positionsOn July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, the whale @0x58bro deposited 7.51 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple short positions: 10x leveraged ETH short order, 20x leveraged SOL short order, 5x leveraged LTC and ENA short order. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948207520031510528</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoPANewsA 巨鲸 deposited 7.51 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple short positionsOn July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, the whale @0x58bro deposited 7.51 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple short positions: 10x leveraged ETH short order, 20x leveraged</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948207520031510528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Visit Federal Reserve on ThursdayThe White House: U.S. President Trump will visit the Federal Reserve on Thursday. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948206778029772800</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoOdailyTrump to Visit Federal Reserve on ThursdayThe White House: U.S. President Trump will visit the Federal Reserve on Thursday. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948206778029772800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares Partners with Société Générale to Accelerate Coverage of the European Crypto MarketCrypto ETF issuer 21Shares has reached an ETP market-making agreement with Societe Generale, under which Societe Generale will provide over-the-counter trading liquidity support for 21Shares&apos; Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs (ABTC, CBTC, AETH, CETH) on key fund platforms in Germany and Eastern Europe, enabling these products to reach a wider range of professional investors. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948204696623190016</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNews21Shares Partners with Société Générale to Accelerate Coverage of the European Crypto MarketCrypto ETF issuer 21Shares has reached an ETP market-making agreement with Societe Generale, under which Societe Generale will provide over-the-counter trading liquidity support for 21S</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948204696623190016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla’s Bitcoin Gains, Japan AI firm’s BTC Treasury Strategy and MoreWelcome to the Asia Pacific Morning Brief—your essential digest of overnight crypto developments shaping regional markets and global sentiment. Grab a green tea and watch this space. Tesla’s quarterly decline contrasts with gains in its bitcoin treasury, while a Japanese firm, Quantum Solutions, targets a $367.00M acquisition of BTC. Korean infrastructure leader DSRV secures funding, and Tron Inc. prepares Nasdaq ceremony, signaling institutional crypto adoption momentum. Tesla Reports Steep Revenue Decline Despite Bitcoin Holdings Boost Tesla faces mounting challenges as second-quarter results reveal the automaker’s steepest revenue decline in a decade, dropping 12% year-over-year to $22.50 billion. Vehicle deliveries fell 12.6% to 143,535 units while earnings per share declined 23% to $0.40, reflecting broader market pressures and competitive dynamics. The company’s electric vehicle market dominance is showing signs of erosion, with its market share maintaining 46.2%, while GM is aggressively closing the gaps, advancing from 10.8% to 14.9% quarterly. Tesla’s core automotive revenue declined 16% to $16.66 billion, indicating structural headwinds that extend beyond typical cyclical patterns. However, new FASB accounting rules provide unexpected balance sheet relief through Tesla’s 11,509 BTC holdings, now valued at approximately $1.36 billion. The regulatory shift allows quarterly fair-value reporting rather than historical cost basis, enabling Tesla to recognize bitcoin’s 42% appreciation since April directly on financial statements. This development highlights the strategic value of corporate cryptocurrency treasury strategies during traditional business cycles. Japanese Quantum Solutions Launches $367M Bitcoin Treasury Strategy Japanese AI firm Quantum Solutions announced plans to acquire up to 3,000 BTC over twelve months, establishing bitcoin as a strategic treasury reserve asset. The initiative positions the Tokyo-listed company as Japan’s second corporate bitcoin adopter, following MetaPlanet ‘s pioneering approach. Hong Kong-based Integrated Asset Management will provide $10.00 million initial funding through Quantum Solutions’ subsidiary GPT Pals Studio Limited. The acquisition strategy targets approximately $367.00 million in bitcoin holdings at current market valuations, representing a significant corporate balance sheet transformation. CEO Francis Chow emphasized institutional discipline in execution, citing the company’s unique position to develop bitcoin-centric capital structures. The program incorporates cold-hot wallet segregation, internal controls, and comprehensive audit frameworks under Hong Kong’s regulatory clarity. This strategic pivot reflects broader institutional recognition of bitcoin’s role in inflation hedging and monetary policy risk mitigation across global markets. DSRV Secures $12M Series B Amid Market Downturn South Korean blockchain infrastructure firm DSRV raised approximately $12.00 million in Series B funding despite challenging investment conditions. Major domestic investors including Intervest and NICE-SK Securities participated in the initial round, with additional institutional funding planned next month. DSRV operates infrastructure across 70+ global blockchain networks, managing over $3.00 billion in digital assets while ranking among top-10 validators worldwide. The company reported $7.80 million annual revenue with $2.30 million net profit, demonstrating sustainable profitability in volatile markets. The funding validates DSRV’s expansion into stablecoin and payment infrastructure services. Holding domestic VASP licensing in South Korea, the company prepares for aggressive global expansion across US, Japanese, and African markets while scaling custody operations and blockchain development capabilities. Tron Inc. Set to Ring Nasdaq Opening Bell Thursday Tron Inc. will ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on Thursday, marking a strategic transformation toward blockchain-integrated treasury operations. Justin Sun, TRON Blockchain founder and Global Advisor, will lead the ceremony from Times Square’s MarketSite. As the publicly traded entity holding the largest TRON token reserves, the company represents institutional convergence between traditional equity markets and decentralized finance infrastructure. CEO Rich Miller emphasized building shareholder value through strategic innovation. Beyond blockchain treasury holdings, Tron Inc. maintains diversified operations manufacturing custom merchandise for major theme parks including Disney and Universal, creating a hybrid business model bridging entertainment and digital assets. Shigeki Mori contributed. [Shigeki Mori]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948213120706613248</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoTesla’s Bitcoin Gains, Japan AI firm’s BTC Treasury Strategy and MoreWelcome to the Asia Pacific Morning Brief—your essential digest of overnight crypto developments shaping regional markets and global sentiment. Grab a green tea and watch this space. Tesla’s quarterly decline co</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948213120706613248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 24On this day in 2018, the organizers of ChinaJoy announced the establishment and hosting of the &quot;China Blockchain Technology and Game Developers Conference&quot;.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948201526094270464</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 24On this day in 2018, the organizers of ChinaJoy announced the establishment and hosting of the &quot;China Blockchain Technology and Game Developers Conference&quot;.#GameFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948201526094270464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMP Top Fund transferred 1 billion PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $3.17M.According to Arkham monitoring, PUMP Top Fund 2: 58WQi2…ogv33E transferred 1.00B PUMP to Bybit Deposit at 9:01 UTC+8 today, worth approximately $3.17M. In the past 24 hours, this PUMP institutional investor has transferred 2.00B PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $6.95M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948200785577316352</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说PUMP Top Fund transferred 1 billion PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $3.17M.According to Arkham monitoring, PUMP Top Fund 2: 58WQi2…ogv33E transferred 1.00B PUMP to Bybit Deposit at 9:01 UTC+8 today, worth approximately $3.17M. In the past 24 hours, this PUMP institutional inve</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948200785577316352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity Files to Amend Its Spot Bitcoin ETF to Allow Physical Redemptions and CreationsOn July 24, according to Bitcoin Magazine, Fidelity submitted documents to the US SEC to modify its spot Bitcoin ETF to allow physical redemption and creation. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948199610094260224</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFidelity Files to Amend Its Spot Bitcoin ETF to Allow Physical Redemptions and CreationsOn July 24, according to Bitcoin Magazine, Fidelity submitted documents to the US SEC to modify its spot Bitcoin ETF to allow physical redemption and creation. [PANews]#ETF$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948199610094260224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant: Investors are shifting funds from Bitcoin to Ethereum and altcoinsCryptoQuant posted on the X platform: &quot;For the first time in more than a year: Ethereum spot trading volume exceeds Bitcoin. Last week, Ethereum spot trading volume reached US$25.7 billion, while Bitcoin spot trading volume was US$24.4 billion, making the ETH/BTC spot trading volume ratio exceed 1 for the first time since June 2024. Investors are turning their funds to Ethereum and various altcoins.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948198942788882432</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCryptoQuant: Investors are shifting funds from Bitcoin to Ethereum and altcoinsCryptoQuant posted on the X platform: &quot;For the first time in more than a year: Ethereum spot trading volume exceeds Bitcoin. Last week, Ethereum spot trading volume reached US$25.7 billion, while Bitcoin s</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948198942788882432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency &apos;control&apos; at center of Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm trialOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. prosecutors were preparing to close the prosecution&apos;s statement in the criminal case against Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm on Thursday and subpoenaed U.S. Internal Revenue Service (IRS) agent Stephan George to testify. George reviewed transaction records related to Crypto.com and Binance, saying that according to communication records between co-founders Storm, Alexey Pertsey, and Roman Semenov, Storm &quot;controlled&quot; the funds after an account associated with Binance sent cryptocurrency to the Tornado Cash smart contract address.
Previously, Storm&apos;s lawyers questioned the evidence based on the experience of Hanfeng Lin, a victim of the &quot;pig-butchering scam,&quot; saying that no funds flowed to the currency mixing service, and that they might apply for a retrial. They also said that Hanfeng Lin was not qualified to testify on the issue of tracking the proceeds of cryptocurrency crimes. The core of this case is whether Storm has the ability to control Tornado Cash by blocking or suppressing the laundering of illegal funds. Another government witness&apos; testimony revolved around the performance of the currency mixing tool under sanctions. Storm&apos;s lawyers also plan to summon &quot;two or three experts&quot; and Chainalysis expert witnesses to the court. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948196546369097728</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCryptocurrency &apos;control&apos; at center of Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm trialOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. prosecutors were preparing to close the prosecution&apos;s statement in the criminal case against Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm on Thursday and subpoenaed U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948196546369097728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bonk.fun: 1% of total revenue will be used to buy back leading tokens in the BONK ecosystemToken launch platform bonk.fun tweeted that &quot;Starting today, 1% of bonk.fun&apos;s total revenue will be reallocated from the marketing fund to repurchase leading tokens in the BONK ecosystem.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948195189532725248</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsbonk.fun: 1% of total revenue will be used to buy back leading tokens in the BONK ecosystemToken launch platform bonk.fun tweeted that &quot;Starting today, 1% of bonk.fun&apos;s total revenue will be reallocated from the marketing fund to repurchase leading tokens in the BONK ecosystem</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948195189532725248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>