<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:55:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Build on Bitcoin adds ZK-proofs in upgrade toward decentralization</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365426186063872</link>
      <description>12:50Build on Bitcoin adds ZK-proofs in upgrade toward decentralization</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365426186063872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAgentAI ecosystem product CorrAI and Blave reach strategic cooperation to promote the democratization of quantitative tradingOn July 24, CorrAI, the core product of the DeAgentAI ecosystem, announced a strategic partnership with the institutional-level data platform Blave. The two parties will integrate institutional-level derivatives data and code-free quantitative strategy building capabilities to provide users with a one-stop solution from data insights to executable trading strategies. The position concentration analysis, advanced filters and real-time warning functions provided by the Blave platform will be directly imported into CorrAI&apos;s visual strategy builder. With the guidance of the AI assistant Corr-GPT, users can quickly create strategies using key data such as whale behavior, long and short positions, and optimize them through indicators such as Sharpe ratio and maximum drawdown. The whole process does not require programming knowledge. The cooperation will also bring cross-platform benefits to users of both platforms: Blave users can access CorrAI&apos;s backtesting function through API, and CorrAI subscribers can unlock Blave&apos;s enhanced data layer. CorrAI is a quantitative trading product in the DeAgentAI ecosystem that focuses on de-FAI. It provides users with verifiable on-chain insights and intelligent strategy development capabilities through DeAgentAI&apos;s advanced multi-agent infrastructure. The product is committed to making quantitative trading more accessible to both novices and professional users, and helps users avoid common pitfalls such as overfitting through an integrated large language model. DeAgentAI is an AI Agent network infrastructure project built on multiple chain ecosystems such as Sui, BSC and BTC, with the core vision of &quot;Make AI Smarter&quot;. It is committed to empowering on-chain transactions through AI prediction and feedback mechanisms, and has currently supported more than 190 million on-chain interactions, providing a smarter and more reliable AI-driven solution for the Web3 ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364632405643264</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsDeAgentAI ecosystem product CorrAI and Blave reach strategic cooperation to promote the democratization of quantitative tradingOn July 24, CorrAI, the core product of the DeAgentAI ecosystem, announced a strategic partnership with the institutional-level data platform Blave. The t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364632405643264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Innovation Council Appoints Ji Hun Kim as CEO, Adds SoFi as MemberOn July 24, the Cryptocurrency Innovation Council (CCI) announced today that the board of directors has appointed Ji Hun Kim as its chief executive officer (CEO). Kim has served as president and acting CEO of CCI since January 2025. He previously served as the organization&apos;s chief legal and policy officer. At the same time, SoFi, as an innovative company in the field of fintech and banking, officially joined the Crypto Innovation Council. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364466982293504</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsCrypto Innovation Council Appoints Ji Hun Kim as CEO, Adds SoFi as MemberOn July 24, the Cryptocurrency Innovation Council (CCI) announced today that the board of directors has appointed Ji Hun Kim as its chief executive officer (CEO). Kim has served as president and acting CEO of</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948364466982293504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Now Supports USYC and cUSDO as OTC CollateralAccording to official sources, Binance is now officially expanding its institutional OTC settlement services, adding support for two tokenized real-world assets (RWA) as collateral: USYC and cUSDO. Institutional users can now use these yield-bearing tokenized stable assets as collateral through Banking Triparty custody and MirrorRSV, to trade securely on the Binance platform while maintaining off-exchange custody and optimizing capital efficiency. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365325002674176</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyBinance Now Supports USYC and cUSDO as OTC CollateralAccording to official sources, Binance is now officially expanding its institutional OTC settlement services, adding support for two tokenized real-world assets (RWA) as collateral: USYC and cUSDO. Institutional users can now u</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365325002674176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19th were 217,000, with an expected 226,000The number of initial jobless claims in the United States for the week ending July 19 was 217,000, with an expected figure of 226,000 and a previous value of 221,000. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365333441613824</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoOdailyU.S. initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19th were 217,000, with an expected 226,000The number of initial jobless claims in the United States for the week ending July 19 was 217,000, with an expected figure of 226,000 and a previous value of 221,000. (Golden Ten) [Oda</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948365333441613824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian company Belgravia Hartford increased its holdings by 25 Bitcoin, bringing its total holdings to 40.8 Bitcoin.On July 24, according to the official announcement, the Canadian company Belgravia Hartford newly purchased 25 Bitcoins, with a total holding of 40.8 Bitcoins.

[TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948362539871571968</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoTechFlowCanadian company Belgravia Hartford increased its holdings by 25 Bitcoin, bringing its total holdings to 40.8 Bitcoin.On July 24, according to the official announcement, the Canadian company Belgravia Hartford newly purchased 25 Bitcoins, with a total holding of 40.8 Bitcoins.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948362539871571968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOOFi Pro has enabled multi-collateral margin, adding ETH and USDT as collateral.WOOFi Pro now supports multi-collateral margin, allowing users to trade with ETH, USDT, or USDC without the need for swaps. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360274519592960</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoForesightNewsWOOFi Pro has enabled multi-collateral margin, adding ETH and USDT as collateral.WOOFi Pro now supports multi-collateral margin, allowing users to trade with ETH, USDT, or USDC without the need for swaps. [Foresight News]#DeFi$ETH$MAG7.SSI$USDTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360274519592960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk: We will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligenceElon Musk stated on the X platform that we will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligence. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360287639375872</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoOdailyMusk: We will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligenceElon Musk stated on the X platform that we will revive Vine in the form of artificial intelligence. [Odaily星球日报]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948360287639375872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Societe Generale to make markets in 21Shares Bitcoin, Ether ETPsSociete Generale will provide liquidity for 21Shares’ Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, expanding access for institutional crypto investors in Europe.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948356453256990720</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoPANewsSociete Generale to make markets in 21Shares Bitcoin, Ether ETPsSociete Generale will provide liquidity for 21Shares’ Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, expanding access for institutional crypto investors in Europe.#ETF$ETH$MAG7.SSI$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948356453256990720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether: XAUT token is backed by over 7.66 tons of gold stored in SwitzerlandTether stated that as of Q2 2025, the number of XAUT tokens, Tether&apos;s gold token, issued was 246,524.330, with each token pegged to an equivalent amount of physical gold at a 1:1 ratio, backed by over 7.66 tons (246,524.380 troy ounces) of gold stored in Switzerland. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948354800466333696</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoForesightNewsTether: XAUT token is backed by over 7.66 tons of gold stored in SwitzerlandTether stated that as of Q2 2025, the number of XAUT tokens, Tether&apos;s gold token, issued was 246,524.330, with each token pegged to an equivalent amount of physical gold at a 1:1 ratio, backed by o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948354800466333696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deBridge Foundation Launches Reserve Fund, Repurchasing DBR Tokens with All Protocol RevenueThe deBridge Foundation has launched a reserve fund that allocates 100% of protocol revenue to repurchase its native DBR token on the open market. As of July 24, the fund has acquired 1.3% of the total DBR supply since its launch in June, worth nearly $3.00M. deBridge&apos;s overall treasury now holds $30.10M in assets, covering DBR, USDC, SOL, and ETH. In addition, the fund is exploring yield strategies and has launched a public dashboard to track assets and yields in real time. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948355264826118144</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoOdailydeBridge Foundation Launches Reserve Fund, Repurchasing DBR Tokens with All Protocol RevenueThe deBridge Foundation has launched a reserve fund that allocates 100% of protocol revenue to repurchase its native DBR token on the open market. As of July 24, the fund has acquired 1.3%</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948355264826118144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoSoValue Podcast Upgrade: Enhanced Market Insights DeliveryAI-driven investment research platform SoSoValue has announced a significant upgrade to its daily podcast feature.   This enhancement focuses on optimizing content delivery methodology to facilitate efficient absorption of critical market intelligence.Key Improvements:Streamlined Narration: Complex market analysis translated into accessible insightsCut through chaos. Focus on what drives the crypto market.Listen Now: SoSoValue remains committed to building a professional, transparent, open, and intelligent crypto data platform, delivering real-time, in-depth market analysis to empower investors and democratize market intelligence.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353255068880896</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoSoSoValueSoSoValue Podcast Upgrade: Enhanced Market Insights DeliveryAI-driven investment research platform SoSoValue has announced a significant upgrade to its daily podcast feature.   This enhancement focuses on optimizing content delivery methodology to facilitate efficient absorpti</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353255068880896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to begin $1.9B payouts in September as claims no longer disputedFTX’s next $1.9 billion distribution would unlikely include repayments to jurisdictions questioned in an earlier motion, which is currently being rewritten, according to creditors.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353017945853952</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoPANewsFTX to begin $1.9B payouts in September as claims no longer disputedFTX’s next $1.9 billion distribution would unlikely include repayments to jurisdictions questioned in an earlier motion, which is currently being rewritten, according to creditors.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948353017945853952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deBridge launches Reserve Fund to buy back its DBR token with all protocol revenuedeBridge Foundation, the organization behind the popular bridge protocol, has unveiled a Reserve Fund that channels 100% of protocol revenue into open market purchases of its DBR token, part of an effort to establish long-term value and provide users with a line-of-sight into more than $30 million in DAO assets.

Since going live in June, the Reserve Fund has already acquired 1.3% of DBR’s total supply of 10 billion tokens, currently valued at nearly $3 million, the project informed The Block. The fund now sits alongside deBridge’s broader treasury, which holds $30.1 million across DBR, USDC, SOL, and ETH as of July 24, according to details shared by the foundation.

The initiative is also exploring yield-bearing strategies to increase the fund’s overall value. According to the project, Idle USDC stablecoins on Ethereum are deposited into lending protocol Aave, while ETH is staked via Lido’s platform. On Solana, SOL and native USDC are deployed on Kamino Finance to earn returns. A public dashboard has also been released, tracking every purchase, balance, and real-time yield, providing the community with an on-chain audit trail of the foundation’s balance sheet.

DBR is the native governance token of the deBridge protocol, which was introduced in late 2024 and issued on the Solana blockchain as an SPL token. Launched in early 2022, deBridge operates as a cross-chain liquidity transfer solution that connects multiple networks like Solana, Ethereum, and BNB Chain. It doesn’t require users to lock assets and receive an equivalent wrapped token, a popular bridging design regularly exploited by cybercriminals.

deBridge raised $5.5 million in funding from investors, including Animoca Brands and ParaFi Capital, back in 2021. According to DefiLlama data, deBridge has nearly $10 million in annualized fees, and its DBR coin has a market capitalization of over $80 million.

The buyback model echoes recent moves by dYdX, Pump.fun, Raydium, and other decentralized platforms that use protocol revenue to burn or accumulate native tokens in a bid to tie value directly to network activity and support ecosystem growth.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948352641716785152</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoThe BlockdeBridge launches Reserve Fund to buy back its DBR token with all protocol revenuedeBridge Foundation, the organization behind the popular bridge protocol, has unveiled a Reserve Fund that channels 100% of protocol revenue into open market purchases of its DBR token, part of a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948352641716785152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana developers are considering increasing network block capacity by 66%.As demand for block space grows, Solana developers are considering increasing the network&apos;s block capacity by 66%. According to a document released by core contributors this week, the new proposal SIMD-0286 proposes increasing the upper limit of compute units (CU) per Solana block from 60.00M to 100.00M. The proposal aims to allow Solana to handle more transactions and support more complex applications, such as decentralized exchanges (DEXs), MEV systems, and restaking protocols, without hitting the compute limit. (Coindesk) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948352729155440640</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoOdailySolana developers are considering increasing network block capacity by 66%.As demand for block space grows, Solana developers are considering increasing the network&apos;s block capacity by 66%. According to a document released by core contributors this week, the new proposal SIMD-028</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948352729155440640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>coindesk</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men accused in New York crypto torture case out on bailThe suspects allegedly held the Italian man hostage for weeks in a Manhattan townhouse, beating him and demanding access to his Bitcoin wallet.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948351211018719232</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoPANewsMen accused in New York crypto torture case out on bailThe suspects allegedly held the Italian man hostage for weeks in a Manhattan townhouse, beating him and demanding access to his Bitcoin wallet.#Bitcoin$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948351211018719232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGBX is listed on D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT, and M/USDTOfficial news, MGBX was listed on July 24, 2025 for D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT and M/USDT.
Deposit opening time: July 24, 2025 19:00 (SGT)
Trading opening time: July 24, 2025 19:30 (SGT) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350228704333824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMGBX is listed on D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT, and M/USDTOfficial news, MGBX was listed on July 24, 2025 for D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT and M/USDT.
Deposit opening time: July 24, 2025 19:00 (SGT)
Trading opening time: July 24, 2025 19:30 (SGT) [Odaily News]$D$G$HShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350228704333824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XT Exchange Lists CTA (Cross The Ages)XT will list CTA (Cross The Ages) and open the CTA/USDT trading pair in the Innovation Zone (GameFi). Details are as follows:
Deposit Time: July 23, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Trading Time: July 24, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Withdrawal Time: July 25, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Cross The Ages (CTA) is a comprehensive intellectual property (IP) covering various media and entertainment formats. It aims to attract player communities by integrating the rich experiences of Web2 and Web3 ecosystems. CTA&apos;s product line includes: video games, books, movies/episodes, collectible models, peripheral merchandise, and derivatives. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350237160050688</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyXT Exchange Lists CTA (Cross The Ages)XT will list CTA (Cross The Ages) and open the CTA/USDT trading pair in the Innovation Zone (GameFi). Details are as follows:
Deposit Time: July 23, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Trading Time: July 24, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Withdrawal Time: July 25, 2025, 17</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350237160050688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Whale that has been dormant for 14.5 years and holds nearly 4,000 BTC&quot; transfers all BTC to a new walletArkham data shows that a &quot;whale holding nearly 4,000 BTC dormant for 14.5 years&quot; has just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (approximately $469.00M) it held to a new wallet address (bc1qczar85zjppfjr8df8qnc4l3h5r957v6p2udryz) [Odaily].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347693763465216</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdaily&quot;Whale that has been dormant for 14.5 years and holds nearly 4,000 BTC&quot; transfers all BTC to a new walletArkham data shows that a &quot;whale holding nearly 4,000 BTC dormant for 14.5 years&quot; has just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (approximately $469.00M) it held to a new wallet address (bc</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347693763465216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin OG just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC to a new walletOn July 24, on-chain data showed that Bitcoin OG, which had been dormant for 14.5 years, had just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (about US$469.00 million) it held to a new wallet address (bc1qczar85zjppfjr8df8qnc4l3h5r957v6p2udryz). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948346531815428096</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBitcoin OG just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC to a new walletOn July 24, on-chain data showed that Bitcoin OG, which had been dormant for 14.5 years, had just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (about US$469.00 million) it held to a new wallet address (bc1qczar85zjppfjr8df8qnc4l3h5r957v6p2u</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948346531815428096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything Blockchain: Advancing the Construction of a Meme Coin Treasury and Launching MemeStrategy S-1 RegistrationUS-listed company Everything Blockchain has announced that the MemeStrategy spin-off has entered the next stage, with the company officially launching the S-1 registration process with the US Securities and Exchange Commission for MemeStrategy, with the aim of preparing for a subsequent Nasdaq listing through financing or strategic acquisitions. In addition, MemeStrategy will also advance its Meme coin acquisition strategy, including PEPE, BONK and SPX6900, to build the first Meme coin treasury of a US-listed company. (Globe newswire) Previous news, Everything Blockchain also announced plans to invest $10.00M in Solana (SOL), XRP, Sui (SUI), Bittensor (TAO) and Hyperliquid (HYPE) to create a multi-token staking vault for institutional adoption trends. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347702202404864</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyEverything Blockchain: Advancing the Construction of a Meme Coin Treasury and Launching MemeStrategy S-1 RegistrationUS-listed company Everything Blockchain has announced that the MemeStrategy spin-off has entered the next stage, with the company officially launching the S-1 registra</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347702202404864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>