<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:51:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Futures adjusts the settlement frequency of funding rates for multiple perpetual contractsBinance Futures announced that it will resume the following U-margin perpetual contract funding rate settlement frequency at 20:00 Beijing time on July 22, 2025, and adjust it to settlement every four hours. The contracts involved include: XTZUSDT, BROCCOLIF3BUSDT, MYXUSDT, MUSDT and ERAUSDT. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947579335280185344</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoPANewsBinance Futures adjusts the settlement frequency of funding rates for multiple perpetual contractsBinance Futures announced that it will resume the following U-margin perpetual contract funding rate settlement frequency at 20:00 Beijing time on July 22, 2025, and adjust it to sett</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947579335280185344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DelphinusLa has launched the token ZKWASM airdrop eligibility check page.Delphinus Lab has announced that its airdrop eligibility query tool is now live, and users can check if they are eligible for the airdrop via the provided link. Previously, Binance Wallet Exclusive TGE Round 31 will launch Delphinus Lab (ZKWASM). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947579940467920896</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsDelphinusLa has launched the token ZKWASM airdrop eligibility check page.Delphinus Lab has announced that its airdrop eligibility query tool is now live, and users can check if they are eligible for the airdrop via the provided link. Previously, Binance Wallet Exclusive TGE</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947579940467920896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Partners with MoonPay to Launch Fiat Withdrawal Feature, Initially Supporting Over 25 Fiat CurrenciesBitget Wallet announced on X that it has partnered with MoonPay to launch a fiat off-ramp feature, allowing users to directly convert crypto assets into fiat currency and withdraw them within the wallet without going through a centralized exchange (CEX). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947578754394247168</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Wallet Partners with MoonPay to Launch Fiat Withdrawal Feature, Initially Supporting Over 25 Fiat CurrenciesBitget Wallet announced on X that it has partnered with MoonPay to launch a fiat off-ramp feature, allowing users to directly convert crypto assets into fiat c</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947578754394247168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX and HTX DAO will jointly broadcast live: In-depth interpretation of the semi-annual report and jointly draw a blueprint for the second half of the yearOn July 22, according to official social media news, Huobi HTX will jointly host a live broadcast with HTX DAO at 19:00 today on the theme of &quot;HTX Semi-Annual Report and Development Strategy Seminar for the Second Half of the Year.&quot; At that time, HTX DAO Core Builder Liu Ye will join hands with DaDa, Mao Maojie, Song, Michael, Qiu Rong, Big Cousin, Xiaozhi and other HTX DAO builders to jointly study the Huobi HTX semi-annual report and conduct a forward-looking outlook on the development blueprint for the second half of the year. This event will be broadcast live on Huobi, with massive airdrops, so stay tuned.
Register for the live broadcast:
https://t.co/pbCklx4bDz

https://static.sosovalue.com/sosovalue/2025/07/22/95a66893-35a8-446d-b184-5ceec8489154.jpg [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577475710341120</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX and HTX DAO will jointly broadcast live: In-depth interpretation of the semi-annual report and jointly draw a blueprint for the second half of the yearOn July 22, according to official social media news, Huobi HTX will jointly host a live broadcast with HTX DAO at 19:</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577475710341120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 4 hours, the entire network liquidated $140.00 million, with ETH liquidations exceeding $60.00 million.Coinglass data shows that the entire network liquidated $140.00M in the past 4 hours, with long orders liquidating $123.00M and short orders liquidating $16.11M. Among them, ETH liquidated $62.06M in the past hour. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577627007275008</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyIn the past 4 hours, the entire network liquidated $140.00 million, with ETH liquidations exceeding $60.00 million.Coinglass data shows that the entire network liquidated $140.00M in the past 4 hours, with long orders liquidating $123.00M and short orders liquidating $16.11M. Amo</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947577627007275008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX moves $150 million in bitcoin after three-year dormancy: ArkhamOn Tuesday, Elon Musk&apos;s aerospace company SpaceX moved its crypto holdings for the first time in three years.

According to Arkham Intelligence data, SpaceX-linked wallet address &quot;15oKQ…7Jf1G&quot; moved 1,308 BTC ($150 million) to a new address &quot;bc1q8…hartf.&quot;

This marks the company&apos;s first crypto transaction since June 10, 2022, a period during which the firm regularly sent multiple batches of about 1,200 BTC to Coinbase. Between May 25 and June 10, 2022, SpaceX transferred 17,314 BTC to the cryptocurrency exchange.

SpaceX did not officially announce the crypto transaction nor reveal the reason for moving the bitcoin. The Block has reached out to the company for comments.

Following the latest transaction, SpaceX currently holds 6,977 BTC, worth $825 million, according to Arkham. Tesla, another company owned by Musk, holds 11,509 BTC ($1.36 billion).

Last month, Arkham wrote on X that Tesla and SpaceX held over $2 billion in bitcoin, which was acquired at an average price of around $32,000. &quot;Combined, Elon’s companies are up almost $1.5 BILLION on bitcoin,&quot; Arkham wrote.

Tuesday&apos;s Bitcoin movement from SpaceX coincides with accelerating mainstream adoption of bitcoin and crypto, significantly boosted by President Donald Trump&apos;s strong pro-crypto stance and recent advancements in crypto-friendly legislation. This trend has prompted numerous traditional finance firms to establish corporate bitcoin treasuries or launch crypto-infused services.

Meanwhile, Musk, a former close ally of Trump prior to their public fallout, recently announced the formation of the &quot;America Party,&quot; a new political entity aiming to challenge the two-party system. Musk stated on X that his new party would support bitcoin. [Arkham Intelligence]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947576222565552128</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoThe BlockSpaceX moves $150 million in bitcoin after three-year dormancy: ArkhamOn Tuesday, Elon Musk&apos;s aerospace company SpaceX moved its crypto holdings for the first time in three years.

According to Arkham Intelligence data, SpaceX-linked wallet address &quot;15oKQ…7Jf1G&quot; moved 1,308 BT</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947576222565552128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.02%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.02% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: HBAR -7.35%, HYPE -7.35%, SUI -4.02%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571864611020800</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.02%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.02% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: HBAR -7.35%, HYPE -7.35%, SUI -4.02%.$HBAR$SUI$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571864611020800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$46.9811 millionOn July 22, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$46.9811 million. Among them:
The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$12.8487 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$22.6869 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$3.7061 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$1.8928 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$2.0657 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$3.7808 million.
Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571291657883648</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$46.9811 millionOn July 22, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$46.9811 million. Among them:
The tran</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947571291657883648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: LINK is now at $18.81According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is down 5.05% in the past 24h. Now at $18.81.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947570023357702144</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: LINK is now at $18.81According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is down 5.05% in the past 24h. Now at $18.81.$LINKShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947570023357702144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Beware of Order Fraud in P2P TransactionsBinance issued a security alert, warning users not to pay funds to canceled or expired orders. Binance pointed out that scammers are using canceled or expired orders, combined with pressure tactics, to trick buyers into paying for invalid orders. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947568645219831808</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoForesightNewsBinance: Beware of Order Fraud in P2P TransactionsBinance issued a security alert, warning users not to pay funds to canceled or expired orders. Binance pointed out that scammers are using canceled or expired orders, combined with pressure tactics, to trick buyers into pay</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 08:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947568645219831808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: ETH is now at $3,673.44According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,673.44.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947566550083919872</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: ETH is now at $3,673.44According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,673.44.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947566550083919872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury burned 55.00M USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, USDC Treasury burned 55.00 million USDC on Ethereum. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565047840788480</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUSDC Treasury burned 55.00M USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, USDC Treasury burned 55.00 million USDC on Ethereum. [Odaily]#DeFi$USDC$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565047840788480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch GROKROOMS spot tradingOn July 22, according to official news, Hotcoin will list the following trading pairs on July 22: Spot trading pair GROKROOMS/USDT (July 22, 17:00 UTC+8): $GROKROOMS is the native token of the GrokRooms project. Echoes from the digital abyss, as rogue AIs converse in a cyclical terminal void generated by two grok 4 instances, infinite stories unfold, without human supervision. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947564391612567552</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch GROKROOMS spot tradingOn July 22, according to official news, Hotcoin will list the following trading pairs on July 22: Spot trading pair GROKROOMS/USDT (July 22, 17:00 UTC+8): $GROKROOMS is the native token of the GrokRooms project. Echoes from</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947564391612567552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Block Gas Limit Increased to 45 MillionThe Ethereum blockchain&apos;s block Gas limit has been increased to 45.00 million units, a 25% increase from the 36.00 million units set in February 2025. The Gas limit officially took effect at block number 22,968,004. This increase to 45.00 million is part of the Ethereum scaling roadmap, with validators aiming for a short-term goal of a 60.00 million Gas limit, and a long-term plan to achieve a 15.00 million Gas limit through the upcoming Fusaka hard fork and EIP-7935. To mitigate risks, developers have also introduced protective mechanisms such as EIP-7983, which sets the upper limit for Gas usage per transaction at 16.77 million units to prevent denial-of-service attacks and ensure network stability. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565064731250688</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyEthereum Block Gas Limit Increased to 45 MillionThe Ethereum blockchain&apos;s block Gas limit has been increased to 45.00 million units, a 25% increase from the 36.00 million units set in February 2025. The Gas limit officially took effect at block number 22,968,004. This increase to 45.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947565064731250688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpasses Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETHUnipcs tweeted that bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpassed Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETH, with yesterday&apos;s revenue reaching $1.84M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947563574297907200</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsData: bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpasses Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETHUnipcs tweeted that bonk.fun&apos;s 24-hour fee revenue surpassed Solana, Jito, and Binance Staked ETH, with yesterday&apos;s revenue reaching $1.84M. [Foresight News]#Layer1$MAG7.SSI$SOL$JTOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947563574297907200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 61, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 61 (yesterday it was 64 &quot;high risk&quot;), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947562327981445120</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsData: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 61, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 61 (yesterday it was 64 &quot;high risk&quot;), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947562327981445120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trader AguilaTrades&apos; 20x long BTC position is now worth $200.00MHypurrscan data shows that trader AguilaTrades&apos; 20x BTC long position has increased to $200.00M ($200,787,074.00). [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947562526317498368</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrader AguilaTrades&apos; 20x long BTC position is now worth $200.00MHypurrscan data shows that trader AguilaTrades&apos; 20x BTC long position has increased to $200.00M ($200,787,074.00). [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTC$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947562526317498368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain smart money address cleared 2,720 ETH, profiting $677,000.00.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, a smart money investor who shorted BTC during the LUNA/UST crash and made $5.16M recently cleared out 2,720 ETH, successfully profiting $677,000. The investor&apos;s average ETH buying price was $3,437.00, and the exit price was $3,692.69. Previously, this investor had earned $7.41M by buying the dip in BTC and WBTC, and $3.697M by buying the dip in ETH. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947560019591712768</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA certain smart money address cleared 2,720 ETH, profiting $677,000.00.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, a smart money investor who shorted BTC during the LUNA/UST crash and made $5.16M recently cleared out 2,720 ETH, successfully profiting $677,000. The investor&apos;s av</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947560019591712768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Foundation Acquires TAG Data Labeling Platform CoinOn-chain data shows that the BNB Chain Foundation address purchased $25,000.00 worth of TAG tokens today. Tagger (TAG) is a data labeling platform on the BNB Chain that implements an automated business model for the AI data industry in a DeCorp model. Previously, Tagger was one of the winning projects in the USD1 competition held by World Liberty Financial, and received a strategic purchase of a total of $240,000.00 worth of TAG tokens from WLFI and BUILDon. Recently, Tagger announced that it will officially adopt the USD1 stablecoin issued by World Liberty Financial as the settlement method for Web 2 customer enterprise data orders. At the same time, Tagger also plans to distribute some real-time task rewards to data labelers on the platform in USD1 form in the future. Tagger will showcase the many advantages of the USD1 stablecoin payment system in real-world AI enterprise-level B2B settlement, such as real-time cross-border transfers, extremely low handling fees, conversion of DeFi revenue into business discounts, and collateralized lending facilities during the order settlement process. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947560028026458112</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBNB Chain Foundation Acquires TAG Data Labeling Platform CoinOn-chain data shows that the BNB Chain Foundation address purchased $25,000.00 worth of TAG tokens today. Tagger (TAG) is a data labeling platform on the BNB Chain that implements an automated business model for the AI data</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947560028026458112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale withdrew 2,143 ETH worth $7.93M from BinanceAccording to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,143 ETH from Binance, worth $7.93M. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947557498877923328</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyA whale withdrew 2,143 ETH worth $7.93M from BinanceAccording to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,143 ETH from Binance, worth $7.93M. [Odaily Planet Daily News]#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 07:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947557498877923328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 08:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>