<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CICC: Stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructureAccording to Zhitong Finance, a research report by CICC states that stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructure. By analyzing the incentive compatibility mechanisms of various participants in stablecoins, the report envisions the potential impact of stablecoins on financial markets and the international monetary system, and further explores China&apos;s response. We believe that the nascent stage of infrastructure is an important development opportunity, and issuing offshore RMB stablecoins may be China&apos;s preferred choice for participating in stablecoin development. However, it should be noted that stablecoins are only a &quot;technique&quot; for promoting the internationalization of the RMB. Whether the RMB can become a widely trusted international currency ultimately depends on the &quot;principles,&quot; namely the &quot;legal anchor&quot; and &quot;functional anchor&quot; of the RMB. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948549091427946496</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsCICC: Stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructureAccording to Zhitong Finance, a research report by CICC states that stablecoins have the potential to become a new type of infrastructure. By analyzing the incentive compatibility mechanisms of vario</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948549091427946496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>510 billion BONK Transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase, Approximately $18.75 millionAccording to @EmberCN monitoring, half an hour after the Bonk project team tweeted that it had repurchased and burned 500.00B BONK (approximately $18.47M), 510.00B BONK (approximately $18.75M) was transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548771264139264</link>
      <description>8 minutes ago吴说510 billion BONK Transferred from Galaxy Digital to Binance and Coinbase, Approximately $18.75 millionAccording to @EmberCN monitoring, half an hour after the Bonk project team tweeted that it had repurchased and burned 500.00B BONK (approximately $18.47M), 510.00B BONK (approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548771264139264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripple co-founder-related addresses transferred approximately $140.00M worth of XRP to trading platforms in the past 7 days.According to on-chain investigator ZachXBT, since July 17, an address long associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen has transferred 50,000,000 XRP. The wallet appears to have transferred approximately $140,000,000.00 worth of tokens into three addresses associated with trading platforms, while another 10,000,000 XRP were deposited into two newly created wallets. Addresses controlled by Chris Larsen still hold approximately 2,810,000,000 XRP, worth about $9,000,000,000.00. Previously, the SEC accused Ripple&apos;s CEO Brad Garlinghouse of personally cashing out $150,000,000.00 worth of XRP over three years when it sued Ripple in 2020. In addition, Larsen and his spouse sold $450,000,000.00 worth of tokens between 2017 and 2020. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548137433501696</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsRipple co-founder-related addresses transferred approximately $140.00M worth of XRP to trading platforms in the past 7 days.According to on-chain investigator ZachXBT, since July 17, an address long associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen has transferred 50,000,000 X</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948548137433501696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinmarketcap: Monad will launch on September 30th, with a total token supply of 100,000,000,000.00On July 25th, according to Coinmarketcap&apos;s Monad token page, Monad will be launched on September 30, 2025 (North American time September 29) Beijing time, with a total token supply of 100.00B.

[Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948547285012516864</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoTechFlowCoinmarketcap: Monad will launch on September 30th, with a total token supply of 100,000,000,000.00On July 25th, according to Coinmarketcap&apos;s Monad token page, Monad will be launched on September 30, 2025 (North American time September 29) Beijing time, with a total token suppl</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948547285012516864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s second son forwards the view that &quot;ETH is undervalued&quot; and expresses his agreement.Trump&apos;s second son, Eric Trump, retweeted, &quot;Ethereum is catching up with global liquidity. If compared to M2 money supply growth, the price of ETH should already be over $8,000.00. This suggests that ETH is currently undervalued and may be one of the best trades right now,&quot; and said, &quot;Totally agree.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948545787805372416</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoForesightNewsTrump&apos;s second son forwards the view that &quot;ETH is undervalued&quot; and expresses his agreement.Trump&apos;s second son, Eric Trump, retweeted, &quot;Ethereum is catching up with global liquidity. If compared to M2 money supply growth, the price of ETH should already be over $8,000.00. T</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948545787805372416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSL Group plans to raise approximately HK$2.355B through a rights issue for strategic acquisitions, stablecoin business, etc.According to Jiemian News, OSL Group entered into a placing and subscription agreement, a general mandate subscription agreement, and a special mandate subscription agreement on July 25, 2025 (before the trading session). The total estimated proceeds from the transactions contemplated under these agreements are approximately HK$2,355.03M, and the estimated net proceeds are approximately HK$2,336.10M. The placing price is HK$14.90 per placing share, representing a discount of approximately 15.34% to the closing price of the shares as quoted on the Stock Exchange on the last trading day. The Company intends to use the total net proceeds for the following: approximately 50% to support the Company&apos;s strategic acquisition initiatives; approximately 30% for the development of global business and new business initiatives (including payment and stablecoin initiatives); and approximately 20% for the general corporate purposes of the Group. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948543627420045312</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoForesightNewsOSL Group plans to raise approximately HK$2.355B through a rights issue for strategic acquisitions, stablecoin business, etc.According to Jiemian News, OSL Group entered into a placing and subscription agreement, a general mandate subscription agreement, and a special mand</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948543627420045312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: SOL is now at $181.26According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 5.01% in the past 24h. Now at $181.26.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948542128647790592</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: SOL is now at $181.26According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 5.01% in the past 24h. Now at $181.26.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948542128647790592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant Founder: Bitcoin Cycle Theory Has Become InvalidOn July 25, CryptoQuant founder Ki Young Ju posted that the cyclical theory of &quot;buy when whales accumulate, sell when retail investors enter&quot; no longer applies to Bitcoin. In previous cycles, whales would sell chips to retail investors, but now old whales are selling to new long-term whales, with institutional participation far exceeding expectations, and the number of holders exceeding the number of traders. Ki Young Ju apologized for his previous misjudgment that &quot;the bull market cycle is over&quot; and said that he will be more cautious in the future and focus on data-driven analysis. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948540004162146304</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoTechFlowCryptoQuant Founder: Bitcoin Cycle Theory Has Become InvalidOn July 25, CryptoQuant founder Ki Young Ju posted that the cyclical theory of &quot;buy when whales accumulate, sell when retail investors enter&quot; no longer applies to Bitcoin. In previous cycles, whales would sell chips to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948540004162146304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US crypto legislation drives $4B surge in stablecoin supplyRegulatory clarity is opening the door for banks, asset managers, and crypto firms to roll out new stablecoin products.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948534676737560576</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUS crypto legislation drives $4B surge in stablecoin supplyRegulatory clarity is opening the door for banks, asset managers, and crypto firms to roll out new stablecoin products.#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948534676737560576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>250,000 Tether Gold tokens in circulation are backed by 7.66 tons of gold, Tether saysTether says it now has nearly 250,000 Tether Gold (XAU₮) tokens in circulation, as of Q2 2025. Each token is backed 1:1 by a troy ounce of physical gold, the equivalent of more than 7.66 tons of gold in total, the company said in an announcement on Thursday.

“Gold-backed digital assets, such as XAU₮, are increasingly viewed as essential portfolio hedges,” Tether said in a statement, pointing to shifting macroeconomic uncertainties, fiat volatility, and rising debt.

“Tether Gold offers a familiar asset in a future-forward format,” the company added. “As the world rethinks the nature of money, XAU₮ stands ready to serve both as a safe haven and a functional, transferable reserve asset for users across the globe.”

Launched in January 2020, Tether Gold is a stablecoin meant to represent one troy ounce of physical gold, specifically London Good Delivery gold bars. It has a total market capitalization above $830 million, according to Tether’s website.

The XAU₮ token, available on platforms like Kraken, KuCoin, and Bitfinex, is meant to give investors an alternative form of exposure to gold. Holders can reportedly redeem their holdings for physical gold that’s held in Swiss vaults.

Tether’s flagship USD-pegged stablecoin, USDT, is the world&apos;s largest with a total market capitalization of $162 billion, according to The Block&apos;s price page. Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino has signaled that the company is looking to enter U.S. markets following President Donald Trump’s signing of the GENIUS Act into law.

Ardoino has also said that obtaining a full review from a Big Four audit firm — Deloitte, EY, PwC, or KPMG — is a &quot;top priority.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948493535115808768</link>
      <description>3 hours agoThe Block250,000 Tether Gold tokens in circulation are backed by 7.66 tons of gold, Tether saysTether says it now has nearly 250,000 Tether Gold (XAU₮) tokens in circulation, as of Q2 2025. Each token is backed 1:1 by a troy ounce of physical gold, the equivalent of more than 7.66 tons of</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948493535115808768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH core developer testifies in Roman Storm defense as gov’t rests caseAfter about two weeks of hearing from US government witnesses, Roman Storm’s legal team called Preston Van Loon to the stand to kick off its defense case.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948479322100142080</link>
      <description>4 hours agoPANewsETH core developer testifies in Roman Storm defense as gov’t rests caseAfter about two weeks of hearing from US government witnesses, Roman Storm’s legal team called Preston Van Loon to the stand to kick off its defense case.#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948479322100142080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey&apos;s Solana staking ETF to pass on 100% of rewards to shareholders as it integrates JitoSOLREX-Osprey’s Solana staking exchange-traded fund has integrated staking rewards through a partnership with JitoSOL, the leading liquid staking token on Solana. This makes it the first and only crypto ETF to offer staking rewards to U.S. investors, according to an announcement on Thursday.

According to the announcement, 100% of the fund’s staking rewards will be “passed through to shareholders, with neither REX nor Osprey retaining any portion.”

The REX-Osprey Solana + Staking ETF went live on July 2 as the first approved fund to stake its assets. The fund has accrued at least $222 million in cumulative trading volume and over $100 million in net assets under management since its debut, according to The Block Research.

“Now by integrating the capability for liquid staking through JitoSOL, we’re enhancing liquidity while continuing to deliver native Solana rewards within a U.S. ETF structure,” Greg King, CEO of REX Financial &amp; Osprey Funds, said in a statement.

JitoSOL, a liquid staking token, is a tokenized version of staked SOL that enables users to continue trading the value of their staked assets while still earning on-chain rewards. There is approximately $3 billion worth of JitoSOL in circulation, according to The Block’s data.

The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has clarified that it does not believe most staking activities fall under its remit. However, the agency has been hesitant to approve staking ETFs. REX-Osprey’s fund was approved under a more stringent regulatory model called the Investment Company Act of 1940, which requires a qualified custodian to hold the assets.

REX-Osprey tapped Anchorage Digital as its custodian and staking partner. Staking represents an increasingly fast-growing part of crypto custodians like Anchorage and BitGo’s business model.

“JitoSOL becoming the first liquid staking token included in a U.S. ETF is a landmark moment — not just for Jito, but for the future of staked assets in traditional financial products,&quot; Thomas Uhm, Jito Foundation chief commercial officer, said in a statement. [The Block Research]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948476776715456512</link>
      <description>4 hours agoThe BlockREX-Osprey&apos;s Solana staking ETF to pass on 100% of rewards to shareholders as it integrates JitoSOLREX-Osprey’s Solana staking exchange-traded fund has integrated staking rewards through a partnership with JitoSOL, the leading liquid staking token on Solana. This makes it the fir</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948476776715456512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil and Gas Made the University of Texas Rich. Can Green Energy Make It Richer?Never miss an episode. Follow The Big Take daily podcast today.With more than $50 billion under management, Harvard has the largest college endowment in the United States. But the University of Texas is not far behind.On today’s Big Take podcast, Bloomberg’s Janet Lorin joins host David Gura to discuss how the University of Texas harnessed land and oil to build the second-largest endowment in higher education and why it’s now adding new kinds of energy — and new ventures — to its portfolio.Read more: Oil-Rich University of Texas Wants to Cash In on AI, Crypto and PowerListen and follow The Big Take on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948482174050701312</link>
      <description>4 hours agoBloombergOil and Gas Made the University of Texas Rich. Can Green Energy Make It Richer?Never miss an episode. Follow The Big Take daily podcast today.With more than $50 billion under management, Harvard has the largest college endowment in the United States. But the University of Texas i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948482174050701312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Myriad Users Are Predicting SharpLink&apos;s Ethereum Buys and MoreSolana tokens PENGU, FARTCOIN, and PUMP are featured in popular prediction markets on Myriad Markets this week. SharpLink Gaming has been accumulating Ethereum, with predictors speculating on its treasury growth. Predictors are also betting on the market cap of PUMP and FARTCOIN on Myriad.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948528688202584064</link>
      <description>5 hours agoDecrptHow Myriad Users Are Predicting SharpLink&apos;s Ethereum Buys and MoreSolana tokens PENGU, FARTCOIN, and PUMP are featured in popular prediction markets on Myriad Markets this week. SharpLink Gaming has been accumulating Ethereum, with predictors speculating on its treasury growth. Pred</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948528688202584064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-UFC Star Promotes Crypto Scam Shortly After Dodging DeathBen Askren, recovering from a severe case of pneumonia and a double lung transplant, promoted a Solana meme coin that quickly crashed in a suspected &quot;rug pull&quot; scam. Despite claims of hacking, evidence suggests Askren was paid to endorse the token launch.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948503519811670016</link>
      <description>5 hours agoDecrptEx-UFC Star Promotes Crypto Scam Shortly After Dodging DeathBen Askren, recovering from a severe case of pneumonia and a double lung transplant, promoted a Solana meme coin that quickly crashed in a suspected &quot;rug pull&quot; scam. Despite claims of hacking, evidence suggests Askren was p</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948503519811670016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confessions of a Laptop Farmer: How an American Helped North Korea’s Wild Remote Worker SchemeWhen Christina Marie Chapman first stumbled blindly into a web of international intrigue, in 2020, she’d been trying to turn her life around. She was living in the tiny town of Brook Park, Minnesota, occupying a run-down travel trailer on a rural property her mother owned. Over Chapman’s adult life she’d lived in Texas, England and Colorado—drifting between jobs at big-box stores, fast-food chains, casinos, mortgage brokers—“not anything that I ever dreamed of doing as a child,” she recalls.The daughter of an ex-Marine father and an accountant mother, she’d been born in South Korea, where her father was stationed, and bounced around before spending her formative years in Pine City, a dozen miles from Brook Park. Now, at 44, she’d retreated home to start over. She took out loans to attend a coding boot camp, hoping to pull herself out of the mire of dead-end jobs. Finally done with the coursework after five months and thousands of dollars, she created a LinkedIn profile to advertise her new skills. Occupation: software engineer.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948482219747643392</link>
      <description>5 hours agoBloombergConfessions of a Laptop Farmer: How an American Helped North Korea’s Wild Remote Worker SchemeWhen Christina Marie Chapman first stumbled blindly into a web of international intrigue, in 2020, she’d been trying to turn her life around. She was living in the tiny town of Brook Par</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948482219747643392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Bear Makes High-Stakes Options Wager on Drop to $110,000A crypto investor just made a high-stakes wager that Bitcoin will fall at least 8% to below $110,000 by early August.On Tuesday, the unidentified speculator paid about $5 million in premium on the Deribit exchange to buy Bitcoin put options expiring on Aug. 8 at the strike price of $110,000, according to prime broker FalconX, which facilitated the trade. There were two transactions - for 3,000 and 2,000 Bitcoin, respectively - making the full trade size roughly $600 million in notional value.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948482264001744896</link>
      <description>6 hours agoBloombergBitcoin Bear Makes High-Stakes Options Wager on Drop to $110,000A crypto investor just made a high-stakes wager that Bitcoin will fall at least 8% to below $110,000 by early August.On Tuesday, the unidentified speculator paid about $5 million in premium on the Deribit exchange to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948482264001744896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Hyperliquid Hype Push HYPE to $69.69? AnalysisHyperliquid&apos;s native token, HYPE, has surged over 550% since its launch, but predictions on Myriad Markets suggest it may not hit $69.69 by September. Technical analysis indicates a 60% rally would be challenging in the near term.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948503527478857728</link>
      <description>6 hours agoDecrptCan Hyperliquid Hype Push HYPE to $69.69? AnalysisHyperliquid&apos;s native token, HYPE, has surged over 550% since its launch, but predictions on Myriad Markets suggest it may not hit $69.69 by September. Technical analysis indicates a 60% rally would be challenging in the near term.$HY</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948503527478857728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy upsizes preferred &apos;Stretch&apos; stock offering to $2.00 billion to buy more bitcoinBitcoin treasury firm Strategy plans to quadruple the size of its recently announced Series A Perpetual Stretch Preferred Stock offer to $2.00 billion from $500.00 million after strong demand for bitcoin‑focused shares, Morgan Stanley, Barclays, Moelis, and TD Securities are bookrunners on the latest Stretch sale.

Proceeds from Strategy’s expanded facility are earmarked to fund additional Bitcoin purchases. Last week, the company spent $739.90 million generated from share sales on 6,220 BTC, increasing its holdings to 607,770, The Block’s data shows. That’s currently valued at over $72.00 billion and roughly 3% of Bitcoin’s total supply of 21 million.

The company, formerly known as MicroStrategy, will offer Stretch shares at a price of $90 per share, a 10% discount to face value and the low end of a marketed range of $100. The securities carry an initial 9% annual dividend that Strategy can reset monthly.

Stretch, the company’s fourth preferred stock program, reportedly ranks senior to the firm’s Strike (STRK) and Stride (STRD) preferred stock and its common shares, but subordinate to its Strife (STRF) preferred series and outstanding convertible notes.

Earlier this week, TD Cowen said the company’s preferred‑stock arsenal could help Strategy lift its holdings to nearly 900,000 BTC by 2027, arguing each share controls more Bitcoin today than 18 months ago despite aggressive issuance. Strategy’s net asset value premium, the percentage by which its market cap surpasses its BTC holdings, is justified since the company can effectively borrow at low rates and stockpile crypto’s largest asset, the brokerage stated.

Strategy’s common stock is trading around $414, giving the firm a market capitalization of $124.00 billion, according to The Block’s data dashboard. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948442129080061952</link>
      <description>7 hours agoThe BlockStrategy upsizes preferred &apos;Stretch&apos; stock offering to $2.00 billion to buy more bitcoinBitcoin treasury firm Strategy plans to quadruple the size of its recently announced Series A Perpetual Stretch Preferred Stock offer to $2.00 billion from $500.00 million after strong demand</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948442129080061952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolv Enables Protocol Fee Mechanism, Returns Will Reward Stakers and Drive Ecosystem ExpansionResolv has announced the official launch of a protocol fee mechanism starting in July 2025, where a portion of the daily revenue will be used for long-term value accumulation and distributed to RESOLV stakers. The protocol fee will gradually increase to 10% of daily profits over 4 weeks and will only be charged when there is a positive return, without affecting the principal or days with zero returns. Protocol revenue will be used to expand DeFi and institutional integration, fund ecosystem development, promote token buybacks, and usage will be made public through a transparent dashboard. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948441027974598656</link>
      <description>7 hours ago吴说Resolv Enables Protocol Fee Mechanism, Returns Will Reward Stakers and Drive Ecosystem ExpansionResolv has announced the official launch of a protocol fee mechanism starting in July 2025, where a portion of the daily revenue will be used for long-term value accumulation and distributed</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948441027974598656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>