<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Ventures announces support for AI trading agent platform BankrOn July 24, Coinbase Ventures announced that it would support the development of the Bankr platform through the Base Ecosystem Fund. It is reported that Bankr is an intelligent trading agent platform integrated into Coinbase&apos;s new Base application. It aims to improve market efficiency through 24-hour operation, faster response and data-driven decision-making through automated trading agents. According to previous news, Coinbase added BNKR, JITOSOL and MPLX to its asset roadmap. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948283017960689664</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsCoinbase Ventures announces support for AI trading agent platform BankrOn July 24, Coinbase Ventures announced that it would support the development of the Bankr platform through the Base Ecosystem Fund. It is reported that Bankr is an intelligent trading agent platform integrated</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948283017960689664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Assists US Authorities in Freezing $1.60 Million USD in Funds Linked to Terrorist FinancingTether announced that it assisted US authorities in freezing and reissuing approximately $1.60M USDT. These funds are related to the Gaza-based company BuyCash and are alleged to be involved in terrorist financing. This action is part of a civil forfeiture case by the US Department of Justice involving approximately $2.00M in digital assets. Tether stated that it has frozen over $2.90B in USDT, cooperating with 275 law enforcement agencies covering 59 jurisdictions, and is committed to continuing to support global law enforcement in combating illegal activities. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282921995014144</link>
      <description>5 minutes ago吴说Tether Assists US Authorities in Freezing $1.60 Million USD in Funds Linked to Terrorist FinancingTether announced that it assisted US authorities in freezing and reissuing approximately $1.60M USDT. These funds are related to the Gaza-based company BuyCash and are alleged to be invol</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282921995014144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Vault is planning to sell the company and is seeking an acquirer.PUNKS Comic and MetaHero Universe publisher Pixel Vault is planning to sell the company and is seeking an acquirer. The team is currently in talks with several institutions interested in acquiring Pixel Vault and its assets and continuing to serve the community. In addition, it is in direct communication with Seedphrase regarding the transition of Wolf Game. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282849605521408</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoForesightNewsPixel Vault is planning to sell the company and is seeking an acquirer.PUNKS Comic and MetaHero Universe publisher Pixel Vault is planning to sell the company and is seeking an acquirer. The team is currently in talks with several institutions interested in acquiring Pixel</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282849605521408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 巨鲸 deposited about $7.00M in HyperLiquid to go long on PEPE, BONK, POPCAT, etc.On July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited about 6,998,000.000 USDC into the HyperLiquid platform and opened or increased long positions in multiple tokens, including: PEPE, BONK, WIF, POPCAT, Trump with 10x leverage, ZK, PUMP with 5x leverage, and LDO, PURR, CHILLGUY with 3x leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282208929779712</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsA 巨鲸 deposited about $7.00M in HyperLiquid to go long on PEPE, BONK, POPCAT, etc.On July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited about 6,998,000.000 USDC into the HyperLiquid platform and opened or increased long positions in multiple tokens, including: PEPE, B</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282208929779712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday and deposited into Bybit.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address yesterday. This address is marked by Solscan as &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2,&quot; i.e., a private placement investor. After receiving the returned funds from Binance yesterday, these 2 billion tokens have been deposited into Bybit, with a value reduced by $6.00M compared to when they were deposited into Binance. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282276646817792</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoOdaily2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday and deposited into Bybit.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address yesterd</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282276646817792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walrus Announces Quilt Bulk Storage Solution, Reshaping How Small Files Are Stored at ScaleOn July 24, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced the release of Quilt, a batch storage solution equipped with an intuitive API that allows developers to conveniently, efficiently, and cost-effectively store and access large numbers of small files, such as NFT series, documents, AI communication data, logs, etc. Instead of storing each file separately, Quilt groups multiple small files into one unit, reducing the overhead and cost of a 100KB blob by approximately 106 times and the overhead and cost of a 10KB blob by approximately 420 times. Using Quilt can also reduce any SUI-denominated Gas fees associated with Walrus storage transactions. Currently, several projects, including Tusky and Gata, have adopted Quilt to optimize their storage architecture. Currently, Quilt has been launched on the Walrus testnet (version 1.29) and will be officially launched with the mainnet version 1.29 on July 30, 2025. It is reported that as a global data infrastructure for on-chain developers, Walrus has carried 800+ TB of encoded data and 14.00 million blobs since its mainnet launch more than three months ago, supporting hundreds of projects built on it. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948280347678019584</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoTechFlowWalrus Announces Quilt Bulk Storage Solution, Reshaping How Small Files Are Stored at ScaleOn July 24, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced the release of Quilt, a batch storage solution equipped with an intuitive API that allows developers to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948280347678019584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Espresso Foundation has completed the snapshot.The blockchain infrastructure Espresso Foundation tweeted that it has completed taking a snapshot. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278173883502592</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoForesightNewsEspresso Foundation has completed the snapshot.The blockchain infrastructure Espresso Foundation tweeted that it has completed taking a snapshot. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278173883502592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic cooperation with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron.According to official sources, Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX recently reached a strategic partnership with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron. Through this collaboration, Safeheron will assist APACX in building a decentralized protocol for stablecoin trading and settlement targeting the Southeast Asian market, constructing a value network for the interconnection and application of multiple stablecoins, especially providing APACX with top-tier security and risk control capabilities. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948279780838805504</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyStablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic cooperation with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron.According to official sources, Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX recently reached a strategic partnership with digital asset self-cus</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948279780838805504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizen Completes Token Migration, ZEN Converted to Base Chain ERC-20 Token, Launches Three-Layer Privacy Application ChainThe Horizen blockchain has migrated its native token ZEN from the original L1 mainnet to the Base chain and converted it to a standard ERC-20 token as part of its Horizen 2.0 three-layer privacy application chain deployment. The total supply of ZEN remains unchanged at 21.00 million. The project team stated that this is the first step in Horizen&apos;s privacy-focused restart of its ecosystem. Previously, Coinbase issued a statement saying that it would automatically complete the conversion of mainnet ZEN to Base chain ERC-20 tokens for users. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948277528602415104</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoChainCatcherHorizen Completes Token Migration, ZEN Converted to Base Chain ERC-20 Token, Launches Three-Layer Privacy Application ChainThe Horizen blockchain has migrated its native token ZEN from the original L1 mainnet to the Base chain and converted it to a standard ERC-20 token as</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948277528602415104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bankers Association Opposes Circle and Others Applying to Establish National Trust Banks in the USRecently, five major US banking associations, including the American Bankers Association, jointly sent a letter to the US Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) opposing the applications of four crypto and stablecoin companies—Circle, Fidelity Digital Assets, Protego Trust, and Ripple—for national trust bank charters. The banking associations stated that although the OCC allows the public to comment on the applications, the application documents of the aforementioned companies have serious disclosure deficiencies, with over 90% of the content being redacted, making it difficult for the public to conduct an effective assessment. [Ledger Insights]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276591079002112</link>
      <description>30 minutes ago吴说American Bankers Association Opposes Circle and Others Applying to Establish National Trust Banks in the USRecently, five major US banking associations, including the American Bankers Association, jointly sent a letter to the US Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) opposin</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276591079002112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A private placement investor missed the best time to sell PUMP due to mistakenly recharging it to Binance, and is expected to lose $6.00 millionOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a PUMP private equity investor &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2&quot; mistakenly recharged 2 billion PUMPs to Binance 8 days ago, when the price of PUMP was $0.0064. Since Binance did not launch PUMP spot trading, the 2 billion PUMPs (worth $6.93 million today) were likely returned to him 23 hours ago. He immediately transferred the 2 billion PUMPs to Bybit after receiving them. This operational error caused him to miss the best time to sell, and if he chose to sell now, he might have lost about $6 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276150249263104</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoPANewsA private placement investor missed the best time to sell PUMP due to mistakenly recharging it to Binance, and is expected to lose $6.00 millionOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a PUMP private equity investor &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2&quot; mistakenly recharged 2 billion PUMPs t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276150249263104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiDeFi index 24hr loss of 10.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDeFi has fallen by 10.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ONDO -12.5%, CAKE -11.54%, LDO -11.01%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948275391981379584</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiDeFi index 24hr loss of 10.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDeFi has fallen by 10.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ONDO -12.5%, CAKE -11.54%, LDO -11.01%.$LDO$CAKE$ONDOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948275391981379584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC Shanghai Headquarters: Actively Explore the Application of Digital Yuan in Offshore Trade SettlementAccording to Jinshi, the Shanghai Headquarters of the People&apos;s Bank of China held a press conference for the third quarter of 2025 on July 24. Shi Jiandong, Deputy Director of the Macro-Prudential Management Department of the Shanghai Headquarters of the People&apos;s Bank of China, stated that the next step for the People&apos;s Bank of China Shanghai Headquarters is to continue to steadily and orderly promote financial reform tasks. First, it will promote comprehensive reform pilots for offshore trade financial services for banks and enterprises with mature conditions, continuously expand the scope of policy benefits, and actively explore the application of digital RMB in offshore trade settlement. Second, based on feedback from public comments, it will revise and improve the &quot;Implementation Measures for Upgrading the Free Trade Account Function in the Shanghai Free Trade Zone&quot; and formally release it to the public after reporting it to the head office of the People&apos;s Bank of China for approval. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273784611475456</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoForesightNewsPBOC Shanghai Headquarters: Actively Explore the Application of Digital Yuan in Offshore Trade SettlementAccording to Jinshi, the Shanghai Headquarters of the People&apos;s Bank of China held a press conference for the third quarter of 2025 on July 24. Shi Jiandong, Deputy Dire</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273784611475456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 63, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 63 (66 &quot;high risk&quot; yesterday), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273099958456320</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsData: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 63, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 63 (66 &quot;high risk&quot; yesterday), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273099958456320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Bull Market Cycle Quick View: When Will This Bull Market End?The market FOMO caused by the RWA narrative may be the profit-taking signal for this cycle.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278589916516352</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsCrypto Bull Market Cycle Quick View: When Will This Bull Market End?The market FOMO caused by the RWA narrative may be the profit-taking signal for this cycle.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278589916516352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant: Bitcoin&apos;s rise is mostly institution-led, with low retail participationCryptoQuant analysts say the current Bitcoin bull run is being led by institutions and large investors, not retail investors. Retail investors have been continuously reducing their holdings since the beginning of 2023, while institutional investors have been actively increasing their holdings since the beginning of 2024. Google Trends data shows that search volume for &quot;Bitcoin&quot; is low, and there is no retail FOMO phenomenon as seen during the 2021 bull market. Analysts believe that the fact that retail investors have not yet entered the market on a large scale means that there is still room for the market to rise, and that when retail investors start to flood in, it may signal that this cycle is nearing its end. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948274728275349504</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoOdailyCryptoQuant: Bitcoin&apos;s rise is mostly institution-led, with low retail participationCryptoQuant analysts say the current Bitcoin bull run is being led by institutions and large investors, not retail investors. Retail investors have been continuously reducing their holdings since</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948274728275349504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Judge Denies Brothers&apos; Motion to Dismiss $25.00M Crypto Fraud ChargesU.S. Judge Jessica Clarke has denied a motion by MIT graduates, the Peraire-Bueno brothers, to dismiss a $25.00M crypto fraud indictment. The two are accused of exploiting a vulnerability in the Ethereum network in May 2024 by deploying 16 validator nodes and 529.5 ETH to execute a four-step &quot;bait-block-search-spread&quot; arbitrage attack, intercepting transaction profits from MEV bots within 12 seconds. The judge ruled that their actions constituted wire fraud, despite the defense&apos;s claim that &quot;system rules allowed it.&quot; The case is set to go to trial in October 2025, and the brothers still face felony charges of wire fraud and conspiracy to commit money laundering. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948269889914998784</link>
      <description>56 minutes ago吴说US Judge Denies Brothers&apos; Motion to Dismiss $25.00M Crypto Fraud ChargesU.S. Judge Jessica Clarke has denied a motion by MIT graduates, the Peraire-Bueno brothers, to dismiss a $25.00M crypto fraud indictment. The two are accused of exploiting a vulnerability in the Ethereum network</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948269889914998784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derlin Holdings: Establishing Virtual Asset OTC and Prime Brokerage Business, Plans to Complete Relevant License Upgrade Before OctoberHong Kong-listed company DL Holdings released a three-stage plan for its digital finance development strategy, including: the first stage is to establish a licensed virtual asset over-the-counter (OTC) and prime brokerage business; it plans to expand the business coverage of Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission licenses 1 (securities trading), 4 (advising on securities) and 9 (asset management) in the virtual asset category within the next 6 months, and expects to complete the regulatory approval process before October; the second stage is a real-world asset (RWA) tokenization and asset management platform, and the third stage is to build a compliant cross-border digital asset fund ecosystem. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948267700727386112</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Derlin Holdings: Establishing Virtual Asset OTC and Prime Brokerage Business, Plans to Complete Relevant License Upgrade Before OctoberHong Kong-listed company DL Holdings released a three-stage plan for its digital finance development strategy, including: the first stage is to establish</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948267700727386112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-Day Correlation Between Bitcoin Volatility Index and S&amp;P 500 VIX Hits All-Time HighOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, data showed that the 90-day correlation coefficient between the Bitcoin 30-day Implied Volatility Index (BVIV/DVOL) and the S&amp;P 500 Volatility Index (VIX) hit a record high of 0.88, indicating that the linkage between the cryptocurrency market and the volatility of US stocks has significantly increased. The current correlation coefficient remains at a high level of 0.75. Analysts pointed out that this phenomenon reflects that Wall Street institutions are dominating this round of crypto market cycle. Markus Thielen, founder of 10x Research, said that institutional investors have compressed volatility by selling a large number of call options, making Bitcoin price movements increasingly affected by the risk appetite of traditional markets. Since the beginning of this year, the BVIV index has dropped from 67% to 42%, while the price of Bitcoin has risen by 26% during the same period, breaking the historical pattern of the two fluctuating in the same direction. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948266788579512320</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANews90-Day Correlation Between Bitcoin Volatility Index and S&amp;P 500 VIX Hits All-Time HighOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, data showed that the 90-day correlation coefficient between the Bitcoin 30-day Implied Volatility Index (BVIV/DVOL) and the S&amp;P 500 Volatility Index (VIX) hit a re</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948266788579512320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PancakeSwap’s Infinity hits Base chain. Will CAKE price follow and hit new highs?PancakeSwap Infinity DEX has just launched on Base, bringing its advanced DeFi features to the Ethereum L2 as PancakeSwap’s CAKE token price tests key resistance, eyeing $4. PancakeSwap’s decentralized exchange, PancakeSwap Infinity, has officially launched on Base, bringing Infinity’s powerful features — including dynamic fee structures via customizable Hooks, dual pool types, and major gas-saving optimizations — to one of the fastest-growing Ethereum Layer 2 ecosystems. The rollout also aligns with PancakeSwap’s broader goal of delivering scalable, low-cost DeFi across chains. The rollout on Base follows closely on the heels of Infinity’s debut on BNB Chain in late April and comes amid a surge in activity on the Base network, which recently hit record highs in both total value locked and DEX volume. It also follows the launch of PancakeSwap’s one-click cross-chain swaps via the Across Protocol, which already supports asset transfers between BNB Chain, Arbitrum, and Base. CAKE price has recently tested the key horizontal resistance in the $2.80–$3.00 range. This level has acted as a significant barrier, having been tested multiple times since early January. This was accompanied by a series of higher lows, forming a well-defined ascending triangle — a bullish continuation pattern that suggests increasing buying pressure at progressively higher levels. Although the price has pulled back from the local peak of $3.00 to $2.65 at the time of writing, CAKE remains technically strong — holding above both the 20-day EMA and the ascending trendline that defines the pattern’s support. Notably, volume also spiked during the recent breakout attempt, signaling growing market interest. This, combined with CAKE’s consistent pattern of higher lows converging toward the key resistance zone, points to mounting bullish pressure that soon culminate in a breakout. A confirmed close above the $3.00 level would validate the ascending triangle breakout, setting the stage for a potential rally toward the $4.00 region, a target derived from the measured move of the triangle’s height. On the downside, the immediate support lies around $2.30, followed by the psychological $2.00 level, which forms the triangle’s base. A breakdown below these levels could invalidate the bullish setup and expose CAKE price to further downside risk toward $1.75 or lower. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948264996252749824</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsPancakeSwap’s Infinity hits Base chain. Will CAKE price follow and hit new highs?PancakeSwap Infinity DEX has just launched on Base, bringing its advanced DeFi features to the Ethereum L2 as PancakeSwap’s CAKE token price tests key resistance, eyeing $4. PancakeSwap’s decentrali</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948264996252749824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>