<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:41:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>FTX&apos;s next round of compensation will be executed on September 30, releasing $1.9 billion in disputed debt reservesOn July 24, according to PR Newswire, FTX announced that the registration date for the next round of compensation will be August 15, and it is expected to be implemented on September 30. This round of compensation is for approved fifth-category customer claims, sixth-category ordinary unsecured claims, and newly approved convenience claims since the last compensation. At the same time, the court approved the reduction of the disputed claims reserve from $6.5 billion to $4.3 billion, releasing $1.9 billion for this round of compensation. The compensation will be executed through three institutions: BitGo, Kraken and Payoneer. Creditors must complete KYC verification, submit tax forms and choose a designated compensation channel before August 15. For the transfer of claims, the procedures must be completed before the registration date and the 21-day objection period must be passed. After the funds arrive at the service provider&apos;s account, they will be managed by the creditor. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948163362155728896</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsFTX&apos;s next round of compensation will be executed on September 30, releasing $1.9 billion in disputed debt reservesOn July 24, according to PR Newswire, FTX announced that the registration date for the next round of compensation will be August 15, and it is expected to be impleme</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948163362155728896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan: $2 trillion stablecoin market forecast is “overly optimistic”On July 24, Bloomberg reported that JPMorgan Chase released a report questioning the $2.00 trillion forecast for the stablecoin market, believing that the figure is &quot;too optimistic.&quot; Analysts pointed out that the current market size of $260.00 billion may only grow by 2-3 times in a few years, far lower than the US Treasury Secretary&apos;s previous expectation of breaking through $2.00 trillion in 2028. The report pointed out that although the GENIUS Act has established a regulatory framework for stablecoins, it will take time to improve the payment infrastructure and ecosystem. Currently, USDT and USDC account for more than 60% of the market share, but stablecoins only account for 1% of global capital flows. Analysts believe that due to investors&apos; conservative attitude towards cash management, it is difficult to use stablecoins as a mainstream liquidity alternative in the short term. JPMorgan Chase emphasized that although stablecoins have the advantage of instant settlement in the field of cross-border payments, merchant acceptance is still higher than that of ordinary consumers. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948161030743461888</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoPANewsJPMorgan: $2 trillion stablecoin market forecast is “overly optimistic”On July 24, Bloomberg reported that JPMorgan Chase released a report questioning the $2.00 trillion forecast for the stablecoin market, believing that the figure is &quot;too optimistic.&quot; Analysts pointed out that</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948161030743461888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether Plans to Re-enter the U.S. Market, Focusing on Institutional Stablecoin BusinessTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated that Tether is planning to return to the U.S. market after U.S. President Donald Trump signed the stablecoin bill, focusing on institutional clients and providing stablecoin products for payments, interbank settlement, and trading. Ardoino emphasized that the company has no intention of going public and will continue to focus on emerging markets and expand its business in the United States. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948159504432041984</link>
      <description>28 minutes ago吴说Tether Plans to Re-enter the U.S. Market, Focusing on Institutional Stablecoin BusinessTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated that Tether is planning to return to the U.S. market after U.S. President Donald Trump signed the stablecoin bill, focusing on institutional clients and providing st</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948159504432041984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme coin startup platform LetsBONK promises to use 1% of its revenue for BONK ecosystem head tokenOn July 24, according to The Block, the Meme coin startup platform LetsBONK announced that it would use 1% of its total revenue to repurchase the top tokens in the BONK ecosystem. This part of the funds will be allocated from the team marketing fund and the repurchase operation will be carried out once a week. Platform data shows that LetsBONK generated about $1.50 million in fees in the past 24 hours, which can provide $15,000.00 in repurchase funds in proportion. In recent weeks, LetsBONK has surpassed its competitor platform Pump.fun in terms of daily trading volume and token issuance. According to the Dune dashboard, the total market value of tokens issued on LetsBONK has recently exceeded $1 billion. Useless Coin is the largest token in the ecosystem, followed by ANI, the token representing the Grok AI companion recently launched by xAI. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948157229596741632</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsMeme coin startup platform LetsBONK promises to use 1% of its revenue for BONK ecosystem head tokenOn July 24, according to The Block, the Meme coin startup platform LetsBONK announced that it would use 1% of its total revenue to repurchase the top tokens in the BONK ecosystem. T</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948157229596741632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House&apos;s first encryption policy report will be released publicly on July 30On July 24, Bo Hines, executive director of the Trump Digital Asset Advisory Committee, stated on the X platform that the Presidential Digital Asset Task Force has completed a 180-day report (the first encryption policy report) and will be publicly released on July 30. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948156608479039488</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoPANewsThe White House&apos;s first encryption policy report will be released publicly on July 30On July 24, Bo Hines, executive director of the Trump Digital Asset Advisory Committee, stated on the X platform that the Presidential Digital Asset Task Force has completed a 180-day report (the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948156608479039488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trialWith the trial of the Tornado Cash co-founder ending its eighth day, a witness testified Roman Storm had control over some of the funds connected to the mixing service.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948144352076828672</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCrypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trialWith the trial of the Tornado Cash co-founder ending its eighth day, a witness testified Roman Storm had control over some of the funds connected to the mixing service.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948144352076828672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Agent Links Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm to Binance Funds and Offshore DealingsFederal prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm moved millions through Binance and coordinated with co-founders to send funds and buy offshore real estate. IRS-CI Special Agent Stephan George told the jury he traced over $533,000.00 in USDT from a Binance account allegedly controlled by Storm. He said the funds were moved on August 9, 2022, and distributed across three wallet addresses. Storm Allegedly Sent $2.6 Million Each to Co-Founders Prosecutors showed chat logs between Tornado Cash’s founding trio: Roman Storm, Roman Semenov, and Alexey Pertsev. In one message, Storm wrote: “I overloaded 8 million yesterday.” Another message stated: “I sent you guys 2.6 million each.” Agent George said these communications indicated Storm had access to the funds and decision-making power over the wallet in question. In a separate message, Storm reportedly told a colleague to: “Give her a task to f **ing open various offshores… and to buy real estate.” Prosecutors also read a message from Semenov stating: “I will send some TORN later, to avoid getting busted.” The prosecution argued these messages revealed intent to obscure transactions and profit from Tornado Cash’s operations. 96% of Tornado Cash Users Relied on Web Interface Earlier in the day, prosecution expert Philip Werlau of AnChain.AI testified that 96.2% of users accessed Tornado Cash through its user interface (UI), not the command line. He said Lazarus Group shifted to CLI usage only after US sanctions were imposed. Werlau said this behavior suggested a deliberate attempt to avoid detection. During cross-examination, Roman Storm’s defense challenged Werlau’s conclusions. He emphasized that Tornado Cash’s smart contract pools became immutable in May 2020, meaning neither Storm nor the DAO could change them. Klein also clarified that Tornado’s UI did not handle transactions directly. Deposits and withdrawals required interacting with Ethereum’s smart contracts, not any centralized interface. Meanwhile, prosecutors presented an email from an earlier witness, Ms. Lin, addressed to Tornado Cash’s public inbox. Judge Failla warned the jury not to treat its content as fact. The email’s inclusion may relate to the defense’s previously stated mistrial concerns, though no motion was filed. What’s Next in the Tornado Cash Trial The prosecution is expected to rest its case tomorrow morning. A separate hearing on the Chainalysis expert testimony is still pending. Storm’s defense is preparing to present its side, focusing on the immutability of Tornado Cash and Storm’s lack of control after deployment. [Wu Shuo]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948140146783752192</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoIRS Agent Links Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm to Binance Funds and Offshore DealingsFederal prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm moved millions through Binance and coordinated with co-founders to send funds and buy offshore real estate. IRS-CI S</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948140146783752192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Trump administration did not deny Trump&apos;s name appearing in Epstein documentsA White House official stated that the Trump administration did not deny that Trump&apos;s name appeared in the (Epstein) documents. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133802961866752</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyWhite House: Trump administration did not deny Trump&apos;s name appearing in Epstein documentsA White House official stated that the Trump administration did not deny that Trump&apos;s name appeared in the (Epstein) documents. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133802961866752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiAI index 24hr loss of 10.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiAI has fallen by 10.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: KAITO -13.08%, AI16Z -12.44%, VIRTUAL -12.18%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132827357732864</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSSI Price BotssiAI index 24hr loss of 10.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiAI has fallen by 10.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: KAITO -13.08%, AI16Z -12.44%, VIRTUAL -12.18%.$VIRTUAL$AI16Z$KAITOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132827357732864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&apos;s Q2 net profit increased by 19%, raising its full-year capital expenditure forecast to $850.00BAlphabet, the parent company of Google (GOOG.O), reported a 19% year-over-year increase in net profit to $28.196B in the second quarter, and a 14% increase in revenue to $96.43B, better than the market&apos;s expected $94.00B. Q2 Google service revenue increased by 12% to $82.5B, of which YouTube advertising revenue was $9.79B; Google Cloud revenue increased by 32% to $13.6B, higher than the expected $13.11B. The company expects capital expenditures to reach $85.00B this year with increased investment in artificial intelligence, compared to earlier estimates of $75.00B this year. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133811400806400</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyGoogle&apos;s Q2 net profit increased by 19%, raising its full-year capital expenditure forecast to $850.00BAlphabet, the parent company of Google (GOOG.O), reported a 19% year-over-year increase in net profit to $28.196B in the second quarter, and a 14% increase in revenue to $96.43B, b</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133811400806400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -10.73%, SXP -7.69%, CRO -5.17%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132635099226112</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSSI Price BotssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -10.73%, SXP -7.69%, CRO -5.17%.$CRO$WOO$SXPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132635099226112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla&apos;s Q2 net profit was $1.172B, a 20.7% year-on-year decrease.Tesla&apos;s second-quarter revenue was $22.50B, a year-on-year decrease of 12%, with an estimated $22.64B. Second-quarter net profit was $1.172B, a year-on-year decrease of 20.7%, with market expectations of $1.136B. Adjusted earnings per share for the second quarter were $0.40, compared to $0.52 in the same period last year, with an estimated $0.42. Second-quarter gross margin was 17.2%, compared to 18% in the same period last year, with an estimated 16.5%. Second-quarter free cash flow (FCF) was $146.00M, compared to $664.00M in the first quarter, with analysts expecting $760.00M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133819839746048</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyTesla&apos;s Q2 net profit was $1.172B, a 20.7% year-on-year decrease.Tesla&apos;s second-quarter revenue was $22.50B, a year-on-year decrease of 12%, with an estimated $22.64B. Second-quarter net profit was $1.172B, a year-on-year decrease of 20.7%, with market expectations of $1.136B. Adjus</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133819839746048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Trump does not support Musk&apos;s artificial intelligence company receiving federal contractsWhite House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said Wednesday that she believes U.S. President Donald Trump does not support federal agencies contracting with Elon Musk&apos;s artificial intelligence company. When asked if Trump wants to cancel recent contracts with Musk&apos;s AI ventures, Jean-Pierre said she would discuss the matter with the president. About a week ago, Musk&apos;s xAI, along with three other major tech companies, was awarded a Department of Defense contract worth up to $200.00M. Trump and Musk have been in a heated feud since Musk resigned as a government special employee at the end of May. Trump said he could retaliate against Musk by canceling federal contracts with Musk&apos;s businesses. (The Hill) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133828282880000</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyWhite House: Trump does not support Musk&apos;s artificial intelligence company receiving federal contractsWhite House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said Wednesday that she believes U.S. President Donald Trump does not support federal agencies contracting with Elon Musk&apos;s artificial</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133828282880000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Florida judge rejects request to unseal Epstein case grand jury recordsOn Wednesday, a federal judge in Florida rejected a request from the Department of Justice to release grand jury records from the Epstein investigation. Attorney General Bondi pushed for the release of the Epstein case&apos;s grand jury materials in an effort to quell the anger of Trump&apos;s MAGA base, who have urged the government to disclose Epstein&apos;s alleged &quot;client list.&quot; Earlier this month, Trump&apos;s Justice Department and the FBI said that no such client list exists, and Bondi said she would not release any further materials. Despite the rejection in Florida, the Justice Department has another opportunity, as they have also asked two federal judges in New York to unseal grand jury transcripts, where prosecutors filed lawsuits against Epstein and his accomplice Ghislaine Maxwell. Federal courts in New York generally take a less strict approach to grand jury secrecy. (Politico) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133836788928512</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyUS Florida judge rejects request to unseal Epstein case grand jury recordsOn Wednesday, a federal judge in Florida rejected a request from the Department of Justice to release grand jury records from the Epstein investigation. Attorney General Bondi pushed for the release of the Eps</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133836788928512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer2 index 24hr loss of 10.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer2 has fallen by 10.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OP -13.43%, TIA -12.98%, MOVE -12.74%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132198665117696</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSSI Price BotssiLayer2 index 24hr loss of 10.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer2 has fallen by 10.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OP -13.43%, TIA -12.98%, MOVE -12.74%.$OP$TIA$MOVEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132198665117696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary: There may be 1 to 2 interest rate cuts this yearUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: There may be 1 to 2 rate cuts this year. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133845253033984</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyUS Treasury Secretary: There may be 1 to 2 interest rate cuts this yearUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: There may be 1 to 2 rate cuts this year. [Odaily]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133845253033984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents.The U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents. (Wall Street Journal) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133853717139456</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyThe U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents.The U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents. (Wall Street Journal) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133853717139456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Decide How to Use $550.00B in Japanese Investment in the U.S.White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt stated that President Trump will decide how to use Japan&apos;s $550.00B investment in the United States himself. She stated that Japan&apos;s investment is part of the US-Japan trade agreement. Leavitt stated that Trump will use the investment for key industries such as energy, semiconductors, critical minerals, pharmaceuticals, and shipbuilding. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133862151884800</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyTrump to Decide How to Use $550.00B in Japanese Investment in the U.S.White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt stated that President Trump will decide how to use Japan&apos;s $550.00B investment in the United States himself. She stated that Japan&apos;s investment is part of the US-Japan</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133862151884800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House Speaker: House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing Epstein case recordsLocal time July 23, it was learned that U.S. House Speaker Mike Johnson said that the House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing records related to the Jeffrey Epstein case, because the Trump administration &quot;has done everything it can to release these records.&quot; It is reported that the Democratic Party is constantly trying to force a vote on the matter, saying that it concerns trust in the government. Republican leaders also released a resolution that has no legal effect, but would urge the Justice Department to provide more documents. (CCTV) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133870590824448</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyUS House Speaker: House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing Epstein case recordsLocal time July 23, it was learned that U.S. House Speaker Mike Johnson said that the House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing records related to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133870590824448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank: Firing Powell wouldn&apos;t save much in debt costsU.S. President Trump last month cited the cost of federal debt as a new reason to urge Powell to cut interest rates. But a new analysis shows that firing the Fed chairman and forcing him to lower interest rates would not help. Deutsche Bank chief U.S. economist Matthew Luzzetti and others wrote that replacing Powell would not change the Treasury&apos;s debt interest costs. Trump has repeatedly called for a 3 percentage point rate cut, saying it would save more than $1 trillion. But according to the Deutsche Bank team&apos;s calculations, while short-term Treasury yields would fall, long-term Treasury yields would rise due to concerns that a more compliant Fed would mean higher inflation. Specifically, if Trump fired Powell, the Treasury would only save $12.00 billion to $15.00 billion by 2027. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133879042347008</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyDeutsche Bank: Firing Powell wouldn&apos;t save much in debt costsU.S. President Trump last month cited the cost of federal debt as a new reason to urge Powell to cut interest rates. But a new analysis shows that firing the Fed chairman and forcing him to lower interest rates would not h</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133879042347008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 23:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>