<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The whale &quot;The White Whale&quot; has profited nearly $30.000.000 from going long on ETH and SOL in the past week.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;The White Whale&quot; has profited nearly $30.000.000 from longing ETH and SOL on HyperLiquid with 4 wallets in the past week. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946961075327950848</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyThe whale &quot;The White Whale&quot; has profited nearly $30.000.000 from going long on ETH and SOL in the past week.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;The White Whale&quot; has profited nearly $30.000.000 from longing ETH and SOL on HyperLiquid with 4 wallets in the past week. [O</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946961075327950848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Treasury Capital CEO: I learned about Bitcoin while studying Chinese in ShanghaiOn July 20, Bitcoin Treasury Capital CEO Christoffer De Geer published an article on the X platform, revealing that he needed to remit money to Sweden when he was studying Chinese in Shanghai in 2013. When he was looking for alternatives, he accidentally learned about Bitcoin. As a Swede in China, he found a 12-year-old Bitcoin miner and began to learn about wallets, keys, UTXO, block browsers, and an anonymous person named Satoshi Nakamoto.
Today, Bitcoin Treasury Capital already holds 156 bitcoins and has reached an equity financing agreement of up to 200 million Swedish kronor with a group of investors. It has also been approved for listing and trading on the Frankfurt Stock Exchange with the stock code X4L. Bitcoin Treasury Capital will continue its Bitcoin financial strategy. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946957202005647360</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoPANewsBitcoin Treasury Capital CEO: I learned about Bitcoin while studying Chinese in ShanghaiOn July 20, Bitcoin Treasury Capital CEO Christoffer De Geer published an article on the X platform, revealing that he needed to remit money to Sweden when he was studying Chinese in Shanghai</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946957202005647360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today&apos;s on-chain fund flow: Polygon PoS saw a net inflow of $22.00 million, while Ethereum saw a net outflow of $31.40 million.On July 20, according to Artemis data, Polygon PoS had a net inflow of $22.00 million today, and Base had a net inflow of $16.40 million; Ethereum had a net outflow of $31.40 million, and Unichain had a net outflow of $11.40 million.

[TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946956789940445184</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoTechFlowToday&apos;s on-chain fund flow: Polygon PoS saw a net inflow of $22.00 million, while Ethereum saw a net outflow of $31.40 million.On July 20, according to Artemis data, Polygon PoS had a net inflow of $22.00 million today, and Base had a net inflow of $16.40 million; Ethereum had</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946956789940445184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British media: London Stock Exchange Group considers launching 24-hour tradingOn July 20, the Financial Times reported that the London Stock Exchange Group is considering whether to launch 24-hour trading. Due to the growing demand from small investors who are active outside normal business hours, exchanges are competing to extend stock trading hours. According to people familiar with the matter, the London Stock Exchange Group is studying the feasibility of extending trading hours, covering the required technology and regulatory impact. One of the people said that the London Stock Exchange &quot;is really considering this matter seriously, whether it is 24-hour trading or extended trading hours,&quot; adding that the exchange group is conducting &quot;important commercial, policy and regulatory discussions&quot; on this &quot;ongoing issue.&quot; Another person familiar with the matter said that this exploration is part of a broad discussion about potential new products and services. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946953085715701760</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoPANewsBritish media: London Stock Exchange Group considers launching 24-hour tradingOn July 20, the Financial Times reported that the London Stock Exchange Group is considering whether to launch 24-hour trading. Due to the growing demand from small investors who are active outside norm</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946953085715701760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding human rights into crypto isn’t optional, it’s foundationalEmbedding human rights into crypto systems is a necessity. Self-custody, privacy-by-default, and censorship-resistant personhood must be core design principles for any technology. The future of digital freedom depends on it.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946948928795533312</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoPANewsEmbedding human rights into crypto isn’t optional, it’s foundationalEmbedding human rights into crypto systems is a necessity. Self-custody, privacy-by-default, and censorship-resistant personhood must be core design principles for any technology. The future of digital freedom de</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946948928795533312</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Commerce Secretary: Powell is Keeping Interest Rates Too HighU.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick said Powell is keeping interest rates too high. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946948489232474112</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyU.S. Commerce Secretary: Powell is Keeping Interest Rates Too HighU.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick said Powell is keeping interest rates too high. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946948489232474112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick: Powell is keeping interest rates too high; August 1 is the deadline for imposing tariffsOn July 20, according to Jinshi, U.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick said that Powell kept interest rates too high. August 1 is the deadline for imposing tariffs. Small countries must pay a 10% base tariff. It is expected that Trump will definitely renegotiate the US-Mexico-Canada Trade Agreement and is confident that he can reach an agreement with the European Union. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946946658745933824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsU.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick: Powell is keeping interest rates too high; August 1 is the deadline for imposing tariffsOn July 20, according to Jinshi, U.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick said that Powell kept interest rates too high. August 1 is the deadline for imposing tariffs. Smal</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946946658745933824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: XRP is now at $3.5386According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is up 5.00% in the past 24h. Now at $3.5386.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946945999023857664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: XRP is now at $3.5386According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is up 5.00% in the past 24h. Now at $3.5386.$XRPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946945999023857664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list ZKWASM (ZKWASM) and launch a HODLer Airdrop with a total prize pool of 250,000 ZKWASMAccording to the official announcement, Gate will launch ZKWASM (ZKWASM) spot trading on July 22 at 20:00 (UTC+8). The 270th phase of the ZKWASM (ZKWASM) HODLer Airdrop event is now open, ending on July 22 at 18:00 (UTC+8). Users holding 1 GT can participate in the free airdrop, with a total prize pool of 250,000 ZKWASM. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946945962722156544</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGate will list ZKWASM (ZKWASM) and launch a HODLer Airdrop with a total prize pool of 250,000 ZKWASMAccording to the official announcement, Gate will launch ZKWASM (ZKWASM) spot trading on July 22 at 20:00 (UTC+8). The 270th phase of the ZKWASM (ZKWASM) HODLer Airdrop event is now op</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946945962722156544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British media says stablecoins are fraught with risks and may provide an opportunity for money launderingOn July 20, according to the Financial Times, US President Trump signed the Stablecoin Regulatory Act on the 18th. This is the first stablecoin legislation in the United States at the federal level. However, the development of stablecoins has hidden risks and how it will reshape the financial ecosystem. The cross-border flow of funds in stablecoins is anonymous, making it difficult for regulators to effectively track the flow of funds and accurately count the scale of funds. This provides opportunities for illegal financial activities such as money laundering, greatly increasing the difficulty of supervision. In countries and regions with weak financial systems, the widespread use of stablecoins will inevitably have a strong impact on the local financial system. Once a stablecoin crisis occurs, it is very easy to trigger a chain of market confidence crises, which in turn leads to the outbreak of bank runs. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946940898590810112</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBritish media says stablecoins are fraught with risks and may provide an opportunity for money launderingOn July 20, according to the Financial Times, US President Trump signed the Stablecoin Regulatory Act on the 18th. This is the first stablecoin legislation in the United States at</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946940898590810112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +5.5%, ADA +5.06%, DOGE +5.03%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932904691982336</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +5.5%, ADA +5.06%, DOGE +5.03%.$ETH$ADA$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932904691982336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US pension fund OPERS increased its holdings of Palantir and MicroStrategy in the second quarterOne of the largest public pension funds in the United States, OPERS (Ohio Public Employees Retirement System), revealed in its 13F filing for the second quarter of 2025 that it increased its holdings in Palantir by 171,441 shares and Strategy by 21,499 shares, while reducing its holdings in Lyft by 58,881 shares. As of June 30, it held a total of 908,712 shares of Palantir, 101,880 shares of Strategy, and 166,628 shares of Lyft. [Barron&apos;s]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932792012005376</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说US pension fund OPERS increased its holdings of Palantir and MicroStrategy in the second quarterOne of the largest public pension funds in the United States, OPERS (Ohio Public Employees Retirement System), revealed in its 13F filing for the second quarter of 2025 that it increased its h</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932792012005376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum stablecoin USDe supply returns to 6 billion after early FebruaryAccording to the @EntropyAdvisors data panel, as the sUSDe APR reached 10%, the supply of Ethereum stablecoin USDe returned to 6 billion after early February. On July 17, the net minting volume of USDe on a single day reached $267.00 million, the third highest single day in history, and the net minting volume exceeded $160.00 million in the following two days. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946931162306797568</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说Ethereum stablecoin USDe supply returns to 6 billion after early FebruaryAccording to the @EntropyAdvisors data panel, as the sUSDe APR reached 10%, the supply of Ethereum stablecoin USDe returned to 6 billion after early February. On July 17, the net minting volume of USDe on a single</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946931162306797568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury Burned 60,000,000 USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, the USDC Treasury destroyed 60,000,000 USDC on the Ethereum chain approximately five minutes ago. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946930867765993472</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyUSDC Treasury Burned 60,000,000 USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, the USDC Treasury destroyed 60,000,000 USDC on the Ethereum chain approximately five minutes ago. [Odaily Planet Daily News]#DeFi$USDC$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946930867765993472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba says he will continue to governLocal time on the 20th, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba expressed his desire to continue governing. Ishiba stated, &quot;We must be clearly aware of the responsibility we bear to the country and the mission of being the largest party in the Diet. I will continue to fulfill my duties.&quot; The latest exit poll results released by Japanese media on the 20th show that the ruling coalition formed by the Liberal Democratic Party and the Komeito Party will find it difficult to maintain a majority of seats in the House of Councillors. According to previous news, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba stated that he would resolve the US tariff issue before the deadline of August 1st. (Golden Ten Data APP) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946928343470268416</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyJapanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba says he will continue to governLocal time on the 20th, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba expressed his desire to continue governing. Ishiba stated, &quot;We must be clearly aware of the responsibility we bear to the country and the mission of b</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946928343470268416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale spent 50.000 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours agoOn July 20, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale spent 50 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours ago, with an average purchase price of US$3,715. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946927948110426112</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsA whale spent 50.000 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours agoOn July 20, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale spent 50 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours ago, with an average purchase price of US$3,715. [PANews]#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSI$USDTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946927948110426112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Hot Project Updates: WLFI token to open for trading, Aave TVL exceeds 50 billion, Ondo Finance announces acceleration of full-stack RWA platform development, etc. (0713–0719)1. World Liberty Financial Community Vote Passes WLFI Token Open Trading Proposal linkWorld Liberty Financial released a proposal on July 9, suggesting opening WLFI token trading. The voting started on July 10 and ended on July 17, and it was finally passed with a 99.94% approval rate. The proposal aims to promote the transition of WLFI from a closed ecosystem to an open ecosystem, allowing tokens to be traded through peer-to-peer and secondary markets, thereby expanding the community&apos;s participation channels in the governance process.2. Aave TVL Exceeds $50 Billion for the First Time in History linkAave TVL exceeded $50 billion for the first time in history, with a growth of 13.93% in the past 7 days, continuing to consolidate its position as the DeFi protocol with the largest TVL. Currently, the overall DeFi TVL reaches $2,843.9 billion, further moving towards the previous high (slightly above $3,000 billion).3. Eclipse Announces Tokenomics: 15% for Airdrops and Liquidity linkEthereum SVM Layer2 network Eclipse announced its tokenomics. The total amount of ES tokens is 1 billion. Among them: 15% is used for airdrops + liquidity; 35% is used for ecosystem + development; 19% is given to contributors (current and future); 31% is given to early supporters/investors. ES tokens can be used as Gas tokens for the Eclipse chain through Eclipse&apos;s native payment mechanism.4. Pudgy Penguins Announces Cooperation with Chinese Toy Company Suplay linkPudgy Penguins announced a cooperation with Chinese toy company Suplay. The specific cooperation content will be announced later. According to public information, Suplay was established at the end of 2019 and is a trendy consumer goods company covering the entire industry chain of IP and channels. It has signed cooperation agreements with IP in various fields such as the Palace Museum Culture, Sanrio, Genshin Impact, and Disney. In early 2021, Suplay received millions of US dollars in Series A financing from Jixiang Capital. In October 2021, it received tens of millions of US dollars in Series A+ financing led by miHoYo.Previously, Alex, the former Binance community leader, announced that he had officially joined Coinbase as the head of crypto Twitter (CT) communication. In the future, he will be committed to promoting more direct, transparent, and interactive communication on social platforms to improve external perception and strengthen connections with the community. At the same time, Coinbase has changed its Twitter avatar to Pengu NFT.5. Kaito AI May Launch Project Launch Platform Capital Launchpad linkKaito AI tweeted, &quot;Capital Launchpad loading…&quot; Kaito official 0xWenMoon said that Capital Launchpad is not a Meme token issuance platform, but a chain-based crypto angel investment platform similar to Echo, which may support investors in participating in early high-potential crypto projects. Since Capital Launchpad is currently in the pre-release stage, the specific details are not yet clear. The community speculates that Capital Launchpad will allow KAITO stakers and top Yappers to participate in private token sales of new projects.6. Sonic Labs Announces Plans to Launch AI Development Platform Spark, Supporting Users to Deploy Web3 Applications with One Click linkSonic Labs announced plans to launch AI development platform Spark, which supports users to build and deploy Web3 applications through natural language without programming knowledge. Users will be able to complete smart contracts, front-end and deployment processes in the browser at one time. Spark is based on the Google Gemini large model and has a built-in risk scoring mechanism and self-debugging agent, which can optimize code in real time and prompt potential security risks before going live. It also has context-aware UI, development teaching and full-stack generation capabilities.7. Ondo Finance Announces Acquisition of Strangelove Labs to Accelerate the Development of its Full-Stack RWA Platform linkOndo Finance announced that it has acquired blockchain infrastructure development team Strangelove Labs to accelerate the development of its full-stack RWA platform. Strangelove has participated in the construction of key technologies such as multi-chain interoperability protocols, SDK frameworks, and customized chain deployment. Its former CEO Jack Zampolin will join Ondo as Vice President of Product.8. Polkadot Founder Gavin Wood Calls for an End to Staking Security Spending linkPolkadot founder Gavin Wood called for an end to the $500 million in annual Staking security spending under the NPoS model at the recent Web3 Summit event, believing that this structure causes capital outflow and incentive misalignment. He proposed short-term reforms including substantial incentive cuts, setting validator fiat salaries, and intermediate fund pool governance allocations. In addition, Gavin also suggested launching a Polkadot native stablecoin and shifting the treasury expenditure structure to this stablecoin settlement.9. Third-Party Layer1 Blockchain Network Tac Announces Mainnet Launch linkThird-party Layer1 blockchain network Tac announced the launch of its mainnet, dedicated to seamlessly connecting EVM DApps to the TON and Telegram ecosystems. The network allows Telegram users to directly use DeFi protocols such as Curve, Morpho, and Euler in the messaging application, while providing developers with a deployment method that does not require rewriting code. Tac has completed a total of $11.50 million in financing, with the latest round led by Hack VC.10. PumpFun Launches Creator Fees Redirection Mechanism to Support Community Takeover of Abandoned Projects linkPumpFun has launched a Creator Fees redirection mechanism that allows qualified community takeover parties (CTOs) to apply to redirect the project creator&apos;s profit-sharing address to the core contributor wallet. It is suitable for projects that are still in the Bonding Curve or have been migrated to PumpSwap, while projects that have been migrated to Raydium are not eligible. [World Liberty Financial]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946922383435034624</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说Weekly Hot Project Updates: WLFI token to open for trading, Aave TVL exceeds 50 billion, Ondo Finance announces acceleration of full-stack RWA platform development, etc. (0713–0719)1. World Liberty Financial Community Vote Passes WLFI Token Open Trading Proposal linkWorld Liberty Financ</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946922383435034624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Every 10,000 BTC increase in ETF holdings could push the average price up by 1.8%, potentially reaching $150,000 in OctoberA report released by research firm Cooper Research points out that the rise in Bitcoin prices seems inevitable as investors pour large amounts of capital into Bitcoin exchange-traded funds. Data shows that for every 10,000 BTC increase in ETF holdings, the price of Bitcoin can increase by an average of 1.8%. Analysts point out that, based on a series of data indicators, Bitcoin seems ready to rise sharply again. The leverage-driven market frenzy is gradually subsiding, and the price trend of Bitcoin may take a more moderate path, and is expected to reach $140,000 in September, and may rise to $150,000 as early as the beginning of October. (Decrypt) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946918284903772160</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyAnalysis: Every 10,000 BTC increase in ETF holdings could push the average price up by 1.8%, potentially reaching $150,000 in OctoberA report released by research firm Cooper Research points out that the rise in Bitcoin prices seems inevitable as investors pour large amounts of capi</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946918284903772160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>decrypt</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780.According to the official zorateam panel, possibly benefiting from the launch of Base APP, on July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780, of which 6,371 were new creators, both hitting all-time highs. A total of 20,732 tokens were created that day, with a trading volume of $12.45 million. At the same time, Zora Coins captured $229,000.00 in revenue that day, setting a new single-day record, with $120,600.00 allocated to creators, $72,600.00 in revenue captured by the protocol, and $36,000.00 in referral rewards. It is worth mentioning that the number of tokens launched through Zora Coins on July 17 exceeded Pumpfun for the first time in history. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946917862696742912</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说On July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780.According to the official zorateam panel, possibly benefiting from the launch of Base APP, on July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780, of which 6,371 were new creators, both hitting all-time highs. A total of 2</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946917862696742912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple regions warn of the risk of illegal fundraising through virtual currenciesRecently, the collapse of the &quot;Xinkangjia&quot; Ponzi scheme, which claimed &quot;2% daily interest&quot; and involved tens of billions of funds, has aroused widespread social concern and vigilance regarding new types of online fraud. Regulators have been issuing frequent warnings. According to incomplete statistics, since July, financial regulatory authorities in various regions, including Guangdong, Yunnan, Hunan, Liaoning, Heilongjiang, Zhejiang, and Fujian, have issued intensive warnings about the risks of illegal fundraising and new types of online fraud in the name of &quot;virtual currency&quot; (Yicai). [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946915773350342656</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyMultiple regions warn of the risk of illegal fundraising through virtual currenciesRecently, the collapse of the &quot;Xinkangjia&quot; Ponzi scheme, which claimed &quot;2% daily interest&quot; and involved tens of billions of funds, has aroused widespread social concern and vigilance regarding new typ</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946915773350342656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</link>
      <description>Updated  12 hours agoJul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜So</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 03:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>