<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Men accused in New York crypto torture case out on bail</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948351001290936320</link>
      <description>11:52Men accused in New York crypto torture case out on bail</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948351001290936320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men accused in New York crypto torture case out on bailThe suspects allegedly held the Italian man hostage for weeks in a Manhattan townhouse, beating him and demanding access to his Bitcoin wallet.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948351211018719232</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoPANewsMen accused in New York crypto torture case out on bailThe suspects allegedly held the Italian man hostage for weeks in a Manhattan townhouse, beating him and demanding access to his Bitcoin wallet.#Bitcoin$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948351211018719232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGBX is listed on D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT, and M/USDTOfficial news, MGBX was listed on July 24, 2025 for D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT and M/USDT.
Deposit opening time: July 24, 2025 19:00 (SGT)
Trading opening time: July 24, 2025 19:30 (SGT) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350228704333824</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoOdailyMGBX is listed on D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT, and M/USDTOfficial news, MGBX was listed on July 24, 2025 for D/USDT, F/USDT, G/USDT, H/USDT and M/USDT.
Deposit opening time: July 24, 2025 19:00 (SGT)
Trading opening time: July 24, 2025 19:30 (SGT) [Odaily News]$D$G$HShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350228704333824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XT Exchange Lists CTA (Cross The Ages)XT will list CTA (Cross The Ages) and open the CTA/USDT trading pair in the Innovation Zone (GameFi). Details are as follows:
Deposit Time: July 23, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Trading Time: July 24, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Withdrawal Time: July 25, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Cross The Ages (CTA) is a comprehensive intellectual property (IP) covering various media and entertainment formats. It aims to attract player communities by integrating the rich experiences of Web2 and Web3 ecosystems. CTA&apos;s product line includes: video games, books, movies/episodes, collectible models, peripheral merchandise, and derivatives. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350237160050688</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoOdailyXT Exchange Lists CTA (Cross The Ages)XT will list CTA (Cross The Ages) and open the CTA/USDT trading pair in the Innovation Zone (GameFi). Details are as follows:
Deposit Time: July 23, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Trading Time: July 24, 2025, 17:00 (UTC+8)
Withdrawal Time: July 25, 2025</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948350237160050688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Whale that has been dormant for 14.5 years and holds nearly 4,000 BTC&quot; transfers all BTC to a new walletArkham data shows that a &quot;whale holding nearly 4,000 BTC dormant for 14.5 years&quot; has just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (approximately $469.00M) it held to a new wallet address (bc1qczar85zjppfjr8df8qnc4l3h5r957v6p2udryz) [Odaily].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347693763465216</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoOdaily&quot;Whale that has been dormant for 14.5 years and holds nearly 4,000 BTC&quot; transfers all BTC to a new walletArkham data shows that a &quot;whale holding nearly 4,000 BTC dormant for 14.5 years&quot; has just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (approximately $469.00M) it held to a new wallet address</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347693763465216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin OG just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC to a new walletOn July 24, on-chain data showed that Bitcoin OG, which had been dormant for 14.5 years, had just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (about US$469.00 million) it held to a new wallet address (bc1qczar85zjppfjr8df8qnc4l3h5r957v6p2udryz). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948346531815428096</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoPANewsBitcoin OG just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC to a new walletOn July 24, on-chain data showed that Bitcoin OG, which had been dormant for 14.5 years, had just transferred all 3,962.62 BTC (about US$469.00 million) it held to a new wallet address (bc1qczar85zjppfjr8df8qnc4l3h5r957v</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948346531815428096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything Blockchain: Advancing the Construction of a Meme Coin Treasury and Launching MemeStrategy S-1 RegistrationUS-listed company Everything Blockchain has announced that the MemeStrategy spin-off has entered the next stage, with the company officially launching the S-1 registration process with the US Securities and Exchange Commission for MemeStrategy, with the aim of preparing for a subsequent Nasdaq listing through financing or strategic acquisitions. In addition, MemeStrategy will also advance its Meme coin acquisition strategy, including PEPE, BONK and SPX6900, to build the first Meme coin treasury of a US-listed company. (Globe newswire) Previous news, Everything Blockchain also announced plans to invest $10.00M in Solana (SOL), XRP, Sui (SUI), Bittensor (TAO) and Hyperliquid (HYPE) to create a multi-token staking vault for institutional adoption trends. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347702202404864</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyEverything Blockchain: Advancing the Construction of a Meme Coin Treasury and Launching MemeStrategy S-1 RegistrationUS-listed company Everything Blockchain has announced that the MemeStrategy spin-off has entered the next stage, with the company officially launching the S-1 regi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948347702202404864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient BTC addresses activated today transferred 3,962.6 BTC to new addressesOn July 24, according to on-chain analyst Ember (@EmberCN)&apos;s monitoring, the ancient BTC address activated today transferred all 3,962.6 BTC in its address to a new address after conducting a small test transfer. The transferred assets are worth approximately $469.00 million. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948344843217997824</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoTechFlowAncient BTC addresses activated today transferred 3,962.6 BTC to new addressesOn July 24, according to on-chain analyst Ember (@EmberCN)&apos;s monitoring, the ancient BTC address activated today transferred all 3,962.6 BTC in its address to a new address after conducting a small te</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948344843217997824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Evening News1. Hong Kong Monetary Authority: It is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the public from August 1;
2. American Bankers Association opposes Circle&apos;s application to establish a national trust bank in the United States;
3. European investment app Lightyear completes $23.00M in financing, led by NordicNinja;
4. Deren Holdings: Establishes virtual asset OTC and prime brokerage business, plans to complete relevant license upgrade before October;
5. EU approves tariff retaliation plan against the US totaling €93.00B;
6. Elympics has opened the ELP token airdrop eligibility query page;
7. Lido&apos;s market share in the Ethereum staking market has fallen to 25.00%, the lowest since March 2022;
8. On-chain detective ZachXBT: Some projects run Yaps campaigns to attract low-quality users and AI-generated content, which will only dilute brand value.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948345193345912832</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyPlanet Evening News1. Hong Kong Monetary Authority: It is illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoins to the public from August 1;
2. American Bankers Association opposes Circle&apos;s application to establish a national trust bank in the United States;
3. European investment app Li</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948345193345912832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reiz Digital Approved HK$80.00M to Develop Web3 Business and Invest in Cryptocurrency AssetsHong Kong-listed company Ruihe Digital Technology Holding Co., Ltd. (3680.HK) has announced its strategic entry into the Web3 and cryptocurrency asset field. The board of directors has approved a budget of up to HK$80,000,000.00 for business expansion and asset allocation in related fields over the next two years. The company stated that this move is aimed at responding to Hong Kong&apos;s policy support for the development of the digital asset industry, and the initial plan will focus on compliant digital currencies, real-world asset (RWA) projects, and related asset management products. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948344255780556800</link>
      <description>30 minutes ago吴说Reiz Digital Approved HK$80.00M to Develop Web3 Business and Invest in Cryptocurrency AssetsHong Kong-listed company Ruihe Digital Technology Holding Co., Ltd. (3680.HK) has announced its strategic entry into the Web3 and cryptocurrency asset field. The board of directors has approve</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948344255780556800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient BTC whale that woke up today transferred $468.00M worth of Bitcoin to a new addressAccording to Whale Alert data, an ancient whale that had been dormant for 14.5 years and just woke up today transferred 3,962 BTC ($468.00M) to an address starting with bc1qc after a test transaction. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948343714992164864</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoForesightNewsAncient BTC whale that woke up today transferred $468.00M worth of Bitcoin to a new addressAccording to Whale Alert data, an ancient whale that had been dormant for 14.5 years and just woke up today transferred 3,962 BTC ($468.00M) to an address starting with bc1qc after a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948343714992164864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$25.2965 millionOn July 24, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$25.2965 million. Among them: The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$5.6603 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$10.0176 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$800,700.00, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$2,024,500.00; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$2.3861 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$4.4072 million. Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948342558664495104</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$25.2965 millionOn July 24, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$25.2965 million. Among them: The tran</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948342558664495104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlockSec: Unverified contract on BSC was attacked, resulting in a loss of over $600,000.00According to BlockSec monitoring, a malicious transaction targeting an unverified contract on Binance Smart Chain (BSC) was discovered, resulting in losses exceeding $600,000.00. As the contract is not open source, our investigation indicates that the root cause is a lack of slippage protection. This vulnerability allowed the attacker to exploit the contract, using a fake liquidity pool to obtain TA tokens, and then selling these tokens in a legitimate pool for profit. It is recommended that users who have granted approval to this contract immediately revoke these permissions to prevent further losses. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948340787892260864</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoForesightNewsBlockSec: Unverified contract on BSC was attacked, resulting in a loss of over $600,000.00According to BlockSec monitoring, a malicious transaction targeting an unverified contract on Binance Smart Chain (BSC) was discovered, resulting in losses exceeding $600,000.00. As t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948340787892260864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US court restarts trademark lawsuit related to Yuga Labs, rules BAYC NFT is a protectable trademarkA U.S. court has reinstated Yuga Labs&apos; trademark lawsuit against conceptual artist Ryder Ripps and developer Jeremy Cahen. The court ruled that a jury must decide whether the duo&apos;s parody NFT series misled consumers. Yuga Labs co-founder Greg Solano said that the court found in this appeal that Yuga&apos;s BAYC NFTs are protectable trademarks and not purely a scam, and also confirmed that NFTs can be protected as &quot;goods&quot; under the Lanham Act, rejecting arguments that NFTs are too intangible to qualify for trademark protection under U.S. law. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948339027387682816</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoForesightNewsUS court restarts trademark lawsuit related to Yuga Labs, rules BAYC NFT is a protectable trademarkA U.S. court has reinstated Yuga Labs&apos; trademark lawsuit against conceptual artist Ryder Ripps and developer Jeremy Cahen. The court ruled that a jury must decide whether the</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948339027387682816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto hacks surpass $3.1B in 2025 as access flaws persist: HackenOver $3.1 billion in crypto has been lost in 2025, according to a Hacken report. Access-control exploits are the primary cause.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948338531335737344</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoPANewsCrypto hacks surpass $3.1B in 2025 as access flaws persist: HackenOver $3.1 billion in crypto has been lost in 2025, according to a Hacken report. Access-control exploits are the primary cause.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948338531335737344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin brand refresh, airdrop of 1,000 Labubu to launch a global creative solicitation, igniting the summer shanzhai season.On July 24th, the global crypto asset trading platform Hotcoin announced the renewal of its official website and launched the &quot;Trading Cute Friends&quot; global creative doll clothing solicitation event in collaboration with the well-known trendy toy IP Labubu. From now until July 31st, users can go to the official Twitter account (@hotcoinzh) to receive the new brand logo integrated into Labubu&apos;s creative doll clothing, and have the opportunity to share 1,000 sets of customized physical dolls. The final winning work selected by popular vote will be officially adopted and mass-produced, and the creator will also have the opportunity to receive $ETH in prize money. This brand upgrade and cross-border linkage marks Hotcoin&apos;s focus on creating a younger crypto new ecosystem, and welcoming the hot altcoin season together with community users. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337575722291200</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin brand refresh, airdrop of 1,000 Labubu to launch a global creative solicitation, igniting the summer shanzhai season.On July 24th, the global crypto asset trading platform Hotcoin announced the renewal of its official website and launched the &quot;Trading Cute Friends&quot; glob</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337575722291200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotion from AugustOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, Hong Kong will begin to implement the Stablecoin Ordinance on August 1, 2025, prohibiting the provision or promotion of unlicensed fiat-backed stablecoins (FRS) to retail investors. Violators may be fined up to HK$50,000.00 and imprisoned for six months. The Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) issued a warning on Wednesday, reminding investors to stay away from unlicensed stablecoins to avoid accidentally violating the law. HKMA President Yu Weiwen said that the new regulations are aimed at bringing credibility and stability to the stablecoin industry while protecting investors from fraud and excessive speculation. Although there are currently as many as 50 companies applying for stablecoin licenses, most applications lack practical implementation plans and only a few licenses will be approved. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337439373856768</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong to criminalize unlicensed stablecoin promotion from AugustOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, Hong Kong will begin to implement the Stablecoin Ordinance on August 1, 2025, prohibiting the provision or promotion of unlicensed fiat-backed stablecoins (FRS) to retail i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337439373856768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale cleared out its last 100 Bitcoin, netting a total profit of approximately $12.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;1EGQSh&quot; address deposited its remaining 100 BTC (approximately $11.88M) into Binance an hour ago, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M (+65%). [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337631573643264</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoOdailyA whale cleared out its last 100 Bitcoin, netting a total profit of approximately $12.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;1EGQSh&quot; address deposited its remaining 100 BTC (approximately $11.88M) into Binance an hour ago, with a total profit of approximately $12.00M</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337631573643264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank will be the first to launch Ponzimon (PONZI)According to official news on July 24, LBank will launch Ponzimon (PONZI) for the first time on July 24, 2025, at 18:30 (SGT), and open the PONZI/USDT trading pair. The deposit service will be opened on July 24 at 18:30 (SGT), and the withdrawal service will be opened on July 25 at 19:00 (SGT). [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337401834835968</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoTechFlowLBank will be the first to launch Ponzimon (PONZI)According to official news on July 24, LBank will launch Ponzimon (PONZI) for the first time on July 24, 2025, at 18:30 (SGT), and open the PONZI/USDT trading pair. The deposit service will be opened on July 24 at 18:30 (SGT), a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948337401834835968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building crypto vaults with Veda co-founder Sun RaghupathiEpisode 35 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and Veda co-founder and CEO Sun Raghupathi.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or wherever you listen to podcasts. Please send feedback and revision requests to[emailprotected]

Tim and Sun discussed how DeFi vaults are simplifying complex finance systems and looking to drive mainstream and institutional adoption. Sun explained on Veda&apos;s Vault architecture, the importance of security, and the evolving competitive landscape in the DeFi space.

OUTLINE
00:00 – Introduction 
00:25 – What is Veda? 
03:31 – Potential Contagion Risks 
04:30 – GMX Hack 
05:39 – DeFi Hacks 
08:16 – Challenges of Building Vaults 
09:48 – DeFi&apos;s Evolution 
15:23 – Institutional Involvement 
16:58 – Vault Uses in TradFi 
17:47 – Tokenized Stocks 
20:44 – Vaults vs. Staking 
22:48 – Types of Vault Strategies 
24:39 – AI in Vault Management 
25:47 – Veda’s Future Plans 
26:37 – Conclusion

The Block Newsletters
The Block&apos;s newsletters bring you the latest news and analysis of the fast-moving crypto and DeFi markets. To subscribe, visit theblock.co/newsletters

Guest links:
Sun - ⁠⁠https://x.com/sunandr_⁠ 
Veda - ⁠⁠⁠https://x.com/veda_labs⁠

Are you hiring in crypto?
Use Campus to quickly find your best candidates with our challenging Crypto Assessment Test.
Faster hiring, stronger teams.

Sign up for a trial today:theblock.co/campus

[The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336925928132608</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockBuilding crypto vaults with Veda co-founder Sun RaghupathiEpisode 35 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and Veda co-founder and CEO Sun Raghupathi.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or where</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336925928132608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Wallet launches BNB and XRP incentive activities to support the use of on-chain assetsOn July 24, according to an official announcement, Gate Wallet hit a new high around the price of BNB and officially launched two online incentive activities covering the two major assets of BNB and XRP.
During the event, new users who complete their first BNB transaction in their wallet (amount ≥ $100) can receive a maximum $10.00 airdrop, limited to the first 1,000 participants. All users who top up BNB can also share a $10,000.00 prize pool based on their top-up ratio, with a maximum single-person reward of $100.00.
In the XRP incentive activity, users who deposit no less than 10 XRP can participate in the $5,000.00 airdrop; those who complete XRP transactions (amount ≥ $50.00) can also participate in the $20,000.00 prize pool. The rewards are distributed according to the transaction ratio, and a single person can get up to $200.00. The activity ends on August 10.
Gate Wallet is the industry-leading multi-chain crypto wallet, connecting 100+ public chains, millions of assets and tens of thousands of DApps in one stop, opening up a professional-level Web3 experience and providing the best solution for every Web3 need. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336439938322432</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsGate Wallet launches BNB and XRP incentive activities to support the use of on-chain assetsOn July 24, according to an official announcement, Gate Wallet hit a new high around the price of BNB and officially launched two online incentive activities covering the two major assets of BN</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948336439938322432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>