<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:18:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Giants Protocol Receives Strategic Investment from Plug and Play and Other Institutions, Fully Accelerating DeFAI Ecosystem LayoutAccording to official sources, Giants Protocol has officially secured strategic investments from several leading institutions and venture capital firms. Investors include Plug and Play VC, LucidBlue Ventures, Trinity Ventures, London Real Ventures, Brinc, Digital Consensus Fund, CSP DAO, PG Capital, BreederDAO, TAP, and Eden Ventures. In addition to funding, the investment institutions will inject global resources, strategic guidance, and a long-term vision into Giants Protocol, providing a strong impetus for the project&apos;s development in the deep integration of DeFi and AI (DeFAI). [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947298281659060224</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyGiants Protocol Receives Strategic Investment from Plug and Play and Other Institutions, Fully Accelerating DeFAI Ecosystem LayoutAccording to official sources, Giants Protocol has officially secured strategic investments from several leading institutions and venture capital firm</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947298281659060224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wu Blockchain Daily Selected Crypto News + This Week&apos;s Macro Indicators1. High-Value Token Unlocks This WeekSingle large unlocks (unlock amount greater than $5.00M) in the next 7 days include AVAIL, VENOM, ALT, SAHARA, SOON, etc.; Linear large unlocks (single-day unlock amount greater than $1.00M) in the next 7 days include SOL, WLD, TRUMP, TIA, DOGE, TAO, AVAX, SUI, DOT, IP, MORPHO, SEI, ETHFI, JTO, NEAR, ENS, FIL, etc., with a total unlock value of over $442.00M.2. Trump Media Group Announces Its Bitcoin Holdings Have Reached Approximately $2.00BTrump Media Group announced that its Bitcoin holdings have reached approximately $2.00B, accounting for two-thirds of the company&apos;s approximately $3.00B in liquid assets. This strategy is supported by $3.00B in liquid funds, with an additional $300.00M used for Bitcoin-related options operations, which may be converted into spot Bitcoin in the future.3. Strategy Increases Bitcoin Holdings by 6,220 BTC, Total Holdings at 607,770 BTCStrategy announced the purchase of 6,220 Bitcoins between July 14 and July 20, at an average price of $118,940.00, for a total cost of $739.80M. As of July 20, 2025, Strategy holds 607,770 BTC, with a total cost of $43.61B and an average price of $71,756.00.4. US Pension Fund OPERS Increases Holdings in Palantir and Strategy in Q2According to the 13F filings submitted by OPERS (Ohio Public Employees Retirement System), one of the largest public pension funds in the United States, in the second quarter of 2025, it increased its holdings in Palantir by 171,441 shares and Strategy by 21,499 shares, while reducing its holdings in Lyft by 58,881 shares. As of June 30, it held a total of 908,712 shares of Palantir, 101,880 shares of Strategy, and 166,628 shares of Lyft.5. QCP: ETH Derivatives Surge, Altcoin Season May Have BegunQCP noted that ETH perpetual contract open interest surged to $28.00B in a week, with ETH ETFs seeing inflows exceeding BTC for two consecutive days, and the market expects the approval of staked spot ETFs. Driven by the GENIUS Act, institutions are reallocating to mainstream L1s such as ETH and custodial stablecoins. ETH&apos;s market share has risen to 11.6%, while BTC dominance has fallen to 60.00%, and bullish bets have also appeared in the options market, indicating signs of an altcoin season.6. WSJ: Dynamix Plans to Merge with Another Entity to Form The Ether Machine, Holding Over $1.50B in EthereumShell company Dynamix is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company called &quot;The Ether Machine,&quot; which plans to hold over $1.50B in Ethereum. The project is chaired by former ConsenSys executive Andrew Keys. Sources say the deal is still in progress and has not been finalized.7. Wu Blockchain&apos;s Macro Indicators and Analysis This Week: Powell&apos;s Speech, ECB Interest Rate DecisionAbstractLast week, the US June inflation data CPI was 2.7%, PPI was 2.3%. The Federal Reserve&apos;s latest Beige Book showed that the overall outlook was neutral to slightly pessimistic, with only a few regions expecting economic activity to grow. There are fewer important data indicators this week, and attention can be paid to Powell&apos;s speech at the regulatory meeting and the ECB&apos;s interest rate decision.Last Week&apos;s ReviewThe US June unadjusted CPI annual rate was 2.7%, expected 2.7%, previous value 2.40%, the highest since February.The US June PPI annual rate was 2.3%, the lowest since September 2024, expected 2.5%, previous value revised from 2.60% to 2.7%.The Federal Reserve&apos;s latest Beige Book shows that from the end of May to the beginning of July, US economic activity grew slightly, employment increased slightly, wages continued to rise moderately, and manufacturing layoffs increased slightly, but overall layoffs were still limited. All regions generally face rising raw material and insurance costs driven by tariffs, and some companies have passed some of the costs on to consumers, which may increase the risk of rising inflation in the coming months. The overall outlook is neutral to slightly pessimistic, with only a few regions expecting economic activity to grow.The number of initial jobless claims in the United States for the week ending July 12 was 221,000, expected 235,000, and the previous value was revised from 227,000 to 228,000.The US Michigan Consumer Confidence Index in July rose to 61.8, a five-month high, but still 16% lower than the end of last year. The annual inflation expectation fell from 5.0% to 4.4%, the lowest this year, and the long-term inflation expectation fell to 3.6%. The survey shows that consumer confidence is still affected by inflation concerns and policy uncertainty.US President Donald Trump announced that the United States will provide Ukraine with &quot;the most advanced weapons&quot; through NATO countries, while threatening Russia that if an agreement to end the war is not reached within 50 days, severe tariffs will be imposed on Russia.Key Events &amp; Indicators This WeekJuly 22Federal Reserve Chairman Powell delivers a welcome speech at a regulatory conference (20:30)Reserve Bank of Australia releases minutes of July monetary policy meeting (09:30)July 23US President Donald Trump delivers a speech at an event called &quot;Winning the AI Race&quot;July 24ECB announces interest rate decision (20:15)US initial jobless claims for the week ending July 19 (10,000s) (20:30)French, German, and Eurozone July Manufacturing PMI Preliminary Values [吴说]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947297361156132864</link>
      <description>11 minutes ago吴说Wu Blockchain Daily Selected Crypto News + This Week&apos;s Macro Indicators1. High-Value Token Unlocks This WeekSingle large unlocks (unlock amount greater than $5.00M) in the next 7 days include AVAIL, VENOM, ALT, SAHARA, SOON, etc.; Linear large unlocks (single-day unlock amount greate</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947297361156132864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto custodian BitGo joins Grayscale in confidentially filing IPO documents with SECCrypto‑custody veteran BitGo Holdings has confidentially filed a draft registration statement with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for a planned initial public offering of its Class A shares, the company said on Monday, teeing up what could become another massive U.S. crypto listings after stablecoin issuer Circle listed on the New York Stock Exchange in June.

Filing IPO documents confidentially with the SEC allows firms like BitGo to keep financial specifics private while working on the offering.

The move comes amid a thaw in capital markets for digital asset operators under President Donald Trump&apos;s pro-crypto administration. Asset‑manager Grayscale Investments also submitted confidential IPO paperwork last week. Peter Thiel-backed crypto exchange Bullish filed for an IPO shortly after Circle shares went live on the NYSE in early June.

Circle&apos;s IPO last month was massively successful, as the firm debuted on the NYSE at $31 per share and has risen to over $223, a 619% increase in less than a quarter, which values the company behind USDC at more than $55 billion, according to The Block&apos;s data. Furthermore, the IPO pipeline may soon expand to include other heavyweights like Kraken, Gemini, Ledger, DCG, and Ledger, to name a few, The Block&apos;s Yogita Khatri reported in last week’s The Funding newsletter.

BitGo&apos;s listing attempt marks a comeback after Mike Novogratz&apos;s Galaxy Digital scrapped a $1.2 billion deal to acquire the firm in 2022, a break‑up that led to years of litigation and forced BitGo to remain private while rivals such as Coinbase expanded.

Founded in 2013 and best known for safeguarding digital assets for exchanges, funds, and corporates, BitGo did not disclose the size of the offering or proposed price range. The company&apos;s platform reportedly has over $100 billion in assets under custody and supports more than 1,200 crypto tokens, according to its website. It also counts clients such as Nike’s RTFKT Studios, Pantera Capital, and dozens of spot‑ETF issuers.

The IPO will proceed &quot;after the SEC completes its review process, subject to market and other conditions,&quot; the company said.
[]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947298180882518016</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoThe BlockCrypto custodian BitGo joins Grayscale in confidentially filing IPO documents with SECCrypto‑custody veteran BitGo Holdings has confidentially filed a draft registration statement with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for a planned initial public offering of its Cla</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947298180882518016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jito Launches Block Assembly Market Aimed at Limiting Negative MEVJito has launched a block assembly market designed to limit negative MEV, make Solana suitable for perpetual contract trading, and allow applications to share revenue with token holders. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296818920706048</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoForesightNewsJito Launches Block Assembly Market Aimed at Limiting Negative MEVJito has launched a block assembly market designed to limit negative MEV, make Solana suitable for perpetual contract trading, and allow applications to share revenue with token holders. [Foresight News]#Lay</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296818920706048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TON narrowly avoids blockchain crash: ‘Security remains highest priority’TON blockchain security firm TonBit announced that it averted a major vulnerability on the TON Virtual Machine. TON blockchain (TON) averted a total crash after discovering a major bug. On Monday, July 21, TonBit announced that it identified a critical vulnerability in the TON Virtual Machine. According to TonBit, the bug could have led to denial-of-service attacks across the network, bringing its infrastructure down. The bug in the INMSGPARAM instruction for the TVM included a null-pointer dereference that could have been used to inject false message parameters. Attackers could exploit this behavior to crash the virtual machine at runtime. In the case of such an exploit, the network would halt its execution of smart contracts and disrupt dApps operating on TON. This would significantly affect the large miniapp ecosystem on Telegram, many of which rely on TON for their infrastructure. TonBit discovered the vulnerability ahead of the rollout of Global Version 11. This enabled maintainers to quietly integrate the fix before the mainnet deployment of the update. For its efforts, TonBit earned a bug bounty from the TON Core development team. This was the third time that the security firm obtained a similar reward, with formal recognition from the TON team. In both cases, the team delivered patches before bad actors were aware of the vulnerabilities. “Ensuring the security and robustness of the TON ecosystem remains our highest priority,” said Paul Li, Co-founder of TonBit. “By continuously probing the deepest layers of TVM and working hand‑in‑hand with the TON Core team, we not only protect users today but also build the foundation of trust necessary for tomorrow’s decentralized applications.” Owned by BitsLab, TonBit is a security firm focusing on the TON ecosystem. The firm is a primary security assurance provider for the network, and specializes in comprehensive audits for TON-based projects.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296570647269376</link>
      <description>14 minutes agocrypto.newsTON narrowly avoids blockchain crash: ‘Security remains highest priority’TON blockchain security firm TonBit announced that it averted a major vulnerability on the TON Virtual Machine. TON blockchain (TON) averted a total crash after discovering a major bug. On Monday, July</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296570647269376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User mistakenly enters a phishing website while searching for Aave, leading to the theft of $1.23M in assets due to LP NFT authorization.According to SlowMist&apos;s Yu Xian, a user mistakenly clicked on a phishing link while searching for Aave on Google, authorizing their Uniswap LP NFT to a malicious contract, and subsequently had approximately $1.23M in assets stolen (including 491,239.00 USDe and 744,997.00 USDT). The attacker used Uniswap&apos;s multicall mechanism to complete the authorization and transfer operations. Users are reminded not to access DeFi protocols through search engines and should verify the official website link. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296633750573056</link>
      <description>15 minutes ago吴说User mistakenly enters a phishing website while searching for Aave, leading to the theft of $1.23M in assets due to LP NFT authorization.According to SlowMist&apos;s Yu Xian, a user mistakenly clicked on a phishing link while searching for Aave on Google, authorizing their Uniswap LP NFT</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296633750573056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram founder: Black market speculation of rare usernames, digital IDs, etc. creates extortion risksOn July 21, Telegram founder Pavel Durov had just posted on his channel that the price of rare usernames, digital IDs and gifts had soared to over $100,000.00, attracting criminals to extort user assets through blackmail and threats. Some channels even charged for deleting posts after defamation as a means of profit. He stressed that such behavior was &quot;illegal and immoral&quot; and Telegram would resolutely remove such perpetrators, and called on victims to send private messages to report and provide evidence. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296095134830592</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsTelegram founder: Black market speculation of rare usernames, digital IDs, etc. creates extortion risksOn July 21, Telegram founder Pavel Durov had just posted on his channel that the price of rare usernames, digital IDs and gifts had soared to over $100,000.00, attracting crimin</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947296095134830592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.07%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.07% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: DOGE +7.97%, ADA +6.21%, SOL +5.52%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947295301277540352</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.07%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.07% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: DOGE +7.97%, ADA +6.21%, SOL +5.52%.$ADA$DOGE$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947295301277540352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next round of Trading Arena on pump.fun will reward 18.00M PUMP tokens.pump.fun announces it will offer 18 million PUMP tokens as rewards in the next round of its Trading Arena event. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293022756864</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoForesightNewsThe next round of Trading Arena on pump.fun will reward 18.00M PUMP tokens.pump.fun announces it will offer 18 million PUMP tokens as rewards in the next round of its Trading Arena event. [Foresight News]$PUMPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293022756864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Hit All-Time Highs IntradayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq both hit record intraday highs, now up 0.38% and 0.67%. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293963262382080</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoTechFlowS&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Hit All-Time Highs IntradayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq both hit record intraday highs, now up 0.38% and 0.67%. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293963262382080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq hit all-time intraday highsMarket data shows that the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq both hit record highs during the session, now up 0.38% and 0.67%. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947295785796521984</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyS&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq hit all-time intraday highsMarket data shows that the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq both hit record highs during the session, now up 0.38% and 0.67%. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947295785796521984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, global listed companies net bought $953.00M in BTC, with MSTR increasing its holdings by over $700.00M in a single week.According to SoSoValue data, as of July 21, 2025, US Eastern Time, the total weekly net inflow of Bitcoin allocated by global listed companies (excluding mining companies) last week was $953.00M. Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) invested $739.80M last week to increase its holdings by 6,220 Bitcoins at a price of $118,940, bringing its total holdings to 607,770. Japanese listed company Metaplanet suspended Bitcoin purchases last week, after five consecutive weeks of continuous increases. French wafer fab Sequans Communication (NYSE:SQNS), listed in the United States, joined the ranks of new BTC purchases last week. Sequans Communication invested $150.00M to increase its holdings by 1,264 Bitcoins at a price of $118,659, bringing its total holdings to 2,317. In addition, three other companies made new purchases last week. The Smarter Web, a UK digital advertising company, invested $36.10M to increase its holdings by 325 Bitcoins at a price of $111,107, bringing its total holdings to 1,600; Semler Scientific, a US healthcare company, invested $25.00M to increase its holdings by 210 BTC at a price of $118,974, bringing its total holdings to 4,846 BTC; Blockchain Group, a French Web3 service company, invested $2.56M to increase its holdings by 22 Bitcoins at a price of $116,516, bringing its total holdings to 1,955. As of press time, the total amount of Bitcoin held by global listed companies (excluding mining companies) in the statistics is 681,680, with a current market value of approximately $80.40B, accounting for 3.43% of the circulating market value of Bitcoin. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293254785716224</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoOdailyLast week, global listed companies net bought $953.00M in BTC, with MSTR increasing its holdings by over $700.00M in a single week.According to SoSoValue data, as of July 21, 2025, US Eastern Time, the total weekly net inflow of Bitcoin allocated by global listed companies (exclu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293254785716224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold hits $3,390.00, up 1.18% on the dayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold continued its gains, breaking through $3,390.00/ounce, up 1.18% on the day. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293049260625920</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoTechFlowSpot gold hits $3,390.00, up 1.18% on the dayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold continued its gains, breaking through $3,390.00/ounce, up 1.18% on the day. [Techflow TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293049260625920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YZi Labs is Hiring a Web3 and AI Investment DirectorYZi Labs announces multiple job openings and is hiring a Web3 Investment Director and an AI Investment Director. The company focuses on supporting the next generation of cutting-edge technology founders in the Web3, AI, and biotech fields, offering a remote-first work model and a global mindset. Interested parties can apply via their X platform, website, or LinkedIn. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293274415104</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoForesightNewsYZi Labs is Hiring a Web3 and AI Investment DirectorYZi Labs announces multiple job openings and is hiring a Web3 Investment Director and an AI Investment Director. The company focuses on supporting the next generation of cutting-edge technology founders in the Web3, AI, a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293274415104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amber Group Accelerator amber.ac Launches BUIDL_QUESTS 2025: Record-breaking Funding of Over $10 Million to Drive Innovation at AgentFiOn July 21, amber.ac, a Web3 accelerator under Amber Group, officially launched the second global hackathon BUIDL_QUESTS 2025, with a total incentive amount of over $10 million, focusing on the AgentFi field to help build the next-generation crypto economy driven by autonomous intelligent agents. The incentives include cash bonuses, ecological incentives, potential investment opportunities, cloud service resources, and TVL liquidity support, etc. Participating projects will also have the opportunity to receive guidance from Amber Group mentors, financing opportunities, and be on the Token2049 offline display stage. In addition, the intelligent economy representative MIA will participate in content co-creation and community interaction as an event ambassador. Registration is now open. For more information, please visit amber.ac or join the official Telegram group. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289994913927168</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoPANewsAmber Group Accelerator amber.ac Launches BUIDL_QUESTS 2025: Record-breaking Funding of Over $10 Million to Drive Innovation at AgentFiOn July 21, amber.ac, a Web3 accelerator under Amber Group, officially launched the second global hackathon BUIDL_QUESTS 2025, with a total incen</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289994913927168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources: Meta, &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn file legal action against Italy&apos;s tax demandsOn July 21, sources said: Meta Platforms (META.O), social media company &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn filed legal proceedings against Italy&apos;s tax requirements. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289305580064768</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoPANewsSources: Meta, &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn file legal action against Italy&apos;s tax demandsOn July 21, sources said: Meta Platforms (META.O), social media company &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn filed legal proceedings against Italy&apos;s tax requirements. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289305580064768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLGY Merges with StablecoinX and Raises $360.0 Million to Advance ENA Treasury StrategySPAC company TLGY Acquisition Corp has announced a merger with Ethena ecosystem infrastructure company StablecoinX Assets Inc., with plans to list on the Nasdaq under the ticker symbol USDE. To support the transaction, TLGY and StablecoinX have signed a PIPE investment agreement of approximately $360.00 million, of which $260.00 million will be used to purchase locked ENA. The Ethena Foundation has simultaneously launched a $260.00 million ENA repurchase program. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288938876260352</link>
      <description>45 minutes ago吴说TLGY Merges with StablecoinX and Raises $360.0 Million to Advance ENA Treasury StrategySPAC company TLGY Acquisition Corp has announced a merger with Ethena ecosystem infrastructure company StablecoinX Assets Inc., with plans to list on the Nasdaq under the ticker symbol USDE. To sup</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288938876260352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Labs Announces $360.0 million PIPE Deal for StablecoinX, Foundation Launches $260.0 million BuybackAccording to official sources, Ethena Labs has announced a $360.0 million PIPE deal for StablecoinX, and its foundation has launched a $260.0 million ENA open market repurchase program. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947290738295590912</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoOdailyEthena Labs Announces $360.0 million PIPE Deal for StablecoinX, Foundation Launches $260.0 million BuybackAccording to official sources, Ethena Labs has announced a $360.0 million PIPE deal for StablecoinX, and its foundation has launched a $260.0 million ENA open market repurcha</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947290738295590912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coolpad Group: RWA business division established, will explore property asset tokenizationAccording to Zhitong Finance, Coolpad Group announced that it has established a Real World Asset Tokenization Division, which aims to promote the tokenization of property assets. As of December 31, 2024, the book value of the Group&apos;s investment properties was approximately HK$3.151B. Currently, preliminary RWA feasibility studies are being conducted on Coolpad Building in Nanshan, Shenzhen, and Coolpad Technology Ecological Park in Songshan Lake, Dongguan. If the pilot project is successful, the Group plans to expand its service model to assist more companies in exploring asset tokenization and promote the large-scale application of RWA technology in related industries. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289638649745408</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoForesightNewsCoolpad Group: RWA business division established, will explore property asset tokenizationAccording to Zhitong Finance, Coolpad Group announced that it has established a Real World Asset Tokenization Division, which aims to promote the tokenization of property assets. As o</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289638649745408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institutional user transferred 540,000 SOL from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet.According to whale_alert monitoring, 540,000 SOL (approximately $103.00M) were transferred from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet address. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054322712576</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoForesightNewsAn institutional user transferred 540,000 SOL from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet.According to whale_alert monitoring, 540,000 SOL (approximately $103.00M) were transferred from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet address. [Foresight News]#Cryp</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054322712576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>