<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:57:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The next round of Trading Arena on pump.fun will reward 18.00M PUMP tokens.pump.fun announces it will offer 18 million PUMP tokens as rewards in the next round of its Trading Arena event. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293022756864</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsThe next round of Trading Arena on pump.fun will reward 18.00M PUMP tokens.pump.fun announces it will offer 18 million PUMP tokens as rewards in the next round of its Trading Arena event. [Foresight News]$PUMPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293022756864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Hit All-Time Highs IntradayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq both hit record intraday highs, now up 0.38% and 0.67%. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293963262382080</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoTechFlowS&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Hit All-Time Highs IntradayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq both hit record intraday highs, now up 0.38% and 0.67%. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293963262382080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana vault firm Upexi announces it has grown its SOL holdings to 1.80M over the past three monthsSolana treasury company Upexi has announced an increase of 100,000 SOL, with a total acquisition price of $17.70 million, increasing its SOL reserves to 1.80 million in the past three months, with a current market value of approximately $331.00 million, and has realized $58.00 million in unrealized gains. Upexi stated that it has staked most of its SOL, with an expected annual staking yield of $26.00 million. In addition, 56% of its holdings are locked SOL purchased at a discount. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293991926255616</link>
      <description>4 minutes ago吴说Solana vault firm Upexi announces it has grown its SOL holdings to 1.80M over the past three monthsSolana treasury company Upexi has announced an increase of 100,000 SOL, with a total acquisition price of $17.70 million, increasing its SOL reserves to 1.80 million in the past three mo</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293991926255616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A user lost $1.23 million in assets due to mistakenly entering a phishing websiteOn July 21, SlowMist founder Cos (Yu Xian) tweeted that a user searched for aave on Google and clicked on the first search result, which led to the theft of assets worth $1.23 million. It is reported that the phishing website used Uniswap&apos;s multicall mechanism to authorize the user&apos;s LP NFT to the phishing contract, and then the assets were transferred. Cos reminded users that as the market heats up, the risk of phishing is also increasing, and they must be vigilant against network security risks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293314109952000</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsA user lost $1.23 million in assets due to mistakenly entering a phishing websiteOn July 21, SlowMist founder Cos (Yu Xian) tweeted that a user searched for aave on Google and clicked on the first search result, which led to the theft of assets worth $1.23 million. It is reported</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293314109952000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week, global listed companies net bought $953.00M in BTC, with MSTR increasing its holdings by over $700.00M in a single week.According to SoSoValue data, as of July 21, 2025, US Eastern Time, the total weekly net inflow of Bitcoin allocated by global listed companies (excluding mining companies) last week was $953.00M. Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) invested $739.80M last week to increase its holdings by 6,220 Bitcoins at a price of $118,940, bringing its total holdings to 607,770. Japanese listed company Metaplanet suspended Bitcoin purchases last week, after five consecutive weeks of continuous increases. French wafer fab Sequans Communication (NYSE:SQNS), listed in the United States, joined the ranks of new BTC purchases last week. Sequans Communication invested $150.00M to increase its holdings by 1,264 Bitcoins at a price of $118,659, bringing its total holdings to 2,317. In addition, three other companies made new purchases last week. The Smarter Web, a UK digital advertising company, invested $36.10M to increase its holdings by 325 Bitcoins at a price of $111,107, bringing its total holdings to 1,600; Semler Scientific, a US healthcare company, invested $25.00M to increase its holdings by 210 BTC at a price of $118,974, bringing its total holdings to 4,846 BTC; Blockchain Group, a French Web3 service company, invested $2.56M to increase its holdings by 22 Bitcoins at a price of $116,516, bringing its total holdings to 1,955. As of press time, the total amount of Bitcoin held by global listed companies (excluding mining companies) in the statistics is 681,680, with a current market value of approximately $80.40B, accounting for 3.43% of the circulating market value of Bitcoin. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293254785716224</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoOdailyLast week, global listed companies net bought $953.00M in BTC, with MSTR increasing its holdings by over $700.00M in a single week.According to SoSoValue data, as of July 21, 2025, US Eastern Time, the total weekly net inflow of Bitcoin allocated by global listed companies (exclud</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293254785716224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold hits $3,390.00, up 1.18% on the dayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold continued its gains, breaking through $3,390.00/ounce, up 1.18% on the day. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293049260625920</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoTechFlowSpot gold hits $3,390.00, up 1.18% on the dayOn July 21, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold continued its gains, breaking through $3,390.00/ounce, up 1.18% on the day. [Techflow TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947293049260625920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YZi Labs is Hiring a Web3 and AI Investment DirectorYZi Labs announces multiple job openings and is hiring a Web3 Investment Director and an AI Investment Director. The company focuses on supporting the next generation of cutting-edge technology founders in the Web3, AI, and biotech fields, offering a remote-first work model and a global mindset. Interested parties can apply via their X platform, website, or LinkedIn. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293274415104</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsYZi Labs is Hiring a Web3 and AI Investment DirectorYZi Labs announces multiple job openings and is hiring a Web3 Investment Director and an AI Investment Director. The company focuses on supporting the next generation of cutting-edge technology founders in the Web3, AI, an</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947294293274415104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amber Group Accelerator amber.ac Launches BUIDL_QUESTS 2025: Record-breaking Funding of Over $10 Million to Drive Innovation at AgentFiOn July 21, amber.ac, a Web3 accelerator under Amber Group, officially launched the second global hackathon BUIDL_QUESTS 2025, with a total incentive amount of over $10 million, focusing on the AgentFi field to help build the next-generation crypto economy driven by autonomous intelligent agents. The incentives include cash bonuses, ecological incentives, potential investment opportunities, cloud service resources, and TVL liquidity support, etc. Participating projects will also have the opportunity to receive guidance from Amber Group mentors, financing opportunities, and be on the Token2049 offline display stage. In addition, the intelligent economy representative MIA will participate in content co-creation and community interaction as an event ambassador. Registration is now open. For more information, please visit amber.ac or join the official Telegram group. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289994913927168</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoPANewsAmber Group Accelerator amber.ac Launches BUIDL_QUESTS 2025: Record-breaking Funding of Over $10 Million to Drive Innovation at AgentFiOn July 21, amber.ac, a Web3 accelerator under Amber Group, officially launched the second global hackathon BUIDL_QUESTS 2025, with a total incen</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289994913927168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources: Meta, &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn file legal action against Italy&apos;s tax demandsOn July 21, sources said: Meta Platforms (META.O), social media company &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn filed legal proceedings against Italy&apos;s tax requirements. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289305580064768</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoPANewsSources: Meta, &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn file legal action against Italy&apos;s tax demandsOn July 21, sources said: Meta Platforms (META.O), social media company &quot;X&quot; and LinkedIn filed legal proceedings against Italy&apos;s tax requirements. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289305580064768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLGY Merges with StablecoinX and Raises $360.0 Million to Advance ENA Treasury StrategySPAC company TLGY Acquisition Corp has announced a merger with Ethena ecosystem infrastructure company StablecoinX Assets Inc., with plans to list on the Nasdaq under the ticker symbol USDE. To support the transaction, TLGY and StablecoinX have signed a PIPE investment agreement of approximately $360.00 million, of which $260.00 million will be used to purchase locked ENA. The Ethena Foundation has simultaneously launched a $260.00 million ENA repurchase program. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288938876260352</link>
      <description>24 minutes ago吴说TLGY Merges with StablecoinX and Raises $360.0 Million to Advance ENA Treasury StrategySPAC company TLGY Acquisition Corp has announced a merger with Ethena ecosystem infrastructure company StablecoinX Assets Inc., with plans to list on the Nasdaq under the ticker symbol USDE. To sup</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288938876260352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Labs Announces $360.0 million PIPE Deal for StablecoinX, Foundation Launches $260.0 million BuybackAccording to official sources, Ethena Labs has announced a $360.0 million PIPE deal for StablecoinX, and its foundation has launched a $260.0 million ENA open market repurchase program. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947290738295590912</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoOdailyEthena Labs Announces $360.0 million PIPE Deal for StablecoinX, Foundation Launches $260.0 million BuybackAccording to official sources, Ethena Labs has announced a $360.0 million PIPE deal for StablecoinX, and its foundation has launched a $260.0 million ENA open market repurcha</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947290738295590912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coolpad Group: RWA business division established, will explore property asset tokenizationAccording to Zhitong Finance, Coolpad Group announced that it has established a Real World Asset Tokenization Division, which aims to promote the tokenization of property assets. As of December 31, 2024, the book value of the Group&apos;s investment properties was approximately HK$3.151B. Currently, preliminary RWA feasibility studies are being conducted on Coolpad Building in Nanshan, Shenzhen, and Coolpad Technology Ecological Park in Songshan Lake, Dongguan. If the pilot project is successful, the Group plans to expand its service model to assist more companies in exploring asset tokenization and promote the large-scale application of RWA technology in related industries. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289638649745408</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoForesightNewsCoolpad Group: RWA business division established, will explore property asset tokenizationAccording to Zhitong Finance, Coolpad Group announced that it has established a Real World Asset Tokenization Division, which aims to promote the tokenization of property assets. As o</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947289638649745408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An institutional user transferred 540,000 SOL from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet.According to whale_alert monitoring, 540,000 SOL (approximately $103.00M) were transferred from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet address. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054322712576</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoForesightNewsAn institutional user transferred 540,000 SOL from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet.According to whale_alert monitoring, 540,000 SOL (approximately $103.00M) were transferred from Coinbase Institutional to an unknown new wallet address. [Foresight News]#Cryp</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288054322712576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stock BTCS announces increased holdings of 22,935 ETH, having additionally raised $10.00M to continue increasing ETH holdings.BTCS Inc. (Nasdaq: BTCS), a company focused on blockchain technologies, today announced that its holdings of 55,788 ETH, cash and other liquid assets have a total market value of approximately $242.2 million, based on an Ethereum (ETH) price of $3,600. The Ethereum holdings increased by 22,935 ETH from the previous announcement (32,853 ETH), with a total holding of 55,788 ETH, an increase of 69.8%. In addition, the company has agreed to issue $10.00 million in convertible notes through a previously announced $56.00 million financing arrangement with ATW Partners LLC. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288217997037568</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoOdailyUS stock BTCS announces increased holdings of 22,935 ETH, having additionally raised $10.00M to continue increasing ETH holdings.BTCS Inc. (Nasdaq: BTCS), a company focused on blockchain technologies, today announced that its holdings of 55,788 ETH, cash and other liquid assets h</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947288217997037568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget has launched USDT-Margined TA Perpetual Contracts with leverage ranging from 1-50xAccording to the official announcement, Bitget has announced the launch of USDT-margined TA perpetual contracts, with a leverage range of 1-50x. Contract trading BOT will be launched simultaneously. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947285531553714176</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget has launched USDT-Margined TA Perpetual Contracts with leverage ranging from 1-50xAccording to the official announcement, Bitget has announced the launch of USDT-margined TA perpetual contracts, with a leverage range of 1-50x. Contract trading BOT will be launched s</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947285531553714176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitGo Crypto Custody Firm Files for U.S. IPOOn July 21, according to Aggr News, cryptocurrency company BitGo has secretly submitted an initial public offering (IPO) application to US regulators. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284170724364288</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoPANewsBitGo Crypto Custody Firm Files for U.S. IPOOn July 21, according to Aggr News, cryptocurrency company BitGo has secretly submitted an initial public offering (IPO) application to US regulators. [PANews]#FundraisingShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284170724364288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>599 Bitcoin transferred to Coinbase Institutional walletAccording to whale_alert data, an unknown wallet transferred 599 Bitcoin to the Coinbase Institutional wallet, worth approximately $70,824,959.00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284253759000576</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoForesightNews599 Bitcoin transferred to Coinbase Institutional walletAccording to whale_alert data, an unknown wallet transferred 599 Bitcoin to the Coinbase Institutional wallet, worth approximately $70,824,959.00. [Foresight News]#Crypto Stocks$MAG7.SSI$BTC$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947284253759000576</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group Up 7.45% PremarketMarket data shows that Trump Media &amp; Technology Group&apos;s stock rose 7.45% in pre-market trading and is now trading at $20.06. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283187113938944</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoOdailyTrump Media &amp; Technology Group Up 7.45% PremarketMarket data shows that Trump Media &amp; Technology Group&apos;s stock rose 7.45% in pre-market trading and is now trading at $20.06. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283187113938944</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX has launched XTZ and TA perpetual contracts and launched the contract trading party.On July 21, according to the official announcement, Huobi HTX launched XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT perpetual contracts on July 21, with a maximum leverage of 20 times. At the same time, Huobi HTX launched the XTZ and TA contract trading party from 20:30 on July 21 to 20:30 on July 28 (UTC+8), with a total prize pool of up to $20,000.00.
During the event, users who complete the registration and participate in XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT contract transactions with a cumulative effective transaction amount of ≥10,000.00 USDT can share the prize pool based on the transaction amount ranking; new contract users who complete XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT contract transactions will also receive exclusive benefits. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947282575244677120</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoPANewsHuobi HTX has launched XTZ and TA perpetual contracts and launched the contract trading party.On July 21, according to the official announcement, Huobi HTX launched XTZ/USDT and TA/USDT perpetual contracts on July 21, with a maximum leverage of 20 times. At the same time, Huobi H</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947282575244677120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs Co-founder: All 1.866 million S tokens allocated for airdrop have been burned.Sonic Labs co-founder Andre Cronje posted on-chain data indicating that Sonic Labs has just burned all 1,866,256.59 S tokens allocated in the airdrop, worth $754,902.66. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283204008595456</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailySonic Labs Co-founder: All 1.866 million S tokens allocated for airdrop have been burned.Sonic Labs co-founder Andre Cronje posted on-chain data indicating that Sonic Labs has just burned all 1,866,256.59 S tokens allocated in the airdrop, worth $754,902.66. [Odaily]$SShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947283204008595456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>