<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Two addresses that participated in the private placement of the PUMP organization have sold a total of approximately 25.50B PUMP in the past week.According to @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, two addresses involved in the PUMP organization&apos;s private placement have sold a total of approximately 25.50B $PUMP (approximately $141.00M) in the past week, with a total profit of approximately $39.65M. Among them, address D6ar...Lazd subscribed to 25.00B PUMP with $100.00M USDC and transferred 13.00B of them to FalconX within a week, making a profit of approximately $19.50M; address 58WQ...v33E subscribed to 12.50B PUMP with $50.00M USDC and transferred all of them to CEX in the past week, making a profit of approximately $20.15M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223957409386496</link>
      <description>2 minutes ago吴说Two addresses that participated in the private placement of the PUMP organization have sold a total of approximately 25.50B PUMP in the past week.According to @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, two addresses involved in the PUMP organization&apos;s private placement have sold a total of approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223957409386496</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigONE launches $8.1 million hacker bounty programOn July 21, according to BigONE’s announcement, in response to the recent theft of encrypted assets, BigONE has officially launched a hacker bounty program with a total amount of US$8.10M, calling on white hat hackers around the world to help track down the stolen funds and identify the attackers. BigONE said that it welcomes security experts to participate in promoting the recovery of stolen assets and the detection of cases. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223567464943616</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsBigONE launches $8.1 million hacker bounty programOn July 21, according to BigONE’s announcement, in response to the recent theft of encrypted assets, BigONE has officially launched a hacker bounty program with a total amount of US$8.10M, calling on white hat hackers around the wo</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223567464943616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Exchange Will List ESPORTS, UPTOP, YFI, and TA Spot TradingOn July 21, WEEX announced that the platform will launch Yooldo (ESPORTS), UPTOP (UPTOP), yearn (YFI), and Trusta.AI (TA) spot trading today at 18:00 (UTC+8). In addition, WEEX spot has recently launched Metaplex (MPLX), TAKER (TAKER), Echo Protocol (ECHO), Medieval Empires (MEE), PrompTale AI (TALE), RCADE (RCADE), Caldera (ERA), Hyperion (RION), and RUDI (RUDI). [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223527086379008</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoTechFlowWEEX Exchange Will List ESPORTS, UPTOP, YFI, and TA Spot TradingOn July 21, WEEX announced that the platform will launch Yooldo (ESPORTS), UPTOP (UPTOP), yearn (YFI), and Trusta.AI (TA) spot trading today at 18:00 (UTC+8). In addition, WEEX spot has recently launched Metaplex (M</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947223527086379008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamix Plans to Hold Over $1.50B in ETH After Merger With Entity to Form Ether MachineDynamix, a blank-check company, is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company called &quot;Ether Machine,&quot; which plans to hold over $1.50B worth of Ethereum (ETH). The core bet behind this plan is that the market will continue to favor companies heavily invested in crypto assets, amid the possibility of a more crypto-friendly regulatory environment under the Trump administration. Kraken and Blockchain.com will provide over $800.00M in equity financing for this transaction, priced at $10.00 per share. (Wall Street Journal) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222794601517056</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailyDynamix Plans to Hold Over $1.50B in ETH After Merger With Entity to Form Ether MachineDynamix, a blank-check company, is preparing to merge with another entity to form a new company called &quot;Ether Machine,&quot; which plans to hold over $1.50B worth of Ethereum (ETH). The core bet behi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222794601517056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto investment products see record $4.4 billion in weekly inflows, pushing year-to-date total to $27B: CoinSharesGlobal crypto investment products attracted a record $4.39 billion of inflows last week, their strongest tally since CoinShares began tracking the data in 2014, and more than the previous $4.27 billion peak logged last December after the U.S. general election, the firm&apos;s head of research, James Butterfill, wrote on Monday.

The surge — the 14th consecutive week of net buying — lifted year‑to‑date inflows to $27 billion and pushed assets under management to a new all‑time high of $220 billion. Trading activity in exchange‑traded products also hit a peak, with turnover jumping to $39.2 billion.

Market leader Bitcoin was a primary driver of last week’s flows, but Ethereum was the star and notched a 13th consecutive week of capital allocations, according to Butterfill. Funds linked to the world’s second‑largest cryptocurrency pulled in $2.12 billion, nearly double their prior weekly record of $1.2 billion and taking 2025 inflows to $6.2 billion, already eclipsing last year’s total. Bitcoin products gathered $2.2 billion, down from $2.7 billion the previous week, but still sizable enough to keep overall flows at historic levels.

The United States unsurprisingly dominated geographically with $4.36 billion of inflows to funds offered by firms like BlackRock, Grayscale, and Bitwise, while Switzerland, Hong Kong, and Australia contributed a combined $78.7 million. Brazil and Germany logged modest outflows of $28.1 million and $15.5 million, respectively.

Among other altcoins, Solana, XRP, and Sui products attracted $39 million, $36 million, and $9.3 million, respectively, signaling risk appetite beyond the crypto’s two top heavyweights.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222623654268928</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoThe BlockCrypto investment products see record $4.4 billion in weekly inflows, pushing year-to-date total to $27B: CoinSharesGlobal crypto investment products attracted a record $4.39 billion of inflows last week, their strongest tally since CoinShares began tracking the data in 2014, a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947222623654268928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address holding 50 WBTC is likely to profit approximately $2.404 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, the address starting with 0x2Be is suspected of clearing 50 WBTC purchased in April last year at a cost of only $65,135. If sold, it will profit approximately $2.404M, with a return rate of approximately 83% for holding the position for 15 months. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947221156860022784</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoForesightNewsAn address holding 50 WBTC is likely to profit approximately $2.404 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, the address starting with 0x2Be is suspected of clearing 50 WBTC purchased in April last year at a cost of only $65,135. If sold, it will profit approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947221156860022784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Degen adjusts liquidity mining rewards, Beefy rewards reduced to 1.25M, Aerodrome increased to 1.75MThe Degen token on the Base network will adjust the distribution of liquidity provider rewards: The daily distribution of Degen tokens on the Beefy platform will decrease from 1.50M to 1.25M; at the same time, an additional 1.75M Degen token rewards will be added to the Aerodrome platform each week to better balance the incentive mechanisms between the two platforms. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070854053888</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoForesightNewsDegen adjusts liquidity mining rewards, Beefy rewards reduced to 1.25M, Aerodrome increased to 1.75MThe Degen token on the Base network will adjust the distribution of liquidity provider rewards: The daily distribution of Degen tokens on the Beefy platform will decrease fr</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070854053888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNB Chain Launches BEP-593, Introducing Weekly Incremental Snapshots to Improve Node EfficiencyBNB Chain is advancing the construction of more efficient node infrastructure. According to the BEP-593 proposal, BNB Chain will introduce a weekly incremental snapshot function to simplify the node synchronization process. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070937939968</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoForesightNewsBNB Chain Launches BEP-593, Introducing Weekly Incremental Snapshots to Improve Node EfficiencyBNB Chain is advancing the construction of more efficient node infrastructure. According to the BEP-593 proposal, BNB Chain will introduce a weekly incremental snapshot function</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947220070937939968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX Wallet Launches PUMP Trading Arena with a Total Prize Pool of 18.00 Million PUMP TokensAccording to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched the PUMP Trading Arena, with the event running from July 21, 2025, 13:30 to July 28, 2025, 13:30 (UTC+8). During the event, users who complete specified trading, invitation, and sharing tasks will have the opportunity to receive rewards. The top 300 users by trading volume will share 12,000,000 PUMP tokens. The total prize pool for the event is 18,000,000 PUMP tokens. It is reported that Pump.Fun is a platform for creating and trading tokens, and PUMP is its official token. OKX Wallet is a leading one-stop Web3 portal in the industry, supporting 130+ popular public chains. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947217749633945600</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoOdailyOKX Wallet Launches PUMP Trading Arena with a Total Prize Pool of 18.00 Million PUMP TokensAccording to official sources, OKX Wallet has launched the PUMP Trading Arena, with the event running from July 21, 2025, 13:30 to July 28, 2025, 13:30 (UTC+8). During the event, users who</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947217749633945600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ping An of China: Actively Studying Industry Regulatory Changes Related to Stablecoins in the Hong Kong MarketAccording to Cailian Press, Ping An of China stated on the interactive platform that the company has noticed industry regulatory changes related to stablecoins in the Hong Kong market. Ping An has a deep accumulation in blockchain technology and will continue to pay close attention and actively research it. [Cailian Press]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210540837523456</link>
      <description>56 minutes ago吴说Ping An of China: Actively Studying Industry Regulatory Changes Related to Stablecoins in the Hong Kong MarketAccording to Cailian Press, Ping An of China stated on the interactive platform that the company has noticed industry regulatory changes related to stablecoins in the Hong Ko</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210540837523456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.11%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.11% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: SOL +6.69%, ADA +5.17%, HBAR +5.07%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947209661064110080</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.11%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.11% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: SOL +6.69%, ADA +5.17%, HBAR +5.07%.$ADA$SOL$HBARShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947209661064110080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$55.7922 millionOn July 21, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$55.7922 million. Among them: The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$17.0465 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$27.77655 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$1.2222 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$2.3379 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$2.2717 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$5.1413 million. Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947208587025862656</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$55.7922 millionOn July 21, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$55.7922 million. Among them: The transact</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947208587025862656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTFS 4.0 Introduces the Storage Provider RoleThe BTFS 4.0 network officially introduces the new role of &quot;Storage Provider&quot; to enhance the performance of the BTFS network, including reliability and long-term scalability. As core infrastructure nodes of the network, storage providers must meet stricter standards in terms of hardware configuration, online rate, and service quality, and must be certified by BTTC verification nodes. The plan aims to build a high-performance distributed storage network and promote the sustainable development of the BitTorrent ecosystem. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210224557641728</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBTFS 4.0 Introduces the Storage Provider RoleThe BTFS 4.0 network officially introduces the new role of &quot;Storage Provider&quot; to enhance the performance of the BTFS network, including reliability and long-term scalability. As core infrastructure nodes of the network, storage providers m</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210224557641728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aster Introduces Active Staking Model, asBNB Staking Can Earn Yield, Collateralize Transactions, and Participate in MiningAster, a decentralized trading platform, has announced that the staking strategy for asBNB has been upgraded from traditional &quot;passive income&quot; to &quot;active participation.&quot; Users can enjoy the following features after minting asBNB:
1: Earn up to 30% APR in BNB ecosystem rewards by holding;
2: Use as trading collateral for Aster Pro;
3: Earn funding rate收益 while hedging BNB holdings.
Aster stated that asBNB&apos;s multi-use model as a staking asset improves staking efficiency and flexibility. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210232996581376</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyAster Introduces Active Staking Model, asBNB Staking Can Earn Yield, Collateralize Transactions, and Participate in MiningAster, a decentralized trading platform, has announced that the staking strategy for asBNB has been upgraded from traditional &quot;passive income&quot; to &quot;active particip</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947210232996581376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand SEC proposes relaxing rules for testing crypto ICO investorsOn July 21, the Securities and Exchange Commission of Thailand (SEC) proposed to relax the knowledge testing requirements for retail crypto investors, allowing investors who have passed the test to be exempted from repeated testing, and changing the current quarterly retesting regulations to a suitability assessment every two years. The new rules require ICO portals to conduct comprehensive suitability testing on all digital token investors to ensure that investment risks match product risks. The proposal aims to reduce the burden on investors and ICO portals while being consistent with existing securities regulatory standards. The SEC is now open for public comments, with a deadline of August 1. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205827186413568</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsThailand SEC proposes relaxing rules for testing crypto ICO investorsOn July 21, the Securities and Exchange Commission of Thailand (SEC) proposed to relax the knowledge testing requirements for retail crypto investors, allowing investors who have passed the test to be exempted from</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205827186413568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23.Binance Alpha will launch Alliance Games (COA) on July 23. Eligible users can visit the Alpha activity page to claim the airdrop using Binance Alpha points after trading opens. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207693962072064</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance Alpha will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23.Binance Alpha will launch Alliance Games (COA) on July 23. Eligible users can visit the Alpha activity page to claim the airdrop using Binance Alpha points after trading opens. [Odaily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207693962072064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruida Futures: No R&amp;D on stablecoin trading clearing systemAccording to Zhitong Finance, Ruida Futures stated on the interactive platform that the company has not conducted research and development of a stablecoin transaction clearing system. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947206203943964672</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsRuida Futures: No R&amp;D on stablecoin trading clearing systemAccording to Zhitong Finance, Ruida Futures stated on the interactive platform that the company has not conducted research and development of a stablecoin transaction clearing system. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947206203943964672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Will List ETC/USDC and Other Spot Trading Pairs and Open Trading Bots ServicesAccording to the official announcement, Binance will launch the ETC/USDC, GRT/USDC, and ROSE/USDC spot trading pairs on July 22, 2025, at 08:00 (UTC). In addition, Binance will open trading bot services for the following trading pairs at the same time: Spot algorithmic orders (ETC/USDC, GRT/USDC, ROSE/USDC); Spot Grid and Spot DCA (PENGU/USDC, XLM/USDC). (This news flash is generated with AI assistance) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207702405206016</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance Will List ETC/USDC and Other Spot Trading Pairs and Open Trading Bots ServicesAccording to the official announcement, Binance will launch the ETC/USDC, GRT/USDC, and ROSE/USDC spot trading pairs on July 22, 2025, at 08:00 (UTC). In addition, Binance will open trading bot serv</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947207702405206016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: NFT rebound suggests traders are rotating out of Bitcoin and exploring other speculative plays in the crypto marketThe total market capitalization of NFTs has now exceeded $6.3 billion, nearly doubling from $3.2 billion less than a month ago. At the same time, Bitcoin&apos;s market share has fallen by 6.6% to around 61%. Market analysis suggests that the return of NFTs provides a signal that traders are cycling out of Bitcoin and re-exploring speculative investments in the crypto market. This means that once Bitcoin consolidates and investors begin to shift capital to higher-risk assets, altcoins tend to see more aggressive movements. (DL News) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205175731310592</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyAnalysis: NFT rebound suggests traders are rotating out of Bitcoin and exploring other speculative plays in the crypto marketThe total market capitalization of NFTs has now exceeded $6.3 billion, nearly doubling from $3.2 billion less than a month ago. At the same time, Bitcoin&apos;s mar</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947205175731310592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: ETH is now at $3,786According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.08% in the past 24h. Now at $3,786.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202446030757888</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: ETH is now at $3,786According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.08% in the past 24h. Now at $3,786.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202446030757888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>