<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:54:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,600According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 1.43% in the past 1H, down 2.47% in the last 24H. Now at $3,600.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948017605884207104</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,600According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 1.43% in the past 1H, down 2.47% in the last 24H. Now at $3,600.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948017605884207104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDRA Life Science to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury and Revenue Generation StrategyAccording to NLNico, US-based ENDRA Life Science Corporation will adopt a cryptocurrency treasury strategy and plans to implement a Bitcoin-based revenue-generating strategy. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948018048534908928</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoOdailyENDRA Life Science to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury and Revenue Generation StrategyAccording to NLNico, US-based ENDRA Life Science Corporation will adopt a cryptocurrency treasury strategy and plans to implement a Bitcoin-based revenue-generating strategy. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948018048534908928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiSocialFi index 24hr loss of 11.25%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiSocialFi has fallen by 11.25% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: TON -9.56%, UXLINK -8.88%, G -4.97%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948016058941005824</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiSocialFi index 24hr loss of 11.25%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiSocialFi has fallen by 11.25% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: TON -9.56%, UXLINK -8.88%, G -4.97%.$TONCOIN$UXLINK$GShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948016058941005824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: If major countries are willing to open their markets to the United States, tariffs will be waivedOn July 23, US President Trump said: I will always be willing to give up tariff terms if major countries can be persuaded to open their markets to the United States. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948016261371334656</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsTrump: If major countries are willing to open their markets to the United States, tariffs will be waivedOn July 23, US President Trump said: I will always be willing to give up tariff terms if major countries can be persuaded to open their markets to the United States. [PANews]Sh</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948016261371334656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Immersion (BMNR) Announces the Start of Options Trading on the NYSECrypto mining firm BitMine Immersion (NYSE: BMNR) has announced that options on the company&apos;s common stock will begin trading on the New York Stock Exchange on July 23, covering multiple standard expiration dates and strike prices. Officials say the move is expected to increase stock liquidity and provide investors with more risk management and strategic trading options. BitMine Chairman of the Board Thomas Lee said this reflects the market&apos;s confidence in its strategy to &quot;acquire 5.00% of global ETH&quot;. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948014247354634240</link>
      <description>20 minutes ago吴说BitMine Immersion (BMNR) Announces the Start of Options Trading on the NYSECrypto mining firm BitMine Immersion (NYSE: BMNR) has announced that options on the company&apos;s common stock will begin trading on the New York Stock Exchange on July 23, covering multiple standard expiration da</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948014247354634240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plasma Launches New Phase of Stablecoin Collective: Workshop Kicks OffOn July 23, according to the Plasma announcement, the Plasma stablecoin collective has officially entered a new stage, launching new initiatives such as monthly seminars. As the mainnet beta is approaching, Plasma has added new roles such as builders and early contributors, and encouraged members to participate in teams to demonstrate the importance of stablecoins in promoting global capital flows. Teams must submit before July 25, and the first seminar will be held on July 28. Plasma said that education is the core of promoting the popularization of stablecoins, and collaborative discussions are an efficient way to make collective progress. Outstanding projects will also have the opportunity to receive support. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948013743182516224</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoPANewsPlasma Launches New Phase of Stablecoin Collective: Workshop Kicks OffOn July 23, according to the Plasma announcement, the Plasma stablecoin collective has officially entered a new stage, launching new initiatives such as monthly seminars. As the mainnet beta is approaching, Pla</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948013743182516224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks open, Dow Jones up 0.36%, S&amp;P 500 up 0.34%, Nasdaq up 0.34%On July 23, according to Jinshi Data, the US stock market opened with the Dow up 0.36%, the S&amp;P 500 up 0.34%, and the Nasdaq up 0.34%. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948017297242787840</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoTechFlowUS stocks open, Dow Jones up 0.36%, S&amp;P 500 up 0.34%, Nasdaq up 0.34%On July 23, according to Jinshi Data, the US stock market opened with the Dow up 0.36%, the S&amp;P 500 up 0.34%, and the Nasdaq up 0.34%. [Techflow TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948017297242787840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic announces Season 2 Gems airdrop, allocating approximately 30.00M SSonic announces the second season Gems airdrop, which will distribute approximately 30.00M S. Gems are primarily calculated based on their performance on key metrics, with specific amounts allocated based on protocol type, on-chain nativeness, incentive model, points, and revenue. After the season, protocols will independently determine the Gems distribution model. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948013846152679424</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoForesightNewsSonic announces Season 2 Gems airdrop, allocating approximately 30.00M SSonic announces the second season Gems airdrop, which will distribute approximately 30.00M S. Gems are primarily calculated based on their performance on key metrics, with specific amounts allocated ba</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948013846152679424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matador Technologies secures $100.00M in funding to purchase more BitcoinCanadian publicly traded company Matador Technologies has secured a $100.00M financing facility to purchase more Bitcoin. Previously reported, Matador Technologies announced that its board of directors has approved a long-term Bitcoin acquisition strategy plan to accumulate up to 6,000 Bitcoin by 2027 or earlier, as well as a medium-term target of accumulating 1,000 BTC by 2026. Matador&apos;s long-term goal is to hold 1% of the Bitcoin supply and become one of the top 20 corporate holders globally. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948013007732281344</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoOdailyMatador Technologies secures $100.00M in funding to purchase more BitcoinCanadian publicly traded company Matador Technologies has secured a $100.00M financing facility to purchase more Bitcoin. Previously reported, Matador Technologies announced that its board of directors has a</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948013007732281344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This coin could repeat XRP’s 2017 price boom and flip $700 into $245,700.00Disclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. XRP turned early investors into millionaires, now, Little Pepe’s $0.0014 presale has crypto watchers wondering if history is about to repeat itself. Table of Contents Back in 2017, XRP shocked the world. It soared from fractions of a cent to over $3, turning modest investments into generational wealth. A mere $700 investment turned into millions. As the cryptocurrency market prepares for yet another bull run, market watchers would not want to miss out on the next ‘ XRP ’ moment. That is, a cryptocurrency with the possibility of sudden growth, solid community backing, and distinctive blockchain principles. Enter Little Pepe, now in Stage 5 of its presale, trading at just $0.0014. Backed by real tech, cultural appeal, and a roadmap advancing faster than expected, Little Pepe could be the breakout star that flips a few hundred dollars into six figures by the next peak. The success of XRP wasn’t just hype, it was built on utility and timing. Similarly, LILPEPE is not your average memecoin. It’s the native token of the Little Pepe ecosystem, a next-gen EVM-compatible Layer 2 chain specifically designed to empower meme culture while delivering serious blockchain speed and security. With ultra-low gas fees, near-instant finality, and advanced protection mechanisms against sniper bots, it sets itself apart in a world of overhyped and underdelivering tokens. While XRP was tied to institutional financial systems, Little Pepe is tied to culture, a smarter bet in today’s crypto landscape. Memecoins now dominate viral adoption, but they often lack the necessary infrastructure to support their growth. Little Pepe fills this gap by building a dedicated Layer 2 chain just for memes, complete with a Launchpad to incubate the next generation of viral tokens. It’s a solution that creators, traders, and investors didn’t even know they needed, until now. Already progressing through its roadmap ahead of schedule, the project has completed its listing on CoinMarketCap and is preparing to list on two major CEXs, with plans in place to list on the world’s largest exchange. When that happens, and demand spikes, early-stage prices like $0.0014 could become the stuff of legends. Just like XRP’s early investors, Little Pepe holders today are planting seeds that could multiply hundreds of times over. For a token to repeat XRP’s meteoric rise, it must be more than just hype, it needs robust tokenomics, sustainable allocation, and a clear strategy to incentivize holding. LILPEPE hits every note. With a total allocation designed to reward early believers and long-term holders, the structure mirrors the success of past launches while injecting innovation where it counts. Compare this to the early days of XRP, where insider control and regulatory uncertainty limited decentralized participation, and Little Pepe emerges as the more democratic, community-powered successor. It’s also worth noting that the project is backed by anonymous crypto veterans who have helped launch several top memecoins. Their involvement adds a layer of credibility and insider experience that most new tokens can only dream of. At its current Stage 5 presale price of $0.0014, a $700 investment nets 500,000 Little Pepe tokens. Now let’s apply XRP’s logic. If LILPEPE reaches just $0.49, that bag becomes $245,000, and that’s without even hitting $1. Given the project’s expanding utility, meme appeal, and scarcity, such a price target is far from a moonshot. History tells us that markets reward tokens that combine community hype with real utility. XRP achieved this in 2017 by riding the wave of cross-border payments. Today, meme culture is the wave, and Little Pepe is the only project building a Layer 2 chain for that wave. With a Launchpad for meme tokens, anti-sniper tech, and a viral marketing strategy already underway, Little Pepe is built to go parabolic. And let’s not forget the $770,000.00 giveaway currently active, 10 winners will each receive $77,000.00 worth of Little Pepe tokens. This isn’t just a promo; it’s a bold way to onboard early users, distribute tokens fairly, and supercharge word-of-mouth adoption across the crypto space. The crypto market loves history, but it rewards innovation. Little Pepe isn’t trying to be the next XRP in function; it’s replicating its trajectory in a more culturally relevant way. By leveraging a unique blend of memetic power, blockchain innovation, and early-stage pricing, it presents a rare opportunity in a market where actual value is often buried under noise. Those who slept on XRP in 2017 now look back with regret. With Little Pepe in its final presale stages, the window is once again open, but it won’t stay that way for long. To learn more about Little Pepe, visit its website , Telegram , and X . Disclosure: This content is provided by a third party. Neither crypto.news nor the author of this article endorses any product mentioned on this page. Users should conduct their own research before taking any action related to the company.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948010827654696960</link>
      <description>30 minutes agocrypto.newsThis coin could repeat XRP’s 2017 price boom and flip $700 into $245,700.00Disclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. XRP turned early investors into millionaires, now, Lit</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948010827654696960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first list of projects for HTX DAO’s governance voting for listing has been announced, and voting has started simultaneously. Participate to share the 10 billion $HTX prize pool.On July 23, according to the official announcement of HTX DAO, the HTX DAO coin listing governance voting activity officially announced the first list of 8 candidate projects, marking the full opening of a new era of community-driven coin listing. This vote brought together more than 50 high-quality projects to compete for the coin listing qualification. The first list is only the beginning, and more projects will be announced later. This round of rankings is based on comprehensive considerations, covering multiple dimensions such as community recommendations, market discussions, user attention, project popularity, and trading performance. The first batch of shortlisted projects for voting include Mira, MONAD, Succinct, MANYU, COCORO, ETHS, KENDU, and Froggie. This vote has set up a special $HTX super prize pool with a total scale of 10 billion. All users who participate in the pledge voting can share the generous rewards, and there are also mysterious &quot;easter egg&quot; rewards waiting to be unlocked. The voting time is from 20:00 on July 22 to 23:30 on July 26 (UTC+8). How to participate: Install the TRONLINK wallet and transfer $HTX, log in to the HTX DAO platform to vote. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948011230391767040</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoPANewsThe first list of projects for HTX DAO’s governance voting for listing has been announced, and voting has started simultaneously. Participate to share the 10 billion $HTX prize pool.On July 23, according to the official announcement of HTX DAO, the HTX DAO coin listing governance</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948011230391767040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: SOL is now at $193.17According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 5.03% in the past 24h. Now at $193.17.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948009285181988864</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: SOL is now at $193.17According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is down 5.03% in the past 24h. Now at $193.17.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948009285181988864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba Cloud Bailian has launched Qwen3-Coder; the price is only 1/3 of Claude 4.On July 23, the latest AI programming model Qwen3-CoderAPI was launched on Alibaba Cloud Bailian, with minimum input and output prices of 4.00 yuan and 16.00 yuan per million tokens respectively, and an average price of 1/3 of Claude4. At the same time, Alibaba Cloud Bailian also launched a limited-time discount of up to 50% off, and the price of 128K-1M long context enjoys a 50% discount. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948011230488236032</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsAlibaba Cloud Bailian has launched Qwen3-Coder; the price is only 1/3 of Claude 4.On July 23, the latest AI programming model Qwen3-CoderAPI was launched on Alibaba Cloud Bailian, with minimum input and output prices of 4.00 yuan and 16.00 yuan per million tokens respectively, an</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948011230488236032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The batch unstaking of 620,000 ETH may be related to the surge in borrowing rates caused by a large withdrawal of ETH deposits from the Aave platform.According to on-chain data analyst Ai Yi, citing the analysis of crypto blogger darkpool, the batch un-staking of 620,000 ETH may be related to the massive withdrawal of ETH deposits from the Aave platform, which led to a surge in borrowing rates. The massive withdrawal of Aave ETH deposits in a short period led to a surge in borrowing rates, causing circular lending players to go from profiting from interest rate spreads to losses, forcing them to redeem stETH to deleverage, resulting in the current situation. Aave ETH borrowing APR once soared to 10.00%, and the Lido stETH current withdrawal waiting period has been extended to 21 days (normally within a week). There is still a discount of nearly 0.40% for on-chain stETH converted to ETH. Regarding the implementation of circular lending, Aave&apos;s collateral rate for ETH is 93.00%, which means that arbitrage players can even use leverage as high as 14x to obtain interest rate spread income. Under normal circumstances, the annualized rate of return on principal can reach 7.00%. Previously, it was reported that the amount of ETH awaiting withdrawal from staking reached 620,000, and the net redemption amount was approximately 271,000. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948010488977231872</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdailyAnalysis: The batch unstaking of 620,000 ETH may be related to the surge in borrowing rates caused by a large withdrawal of ETH deposits from the Aave platform.According to on-chain data analyst Ai Yi, citing the analysis of crypto blogger darkpool, the batch un-staking of 620,00</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948010488977231872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump criticizes Powell, says FOMC should take actionOn July 23, Trump posted that the housing market has lagged because Powell refused to lower interest rates. Families are hurt because interest rates are too high, and even our country itself has to pay higher interest rates than it should. Our interest rates should be three percentage points lower than they are now, which would save the entire country $1 trillion a year. Powell, this stubborn guy, just doesn&apos;t understand, never has, and will never understand. The Board of Governors should take action, but they don&apos;t have the courage to do so. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948011230534373376</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoPANewsTrump criticizes Powell, says FOMC should take actionOn July 23, Trump posted that the housing market has lagged because Powell refused to lower interest rates. Families are hurt because interest rates are too high, and even our country itself has to pay higher interest rates tha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948011230534373376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Commerce Secretary: Trump Wants EU to Fully Open MarketsU.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick: Trump wants the EU to fully open its markets. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948007964148830208</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyU.S. Commerce Secretary: Trump Wants EU to Fully Open MarketsU.S. Commerce Secretary Lutnick: Trump wants the EU to fully open its markets. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948007964148830208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cango Announces Completion of Secondary Acquisition and Appointment of New Management TeamOn July 23, Cango Inc. (NYSE: CANG) announced its completion of the transformation into global Bitcoin mining, and also appointed a new board of directors (referred to as the &quot;Board&quot;) and senior management team. According to the resolution passed on July 23, 2025, the Board appointed: (1) Xin Jin as Chairman of the Board and Non-Executive Director; (2) Peng Yu as Chief Executive Officer and Director; (3) Chang-Wei Chiu as Director; (4) Yongyi Zhang as Chief Financial Officer; (5) Simon Ming Yeung Tang as Chief Investment Officer. To enhance governance, the Board also appointed: (1) Independent Director Chi Ming Lee as a member of the Compensation Committee and the Nomination and Corporate Governance Committee; (2) Independent Director Yanjun Lin as Chairman of the Compensation Committee and a member of the Nomination and Corporate Governance Committee; (3) Haitian Lu as Chairman of the Nomination and Corporate Governance Committee and a member of the Compensation Committee. During the same period, the Board accepted Xiaojun Zhang&apos;s resignation as Director and Chairman of the Board, and Jiayuan Lin&apos;s resignation as Chief Executive Officer, Interim Chief Financial Officer, and Director. The two also completed a secondary acquisition—selling a total of 10.00 million Class B ordinary shares to Enduring Wealth Capital Limited for a total consideration of $70.00 million; and voluntarily converted all remaining Class B ordinary shares held by their holding company into Class A ordinary shares with one vote per share. After the transaction, they collectively hold 18.54% of the company&apos;s total outstanding shares and 12.07% of the total voting rights; Enduring Wealth Capital Limited holds approximately 2.82% of the outstanding shares and 36.73% of the voting rights. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948007972591964160</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoOdailyCango Announces Completion of Secondary Acquisition and Appointment of New Management TeamOn July 23, Cango Inc. (NYSE: CANG) announced its completion of the transformation into global Bitcoin mining, and also appointed a new board of directors (referred to as the &quot;Board&quot;) and se</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948007972591964160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto entrepreneurs were fleeing America, but we can bring them backRegulatory uncertainty drove crypto innovation offshore, but new bipartisan leadership and clear frameworks can restore America’s financial dominance.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948006192143470592</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoPANewsCrypto entrepreneurs were fleeing America, but we can bring them backRegulatory uncertainty drove crypto innovation offshore, but new bipartisan leadership and clear frameworks can restore America’s financial dominance.#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948006192143470592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Senate Agriculture Committee plans to release market structure discussion draft in early SeptemberOn July 23, according to Eleanor Terrett, the U.S. Senate Agriculture Committee, which is responsible for supervising the CFTC and participating in market structure legislation, plans to release its discussion draft in early September. It is reported that the draft will focus on the CFTC&apos;s regulatory functions in the field of digital commodities and strive to achieve bipartisan cooperation. It is expected that multiple parties, including senior members of the Democratic Party, will participate in the drafting. Yesterday, the Senate Banking Committee released a draft for the SEC&apos;s regulatory structure, and the two bills are expected to be merged in the future. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948006192265105408</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoPANewsU.S. Senate Agriculture Committee plans to release market structure discussion draft in early SeptemberOn July 23, according to Eleanor Terrett, the U.S. Senate Agriculture Committee, which is responsible for supervising the CFTC and participating in market structure legislation,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948006192265105408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H.C. Wainwright initiates coverage of Cango with a Buy rating and a target price of $8.00.H.C. Wainwright analyst Kevin Dede initiated coverage on Cango (NASDAQ: CANG) with a &quot;Buy&quot; rating and a price target of $8.00. In addition, TipRanks data shows that the analyst&apos;s total win rate over the past year is 42.60%, with a total average return rate of 11.80%. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948005439744053248</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailyH.C. Wainwright initiates coverage of Cango with a Buy rating and a target price of $8.00.H.C. Wainwright analyst Kevin Dede initiated coverage on Cango (NASDAQ: CANG) with a &quot;Buy&quot; rating and a price target of $8.00. In addition, TipRanks data shows that the analyst&apos;s total win r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948005439744053248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>