<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:35:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Block was officially included in the S&amp;P 500 index today, holding 8,584 bitcoinsOn July 23 that according to CNBC, payment giant Block Inc. will officially join the S&amp;P 500 index today. Block currently holds 8,584 bitcoins in its balance sheet and continues to implement its digital asset strategy. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948042356078481408</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsBlock was officially included in the S&amp;P 500 index today, holding 8,584 bitcoinsOn July 23 that according to CNBC, payment giant Block Inc. will officially join the S&amp;P 500 index today. Block currently holds 8,584 bitcoins in its balance sheet and continues to implement its digita</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948042356078481408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Launches BMNR Options Trading on NYSE, Plans to Acquire 5% of Ethereum SupplyAccording to The Block, BitMine, an Ethereum vault and crypto mining company backed by Peter Thiel and ARK, launched options trading for its common stock BMNR on the New York Stock Exchange on Wednesday. BitMine plans to acquire 5% of the global Ethereum (ETH) supply. The company&apos;s stock price has risen sharply since announcing its shift to ETH accumulation, with Founders Fund now being the largest shareholder, and ARK Invest also purchasing $182.00M worth of shares this week to invest in ETH. As of July 17, the total value of ETH held by BitMine has exceeded $1.00B. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041435298729984</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoForesightNewsBitMine Launches BMNR Options Trading on NYSE, Plans to Acquire 5% of Ethereum SupplyAccording to The Block, BitMine, an Ethereum vault and crypto mining company backed by Peter Thiel and ARK, launched options trading for its common stock BMNR on the New York Stock Exchang</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041435298729984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark launches SPK farm and other new features to optimize user revenue experienceOn July 23, the Spark platform recently launched a number of practical functions, including SPK farm (supply USDS to earn SPK), Overdrive (increase airdrop rewards), USDS (SPK farm) pool (stake SPK to enjoy SPK annualized income), and earning USDS points through Pendle. Users can increase their income by providing USDS, staking SPK, or participating in Overdrive activities, with no lock-up period and no additional threshold, further enriching the way to participate in DeFi. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948040730047483904</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsSpark launches SPK farm and other new features to optimize user revenue experienceOn July 23, the Spark platform recently launched a number of practical functions, including SPK farm (supply USDS to earn SPK), Overdrive (increase airdrop rewards), USDS (SPK farm) pool (stake SPK</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948040730047483904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun May Be the Cause of Most Ethereum Withdrawal EventsOver the past week, people have withdrawn as much as $1.7 billion worth of Ethereum from the lending protocol Aave. The reduction in available liquidity has caused the protocol to charge borrowers interest rates exceeding 10%. Aave contributor Marc Zeller told DL News that Justin Sun may be the cause of most of the Ethereum withdrawals, as he regularly moves large sums of money in and out of the lending protocol, &quot;He&apos;s so unpredictable, he moves billions of dollars like I go to the supermarket to buy something.&quot; Over the past three days, wallets on Arkham that users have tagged as belonging to Justin Sun have withdrawn over $646.00 million worth of Ethereum from Aave. [DLNEWS]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041040732164096</link>
      <description>13 minutes ago吴说Justin Sun May Be the Cause of Most Ethereum Withdrawal EventsOver the past week, people have withdrawn as much as $1.7 billion worth of Ethereum from the lending protocol Aave. The reduction in available liquidity has caused the protocol to charge borrowers interest rates exceeding</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041040732164096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: ETH is now at $3,606.15According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.06% in the past 24h. Now at $3,606.15.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948039610683580416</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: ETH is now at $3,606.15According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.06% in the past 24h. Now at $3,606.15.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948039610683580416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.09%, HBAR -7.02%, TON -6.98%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038775522156544</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.09%, HBAR -7.02%, TON -6.98%.$ADA$TONCOIN$HBARShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038775522156544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH to its internal addressOn July 23, Arkham data showed that 4 hours ago, the Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH (about $3.67M) to its internal address. The address currently holds 10,000 ETH, worth about $36.1M. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038332935639040</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoPANewsThe Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH to its internal addressOn July 23, Arkham data showed that 4 hours ago, the Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH (about $3.67M) to its internal address. The address currently holds 10,000 ETH, worth about $36.1M. [PANews]#Layer1$</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038332935639040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares Signs ETP Market Making Fund Platform Agreement with Société GénéraleCryptocurrency ETP issuer 21Shares has signed an ETP market-making fund platform agreement with Société Générale, which will support 21Shares&apos; Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, including: ABTC, CBTC, AETH, CETH, by providing over-the-counter liquidity through major fund platforms in Germany and Eastern Europe. (Globe Newswire) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038177276628992</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoOdaily21Shares Signs ETP Market Making Fund Platform Agreement with Société GénéraleCryptocurrency ETP issuer 21Shares has signed an ETP market-making fund platform agreement with Société Générale, which will support 21Shares&apos; Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, including: ABTC, CBTC, AETH, CET</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038177276628992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Increases Holdings by 117.93 BTC, Total Holdings Reach 628.22 BTCSwedish health tech company H100 Group announced the additional purchase of 117.93 Bitcoins, with an average purchase price of approximately 1,120,973.00 Swedish krona/Bitcoin, for a total amount of approximately 132.00 million Swedish krona (approximately $13.87 million). This increase is part of its Bitcoin treasury strategy, with some funds coming from the company&apos;s convertible bond agreement. H100 currently has a total holding of 628.22 BTC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948035325070217216</link>
      <description>35 minutes ago吴说H100 Group Increases Holdings by 117.93 BTC, Total Holdings Reach 628.22 BTCSwedish health tech company H100 Group announced the additional purchase of 117.93 Bitcoins, with an average purchase price of approximately 1,120,973.00 Swedish krona/Bitcoin, for a total amount of approxima</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948035325070217216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub calls for European sovereign tech fund to support open source softwareOn July 23, according to the GitHub blog, open source software as digital infrastructure is vital to the economy and society, but its maintenance funds have long been insufficient. The GitHub Developer Policy Team commissioned Open Forum Europe, Fraunhofer ISI, and the European University Institute to conduct a feasibility study to explore the extension of the successful experience of Germany&apos;s sovereign technology institutions to the EU level and promote the establishment of the &quot;EU Sovereign Technology Fund&quot; (EU-STF). The study recommends that the fund should focus on investing in open source dependency, maintenance, security, improvement, and ecosystem construction, and proposes seven design standards, including funding pools, low bureaucracy, political independence, flexible funding, community participation, strategic alignment, and high transparency. GitHub calls on the EU to invest at least 350.00 million euros in the 2028-2035 budget, and to jointly fund with industry and countries to ensure the sustainable development and digital sovereignty of open source software. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948034655252451328</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoPANewsGitHub calls for European sovereign tech fund to support open source softwareOn July 23, according to the GitHub blog, open source software as digital infrastructure is vital to the economy and society, but its maintenance funds have long been insufficient. The GitHub Developer P</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948034655252451328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, over $509.00M was liquidated across the entire network, with long positions being the primary target.Coinglass data shows that the total liquidation volume across the network in the past 24 hours was $509.00 million, with long positions accounting for $382.00 million and short positions accounting for $127.00 million. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948033133621874688</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyIn the past 24 hours, over $509.00M was liquidated across the entire network, with long positions being the primary target.Coinglass data shows that the total liquidation volume across the network in the past 24 hours was $509.00 million, with long positions accounting for $382.0</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948033133621874688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto ATMs were just banned in New Zealand: Here’s why it mattersNew Zealand’s financial watchdog outlawed crypto ATMs, citing regulatory gaps and AML concerns and raising questions about retail access and compliance.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948032056356835328</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoPANewsCrypto ATMs were just banned in New Zealand: Here’s why it mattersNew Zealand’s financial watchdog outlawed crypto ATMs, citing regulatory gaps and AML concerns and raising questions about retail access and compliance.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948032056356835328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The intersection of crypto and AI, presented by OpenLedgerEpisode 34 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and OpenLedger Core Contributor Ram Kumar.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or wherever you listen to podcasts. Please send feedback and revision requests to[emailprotected]

In this episode, sponsored by OpenLedger, Tim and Ram discussed the emerging intersection of decentralized AI and blockchain technology. Ram explains how OpenLedger is building infrastructure to let users contribute proprietary data to train AI models, with on-chain attribution and rewards for data contributors. The conversation covers OpenLedger’s upcoming mainnet launch, tokenomics, and the broader promise of creating a transparent, community-driven AI economy.

OUTLINE
00:00 – Introduction
01:02 – What is Openledger?
02:27 – Data Contribution Model
08:47 – Access to Agents
15:16 – Ensuring Quality Data
19:09 – Incentive Structures
23:18 – The Role of Tokens
24:56 – The Convergence of AI and Crypto
27:53 – Competing with Centralized Systems
30:23 – Openledger&apos;s Future and Success
33:32 – Data Economy Insights
36:17 – Conclusion

The Block Newsletters
The Block&apos;s newsletters bring you the latest news and analysis of the fast-moving crypto and DeFi markets. To subscribe, visit theblock.co/newsletters

Guest links:
Ram -⁠⁠ https://x.com/Ramkumartweet⁠⁠
OpenLedger - ⁠⁠https://x.com/OpenledgerHQ⁠⁠

Are you hiring in crypto?
Use Campus to quickly find your best candidates with our challenging Crypto Assessment Test.
Faster hiring, stronger teams.

Sign up for a trial today:theblock.co/campus

[The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948032318576332800</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoThe BlockThe intersection of crypto and AI, presented by OpenLedgerEpisode 34 of The Crypto Beat was recorded with The Block&apos;s Head of Growth, Tim Copeland, and OpenLedger Core Contributor Ram Kumar.

Listen below, and subscribe to The Crypto Beat on YouTube,Apple,Spotify, Twitch or wh</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948032318576332800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusta.AI responds to third-party contract fraud incident, official $TA tokens are safeOn July 23, Trusta.AI reported that an external fraud incident involving an unverified third-party contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) recently occurred on the blockchain. Trusta and the official $TA tokens remain safe and intact, and no vulnerabilities or problems have been found. The attack was caused by the failure of the non-open source contract to verify user input, which allowed the attacker to use the WBNB tokens of authorized users to exchange through the self-built WBNB-TA pool and sell their own $TA tokens to illegally obtain WBNB. Trusta.AI recommends that users immediately revoke their authorization to the contract and promises to repurchase $TA worth $200,000.00 to protect user interests. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031398367006720</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoPANewsTrusta.AI responds to third-party contract fraud incident, official $TA tokens are safeOn July 23, Trusta.AI reported that an external fraud incident involving an unverified third-party contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) recently occurred on the blockchain. Tru</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031398367006720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature&apos;s Miracle Announces Launch of Company-Level XRP Treasury Program of Up to $20.00MNature’s Miracle Holding Inc (OTCQB: NMHI) has announced the launch of a corporate-level XRP treasury program of up to $20.00M. The company will use equity financing funds under an S-1 registration statement already approved by the SEC to purchase XRP for long-term strategic reserves, staking yields, and participation in the Ripple ecosystem. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031358676307968</link>
      <description>51 minutes ago吴说Nature&apos;s Miracle Announces Launch of Company-Level XRP Treasury Program of Up to $20.00MNature’s Miracle Holding Inc (OTCQB: NMHI) has announced the launch of a corporate-level XRP treasury program of up to $20.00M. The company will use equity financing funds under an S-1 registratio</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031358676307968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. House Speaker Johnson: Legal compliance of firing Fed chairman unclearOn July 23, U.S. House Speaker Johnson said he was &quot;disappointed&quot; with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell, and the legal compliance of firing the Federal Reserve Chairman was unclear. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948030421631045632</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoPANewsU.S. House Speaker Johnson: Legal compliance of firing Fed chairman unclearOn July 23, U.S. House Speaker Johnson said he was &quot;disappointed&quot; with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell, and the legal compliance of firing the Federal Reserve Chairman was unclear. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948030421631045632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaia Labs raises $20 million to launch first AI-native smartphoneOn July 23, Gaia Labs, a decentralized AI infrastructure developer, announced the completion of a total of $20.00 million in seed and Series A financing. This round of financing was led by ByteTrade/SIG Capital (Susquehanna) and Mirana/Mantle Eco Fund, and participated by EVM Capital, Taisu Ventures, NGC Ventures and other institutions. Gaia Labs currently supports more than 700,000 active nodes, with a cumulative inference time of more than 17.00 trillion times, and the network covers thousands of App-Chain domains and blockchain ecosystems. The new round of funds will be used to launch decentralized AI smartphones, expand node capacity, improve development toolkits and promote Web3 integration. Gaia Labs plans to release a limited number of smartphones equipped with local AI inference capabilities this year. The Gaia AI Phone is based on the Galaxy S25 Edge hardware and can run decentralized AI inference locally without relying on the cloud or data extraction, enabling users to fully control the agent. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948029236043911168</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoPANewsGaia Labs raises $20 million to launch first AI-native smartphoneOn July 23, Gaia Labs, a decentralized AI infrastructure developer, announced the completion of a total of $20.00 million in seed and Series A financing. This round of financing was led by ByteTrade/SIG Capital (Sus</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948029236043911168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNY, Goldman Sachs ink tokenized money market fund deal to bring $7.1 trillion industry onchainBank of New York Mellon and Goldman Sachs on Wednesday launched a blockchain-based system that issues “mirror” tokens of money market fund shares, letting institutional investors subscribe and redeem through BNY’s LiquidityDirect platform while ownership is recorded on Goldman’s GS DAP ledger, marking the first U.S. rollout of tokenized MMF shares by major lenders.

Under the initiative, BNY will keep the official books and settlement records for participating funds, which reportedly already includes products from BlackRock, Fidelity, Federated Hermes, BNY’s Dreyfus unit, and Goldman Sachs Asset Management. BNY will also create digital token representations simultaneously, designed to boost collateral mobility and transferability.

The project targets a $7.1 trillion money market industry and arrives a week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act, establishing the first federal framework for U.S. stablecoins. Policymakers are also working on a crypto market structure bill that they say should broaden access to regulated digital asset services.

Unlike traditional money markets that trade during limited market hours, tokenized funds enjoy round-the-clock availability and expansive liquidity features because they sit on a blockchain network.

Mathew McDermott, Goldman Sachs&apos; global head of digital assets, said tokenizing MMF shares could unlock their use as collateral and pave the way for faster, more seamless moves across markets. The Goldman exec sees it as part of a longer-term push to modernize market plumbing, while BNY framed the project as a step toward a real-time financial architecture. &quot;Mirrored tokenization of MMF shares is a first step in this transition,&quot; Laide Majiyagbe, global head of liquidity, financing, and collateral at BNY, said.

It’s the first time major banks have ventured into blockchain-based money markets, but the tokenization trend has already attracted notable traditional finance players. Onchain products like BlackRock’s BUIDL and Franklin Templeton’s BENJI collectively command over $3 billion in assets, while the total real-world asset value in DeFi has exceeded $10.7 billion according to The Block’s data dashboard. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028347660963840</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockBNY, Goldman Sachs ink tokenized money market fund deal to bring $7.1 trillion industry onchainBank of New York Mellon and Goldman Sachs on Wednesday launched a blockchain-based system that issues “mirror” tokens of money market fund shares, letting institutional investors subscri</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028347660963840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ByteFederal Launches Crypto Real Estate Service in Florida, Partners with NEO and OPISASByteFederal, a blockchain technology company, has launched a pilot program in Florida enabling real estate buyers to use Bitcoin for property purchases, with settlements delivered in U.S. dollars to sellers. Announced on July 21, 2025, the service targets new construction properties and is facilitated through a strategic partnership with New Estate Only (NEO), a platform specializing in new real estate developments. Additionally, ByteFederal’s collaboration with OPISAS, an international real estate firm, allows foreign investors to purchase U.S. properties with cryptocurrency, expanding access to Florida’s housing market. The Florida pilot enables buyers to pay security deposits and final closing payments in Bitcoin, which ByteFederal converts to USD for escrow or title companies. “We generate a Bitcoin QR code, you make the Bitcoin payment, we handle the conversion, and then we deliver USD fiat to the escrow or title company for closing,” said Paul Tarantino, CEO of ByteFederal, in an interview. The service, currently manual, has a growing waitlist and is set to become fully automated soon. Buyers can fund transactions entirely in Bitcoin or combine crypto with fiat, offering flexibility for diverse financial strategies. ByteFederal’s partnership with NEO leverages the latter’s platform, which serves as a multiple listing service (MLS) for new construction, a market segment traditionally absent from traditional MLS platforms. NEO, venture capital-backed and operational in Florida and Texas, lists properties like single-family homes, townhomes, condos and high-rise apartments. “NEO is the first company to build a big platform for all the new housing and development projects,” Tarantino explained.  The collaboration with OPISAS targets international investors, particularly from Italy, seeking U.S. real estate. OPISAS facilitates property selection, while ByteFederal handles crypto-to-fiat conversions, ensuring sellers receive USD without exposure to Bitcoin’s price volatility. This partnership aligns with growing global interest in U.S. real estate, with NEO planning expansions to Colombia, El Salvador, Italy and Dubai. “They can be going in both directions — someone in the U.S. buying real estate in Colombia or someone in Colombia buying in the U.S.,” Tarantino noted, highlighting the platform’s global potential. ByteFederal, based in Florida, operates Bitcoin ATMs, offers the ByteWallet and provides ByteConnect, a point-of-sale system for merchants. With 15 money transmitter licenses, the company emphasizes regulatory compliance, positioning itself to benefit from recent U.S. regulatory developments like the Clarity Act, which may provide legal clarity for stablecoins like Tether and Lightning Network transactions. “It’s going to bring a lot of new users into the market who were maybe afraid of it or didn’t feel comfortable stepping in yet,” Tarantino said, referencing the custodial wallet launch planned for September 2025. This initiative comes amid broader shifts in U.S. financial policy. The Federal Housing Finance Agency is exploring crypto assets for mortgage underwriting, a move that could integrate digital currencies into mainstream finance. ByteFederal’s service addresses key challenges, such as taxation and liquidity, by providing a compliant bridge between crypto and fiat. The company’s focus on new construction and international buyers positions it to capitalize on Florida’s robust real estate market and growing crypto adoption.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948035199996071936</link>
      <description>1 hour agobitcoinmagazineByteFederal Launches Crypto Real Estate Service in Florida, Partners with NEO and OPISASByteFederal, a blockchain technology company, has launched a pilot program in Florida enabling real estate buyers to use Bitcoin for property purchases, with settlements delivered in U.S.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948035199996071936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House launches AI.Gov website to strengthen US leadership in artificial intelligenceSpecial Assistant to the President and White House Principal Deputy Press Secretary Harrison Fields posted on the X platform that the White House has launched AI.Gov to strengthen the United States&apos; leadership in the field of artificial intelligence. Thanks to David Sacks and Michael Kratsios for their dedication and commitment. Trump is committed to promoting innovation and competition to win the global artificial intelligence race. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028100910059520</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyThe White House launches AI.Gov website to strengthen US leadership in artificial intelligenceSpecial Assistant to the President and White House Principal Deputy Press Secretary Harrison Fields posted on the X platform that the White House has launched AI.Gov to strengthen the United</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028100910059520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>