<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>MoonPay launches Solana staking as investor demand for onchain yield grows</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948081530227724288</link>
      <description>18:02MoonPay launches Solana staking as investor demand for onchain yield grows</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948081530227724288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burwick Law names Solana and Jito executives in expanded RICO case against PumpLaw firms Burwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded their lawsuit against memecoin generator Pump to include the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, and Jito, as well as several high-ranking individuals in the Solana ecosystem, including network co-creators Anatoly Yakovenko and Raj Gokal.

In an amended complaint filed on Wednesday, the law firms allege RICO claims against Yakovenko and Gokal as well as Solana Foundation Executive Director Dan Albert, President Lily Liu, and former communications lead Austin Federa.

The firms also sued Jito CEO Lucas Bruder and COO Brian Smith as well as Pump co-founders Alon Cohen, Dylan Kerler, and Noah Bernhard Hugo Tweedale. Pump, run by the UK-based Baton Corporation, and the Solana Foundation failed to immediately respond when reached for comment. A Jito representative declined to comment.

“The claims against defendants in this matter include RICO claims (predicated on illegal gambling, wire fraud, intellectual property theft, and unlicensed money transmission), Securities claims, and NY GBL 349 &amp; 350 claims,” Burwick wrote on X.

&quot;At every level—from token design to fee extraction, to infrastructure maintenance and validator orchestration—Solana Labs and Jito Labs were knowing, intentional participants in the conduct at issue,&quot; the plaintiffs wrote. &quot;They are not bystanders to fraud. They are its architects, beneficiaries, and co-conspirators.&quot;

RICO claims stem from the Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act, a U.S. federal law passed in 1970 to combat organized crime. It enables prosecutors to target individuals or groups by tying together disparate crimes into a single case.

According to the filing, the firms allege that Pump “is operating in clear violation of multiple U.S. financial crime prevention statutes and regulations” including Section 311 of the USA PATRIOT Act, the Bank Secrecy Act, FinCEN rules, OFAC sanctions rules, and state money transmitter licensing requirements.

“By refusing to verify user identities, failing to monitor or report suspicious transactions, and neglecting any formal AML program, Pump.Fun exposes the public to severe risks of criminal exploitation—facilitating money laundering, terrorist financing, sex trafficking, and other serious crimes,” the plaintiffs wrote.

Notably, the plaintiffs argue that Pump&apos;s lack of controls enabled the North Korean hacking collective Lazarus Group to allegedly launder funds stolen during the $1.5 billion Bybit hack by launching the “QinShihuang” memecoin.

The lawyers also accused Pump of “knowingly” facilitating the creation and promotion of “tokens that exploit hate speech, violence, and exploitation to generate attention and trading volume” and trademark violations.

In a June filing, Judge Colleen McMahon consolidated an earlier class action brought against Pump by investors in the PNUT memecoin. The lead plaintiffs in the new case are Diego Aguilar, Kendall Carnahan, and Lead Plaintiff Michael Okafor.

“This action is brought by, and on behalf of, victims of a coordinated racketeering enterprise designed to simulate the functions of a digital casino operated illegally under the guise of meme coin creation and trading,” the complaint reads. “In truth, Pump.fun is merely the front-facing slot machine cabinet, operated as part of a broader illegal gambling and money transmission scheme engineered and maintained jointly by” Pump, Jito, and Solana leadership.

The lawsuit notes that Pump has generated $722.85 million from its “illegal gambling enterprise,” which uses a bonding curve to allegedly exploit users. Meanwhile, the plaintiffs argue Jito Labs “monitored the spins and intercepted profitable transactions – the ‘winning spins’ – and sent them to whoever bribed them the most.”

Last month, Pump parent company retained several high-profile attorneys with international law firm Brown Rudnick to bolster its defense. Pump’s legal team includes veteran crypto attorney Stephen D. Palley and former SEC investigator Daniel L. Sachs.

Burwick, which specializes in digital asset litigation, is also leading lawsuits against other crypto platforms and memecoin creators, including influencer Haliey Welch of “Hawk Tuah” infamy.

The expanded suit comes amid a series of developments for Pump, which recently introduced a native PUMP token and made its first corporate acquisition. In July, rival memecoin generator LetsBONK surpassed Pump in token launches for the first time. [No source attribution]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948085148490207232</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoThe BlockBurwick Law names Solana and Jito executives in expanded RICO case against PumpLaw firms Burwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded their lawsuit against memecoin generator Pump to include the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, and Jito, as well as several high-ranking individuals</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948085148490207232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: XRP is now at $3.16009According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 10.13% in the past 24h. Now at $3.16009.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948070918004629504</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: XRP is now at $3.16009According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 10.13% in the past 24h. Now at $3.16009.$XRPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948070918004629504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil’s VERT launches private credit solution on the XRP LedgerVERT, a Brazil-based capital markets firm, has joined the growing trend of companies looking to tap into tokenization with a new solution on XRP Ledger. The fund management firm’s move comes as Wall Street giants such as Goldman Sachs, BNY and JPMorgan a tokenized assets market that has attracted products from fund behemoths like BlackRock, Fidelity and Franklin Templeton. XRP Ledger is powered by the XRP ( XRP ) token. VERT’s blockchain-based platform on the XRPL will focus on the issuance and management of private credit operations. Ripple expands its reach in LATAM with this initiative. According to the details, the on-chain venture goes live with the issuance of an Agribusiness Receivables Certificate. The RCA is a regulated credit instrument managed across a sector that accounts for over 20% of Brazil ’s gross domestic product. “Agribusiness plays an essential role in Brazil’s economy, and improving how credit is structured and tracked in this sector is a meaningful advancement,” said Silvio Pegado, managing director of Ripple in Latin America. The first CRA transaction will be valued at 700 million Brazilian real, or approximately $130 million. Recently, Token Relations revealed the total tokenized real-world assets on XRPL had grown by more than 2,260% in six months — from $5 million at the start of the year to over $118 million at the beginning of July. Mercado Bitcoin, Latin America’s largest cryptocurrency exchange and alternative asset investment platform, announced on July 4 that it will bring over $200 million in tokenized RWAs to the XRPL. The assets the platform plans to tokenize on the blockchain include fixed income and equity instruments. Guggenheim Capital is also tapping into the XRP Ledger. Its subsidiary, Guggenheim Treasury Services, issued U.S. Treasury-backed digital commercial paper on the Ripple blockchain platform. June also saw tokenized assets platform Ondo Finance unveil its short-term Treasuries bill OUSG , while Circle added native USDC ( USDC ) to XRP Ledger. VERT’s initiative will add to this traction as it helps Brazil’s capital markets come on-chain. The company aims to generate $500 million in value that will be on-chain. Benefits will include increased operational efficiency, transparency, and accessibility. As well as issuing private credit on the XRPL, VERT is integrating Ripple’s Ethereum-compatible protocol XRPL EVM Sidechain to leverage smart contracts for programmable automation among other functionality. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948069413860741120</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsBrazil’s VERT launches private credit solution on the XRP LedgerVERT, a Brazil-based capital markets firm, has joined the growing trend of companies looking to tap into tokenization with a new solution on XRP Ledger. The fund management firm’s move comes as Wall Street giants su</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948069413860741120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNC Bank Partners with Coinbase to Launch Customer Crypto Trading ServicesAccording to Reuters, PNC Bank, the eighth-largest bank in the U.S., is partnering with Coinbase to roll out cryptocurrency trading services for its customers. PNC will leverage Coinbase&apos;s institutional-grade &quot;crypto-as-a-service&quot; platform to enable customers to buy, sell, and hold crypto assets, and will provide some banking services to Coinbase. [Reuters]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948059670664515584</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说PNC Bank Partners with Coinbase to Launch Customer Crypto Trading ServicesAccording to Reuters, PNC Bank, the eighth-largest bank in the U.S., is partnering with Coinbase to roll out cryptocurrency trading services for its customers. PNC will leverage Coinbase&apos;s institutional-grade &quot;cryp</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948059670664515584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU diplomat: EU and US moving towards possible trade deal, with US benchmark tariffs on EU goods at 15%EU diplomat: The EU and the US are moving towards a possible trade agreement, with the US benchmark tariff on EU goods at 15.00%. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948058298900615168</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyEU diplomat: EU and US moving towards possible trade deal, with US benchmark tariffs on EU goods at 15%EU diplomat: The EU and the US are moving towards a possible trade agreement, with the US benchmark tariff on EU goods at 15.00%. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948058298900615168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tron Inc. to Ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on July 24Tron Inc. (Nasdaq: TRON) has announced that it will hold an opening bell ceremony at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York on July 24th, US Eastern Time, hosted by Justin Sun, founder of TRON and Global Advisor of Tron Inc. This marks the company&apos;s official transformation into a technology company focused on blockchain and digital asset innovation. The company stated that the bell-ringing is not only an important milestone in the development of Tron Inc., but also highlights its long-term vision of driving shareholder value growth through innovation and strategic leadership. Formerly known as SRM Entertainment, the company is currently the listed company holding the most TRON (TRX) tokens. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948055775972233216</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTron Inc. to Ring the Nasdaq Opening Bell on July 24Tron Inc. (Nasdaq: TRON) has announced that it will hold an opening bell ceremony at the Nasdaq MarketSite in Times Square, New York on July 24th, US Eastern Time, hosted by Justin Sun, founder of TRON and Global Advisor of Tron Inc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948055775972233216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark launches SPK farm and other new features to optimize user revenue experienceOn July 23, the Spark platform recently launched a number of practical functions, including SPK farm (supply USDS to earn SPK), Overdrive (increase airdrop rewards), USDS (SPK farm) pool (stake SPK to enjoy SPK annualized income), and earning USDS points through Pendle. Users can increase their income by providing USDS, staking SPK, or participating in Overdrive activities, with no lock-up period and no additional threshold, further enriching the way to participate in DeFi. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948040730047483904</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsSpark launches SPK farm and other new features to optimize user revenue experienceOn July 23, the Spark platform recently launched a number of practical functions, including SPK farm (supply USDS to earn SPK), Overdrive (increase airdrop rewards), USDS (SPK farm) pool (stake SPK to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948040730047483904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun May Be the Cause of Most Ethereum Withdrawal EventsOver the past week, people have withdrawn as much as $1.7 billion worth of Ethereum from the lending protocol Aave. The reduction in available liquidity has caused the protocol to charge borrowers interest rates exceeding 10%. Aave contributor Marc Zeller told DL News that Justin Sun may be the cause of most of the Ethereum withdrawals, as he regularly moves large sums of money in and out of the lending protocol, &quot;He&apos;s so unpredictable, he moves billions of dollars like I go to the supermarket to buy something.&quot; Over the past three days, wallets on Arkham that users have tagged as belonging to Justin Sun have withdrawn over $646.00 million worth of Ethereum from Aave. [DLNEWS]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041040732164096</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说Justin Sun May Be the Cause of Most Ethereum Withdrawal EventsOver the past week, people have withdrawn as much as $1.7 billion worth of Ethereum from the lending protocol Aave. The reduction in available liquidity has caused the protocol to charge borrowers interest rates exceeding 10%</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041040732164096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase to List JITOSOL and MPLXCoinbase has announced the listing of Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL) and Metaplex (MPLX) on the Solana network, with plans to enable JITOSOL/USD and MPLX/USD trading pairs in phases starting July 24, 2025, at 9:00 AM (PT), pending liquidity conditions. The official reminder is not to send assets through other networks to prevent fund loss. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948053257041022976</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyCoinbase to List JITOSOL and MPLXCoinbase has announced the listing of Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL) and Metaplex (MPLX) on the Solana network, with plans to enable JITOSOL/USD and MPLX/USD trading pairs in phases starting July 24, 2025, at 9:00 AM (PT), pending liquidity conditions. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948053257041022976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the dayOn July 23, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the day. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948050492361347072</link>
      <description>2 hours agoTechFlowSpot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the dayOn July 23, according to Jinshi Data, spot gold fell below $3,400.00/ounce, down 0.91% on the day. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948050492361347072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US government&apos;s AI.Gov official website is officially launched, focusing on Trump&apos;s AI strategyOn July 23, the US government launched a new AI.Gov official website today, systematically launching the &quot;American AI Action Plan&quot;, proposing three pillar strategies of &quot;accelerating innovation, building AI infrastructure, and leading international AI diplomacy and security&quot;. The plan was led by President Donald Trump in the early days of his second term, emphasizing the improvement of national AI competitiveness by reducing regulation, supporting open source AI, strengthening infrastructure and international cooperation, and promoting the application of AI in key areas such as medicine, manufacturing, and national defense, in order to consolidate the United States&apos; global AI leadership. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948049419613573120</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsThe US government&apos;s AI.Gov official website is officially launched, focusing on Trump&apos;s AI strategyOn July 23, the US government launched a new AI.Gov official website today, systematically launching the &quot;American AI Action Plan&quot;, proposing three pillar strategies of &quot;accelerating i</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948049419613573120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today&apos;s on-chain fund flows: Polygon PoS net inflow of $58.00M, Ethereum net outflow of $72.90MOn July 23, according to Artemis data, Polygon PoS saw a net inflow of $58.00M today, and OP Mainnet saw a net inflow of $16.70M; Ethereum saw a net outflow of $72.90M, and Base saw a net outflow of $18.40M. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948047984687648768</link>
      <description>2 hours agoTechFlowToday&apos;s on-chain fund flows: Polygon PoS net inflow of $58.00M, Ethereum net outflow of $72.90MOn July 23, according to Artemis data, Polygon PoS saw a net inflow of $58.00M today, and OP Mainnet saw a net inflow of $16.70M; Ethereum saw a net outflow of $72.90M, and Base saw a ne</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948047984687648768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payment giant Block added to S&amp;P 500 index today, holding 8,584 BitcoinsPayment giant Block will officially join the S&amp;P 500 index today. Block currently holds 8,584 Bitcoin on its balance sheet. (CNBC) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948045730173751296</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyPayment giant Block added to S&amp;P 500 index today, holding 8,584 BitcoinsPayment giant Block will officially join the S&amp;P 500 index today. Block currently holds 8,584 Bitcoin on its balance sheet. (CNBC) [Odaily]#Crypto Stocks$BTC$BLOCK$XYZShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948045730173751296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the entire network liquidation was $501.00M, mainly liquidating long positions.On July 23, according to Coinglass data, the total liquidation amount in the cryptocurrency market in the past 24 hours reached $501.00 million, of which $384.00 million were long liquidations and $117.00 million were short liquidations. The liquidation amount of ETH reached $107.00 million, BTC liquidated $50.61 million, and XRP liquidated $49.20 million. In the past 24 hours, 176,047 people were liquidated, and the largest single liquidation occurred on Binance&apos;s ETH-USDT trading pair, worth $3.97 million.  [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948043931521978368</link>
      <description>2 hours agoTechFlowIn the past 24 hours, the entire network liquidation was $501.00M, mainly liquidating long positions.On July 23, according to Coinglass data, the total liquidation amount in the cryptocurrency market in the past 24 hours reached $501.00 million, of which $384.00 million were long</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948043931521978368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitMine Launches BMNR Options Trading on NYSE, Plans to Acquire 5% of Ethereum SupplyAccording to The Block, BitMine, an Ethereum vault and crypto mining company backed by Peter Thiel and ARK, launched options trading for its common stock BMNR on the New York Stock Exchange on Wednesday. BitMine plans to acquire 5% of the global Ethereum (ETH) supply. The company&apos;s stock price has risen sharply since announcing its shift to ETH accumulation, with Founders Fund now being the largest shareholder, and ARK Invest also purchasing $182.00M worth of shares this week to invest in ETH. As of July 17, the total value of ETH held by BitMine has exceeded $1.00B. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041435298729984</link>
      <description>2 hours agoForesightNewsBitMine Launches BMNR Options Trading on NYSE, Plans to Acquire 5% of Ethereum SupplyAccording to The Block, BitMine, an Ethereum vault and crypto mining company backed by Peter Thiel and ARK, launched options trading for its common stock BMNR on the New York Stock Exchange o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948041435298729984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: ETH is now at $3,606.15According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.06% in the past 24h. Now at $3,606.15.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948039610683580416</link>
      <description>3 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: ETH is now at $3,606.15According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is down 3.06% in the past 24h. Now at $3,606.15.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948039610683580416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.09%, HBAR -7.02%, TON -6.98%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038775522156544</link>
      <description>3 hours agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.09%, HBAR -7.02%, TON -6.98%.$ADA$TONCOIN$HBARShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038775522156544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH to its internal addressOn July 23, Arkham data showed that 4 hours ago, the Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH (about $3.67M) to its internal address. The address currently holds 10,000 ETH, worth about $36.1M. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038332935639040</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsThe Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH to its internal addressOn July 23, Arkham data showed that 4 hours ago, the Ethereum Foundation transferred 1,000 ETH (about $3.67M) to its internal address. The address currently holds 10,000 ETH, worth about $36.1M. [PANews]#Layer1$ETH</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038332935639040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares Signs ETP Market Making Fund Platform Agreement with Société GénéraleCryptocurrency ETP issuer 21Shares has signed an ETP market-making fund platform agreement with Société Générale, which will support 21Shares&apos; Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, including: ABTC, CBTC, AETH, CETH, by providing over-the-counter liquidity through major fund platforms in Germany and Eastern Europe. (Globe Newswire) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038177276628992</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdaily21Shares Signs ETP Market Making Fund Platform Agreement with Société GénéraleCryptocurrency ETP issuer 21Shares has signed an ETP market-making fund platform agreement with Société Générale, which will support 21Shares&apos; Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs, including: ABTC, CBTC, AETH, CETH,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948038177276628992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group Increases Holdings by 117.93 BTC, Total Holdings Reach 628.22 BTCSwedish health tech company H100 Group announced the additional purchase of 117.93 Bitcoins, with an average purchase price of approximately 1,120,973.00 Swedish krona/Bitcoin, for a total amount of approximately 132.00 million Swedish krona (approximately $13.87 million). This increase is part of its Bitcoin treasury strategy, with some funds coming from the company&apos;s convertible bond agreement. H100 currently has a total holding of 628.22 BTC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948035325070217216</link>
      <description>3 hours ago吴说H100 Group Increases Holdings by 117.93 BTC, Total Holdings Reach 628.22 BTCSwedish health tech company H100 Group announced the additional purchase of 117.93 Bitcoins, with an average purchase price of approximately 1,120,973.00 Swedish krona/Bitcoin, for a total amount of approximatel</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948035325070217216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 18:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>