<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Azuki Partners with OpenSea to Release Mizuki Short Films as ERC-1155 CollectiblesOn July 24, according to official news, Azuki is working with OpenSea to release Mizuki short films as ERC-1155 collectibles. The proceeds will be used to support the production of Mizuki short films and help creators turn these stories into reality. The first version will be open for one week, and then the general version will be launched and open for 6 months. The casting price is 0.0014 ETH, with no limit on the number of wallets held and no whitelist requirements. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948202314191409152</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsAzuki Partners with OpenSea to Release Mizuki Short Films as ERC-1155 CollectiblesOn July 24, according to official news, Azuki is working with OpenSea to release Mizuki short films as ERC-1155 collectibles. The proceeds will be used to support the production of Mizuki short films</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948202314191409152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 24On this day in 2018, the organizers of ChinaJoy announced the establishment and hosting of the &quot;China Blockchain Technology and Game Developers Conference&quot;.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948201526094270464</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 24On this day in 2018, the organizers of ChinaJoy announced the establishment and hosting of the &quot;China Blockchain Technology and Game Developers Conference&quot;.#GameFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948201526094270464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares Partners with Société Générale to Expand European Crypto ETP Market CoverageCryptocurrency ETP issuer 21Shares has announced a market making agreement with Société Générale. According to the agreement, Société Générale will provide over-the-counter trading liquidity support for 21Shares&apos; Bitcoin and Ethereum ETPs (ABTC, CBTC, AETH, CETH) on key fund platforms in Germany and Eastern Europe, enabling these products to reach a wider group of professional investors. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948201555991269376</link>
      <description>8 minutes ago吴说21Shares Partners with Société Générale to Expand European Crypto ETP Market CoverageCryptocurrency ETP issuer 21Shares has announced a market making agreement with Société Générale. According to the agreement, Société Générale will provide over-the-counter trading liquidity support f</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948201555991269376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Solana Treasury Company Accelerate Plans to Raise $1.5 Billion, Joe McCann to Become CEOOn July 24, according to Unchained, Joe McCann, founder of crypto hedge fund Asymmetric, will serve as CEO of the newly established Solana treasury company Accelerate. The company plans to go public through a SPAC merger and intends to raise $1.5 billion in funds, of which $800.0 million will come from PIPE financing and $358.8 million will come from SPAC shell companies. If the fundraising is successful, Accelerate is expected to become the largest SOL treasury company with 7.32 million SOL (currently worth about $1.36 billion). Informed investors revealed that Accelerate&apos;s fundraising plan has been in preparation for several months, and the transaction is expected to be completed by the end of 2025. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948200794469240832</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoPANewsNew Solana Treasury Company Accelerate Plans to Raise $1.5 Billion, Joe McCann to Become CEOOn July 24, according to Unchained, Joe McCann, founder of crypto hedge fund Asymmetric, will serve as CEO of the newly established Solana treasury company Accelerate. The company plans to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948200794469240832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMP Top Fund transferred 1 billion PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $3.17M.According to Arkham monitoring, PUMP Top Fund 2: 58WQi2…ogv33E transferred 1.00B PUMP to Bybit Deposit at 9:01 UTC+8 today, worth approximately $3.17M. In the past 24 hours, this PUMP institutional investor has transferred 2.00B PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $6.95M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948200785577316352</link>
      <description>11 minutes ago吴说PUMP Top Fund transferred 1 billion PUMP to Bybit Deposit, worth approximately $3.17M.According to Arkham monitoring, PUMP Top Fund 2: 58WQi2…ogv33E transferred 1.00B PUMP to Bybit Deposit at 9:01 UTC+8 today, worth approximately $3.17M. In the past 24 hours, this PUMP institutional</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948200785577316352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pop artist Takashi Murakami to launch collectible trading cards onchain via Base appJapanese pop artist Takashi Murakami announced today that he plans to launch his collectible trading cards, 108 Flowers Revised, as NFTs.
&quot;My collectible trading cards — inspired by my physical works — are now onchain,&quot; Murakami said in an X post Wednesday, adding that it will be available for minting on the Base application. Minting is set to begin on July 31.
Murakami is known for his &quot;Superflat&quot; style, featuring smiling flowers and bold colors, with inspiration from pop culture, anime, manga and consumerism. He has previously collaborated with brands such as Louis Vuitton, Supreme and Vans, and various musical acts including Billie Eilish and New Jeans.
The artist has ventured into the NFT space since the 2021 boom, launching his own NFT line Murakami.Flowers on Ethereum. Murakami also collaborated with Nike&apos;s now-scrapped NFT project RTFKT.
The NFT market recently saw a surge in market capitalization, likely benefiting from the broader crypto market rally that has gone on for weeks. The total NFT market cap currently stands at around $6 billion, with a recent peak being above $6.6 billion on July 22. This is significantly higher than April&apos;s $3 billion and the highest level since January, according to Coingecko data.
&quot;The NFT markets gain momentum from the bullish trend and increased risk-on sentiment,&quot; LVRG Research Director Nick Ruck previously told The Block.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948199793607643136</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoThe BlockPop artist Takashi Murakami to launch collectible trading cards onchain via Base appJapanese pop artist Takashi Murakami announced today that he plans to launch his collectible trading cards, 108 Flowers Revised, as NFTs.
&quot;My collectible trading cards — inspired by my physical</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948199793607643136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fidelity Files to Amend Its Spot Bitcoin ETF to Allow Physical Redemptions and CreationsOn July 24, according to Bitcoin Magazine, Fidelity submitted documents to the US SEC to modify its spot Bitcoin ETF to allow physical redemption and creation. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948199610094260224</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoPANewsFidelity Files to Amend Its Spot Bitcoin ETF to Allow Physical Redemptions and CreationsOn July 24, according to Bitcoin Magazine, Fidelity submitted documents to the US SEC to modify its spot Bitcoin ETF to allow physical redemption and creation. [PANews]#ETF$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948199610094260224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant: Investors are shifting funds from Bitcoin to Ethereum and altcoinsCryptoQuant posted on the X platform: &quot;For the first time in more than a year: Ethereum spot trading volume exceeds Bitcoin. Last week, Ethereum spot trading volume reached US$25.7 billion, while Bitcoin spot trading volume was US$24.4 billion, making the ETH/BTC spot trading volume ratio exceed 1 for the first time since June 2024. Investors are turning their funds to Ethereum and various altcoins.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948198942788882432</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoPANewsCryptoQuant: Investors are shifting funds from Bitcoin to Ethereum and altcoinsCryptoQuant posted on the X platform: &quot;For the first time in more than a year: Ethereum spot trading volume exceeds Bitcoin. Last week, Ethereum spot trading volume reached US$25.7 billion, while Bitco</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948198942788882432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency &apos;control&apos; at center of Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm trialOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. prosecutors were preparing to close the prosecution&apos;s statement in the criminal case against Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm on Thursday and subpoenaed U.S. Internal Revenue Service (IRS) agent Stephan George to testify. George reviewed transaction records related to Crypto.com and Binance, saying that according to communication records between co-founders Storm, Alexey Pertsey, and Roman Semenov, Storm &quot;controlled&quot; the funds after an account associated with Binance sent cryptocurrency to the Tornado Cash smart contract address.
Previously, Storm&apos;s lawyers questioned the evidence based on the experience of Hanfeng Lin, a victim of the &quot;pig-butchering scam,&quot; saying that no funds flowed to the currency mixing service, and that they might apply for a retrial. They also said that Hanfeng Lin was not qualified to testify on the issue of tracking the proceeds of cryptocurrency crimes. The core of this case is whether Storm has the ability to control Tornado Cash by blocking or suppressing the laundering of illegal funds. Another government witness&apos; testimony revolved around the performance of the currency mixing tool under sanctions. Storm&apos;s lawyers also plan to summon &quot;two or three experts&quot; and Chainalysis expert witnesses to the court. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948196546369097728</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoPANewsCryptocurrency &apos;control&apos; at center of Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm trialOn July 24, according to Cointelegraph, U.S. prosecutors were preparing to close the prosecution&apos;s statement in the criminal case against Tornado Cash co-founder Roman Storm on Thursday and subpoenaed</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948196546369097728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bonk.fun: 1% of total revenue will be used to buy back leading tokens in the BONK ecosystemToken launch platform bonk.fun tweeted that &quot;Starting today, 1% of bonk.fun&apos;s total revenue will be reallocated from the marketing fund to repurchase leading tokens in the BONK ecosystem.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948195189532725248</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoForesightNewsbonk.fun: 1% of total revenue will be used to buy back leading tokens in the BONK ecosystemToken launch platform bonk.fun tweeted that &quot;Starting today, 1% of bonk.fun&apos;s total revenue will be reallocated from the marketing fund to repurchase leading tokens in the BONK ecosy</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948195189532725248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pumpfun Co-founder: Airdrop event will not be held in the near futurePumpfun co-founder Alon said in an interview with KOL Thread Guy that we are eager to reward the community that has supported our platform for the past year and a half, and our goal is to ensure that this airdrop is carried out smoothly and meaningfully. This will provide us with an excellent opportunity to strengthen our ecosystem, increase trading volume, and maintain activity over a longer period of time. This is crucial for re-attracting attention and sparking interest, but the airdrop will not be held in the near future, and the specific timeline and implementation details will be announced in the future. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948194411288006656</link>
      <description>36 minutes ago吴说Pumpfun Co-founder: Airdrop event will not be held in the near futurePumpfun co-founder Alon said in an interview with KOL Thread Guy that we are eager to reward the community that has supported our platform for the past year and a half, and our goal is to ensure that this airdrop is</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948194411288006656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet GM News1. Trump criticizes Powell, saying the FOMC should take action;
2. British media: US and Europe are close to reaching a 15% tariff agreement;
3. pump.fun co-founder: Airdrop will not be conducted in the near future;
4. White House&apos;s first crypto policy report to be released on July 30;
5. FTX to launch a new round of debt distribution on September 30, releasing $1.90B in disputed reserve funds;
6. Machi Big Brother&apos;s PUMP long positions have suffered floating losses of over $5.80M, and he continues to add to his positions;
7. Law firm Burwick Law expands its lawsuit against Pump.fun, listing Solana and Jito executives as defendants;
8. An institution lost $700,000.00 after participating in PUMP private placement and leaving the market;
9. Tron Inc. to ring the opening bell at Nasdaq on July 24;
10. DDC founder, a US-listed company: Plans to hold 10,000 BTC by the end of 2025 and become a top three BTC reserve company in the world within 3 years;
11. The US Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents;
12. Analysis: The batch un-staking of 620,000.00 ETH may be related to a sharp increase in borrowing rates due to a large withdrawal of ETH deposits from the Aave platform;
13. XRP&apos;s market cap surpasses Pepsi and BlackRock, approaching McDonald&apos;s;
14. BNB&apos;s market cap surpasses Starbucks, ranking 197th in global asset market cap;
15. Matador Technologies secures $100.00M in financing to purchase more Bitcoin;
16. Vaulta (formerly EOS) receives a $6.00M investment commitment from WLFI to promote Web3 banking development in the US;
17. Nature&apos;s Miracle Holding announces the launch of a $20.00M corporate XRP treasury program;
18. SharpLink Gaming generates 567 ETH in revenue through Ethereum staking;
19. Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon jointly launch a money market fund tokenization solution;
20. Analysis: Ethereum&apos;s rise is driven by ETF and corporate funds, with supply and demand imbalance as the main reason.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948194198892646400</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoOdailyPlanet GM News1. Trump criticizes Powell, saying the FOMC should take action;
2. British media: US and Europe are close to reaching a 15% tariff agreement;
3. pump.fun co-founder: Airdrop will not be conducted in the near future;
4. White House&apos;s first crypto policy report to be</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948194198892646400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale opened a short position of about 5,444 ETH, equivalent to about $19.82 million.On July 24, according to monitoring by on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the whale &quot;Set 10 Big Targets First&quot; (@jasonleo) opened a short position of 5444.155 ETH, about $19.82 million, with an opening price of $3,528.85 and a margin of $3.845 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948191907053637632</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsA whale opened a short position of about 5,444 ETH, equivalent to about $19.82 million.On July 24, according to monitoring by on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the whale &quot;Set 10 Big Targets First&quot; (@jasonleo) opened a short position of 5444.155 ETH, about $19.82 million, with an ope</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948191907053637632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bo Hines: White House&apos;s First Crypto Policy Report to be Publicly Released on July 30White House digital asset policy advisor Bo Hines tweeted that the President&apos;s Working Group on Digital Assets has completed its 180-day report, which will be released publicly on July 30. The report is expected to contain regulatory and legislative recommendations, but the specific content is not yet clear. The task force&apos;s original tasks included developing a federal digital asset framework covering stablecoins (Congress has initiated relevant procedures), and exploring whether to establish a national digital asset reserve (Trump established one in March). [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948190591325638656</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoForesightNewsBo Hines: White House&apos;s First Crypto Policy Report to be Publicly Released on July 30White House digital asset policy advisor Bo Hines tweeted that the President&apos;s Working Group on Digital Assets has completed its 180-day report, which will be released publicly on July 30.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948190591325638656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has taken profit on PENGU, with a total profit of $2.13MAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has sold 73.64M PENGU for 3.13M USDC, with an average transaction price of $0.042. The whale purchased this PENGU with 1.00M USDC three months ago and has now realized a profit of $2.13M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948191698001137664</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoOdailyA whale has taken profit on PENGU, with a total profit of $2.13MAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale has sold 73.64M PENGU for 3.13M USDC, with an average transaction price of $0.042. The whale purchased this PENGU with 1.00M USDC three months ago and has now realized a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948191698001137664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jasonleo shorted 5,444.155 ETH, worth approximately $19.82 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, jasonleo revealed his ETH short position 3 hours ago and stated that shorting BTC and ETH are not hedging behaviors. His account is shorting a total of 5444.155 ETH (approximately $19.82M), with an opening price of $3,528.85 and a margin of $3.845M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948189622512717824</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoForesightNewsjasonleo shorted 5,444.155 ETH, worth approximately $19.82 million.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, jasonleo revealed his ETH short position 3 hours ago and stated that shorting BTC and ETH are not hedging behaviors. His account is shorting a total of 5444.155 ETH (ap</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948189622512717824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha fund is winding down after suffering heavy lossesAccording to CoinDesk, Asymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha fund is gradually closing due to massive losses. Joe McCann said in a statement that investors can redeem their funds or roll capital into a new illiquid investment strategy. The company consists of multiple investment vehicles, and although the Liquid Alpha fund has performed poorly, other parts of the business, especially its venture capital strategy, remain intact. The venture capital arm will continue to support early-stage blockchain projects. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948188937616429056</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsAsymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha fund is winding down after suffering heavy lossesAccording to CoinDesk, Asymmetric&apos;s Liquid Alpha fund is gradually closing due to massive losses. Joe McCann said in a statement that investors can redeem their funds or roll capital into a new illiquid</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948188937616429056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited 3.000000M USDC into Hyperliquid and went long ETH 20 timesOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale 0x8F93 deposited 3.000 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened a 20x leveraged ETH long position, holding 7,200 ETH (worth US$26.300 million). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186715428032512</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsA whale deposited 3.000000M USDC into Hyperliquid and went long ETH 20 timesOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale 0x8F93 deposited 3.000 million USDC into Hyperliquid and opened a 20x leveraged ETH long position, holding 7,200 ETH (worth US$26.300 million). [PANe</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186715428032512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Let&apos;s break up this company&quot;! Trump reveals: He once considered splitting up Nvidia&quot;I originally thought we could step in, break them up a bit, and create some competition, but it turns out this industry isn&apos;t easy to do that with.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948203101508407296</link>
      <description>1 hour ago行业观察&quot;Let&apos;s break up this company&quot;! Trump reveals: He once considered splitting up Nvidia&quot;I originally thought we could step in, break them up a bit, and create some competition, but it turns out this industry isn&apos;t easy to do that with.&quot;Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948203101508407296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law firm Burwick Law expands lawsuit against pump.fun, names Solana and Jito executives as defendants.According to The Block, law firms Burwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against pump.fun to include the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito, and their executives as defendants, including Solana co-founders Anatoly Yakovenko and Raj Gokal, Solana Foundation Executive Director Dan Albert, Chairman Lily Liu, and former Head of Communications Austin Federa. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186400939118592</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsLaw firm Burwick Law expands lawsuit against pump.fun, names Solana and Jito executives as defendants.According to The Block, law firms Burwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against pump.fun to include the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito, an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 01:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948186400939118592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>