<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:46:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX will list COOKIE (Cookie DAO) at 17:00 on July 24, and will simultaneously add COOKIE/USDT (10X) for isolated margin trading.
According to an announcement by Huobi HTX on July 23, Huobi HTX will open the deposit service for COOKIE at 17:30 (GMT+8) on July 23. The COOKIE/USDT spot trading will be opened at 17:00 (GMT+8) on July 24. The withdrawal service for COOKIE will be opened at 17:00 (GMT+8) on July 25. At the same time, Huobi Leverage will add COOKIE/USDT (10X) isolated margin trading at 17:00 (GMT+8) on July 24.
It is reported that COOKIE is the utility token of Cookie DAO and represents the &quot;information value&quot; in the agentic economy. Its core function is to ensure that Cookie DAO continuously collects and indexes the growing AI agent data.
 [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947954870396456960</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX will list COOKIE (Cookie DAO) at 17:00 on July 24, and will simultaneously add COOKIE/USDT (10X) for isolated margin trading.
According to an announcement by Huobi HTX on July 23, Huobi HTX will open the deposit service for COOKIE at 17:30 (GMT+8) on July 23. The COOKI</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947954870396456960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fartcoin derivatives open interest ranks among the top ten, speculative boom emergesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Fartcoin (FARTCOIN), a meme coin of the Solana ecosystem, has now become one of the top ten tokens in terms of open interest in cryptocurrency derivatives. Data shows that the nominal open interest of Fartcoin-related futures has exceeded $1.00 billion, surpassing mainstream currencies such as Litecoin, LINK, and AVAX. It is worth noting that Fartcoin&apos;s open interest has reached 65.00% of its market value, while its market value ranks 83rd in the world. This abnormally high open interest is considered a signal of overheated market speculation. Similar phenomena are also reflected in other small-cap currencies, which may lead to large-scale investor liquidation risks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947953345834061824</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoPANewsFartcoin derivatives open interest ranks among the top ten, speculative boom emergesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Fartcoin (FARTCOIN), a meme coin of the Solana ecosystem, has now become one of the top ten tokens in terms of open interest in cryptocurrency derivatives. Data</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947953345834061824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted on the X platform, saying, &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world economy (except for food and energy production) is essentially a status game, so how could the internet society be any different?&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955124432867328</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyArthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted on the X platform, saying, &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world econom</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955124432867328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southeast Asian stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Philippine OTC institution Moneybees to optimize the remittance experience for overseas Filipino workers.Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Moneybees, the largest over-the-counter (OTC) institution in the Philippines. This collaboration optimizes the remittance experience for Overseas Filipino Workers (OFW) by combining stablecoin technology with offline exchange networks. Users who receive stablecoin remittances can convert APACX-incubated Philippine Peso stablecoin PHT into cash at Moneybees&apos; more than 1,000 offline locations in the Philippines. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952904685555712</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoForesightNewsSoutheast Asian stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Philippine OTC institution Moneybees to optimize the remittance experience for overseas Filipino workers.Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX has reached a strategic p</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952904685555712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoPANewsSouth Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that Galaxy Digital is well-positioned to capture upside opportunities in a favorable cryptocurrency regulatory environment. The investment bank noted that the passage of the U.S. GENIUS Act provides a &quot;favorable market structure&quot; for Galaxy&apos;s business. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoTechFlowJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits.Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino posted that the Tether Group has invested in over 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. Relevant investment information has been published on the official Tether website. Paolo Ardoino stated that the source of funds is independent of USDT and other stablecoin reserves (reaching $13.70B in 2024) and falls within the business scope of Tether Investments investment division. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952604511801344</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyTether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits.Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino posted that the Tether Group has invested in over 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. Relevant investm</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952604511801344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Pastor Charged in $3.40M Crypto ScamA Denver, Colorado-based online pastor and his wife were indicted on Tuesday in connection with a cryptocurrency fraud scheme that raised over $3 million from faith-based investors. Between January 2022 and July 2023, the Regalados raised nearly $3.40 million by encouraging people in their religion to purchase INDXcoin through the Kingdom Wealth Exchange platform, with at least 300 people investing in the token and suffering losses. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947948979861393408</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoForesightNewsColorado Pastor Charged in $3.40M Crypto ScamA Denver, Colorado-based online pastor and his wife were indicted on Tuesday in connection with a cryptocurrency fraud scheme that raised over $3 million from faith-based investors. Between January 2022 and July 2023, the Regala</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947948979861393408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares obtains EU MiCA license, becoming the first licensed crypto asset management companyOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, European crypto asset management company CoinShares announced that it had obtained the EU&apos;s &quot;Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation&quot; (MiCA) license, becoming the first European crypto asset management company to obtain this license. The license was issued by the French Financial Markets Authority (AMF), enabling CoinShares to provide crypto asset portfolio management services within the 27 EU countries, and together with its existing MiFID and AIFM licenses, it constitutes a triple regulatory qualification. CoinShares said that this milestone is expected to promote the EU&apos;s $38.7 trillion asset management industry to further open up compliant crypto investment products. So far, the company has managed assets of more than $9 billion, and its stock price has risen by more than 46% this year. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946967392391168</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsCoinShares obtains EU MiCA license, becoming the first licensed crypto asset management companyOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, European crypto asset management company CoinShares announced that it had obtained the EU&apos;s &quot;Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation&quot; (MiCA) license, beco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946967392391168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$51.5214 millionOn July 23, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$51.5214 million. Among them:
The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$22.4015 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$23.3565 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$1.0478 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$0.9224 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$1.8167 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$1.9765 million.
Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946525744762880</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$51.5214 millionOn July 23, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$51.5214 million. Among them:
The tran</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946525744762880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Stock Exchange holds a symposium for companies in the Shanghai artificial intelligence industry chainOn July 23, the Shanghai Stock Exchange conducted a special survey on Shanghai&apos;s &quot;Model Speed Space&quot; and jointly held a symposium with the Xuhui District People&apos;s Government on Shanghai&apos;s artificial intelligence industry chain enterprises, and had in-depth face-to-face exchanges with key enterprises, investment institutions, and sponsors to accelerate the construction of a good ecology adapted to the era of artificial intelligence science and innovation. The Shanghai Stock Exchange said that it hopes that high-quality technology companies at different stages of development will seize the development opportunities of the capital market, make full use of policy reform tools, and use the capital market to become better and stronger, and win new advantages for future development with technological innovation. In the next step, the Shanghai Stock Exchange will follow the unified deployment of the China Securities Regulatory Commission, take the &quot;1+6&quot; policy of the Science and Technology Innovation Board reform as an opportunity, widely gather market consensus, and use cutting-edge technology fields such as artificial intelligence as strategic fulcrums to further strengthen the cultivation and service of high-quality technology companies throughout their life cycle, product lines, and business chains, accelerate the implementation of typical cases as soon as possible, and promote the development of new quality productivity to a new level. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945987372290048</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoPANewsShanghai Stock Exchange holds a symposium for companies in the Shanghai artificial intelligence industry chainOn July 23, the Shanghai Stock Exchange conducted a special survey on Shanghai&apos;s &quot;Model Speed Space&quot; and jointly held a symposium with the Xuhui District People&apos;s Governm</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945987372290048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address transferred 16.81M XRP, worth $58.37M, to CoinbaseOn July 23, according to Whale Alert monitoring, an address transferred 16,812,113 XRP to Coinbase, worth approximately $58,365,018.00. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945654059339776</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoTechFlowAn address transferred 16.81M XRP, worth $58.37M, to CoinbaseOn July 23, according to Whale Alert monitoring, an address transferred 16,812,113 XRP to Coinbase, worth approximately $58,365,018.00. [TechFlow]#Crypto Stocks$MAG7.SSI$XRP$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945654059339776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Now Lists COAThe official interface shows that Binance Alpha has listed COA. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947947571019845632</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha Now Lists COAThe official interface shows that Binance Alpha has listed COA. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947947571019845632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of stablecoin licensing regime next weekOn July 23, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, said that the Stablecoin Ordinance will take effect on August 1, when it will be illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoin to the Hong Kong public. He pointed out that there have been recent scams targeting stablecoins and digital assets in the market, causing losses to the public. In response to market concerns about the application process, the HKMA plans to publish a summary of the &quot;Licensing System for Stablecoin Issuers&quot; next week, which will detail the acceptance and processing arrangements for license applications. Eddie Yue called on interested parties to stay tuned. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944419080081408</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of stablecoin licensing regime next weekOn July 23, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, said that the Stablecoin Ordinance will take effect on August 1, when it will be illegal to promote any unlicensed s</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944419080081408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sygnum: Bitcoin network transaction volume surpasses VisaRegulated digital asset bank Sygnum said that the Bitcoin network&apos;s existing annual transaction volume is estimated at $20 trillion, exceeding Visa&apos;s $13 trillion. The report also highlighted other data, such as Bitcoin&apos;s liquid supply on exchanges falling to a near seven-year low, ETFs currently holding over $150.00 billion in Bitcoin, and publicly listed companies holding approximately $80.00 billion in Bitcoin. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944481038340096</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoForesightNewsSygnum: Bitcoin network transaction volume surpasses VisaRegulated digital asset bank Sygnum said that the Bitcoin network&apos;s existing annual transaction volume is estimated at $20 trillion, exceeding Visa&apos;s $13 trillion. The report also highlighted other data, such as Bitc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944481038340096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi to Mars, they are pioneering narratives! Sun, who is flying to space, and the women who are changing the industry.&quot; YIYI, Damei Una, Li Qian, Silvia Wanqing, Crayon Xiaomi and other crypto KOLs will gather together to discuss the female power unique to Web3. This event will be broadcast simultaneously via Huobi Live and X Space, with constant red envelope rain, so stay tuned. Book a live broadcast: https://www.htx.com.de/zh-cn/live/detail/h5?id=79115&amp;invite_code=ip549223&amp;inviter_id=11351630 [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure with native on-chain staking rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoForesightNewsREX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito is postponing the Espresso launch to July 24th at 20:00.Due to KYC process issues, Kaito has postponed the launch of Espresso to 20:00 on July 24th. Kaito has partnered with identity platform Persona to update the KYC address verification section. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942693002350592</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoForesightNewsKaito is postponing the Espresso launch to July 24th at 20:00.Due to KYC process issues, Kaito has postponed the launch of Espresso to 20:00 on July 24th. Kaito has partnered with identity platform Persona to update the KYC address verification section. [Foresight News]Sha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942693002350592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side.The Ministry of Commerce stated that, as agreed upon by both China and the United States, He Lifeng, member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and Vice Premier of the State Council, will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the United States. The two sides will follow the important consensus reached by the two heads of state during their phone call on June 5th, give full play to the role of the China-U.S. economic and trade consultation mechanism, and continue to conduct consultations on economic and trade issues of mutual concern based on the principles of mutual respect, peaceful coexistence, and win-win cooperation. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942527096655872</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoOdailyHe Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side.The Ministry of Commerce stated that, as agreed upon by both China and the United States, He Lifeng, member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and Vice Premi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942527096655872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>