<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital Founder: ETH&apos;s Strong Performance is Nearing the End of FluctuationsLD Capital founder Jack Yi said, &quot;ETH is strongly approaching the end of the volatility. This was originally a huge pressure level, a place where many OGs collectively got out of trouble. In a bull market trend, no matter what the negative news is, don&apos;t short or try to short as much as possible, and stick to the principle of trend investing.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948403486449799168</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsLD Capital Founder: ETH&apos;s Strong Performance is Nearing the End of FluctuationsLD Capital founder Jack Yi said, &quot;ETH is strongly approaching the end of the volatility. This was originally a huge pressure level, a place where many OGs collectively got out of trouble. In a bu</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948403486449799168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men suspected in New York cryptocurrency kidnapping torture case released on million-dollar bailTwo suspects, John Woeltz and William Duplessie, accused of kidnapping and abusing a Bitcoin investor in New York, were granted bail on Wednesday for $1.00M each. Despite facing charges that could lead to life imprisonment, the judge stated that the credibility of witnesses and discrepancies in the narratives of both sides in the case led to the decision to grant bail. Prosecutors allege that the two men subjected an Italian businessman to two weeks of violent coercion, including electric shocks, beatings, and death threats, with the aim of obtaining crypto assets. The defense claims that the so-called &quot;victim&quot; was not forcibly detained and submitted videos of him participating in social activities as evidence. Casa Security stated that it has tracked 30 similar incidents in the first half of 2025 alone, calling on crypto holders to strengthen their physical security. [Decrypt]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948403060937658368</link>
      <description>6 minutes ago吴说Two men suspected in New York cryptocurrency kidnapping torture case released on million-dollar bailTwo suspects, John Woeltz and William Duplessie, accused of kidnapping and abusing a Bitcoin investor in New York, were granted bail on Wednesday for $1.00M each. Despite facing charges</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948403060937658368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Monetary Fund: El Salvador&apos;s strategic Bitcoin reserve fund accumulation of Bitcoin meets planned conditionsAccording to Jinshi, the International Monetary Fund stated that El Salvador&apos;s strategic Bitcoin reserve fund&apos;s accumulation of Bitcoin meets the program conditions. El Salvador&apos;s Bitcoin holdings are in line with the country&apos;s planned commitments. The total amount of Bitcoin held in the El Salvadoran government wallet remains unchanged. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948402566408245248</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsInternational Monetary Fund: El Salvador&apos;s strategic Bitcoin reserve fund accumulation of Bitcoin meets planned conditionsAccording to Jinshi, the International Monetary Fund stated that El Salvador&apos;s strategic Bitcoin reserve fund&apos;s accumulation of Bitcoin meets the progra</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948402566408245248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana Foundation and ecosystem partners jointly release &quot;Internet Capital Market&quot; roadmapThe Solana Foundation, Anza, Jito Labs, DoubleZero, Drift, and Multicoin Capital leaders have co-authored a roadmap for the &quot;Internet Capital Markets.&quot; It proposes application-controlled execution (ACE) as the core direction for future evolution, with the goal of creating the next generation of decentralized, high-performance financial infrastructure. The roadmap points out that the biggest challenge currently lies in market microstructure optimization, with ACE allowing smart contracts to control transaction sequencing with millisecond-level precision. In the long-term plan, Solana will implement an MCL (multi-leader parallel proposal) architecture to break through the &quot;single proposer bottleneck,&quot; improve censorship resistance, and achieve global market synchronization. [CoinDesk]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948401654734327808</link>
      <description>12 minutes ago吴说Solana Foundation and ecosystem partners jointly release &quot;Internet Capital Market&quot; roadmapThe Solana Foundation, Anza, Jito Labs, DoubleZero, Drift, and Multicoin Capital leaders have co-authored a roadmap for the &quot;Internet Capital Markets.&quot; It proposes application-controlled executi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948401654734327808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +4.02%, ADA +1.64%, SUI +1.57%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948401221751496704</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +4.02%, ADA +1.64%, SUI +1.57%.$ETH$ADA$SUIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948401221751496704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraken Announces Integration of INK Token and its Ink Layer 2 Network into Core Product SystemKraken has announced the integration of the INK token and its Ink Layer 2 network into its core product system, opening it up to global users and simultaneously including it in the Kraken Drops airdrop reward program. Officials stated that this move aims to promote the integration of on-chain infrastructure and centralized platforms, and expand scenarios such as liquidity aggregation, on-chain lending, and trading. Ink Network is a member of the Optimism &quot;Superchain&quot; ecosystem, and is in the same expansion system as Base, Uniswap L2, Sony Chain, etc. [TheBlock]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948399647675977728</link>
      <description>19 minutes ago吴说Kraken Announces Integration of INK Token and its Ink Layer 2 Network into Core Product SystemKraken has announced the integration of the INK token and its Ink Layer 2 network into its core product system, opening it up to global users and simultaneously including it in the Kraken Dr</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948399647675977728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz Predicts Bitcoin To Hit $150,000 Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz told CNBC this week that he believes Bitcoin could reach $150,000 in the near term—driven by strong market momentum and favorable macro conditions. JUST IN: 🇺🇸 Galaxy Digital CEO on CNBC predicts  #Bitcoin  to hit $150,000 🚀  pic.twitter.com/372in1k54y “Yeah, listen, we’re in price discovery in a lot of these things, and $150k seems to me a decent  target ,” said Novogratz during the CNBC interview.  He acknowledged that there’s been resistance along the way, noting that “we have seen sellers that have come in, right? And so it’s not a one-directional trade, there have been some sellers that have come in and slowed things down.”  Still, Novogratz believes the trend remains upward, as long as current narratives hold. “But it feels like we’re destined to go higher, as long as this narrative continues,” he added. He cautioned that a shift in interest rate expectations, particularly if former President Trump were to signal strength in the economy that negates the need for rate cuts, could alter the trajectory. “If Trump changes his mind, you know, and says, hey, we’ve done such good work, the economy doesn’t need lower rates, that would change my thesis. But until that happens, I think we’re headed towards $150k.”  This isn’t the first time Novogratz has forecasted a bullish price prediction for Bitcoin. In a June 12 CNBC interview, he  stated  that Bitcoin could one day replace gold and even reach $1,000,000. “Bitcoin has become a macro asset,” he said. “It’s just becoming institutionalized.”  JUST IN: 🇺🇸 Galaxy Digital CEO told CNBC that Bitcoin will replace gold and go to $1,000,000 🚀  pic.twitter.com/Tf831LBt1h Novogratz pointed to a weakening U.S. dollar, increased institutional adoption, and Bitcoin’s fixed supply of 21 million as critical components of its  long-term growth . “There is no more Bitcoin,” he noted. “There have been more Bitcoins lost than will be mined for the rest of eternity.”  He argued that Bitcoin’s scarcity, coupled with its growing role in diversified portfolios alongside gold and silver, is pushing it closer to mainstream acceptance. “The bull case becomes that over time, gold slowly gets replaced by Bitcoin,” said Novogratz. “So that is $1,000,000 a Bitcoin just to be where gold is.” [Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948400890506973184</link>
      <description>21 minutes agobitcoinmagazineGalaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz Predicts Bitcoin To Hit $150,000 Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz told CNBC this week that he believes Bitcoin could reach $150,000 in the near term—driven by strong market momentum and favorable macro conditions. JUST IN: 🇺🇸 Galaxy D</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948400890506973184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>glassnode: Increased WETH Lending Rates on Aave Cause stETH to DepegAccording to glassnode data, the increase in WETH lending rates on Aave has made stETH leveraged loops unprofitable, triggering the liquidation of ETH/stETH pool imbalances and causing stETH to depeg, exacerbating ETH&apos;s selling pressure. In addition, the growing validator exit queue has also increased arbitrage resistance, slowing the recovery of the peg. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948398385425354752</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoForesightNewsglassnode: Increased WETH Lending Rates on Aave Cause stETH to DepegAccording to glassnode data, the increase in WETH lending rates on Aave has made stETH leveraged loops unprofitable, triggering the liquidation of ETH/stETH pool imbalances and causing stETH to depeg, exac</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948398385425354752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-GN Announces $5.00M Pre-Seed Funding RoundCentralized AI data platform D-GN (Data Guardians Network) has announced the completion of a $5.00M Pre-Seed funding round, co-invested by droppGroup, Saudi businessman Hamoud Al-Rumayyan, and veteran crypto institution Hub Culture. D-GN uses blockchain technology for data traceability verification and pays stablecoin rewards to global contributors via USDT, emphasizing the elimination of gray content sources and low-cost data outsourcing. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948398079882891264</link>
      <description>26 minutes ago吴说D-GN Announces $5.00M Pre-Seed Funding RoundCentralized AI data platform D-GN (Data Guardians Network) has announced the completion of a $5.00M Pre-Seed funding round, co-invested by droppGroup, Saudi businessman Hamoud Al-Rumayyan, and veteran crypto institution Hub Culture. D-GN us</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948398079882891264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: ETH is now at $3,705.389According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,705.389.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395146662862848</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: ETH is now at $3,705.389According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.02% in the past 24h. Now at $3,705.389.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395146662862848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is up 1.50% in the past 1H, up 2.97% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395126324682752</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is up 1.50% in the past 1H, up 2.97% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395126324682752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America: Stablecoin market to grow by $25B-$75B in the near termBank of America (BofA), one of the four largest banks in the United States, released a report stating that with the GENIUS Act officially signed into law last week, U.S. stablecoin regulation has entered a critical turning point, and the stablecoin supply is expected to grow by $25.00B to $75.00B in the short term. The report points out that regulatory clarity will drive product launches, infrastructure investment, and alliance stablecoin issuance models among banks. BofA also noted that the increased demand for short-term U.S. Treasury bonds from stablecoin reserves may prompt the Treasury Department to adjust the structure of Treasury bond issuance. [CoinDesk]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948394962437083136</link>
      <description>38 minutes ago吴说Bank of America: Stablecoin market to grow by $25B-$75B in the near termBank of America (BofA), one of the four largest banks in the United States, released a report stating that with the GENIUS Act officially signed into law last week, U.S. stablecoin regulation has entered a critic</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948394962437083136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Ethereum core developer: The bullish logic for ETH in the coming years is not corporate balance sheet allocation, but the global adoption of stablecoins.Former Ethereum core developer Eric Conner posted on social media that the bullish logic for ETH in the next few years is not corporate balance sheet allocation, but the global adoption of stablecoins. He pointed out that people around the world want access to USD exposure, and this demand will see explosive growth. In the process, potentially billions of people will discover the Ethereum network. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395527736987648</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoOdailyFormer Ethereum core developer: The bullish logic for ETH in the coming years is not corporate balance sheet allocation, but the global adoption of stablecoins.Former Ethereum core developer Eric Conner posted on social media that the bullish logic for ETH in the next few years i</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948395527736987648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America: U.S. stablecoin supply may increase by $25 billion to $75 billion in the short term due to the GENIUS ActOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, Bank of America said that with the passage of the GENIUS Act, the supply of stablecoins is expected to grow by $25 billion to $75 billion in the short term. The bill lays the foundation for stablecoin regulation in the United States and promotes the development of related infrastructure and tokenized finance. Bank of America also pointed out that the banking industry is preparing to issue stablecoins through a consortium model, and this growth is expected to drive an increase in demand for U.S. Treasuries and promote the widespread adoption of digital assets. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948392923267141632</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsBank of America: U.S. stablecoin supply may increase by $25 billion to $75 billion in the short term due to the GENIUS ActOn July 24, according to CoinDesk, Bank of America said that with the passage of the GENIUS Act, the supply of stablecoins is expected to grow by $25 billion</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948392923267141632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1.0350 million ETH since July, bringing its total holdings to 2.8000 million.According to Lookonchain monitoring, BlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1,035,653 ETH since July 1st, worth approximately $3.76B. BlackRock currently holds a total of 2.80M ETH, worth approximately $10.22B. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948393003449651200</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoOdailyBlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1.0350 million ETH since July, bringing its total holdings to 2.8000 million.According to Lookonchain monitoring, BlackRock has cumulatively increased its holdings by 1,035,653 ETH since July 1st, worth approximately $3.76B. Bl</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948393003449651200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, will ship on August 4th; users with unconfirmed addresses may miss the first batch.Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, announced that it will begin shipping on August 4th. If users have pre-ordered but have not yet confirmed their shipping address and taxes, the device may be delayed, thus missing the first batch of shipments. Users are reminded to update as soon as possible. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948388922261835776</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsSolana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, will ship on August 4th; users with unconfirmed addresses may miss the first batch.Solana&apos;s second-generation phone, Seeker, announced that it will begin shipping on August 4th. If users have pre-ordered but have not yet confirmed thei</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948388922261835776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine increases its market stock offering to $4.50B to increase its Ethereum holdingsBitmine Immersion (BMNR) has increased the size of its &quot;at-the-market&quot; (ATM) program from $2.00 billion to $4.50 billion. The company filed a prospectus supplement with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on July 24, authorizing the continuous sale of common stock in the open market through two brokerage firms, Cantor Fitzgerald and ThinkEquity. This additional issuance provides financial support for the company to further increase its ETH holdings and expand its asset reserves. According to previous reports, Bitmine updated its ETH holdings, and as of 11:59 PM ET on July 23, 2025 (11:59 AM Beijing time today), Bitmine held a total of 566,776 ETH, worth more than $2.00 billion. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387989222133760</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitmine increases its market stock offering to $4.50B to increase its Ethereum holdingsBitmine Immersion (BMNR) has increased the size of its &quot;at-the-market&quot; (ATM) program from $2.00 billion to $4.50 billion. The company filed a prospectus supplement with the U.S. Securities and Exch</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948387989222133760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign sponsors American esports club NTMR to compete in the Esports World Cup
On July 24, blockchain digital infrastructure company Sign announced a partnership with well-known esports club NTMR to jointly establish the Sign Esports club, which will compete in the 2025 Esports World Cup with a brand new orange brand.
Sign is a technology company building blockchain infrastructure, providing token distribution services to 40 million blockchain users.
NTMR is one of the most active esports clubs in North America, with its teams repeatedly achieving excellent results in events such as Overwatch 2 and Rainbow Six. Recent achievements include winning the first stage of the 2025 Overwatch Championship Series North America and the Marvel Rivals North American Invitational Tournament, as well as reaching the top three in the 2025 Global Finals, demonstrating strong dominance.
 [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385430822522880</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowSign sponsors American esports club NTMR to compete in the Esports World Cup
On July 24, blockchain digital infrastructure company Sign announced a partnership with well-known esports club NTMR to jointly establish the Sign Esports club, which will compete in the 2025 Esports World</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385430822522880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchorage Digital to issue first GENIUS‑compliant stablecoin in US with Ethena LabsAnchorage Digital, the first federally chartered crypto bank in the United States, will issue Ethena Labs’ USDtb token onshore as the first stablecoin engineered to comply with the new GENIUS Act, the companies said on Thursday.

Ethena’s USDtb is a yield-bearing dollar token primarily backed by BlackRock’s BUIDL and crypto collateral rather than traditional reserves to maintain its $1 peg. The synthetic stablecoin has circulated offshore since December and amassed $1.45 billion in total value locked, according to DefiLlama data.

Under the partnership, Anchorage Digital Bank will mint and redeem USDtb tokens directly in the U.S., bringing the asset under a federal regulatory umbrella for the first time. Anchorage said its stablecoin issuance platform will serve as a turnkey infrastructure for Ethena’s stablecoin to “launch and distribute fully regulated digital dollars.”

The move comes one week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act, the country’s first law governing stablecoin issuance. Industry players and U.S. officials like Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent expect the legislation to accelerate demand from asset managers, payments firms, and corporates looking for yield‑bearing, programmable dollars.

The passage of GENIUS gives federally regulated institutions a green light and clarity to participate in the stablecoin ecosystem, Anchorage CEO Nathan McCauley noted in the release.

Guy Young, Ethena Labs CEO, added that products like USDtb stand to benefit from federal oversight and regulated appetite. “While we’ve already seen strong demand for USDtb, we expect GENIUS compliance to empower our partners and holders to confidently and significantly expand its use across new products and platforms,” he said.

Anchorage’s announcement positions it alongside giants such as Circle and PayPal, which already operate dollar‑pegged tokens but must adapt to GENIUS requirements. Major banks like JPMorganand Citihave flagged plans to experiment with stablecoins and deposit‑backed tokens once the rules settle. [companies]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385281941508096</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockAnchorage Digital to issue first GENIUS‑compliant stablecoin in US with Ethena LabsAnchorage Digital, the first federally chartered crypto bank in the United States, will issue Ethena Labs’ USDtb token onshore as the first stablecoin engineered to comply with the new GENIUS Act, t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948385281941508096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether: Gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold (XAUT) has a market cap of approximately $814.00MTether has released the latest data for Tether Gold (XAUT) for the second quarter of 2025. The total circulation of the gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold is 246,524.33 coins, corresponding to 246,524.38 troy ounces of physical gold (approximately 7.66 tons), with a market value of approximately $814.00M. All physical gold reserves of XAUT are stored in Switzerland and meet London delivery standards. Tether stated that the current global macro environment is turbulent, and gold-based digital assets are becoming an important tool in investors&apos; hedging portfolios. XAUT serves as a compliant on-chain gold solution that can be transferred. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948389936792670208</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Tether: Gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold (XAUT) has a market cap of approximately $814.00MTether has released the latest data for Tether Gold (XAUT) for the second quarter of 2025. The total circulation of the gold-backed stablecoin Tether Gold is 246,524.33 coins, corresponding to 246</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 14:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948389936792670208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>