<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:58:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Thai SEC Considers Relaxing Crypto Investor Testing RulesAccording to Decrypt, the Securities and Exchange Commission of Thailand has proposed amending ICO regulatory rules to allow non-institutional investors to avoid repeated testing after passing a knowledge test once, replacing the current requirement of testing every three months. The new rules will require ICO portals to conduct suitability tests on all digital token investors and review them every two years to ensure that investors&apos; risk tolerance matches the product risk. This move aims to reduce the burden on investors and align with existing securities regulatory standards. The public can submit comments on the proposal before August 1. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947203872187764736</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsThai SEC Considers Relaxing Crypto Investor Testing RulesAccording to Decrypt, the Securities and Exchange Commission of Thailand has proposed amending ICO regulatory rules to allow non-institutional investors to avoid repeated testing after passing a knowledge test once, r</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947203872187764736</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: ETH is now at $3,786According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.08% in the past 24h. Now at $3,786.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202446030757888</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: ETH is now at $3,786According to SoSoValue, ETH (Ethereum) is up 3.08% in the past 24h. Now at $3,786.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202446030757888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ping An of China: Will Continue to Pay Attention to Regulatory Changes in Hong Kong Stablecoins and Actively Conduct ResearchPing An of China stated that it has noticed the regulatory changes in the Hong Kong market regarding stablecoins. The company has a deep accumulation of blockchain technology and will pay close attention to this and actively carry out relevant research. (Cailian Press) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202649745281024</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailyPing An of China: Will Continue to Pay Attention to Regulatory Changes in Hong Kong Stablecoins and Actively Conduct ResearchPing An of China stated that it has noticed the regulatory changes in the Hong Kong market regarding stablecoins. The company has a deep accumulation of blo</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202649745281024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave community vote approves ARFC proposal to deploy a white-label version of Aave V3 on the Ink chainThe Aave community has passed a proposal authorizing the Ink Foundation to deploy a white-label version of the Aave V3 lending platform on the Ink chain. The platform will be centrally governed by the Ink Foundation, branded as &quot;Powered by Aave,&quot; and will not have a governance token. The Aave DAO will receive no less than 5% of the platform&apos;s lending revenue as a share. Aave ecosystem service providers (such as ACI, Chaos Labs, etc.) will assist in operation and maintenance for the first 6 months, and Ink will arrange its own commercial support thereafter. Ink has committed to injecting over $250.00M in initial liquidity and reserving 4% of future governance tokens for incentives. The platform is not included in the Aave DAO insurance system, and Ink will exclusively operate the lending protocol for 12 months after deployment. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202459332268032</link>
      <description>11 minutes ago吴说Aave community vote approves ARFC proposal to deploy a white-label version of Aave V3 on the Ink chainThe Aave community has passed a proposal authorizing the Ink Foundation to deploy a white-label version of the Aave V3 lending platform on the Ink chain. The platform will be central</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202459332268032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian publicly traded company Jetking&apos;s board of directors approves the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares to further expand its Bitcoin strategy.The board of directors of Indian listed company Jetking has approved the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares (approximately $1.30M at most) to further expand its Bitcoin strategy. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202428940341248</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoForesightNewsIndian publicly traded company Jetking&apos;s board of directors approves the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares to further expand its Bitcoin strategy.The board of directors of Indian listed company Jetking has approved the issuance of 460,000 preferred shares (approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947202428940341248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A certain whale is currently shorting altcoins with a floating loss of $12.48M.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, the wallet address that &quot;once leveraged $2.82M to arbitrage 14.81M USDe&quot; recently opened mixed long and short positions on Hyperliquid. The long positions only include BTC and AAVE, while the remaining 26 currencies are short positions. Currently, only 38% are in a floating profit state, with a cumulative floating loss of $12.48M, of which XRP alone has a loss of $9.00M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200152184049664</link>
      <description>21 minutes agoOdailyA certain whale is currently shorting altcoins with a floating loss of $12.48M.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi @ai_9684xtpa&apos;s monitoring, the wallet address that &quot;once leveraged $2.82M to arbitrage 14.81M USDe&quot; recently opened mixed long and short positions on Hyperliquid. Th</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200152184049664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale with over $24.00M in long position profits has opened multiple short positions.According to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited $5.00M USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple leveraged short positions, including: SOL (20x), DOGE, FARTCOIN, BONK, LTC, PEPE (all 10x), and PENGU, SPX (both 5x). In addition, the whale holds multiple long positions in another address, with current unrealized profits exceeding $24.00M. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200160639766528</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoOdailyA whale with over $24.00M in long position profits has opened multiple short positions.According to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited $5.00M USDC into Hyperliquid and opened multiple leveraged short positions, including: SOL (20x), DOGE, FARTCOIN, BONK, LTC, PEPE (all 10x</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947200160639766528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch CSKY spot tradingOn July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will list the following trading pairs on July 21: Spot trading pair CSKY/USDT (July 21, 20:20 UTC+8): $CSKY is the native token of the CoreSky project. Coresky is a new generation Web3 meme incubation platform that aims to discover, empower, and launch community-driven meme projects. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195954121953280</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch CSKY spot tradingOn July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will list the following trading pairs on July 21: Spot trading pair CSKY/USDT (July 21, 20:20 UTC+8): $CSKY is the native token of the CoreSky project. Coresky is a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195954121953280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX-sponsored ChainCatcher &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party in Hanoi, Vietnam will be held on July 31.The &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party, sponsored by HTX and hosted by ChainCatcher, will be grandly held in Hanoi, Vietnam on July 31st from 19:30 - 22:30 (GMT+7). As the third time this brand event has been held in Vietnam, previous events have successfully brought together leading local Vietnamese Web3 project teams, top investors, well-known KOLs, and core community members, creating a highly influential communication platform in the industry. This event will further promote in-depth cooperation and resource docking within the Vietnamese Web3 ecosystem. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195150010961920</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoChainCatcherHTX-sponsored ChainCatcher &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party in Hanoi, Vietnam will be held on July 31.The &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party, sponsored by HTX and hosted by ChainCatcher, will be grandly held in Hanoi, Vietnam on July 31st from 19:30 - 22:30</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195150010961920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinTax Founder: Web3-related crypto income may become a focus of taxation in the futureIn recent years, the data analysis capabilities of tax authorities have significantly improved, and tax bureaus have begun to proactively analyze CRS data. As a Chinese tax resident, if your overseas assets and income are conspicuous enough, you are likely to come into the view of the tax bureau. In the long run, these overseas assets will sooner or later face the attention and management of tax authorities. This reflects the upgrading of the collection and management mechanism—based on specific risk indicators, using internal &quot;five-step work method&quot; and other means to conduct a systematic assessment of the overseas income of natural persons. Currently, common targets of verification include those who invest in Hong Kong and US stocks, and those who realize overseas equity in Internet companies. However, Web3-related crypto income may become one of the focuses in the future. [Securities Times]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947189008828485632</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说FinTax Founder: Web3-related crypto income may become a focus of taxation in the futureIn recent years, the data analysis capabilities of tax authorities have significantly improved, and tax bureaus have begun to proactively analyze CRS data. As a Chinese tax resident, if your overseas a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947189008828485632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish listed company H100 Group plans to raise $1.50M to increase its holdings of BitcoinPublicly listed company H100 Group announced that its board of directors has decided to conduct a directed issue of up to 1,523,089 new shares to certain qualified investors at a price of SEK 9.30 per share, with total proceeds expected to be approximately SEK 14.10 million (approximately $1.50 million). The announcement stated that the net proceeds from this fundraising will be used to seek new investment opportunities within its Bitcoin reserve strategy framework. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947190076857667584</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySwedish listed company H100 Group plans to raise $1.50M to increase its holdings of BitcoinPublicly listed company H100 Group announced that its board of directors has decided to conduct a directed issue of up to 1,523,089 new shares to certain qualified investors at a price of SEK 9</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947190076857667584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank and credit union groups in the US are asking the OCC to delay decisions on bank charter applications submitted by crypto firmsAccording to Cointelegraph, banking and credit union groups in the United States have asked the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) to delay decisions on bank charter applications submitted by crypto companies, citing &quot;significant policy and procedural issues.&quot; &quot;There are significant policy and legal questions regarding whether the business plans proposed by the applicants involve the types of fiduciary activities conducted by national trust banks. The public portions of the applications fail to provide sufficient information for the public to assess or meaningfully comment on the applicants’ proposed business models and operations. If the OCC approves these applications, the public should also be able to review the OCC’s decisions.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947188615226609664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBank and credit union groups in the US are asking the OCC to delay decisions on bank charter applications submitted by crypto firmsAccording to Cointelegraph, banking and credit union groups in the United States have asked the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947188615226609664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Will Launch TA Perpetual Contract TradingAccording to the official announcement, Gate will launch TA perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement) at 15:30 (UTC+8) on July 21, supporting 1-20x leverage. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947187563383246848</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGate Will Launch TA Perpetual Contract TradingAccording to the official announcement, Gate will launch TA perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement) at 15:30 (UTC+8) on July 21, supporting 1-20x leverage. [Odaily]$USDT$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947187563383246848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has premiered PsyopCoin (PSYOP)On July 21, according to official news, LBank has launched PsyopCoin (PSYOP) for the first time on July 21, 2025, at 13:30 (SGT), and opened the PSYOP/USDT trading pair. Deposits are now open, and withdrawals will be open on July 22 at 13:00 (SGT). [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182627861843968</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowLBank has premiered PsyopCoin (PSYOP)On July 21, according to official news, LBank has launched PsyopCoin (PSYOP) for the first time on July 21, 2025, at 13:30 (SGT), and opened the PSYOP/USDT trading pair. Deposits are now open, and withdrawals will be open on July 22 at 13:00 (SG</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182627861843968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.69% in the past 1H, up 1.06% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182453138350080</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.69% in the past 1H, up 1.06% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182453138350080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha Points can claim TA token airdropOn July 21, according to the official announcement, Binance released an update on the launch of Trusta AI (TA), stating that after the start of trading, users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha points can apply for a 750 TA token airdrop. First come, first served, until the airdrop pool is full or the event ends. Please note that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha points. Users must confirm the claim within 24 hours on the Alpha event page, otherwise it will be deemed to have given up the airdrop.
Starting today, the risk pre-check for airdrop activities will be opened 5 minutes before the start, please prepare in advance. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947181839848591360</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBinance: Users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha Points can claim TA token airdropOn July 21, according to the official announcement, Binance released an update on the launch of Trusta AI (TA), stating that after the start of trading, users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha points</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947181839848591360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: The TA airdrop claim threshold is 210 points, and claiming will consume 15 points.Binance has announced that TA trading will be available on Binance Alpha on July 21, 2025 at 7:00 (UTC), and futures trading will begin at 7:30. At that time, users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha points can get an airdrop of 750 TA tokens on a first-come, first-served basis, which will end when the airdrop pool is exhausted or the event expires. Claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points, and users need to confirm the application on the Alpha event page within 24 hours, otherwise it will be deemed as a waiver. Binance will conduct an airdrop risk pre-check 5 minutes before the start of the event, so please be prepared in advance. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182537009025024</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance Alpha: The TA airdrop claim threshold is 210 points, and claiming will consume 15 points.Binance has announced that TA trading will be available on Binance Alpha on July 21, 2025 at 7:00 (UTC), and futures trading will begin at 7:30. At that time, users holding at least 210 B</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182537009025024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches Trading Lucky Draw with Up to 3 ETH to be WonTo celebrate Ethereum&apos;s strong comeback, Bitget is launching a trading lucky draw event, open to both new and existing users. During the event, complete the corresponding contract trading volume tasks to get a specific number of chances to win a prize, up to 11 times. Each additional draw increases the chance of winning a grand prize, with a maximum of 3 ETH per draw. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182349267783680</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitget Launches Trading Lucky Draw with Up to 3 ETH to be WonTo celebrate Ethereum&apos;s strong comeback, Bitget is launching a trading lucky draw event, open to both new and existing users. During the event, complete the corresponding contract trading volume tasks to get a specif</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182349267783680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain Group Increases Holdings by 22 BitcoinEuropean listed company The Blockchain Group officially announced on Twitter that it spent approximately 2.20 million euros (approximately $2.56 million) to increase its holdings by 22 Bitcoin, and its total holdings have now reached 1955. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180695894118400</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说The Blockchain Group Increases Holdings by 22 BitcoinEuropean listed company The Blockchain Group officially announced on Twitter that it spent approximately 2.20 million euros (approximately $2.56 million) to increase its holdings by 22 Bitcoin, and its total holdings have now reached 1</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180695894118400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyStonks and BIT Reach Strategic Partnership to Accelerate Deep Integration of Digital Assets and Traditional SecuritiesMyStonks announces a deep strategic partnership with global professional digital asset trading platform BIT. MyStonks is a leading global decentralized US stock token platform, and BIT focuses on providing digital asset services to global users. This collaboration marks an important upgrade to the on-chain securities and crypto asset trading ecosystem. This round of cooperation will cover multiple levels, including API integration, traffic referral, joint construction of agent channels, and dual community linkage. The two parties will bring users a convenient cross-platform jump experience, exclusive transaction discounts, and diverse interactive activities, and plan to integrate MyStonks digital securities products on the BIT platform in the future to promote the continuous implementation of one-stop on-chain financial services. This strong alliance will not only help both parties improve service coverage and market influence, but also accelerate the deep integration of digital assets and traditional securities, bringing investors more efficient and diverse asset allocation choices and innovative experiences. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180005536845824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMyStonks and BIT Reach Strategic Partnership to Accelerate Deep Integration of Digital Assets and Traditional SecuritiesMyStonks announces a deep strategic partnership with global professional digital asset trading platform BIT. MyStonks is a leading global decentralized US stock tok</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180005536845824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>