<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:17:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia&apos;s large-scale anti-fraud operation halts the business of Potato Guaranteed Public Groups.On July 14, the Cambodian government launched a nationwide crackdown on online scams, arresting 2,270 criminal suspects as of July 18. According to on-chain analysis firm Bitrace, during this period, the escrow addresses of the Cambodia-based cryptocurrency transaction escrow platform &quot;Potato Escrow&quot; stopped transferring funds, the scale of merchant deposit payments dropped to nearly zero, and the public group business basically stalled. The private group business briefly declined before partially recovering. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254128803860480</link>
      <description>2 minutes ago吴说Cambodia&apos;s large-scale anti-fraud operation halts the business of Potato Guaranteed Public Groups.On July 14, the Cambodian government launched a nationwide crackdown on online scams, arresting 2,270 criminal suspects as of July 18. According to on-chain analysis firm Bitrace, during</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254128803860480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antalpha&apos;s shareholders&apos; meeting passed several important resolutions, including increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital and restructuring share classes.Antalpha Platform Holdings held a special general meeting, with a total of 19,318,273 common shares voting at the meeting, representing approximately 81.6% of the company&apos;s total common shares as of June 20, 2025. At this general meeting, the company&apos;s shareholders approved the following proposals: increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital from &quot;$50,000.00, divided into 50,000,000 common shares with a par value of $0.001&quot; to &quot;$62,500.00, divided into 62,500,000 common shares with a par value of $0.001&quot;; reclassifying 59,375,000 authorized common shares as Class A common shares, while reclassifying 3,125,000 unissued authorized common shares as Class B common shares; amending the company&apos;s articles of association and memorandum to reflect the new authorized share capital structure; the Chairman of the Board and CEO of the company may receive an award of up to 1.50M Class B common shares under the 2024 Equity Incentive Plan; and the company will adopt a financial management plan to improve the company&apos;s financial management. All of the above proposals have been approved. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254027649830912</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsAntalpha&apos;s shareholders&apos; meeting passed several important resolutions, including increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital and restructuring share classes.Antalpha Platform Holdings held a special general meeting, with a total of 19,318,273 common shares voting at t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947254027649830912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundstrat Co-Founder: Predicts Bitcoin Price Could Break $1 Million in the Next Few YearsOn July 21, CNBC reported that Fundstrat co-founder and managing partner Tom Lee said in an interview with &quot;Squawk Box&quot; that the price of Bitcoin could exceed $1 million per coin in the coming years. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947253121936019456</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoTechFlowFundstrat Co-Founder: Predicts Bitcoin Price Could Break $1 Million in the Next Few YearsOn July 21, CNBC reported that Fundstrat co-founder and managing partner Tom Lee said in an interview with &quot;Squawk Box&quot; that the price of Bitcoin could exceed $1 million per coin in the comi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947253121936019456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-founder Joseph Lubin will serve as the torchbearer for Ethereum&apos;s 10th anniversary, saying the protocol has been running stably and uninterruptedly for ten years.On July 21, Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin was invited to be the torchbearer for the 10th anniversary celebration of Ethereum. He said that the Ethereum protocol has been running stably for nearly ten years since its release, and even though it has undergone several major upgrades during this period, it has never lost a block, demonstrating the high reliability and strong vitality of the protocol. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947252518648303616</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoPANewsCo-founder Joseph Lubin will serve as the torchbearer for Ethereum&apos;s 10th anniversary, saying the protocol has been running stably and uninterruptedly for ten years.On July 21, Ethereum co-founder Joseph Lubin was invited to be the torchbearer for the 10th anniversary celebration</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947252518648303616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jingwei Tiandi: Launching a self-developed global stable currency payment platformOn July 21, Jingwei Tiandi announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that the company announced its entry into the field of crypto payments and will release its first mobile application &quot;Fopay&quot; on July 21, 2025, providing a one-stop payment platform. Fopay is developed based on the concept of stablecoin crypto payments and currently provides stablecoin custody and prepaid card payment functions through several licensed partners. The board of directors believes that the launch of Fopay and new business segments can explore more business opportunities for the company and benefit shareholders as a whole. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251533666340864</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsJingwei Tiandi: Launching a self-developed global stable currency payment platformOn July 21, Jingwei Tiandi announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that the company announced its entry into the field of crypto payments and will release its first mobile application &quot;Fopay&quot; on J</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251533666340864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Ethereum is expected to reach around $8,000.00 in early 2026, with its price structure similar to the 1980s Dow Jones bull market patternOn July 21, Cointelegraph reported that analyst Gert van Lagen pointed out that Ethereum (ETH) is in the &quot;final surge&quot; stage and may move towards the $8,000.00 price level. He found that ETH&apos;s current price structure is strikingly similar to the bull market pattern of the Dow Jones Index in 1980. The analysis is based on the &quot;textbook expansion diagonal&quot; pattern, which has provided strong support for Ethereum&apos;s main rebound since mid-2022. Currently, ETH is trading between the upper and lower boundaries of this pattern, and is expected to reach the upper boundary of about $8,000.00 in early 2026. Technically, ETH has re-established a multi-year upward trend line as support and is consolidating within an ascending triangle pattern. A break above the $3,900.00-$4,150.00 level resistance zone could trigger a rise to $7,150.00, close to the target price of the trumpet pattern. Analysts say that macroeconomic factors such as the expected Fed rate cuts and continued ETH ETF inflows may support this upward trend. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249833433911296</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoTechFlowAnalyst: Ethereum is expected to reach around $8,000.00 in early 2026, with its price structure similar to the 1980s Dow Jones bull market patternOn July 21, Cointelegraph reported that analyst Gert van Lagen pointed out that Ethereum (ETH) is in the &quot;final surge&quot; stage and may</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249833433911296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ether Machine to list on Nasdaq with $1.50 billion war chest for Ethereum treasuryThe Ether Machine plans to list on Nasdaq with more than $1.5 billion in fully committed capital and over 400,000 Ether on its balance sheet, potentially positioning the newly formed company as the largest publicly traded vehicle focused exclusively on Ethereum, according to a definitive merger announcement on Monday.

Financing includes an anchor contribution of roughly $645 million, about 169,984 ETH, from co‑founder Andrew Keys, who will serve as chairman, and more than $800 million in common‑stock commitments from institutional and crypto‑native investors such as 1Roundtable/10T Holdings, Archetype, Blockchain.com, cyber Fund, Electric Capital, Kraken, and Pantera Capital.

Dynamix’s $170 million cash trust could lift gross proceeds above $1.6 billion, the statement notes. David Merin, the former head of corporate development at Consensys, will also become the CEO, with Morgan Stanley alumnus Jonathan Christodoro serving as vice chairman.

The Ether Machine will go public through a business combination with Dynamix Corporation (DYNX), a special-purpose acquisition company that launched its initial public offering in late 2024. The company says it will generate ETH‑denominated returns through staking, restaking, and decentralized‑finance strategies while offering institutions turnkey exposure to Ethereum yields. Upon closing — targeted for the fourth quarter and contingent on shareholder approval — the combined entity will trade under the ticker ETHM.

If successful, the listing would eclipse SharpLink Gaming’s 353,000 ETH treasury and BitMine Immersion’s 300,657 ETH stash, making Ether Machine the largest public ether holder at launch. It would also extend a growing trend of pure proxy players for investors seeking Ethereum exposure via U.S. equities</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251572945997824</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoThe BlockThe Ether Machine to list on Nasdaq with $1.50 billion war chest for Ethereum treasuryThe Ether Machine plans to list on Nasdaq with more than $1.5 billion in fully committed capital and over 400,000 Ether on its balance sheet, potentially positioning the newly formed company</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947251572945997824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITIC Bank Shijiazhuang Branch Lands Industry&apos;s First Purely Online Digital RMB Government Procurement LoanAccording to People&apos;s Daily, China CITIC Bank&apos;s Xiong&apos;an branch has successfully implemented the first inclusive finance pure online digital RMB government procurement loan (&quot;Digital Currency Government Procurement e-Loan&quot;) in the industry. This business is based on the security of blockchain and the colorability of digital RMB, combined with CITIC Bank&apos;s mature internal risk control system. After verifying the authenticity of the government procurement transaction background, it realizes the rapid verification of the loan amount and the entire process of pure online lending. This model effectively links the three parties of the purchaser, supplier, and bank, promotes information sharing and credit transmission, not only provides suppliers with convenient and efficient financing channels, but also strengthens the payment security of fiscal funds and contract performance supervision, and opens up a new path for credit financing in the field of government procurement. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249012424069120</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoForesightNewsCITIC Bank Shijiazhuang Branch Lands Industry&apos;s First Purely Online Digital RMB Government Procurement LoanAccording to People&apos;s Daily, China CITIC Bank&apos;s Xiong&apos;an branch has successfully implemented the first inclusive finance pure online digital RMB government procuremen</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947249012424069120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRP vs. LILPEPE: Potential 1-year returns on a $2,000.00 investmentDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. As institutional money eyes XRP and altcoins regain momentum, traders are weighing stable bets like XRP against high-upside plays like LILPEPE. Table of Contents The crypto market is thawing out once more. As the possibility of an eventual significant interest in the space grows institutional, with XRP as one of the leading forms of altcoin cryptocurrency, investors are assessing how far the benchmark of 2k holdings can be pushed through hypothetical progression.  As the name XRP has easily become one of the most well-known brands in the crypto world, there has been some doubt among traders about whether this is where they want to be when it comes to massive gains in the new cycle. Enter Little Pepe (LILPEPE), a shot-to-success memecoin with actual infrastructure and genuine community interest.  Currently in the final stage of the presale (Stage 6), LILPEPE offers a price of only $0.0015 and is already listed on CoinMarketCap. Although XRP may be a good hold, investors seeking high returns on their investments are now turning to LILPEPE as a more promising investment option. XRP  has been a pillar of the altcoin market for a long time. Being one of the most tested digital assets, it has stood out in the storm of regulations, crashes, and FUD. Most expect the token to reach new all-time highs with the possible release of XRP-backed ETFs.  XRP is currently trading at $2.90 as of mid-July 2025, and the two most common scenarios suggest either returning to its former peak of approximately $3.50 or even surpassing it should ETF demand intensify. That would be a 5x appreciation over its current price – i.e., a $2,000 investment would rapidly compound in a 12-month optimistic horizon to approximately $10,000.  However, to achieve this, XRP would need to capture billions of dollars of institutional capital, and its current large market cap already creates a mathematical drag on a parabolic advance. For traders seeking 20x, 50x, and 100x returns, XRP may not get there soon enough. So, compare that to Little Pepe, the meme token that is fast becoming no laughing matter. LILPEPE has raised more than $6.8 million at merely $0.0015 during Stage 6 of its presale and is already listed on CoinMarketCap, a positive indication of increasing popularity and reach.  Real world functionality is different from DOGE or SHIB through LILPEPE. It is a Layer-2 blockchain-based token that facilitates blazing-fast and cost-free transactions, providing real utility through its Pepe Pump Pad, a security-enabled launchpad for new meme tokens featuring locked liquidity and protection against rug pulls. It is this mix of meme value over serious infrastructure that is exciting early-stage investors.  At that rate, an investment of $2,000 at $0.15 could turn into an impressive figure of $200,000 by 2026, representing a 100-fold increase from the initial investment.  As much as XRP is enjoying the ride of an ETF and boasts institutional hype, the math is plain and simple when it comes to the sheer upper-bound potential of smaller-cap tokens like LILPEPE. This is the reason why traders are rotating:  A penny to a pawn: LILPEPE is a penny (0.0015) that provides an enormous future, considering a minimal investment. With the market cap of XRP standing at over $30 billion, achieving any percentage gains is tough.  Not a hype: Unlike the majority of meme tokens, LILPEPE will have a place in the blockchain through its launchpad. This places it somewhere between a meme culture and actual DeFi infrastructure. Layer-2 benefit: LILPEPE blockchain is low cost and high speed, and is scalable, which is precisely what memecoins, NFTs, and low-gas DeFi are built to do, and will also be popular in 2025-2026.  Viral energy: LILPEPE is going viral with powerful social campaigns, a giveaway of 777k, and an interesting community is already in the competitive spirit of capturing the early buzz of DOGE and SHIB in previous bull markets. The presale cost rises with every phase, and this is why every postponement eats into possible ROI.  No one doubts the fact that XRP is a perfect choice for an investor seeking stability, institutional support, and an established altcoin. However, to anyone who wishes to take a minor commitment and make it a whole lot bigger, LILPEPE is unlike any other in terms of 100x potential, real-life utility, and unparalleled upside potential, starting with the current price points as its foundation. There is a chance of profiting with XRP; Nevertheless, LILPEPE might grant the profits that can change one’s life, but only the early coins can grant them.  To learn more about Little Pepe, visit the website , Telegram , and X .             Disclosure: This content is provided by a third party. Neither crypto.news nor the author of this article endorses any product mentioned on this page. Users should conduct their own research before taking any action related to the company.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247270370234368</link>
      <description>28 minutes agocrypto.newsXRP vs. LILPEPE: Potential 1-year returns on a $2,000.00 investmentDisclosure: This article does not represent investment advice. The content and materials featured on this page are for educational purposes only. As institutional money eyes XRP and altcoins regain momentum,</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247270370234368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WINkLink oracle officially supports USD1 price service, empowering the TRON stablecoin ecosystemAccording to official sources, WINkLink oracle has now added USD1/TRX price service to further expand its decentralized data ecosystem and provide a more secure and reliable price source for stablecoin applications on the TRON network. This move will accelerate the infrastructure construction of DeFi scenarios such as lending, synthetic assets, and derivatives, and help the prosperous development of the TRON ecosystem. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247957162348544</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoOdailyWINkLink oracle officially supports USD1 price service, empowering the TRON stablecoin ecosystemAccording to official sources, WINkLink oracle has now added USD1/TRX price service to further expand its decentralized data ecosystem and provide a more secure and reliable price sour</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947247957162348544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Crypto Airdrops for the Fourth Week of JulyAs interest transitions from Bitcoin (BTC) to altcoins, several crypto airdrops offer investors a chance to diversify their portfolios, providing low-barrier entries into high-potential projects. The following projects, backed by significant investor muscle, offer airdrop opportunities for interested farmers. Nexus The Nexus chain is among the top crypto airdrops to watch. While it remains in the potential (not yet confirmed) status, the project has significant backing from notable investors. Among them are Pantera Capital and DragonFly Capital, which co-led the tier-1 fundraiser. After a four-tier fundraiser, Nexus has accumulated $27.2 million and launched a community point incentive program. To participate, users can create various components of the project and earn points. The first point distribution will be on Tuesday, July 22. Ambassadors and users with roles in Dll receive additional points. Notably, the Nexus airdrop is linked to Nexus Labs’ zkVM-powered Layer 1 blockchain, rewarding early participants with NEX points. The points are convertible to tokens upon mainnet launch in Q3 2025. To participate, users can join the Devnet phase and contribute computing power via a browser-based node or dedicated hardware for higher points. Additional rewards come from social tasks, creating content, or earning Discord roles. Common Another crypto airdrop to watch is Common, a social network  boasting up to $20.0 million in funds raised. Notable backers or investors include DragonFly Capital, which led the first-tier fundraiser. Other participants include Coinbase Ventures and Polychain Capital. During the second tier, venture firm ParaFi Capital led the fundraiser, alongside participants such as Hashed Fund and CMS Holdings. Common launched Aura points in April, with the social function still open. This allows participants to perform tasks and qualify for a potential airdrop from the project. While some functions end on a given day, the project adds new ones periodically. On July 17, Common updated the project, adding new quests for airdrop farmers to participate in and earn points. Try Your Best AdditionalTradersmonitor Try Your Best is a social platform with $20.8 million in funds raised. It enjoys the backing of Coinbase Ventures, among other participants like Strobe Ventures and Offline Ventures. The founder, TY Haney, recently advertised the social platform as the future of community commerce. The Try Your Best platform connects brands with their communities, runni ng atop the Avalanche blockchain. On its website, airdrop farmers can complete quests and earn TYB coins, which can be converted into project tokens in the future.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947250553142923264</link>
      <description>37 minutes agobeincryptoTop 3 Crypto Airdrops for the Fourth Week of JulyAs interest transitions from Bitcoin (BTC) to altcoins, several crypto airdrops offer investors a chance to diversify their portfolios, providing low-barrier entries into high-potential projects. The following projects, backed</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947250553142923264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX&apos;s new &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; program premieres today at 20:00: Discussing passions and self-expression beyond market trends.On July 21st, according to official social media news, the new issue of Huobi HTX&apos;s &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; will hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;Starting from the Individual: Beyond the Market, There is Still Love and Expression.&quot; Deep insight outputter Bi Shi Wang, G+ Women&apos;s Power initiator Gigiz.Eth, and other in-depth content creators will be invited to attend and chat about how to persist in expression during the market cycle and how to see oneself outside of the crypto narrative. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947244478092038144</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX&apos;s new &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; program premieres today at 20:00: Discussing passions and self-expression beyond market trends.On July 21st, according to official social media news, the new issue of Huobi HTX&apos;s &quot;Partner 1+1&quot; will hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the them</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947244478092038144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequans increased its holdings by 1,264 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 2,317 BTC.According to NLNico monitoring, French listed company Sequans recently purchased 1,264 BTC, increasing its total BTC holdings to 2,317 BTC. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947242915780907008</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailySequans increased its holdings by 1,264 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 2,317 BTC.According to NLNico monitoring, French listed company Sequans recently purchased 1,264 BTC, increasing its total BTC holdings to 2,317 BTC. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTC$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947242915780907008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merlin Chain Releases Merlin 2.0 - &quot;Hold, Earn, Invest&quot; Reshaping BTCMerlin Chain has announced its new Merlin 2.0, proposing a development direction of &quot;Reinvent Bitcoin: Hold, Earn, Invest,&quot; aiming to expand Bitcoin from a &quot;store of value&quot; to a &quot;yield-generating, deployable core asset.&quot; Merlin 2.0 focuses on three major areas: BTCFi expansion, chain abstraction technology, and AI applications (such as Merlin Wizard), further enhancing the liquidity and utility of BTC in multi-chain ecosystems. It also lowers the barrier to entry for BTC, allowing users to participate in various investment opportunities across chains without having to exchange other assets, conveniently realizing BTC holding, yield acquisition, and liquidity participation. According to previous reports, since the mainnet launch in February 2024, Merlin Chain has promoted the rise of BTCFi, giving rise to several representative projects including Solv, Bedrock, Avalon, and Babylon, with over $3.80B in BTC cumulatively staked on the chain. Currently, the Merlin-related ecosystem contributes approximately $2.00B in BTCFi TVL, accounting for over 20.00%. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237887540219904</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMerlin Chain Releases Merlin 2.0 - &quot;Hold, Earn, Invest&quot; Reshaping BTCMerlin Chain has announced its new Merlin 2.0, proposing a development direction of &quot;Reinvent Bitcoin: Hold, Earn, Invest,&quot; aiming to expand Bitcoin from a &quot;store of value&quot; to a &quot;yield-generating, deployable core as</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947237887540219904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Central Bank of Morocco Completes Draft Law on Crypto AssetsAccording to Zhitong Finance, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law that would legalize the use of crypto assets. The law ensures &quot;adequate protection for consumers and investors, strengthens market integrity, combats fraud, manipulation, money laundering and terrorist financing, and maintains financial stability.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236660978929664</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsThe Central Bank of Morocco Completes Draft Law on Crypto AssetsAccording to Zhitong Finance, the Governor of the Central Bank of Morocco stated at the African Central Bank Conference in Rabat that Morocco has finalized a draft law that would legalize the use of crypto assets.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236660978929664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Warning Signs Bitcoin May Be Headed for a Cooldown This JulyBitcoin (BTC) has entered its fourth consecutive month of gains. However, it just ended the first red weekly candle of July. While many analysts believe the bullrun may not be over yet, some concerning signals have begun to emerge, hinting at a possible price correction or consolidation. After Four Months of Gains, Is Bitcoin Due for a Breather? These warning signs don’t necessarily mean Bitcoin will reverse, but they serve as early indicators that demand attention before stronger moves or major volatility occur. First, Bitcoin Whale-to-Exchange Flow data shows a significant increase in July. This metric reflects the volume of BTC large holders (whales) send to exchanges, usually implying an intention to sell. According to analyst Darkfost, in the last two market peaks, whale capital inflows exceeded $75 billion, marking the beginning of a correction or consolidation phase. Between July 14 and July 18, 2025, the figure has already reached $45 billion. This sharp rise indicates increased activity from large investors. Darkfost’s view aligns with recent on-chain observations from Lookonchain. Today, Lookonchain reported that a savvy Bitcoin whale sent 400 BTC (worth $47.1 million) to Binance to take profits, with total realized gains reaching $91.5 million. Beyond whale flows, on-chain data shows another signal: Bitcoin’s Coin Days Destroyed (CDD) in July reached a one-year high. CDD measures how long coins were held before being moved. It reflects the sentiment and behavior of long-term holders. A high CDD value suggests long-term holders are moving their coins and are likely to sell them. According to CryptoQuant, the 30-day average CDD in July surpassed 31 million, the highest since April 2024. A previous report from BeInCrypto noted that a spike in this metric often precedes major market corrections. However, on the positive side, it can also be seen as a redistribution to new investors. Finally, changes in the correlation between altcoins and Bitcoin have raised further concern. According to Alphractal, the Altcoin-Bitcoin Correlation Heatmap recently dropped below zero. This shift means that altcoins have outperformed Bitcoin in recent days. However, historical data shows that a low correlation between Bitcoin and altcoins is often a red flag. Since the start of 2025, this indicator has turned negative thrice. The first was in January, followed by a drop in Bitcoin’s price from $110,000 to $74,900. The second time was in May, when BTC fell from $112,000 to $98,500. Now, we are seeing the third occurrence. A recent report from BeInCrypto also highlighted another concerning signal. The Coinbase Premium has decoupled from the Kimchi Premium. This disconnection suggests an uneven bullrun across global regions, primarily driven by strong institutional demand in the US. []</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947240976196325376</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincrypto3 Warning Signs Bitcoin May Be Headed for a Cooldown This JulyBitcoin (BTC) has entered its fourth consecutive month of gains. However, it just ended the first red weekly candle of July. While many analysts believe the bullrun may not be over yet, some concerning signals have beg</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947240976196325376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn closed positions in various assets, making a profit of approximately $178,000.00 in 6 daysAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, James Wynn has closed his 10x long positions in DOGE and PEPE, as well as his 40x short position in BTC, with a loss of $625,222.00. In the past 6 days, James deposited 1.25M USDC into HyperLiquid and made a profit of $177,675.00. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236412231536640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsJames Wynn closed positions in various assets, making a profit of approximately $178,000.00 in 6 daysAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, James Wynn has closed his 10x long positions in DOGE and PEPE, as well as his 40x short position in BTC, with a loss of $625,222.00. In th</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947236412231536640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain compliance tools can slash TradFi costs — Chainlink co-founderInstitutional investors will increasingly adopt blockchain-based compliance solutions and tokenized RWAs, Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov told Cointelegraph. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234608521433088</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBlockchain compliance tools can slash TradFi costs — Chainlink co-founderInstitutional investors will increasingly adopt blockchain-based compliance solutions and tokenized RWAs, Chainlink’s co-founder Sergey Nazarov told Cointelegraph. [Cointelegraph]#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234608521433088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory releases ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutionOn July 21, according to Xinhua Finance, Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory released DeepLink ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutions, which supports cross-domain long-term stable mixed training of large models with hundreds of billions of parameters in multiple intelligent computing centers over a thousand kilometers, such as connecting the intelligent computing centers between Shanghai and Jinan over 1,500 kilometers, and realizing the interconnection and large-model mixed training of intelligent computing centers in Beijing, Shanghai, Guizhou and other places. At present, the DeepLink open computing system of Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory has been deeply integrated into intelligent computing platforms such as China Unicom, China Telecom, SenseTime, and Yidian, achieving stable operation of &quot;1 platform + N chips + X regions&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234435628027904</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsShanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory releases ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology solutionOn July 21, according to Xinhua Finance, Shanghai Artificial Intelligence Laboratory released DeepLink ultra-large-scale cross-domain mixed training technology soluti</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947234435628027904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum NFT marketplace weekly trading volume reaches $84.03M, highest since mid-to-late February this year.According to @hildobby&apos;s data panel, in the past week (July 14 to 20), the weekly trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market reached $84,029,000.00, the highest point since mid-to-late February this year. Among them, OpenSea reached $40,143,000.00, and Blur reached $25,552,000.00. In addition, on July 21, with the support of CryptoPunks whales&apos; purchases, the daily trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market has exceeded $25,900,000.00, the highest point since February 18 this year. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947232369966862336</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Ethereum NFT marketplace weekly trading volume reaches $84.03M, highest since mid-to-late February this year.According to @hildobby&apos;s data panel, in the past week (July 14 to 20), the weekly trading volume of the Ethereum NFT market reached $84,029,000.00, the highest point since mid-to-</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947232369966862336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>