<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:32:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted that &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world economy (except for food and energy production) is essentially a status game, so how could the internet society be any different.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952400467300352</link>
      <description>1 minute agoForesightNewsArthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted that &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world economy (except for foo</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952400467300352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</link>
      <description>1 minute agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</link>
      <description>4 minutes agoPANewsSouth Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that Galaxy Digital is well-positioned to capture upside opportunities in a favorable cryptocurrency regulatory environment. The investment bank noted that the passage of the U.S. GENIUS Act provides a &quot;favorable market structure&quot; for Galaxy&apos;s business. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoTechFlowJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether announces part of its investment portfolio, the group has invested in more than 120 companiesOn July 23, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino tweeted that Tether announced some of its investments and venture capital portfolios today. Overall, the Tether Group has invested in more than 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. These investments are all made from Tether&apos;s own profits (US$13.7 billion in 2024), and do not involve USDt and other stablecoin reserves, and are operations of Tether&apos;s investment department. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947950865989570560</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsTether announces part of its investment portfolio, the group has invested in more than 120 companiesOn July 23, Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino tweeted that Tether announced some of its investments and venture capital portfolios today. Overall, the Tether Group has invested in more than</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947950865989570560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Pastor Charged in $3.40M Crypto ScamA Denver, Colorado-based online pastor and his wife were indicted on Tuesday in connection with a cryptocurrency fraud scheme that raised over $3 million from faith-based investors. Between January 2022 and July 2023, the Regalados raised nearly $3.40 million by encouraging people in their religion to purchase INDXcoin through the Kingdom Wealth Exchange platform, with at least 300 people investing in the token and suffering losses. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947948979861393408</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoForesightNewsColorado Pastor Charged in $3.40M Crypto ScamA Denver, Colorado-based online pastor and his wife were indicted on Tuesday in connection with a cryptocurrency fraud scheme that raised over $3 million from faith-based investors. Between January 2022 and July 2023, the Regala</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947948979861393408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares obtains EU MiCA license, becoming the first licensed crypto asset management companyOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, European crypto asset management company CoinShares announced that it had obtained the EU&apos;s &quot;Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation&quot; (MiCA) license, becoming the first European crypto asset management company to obtain this license. The license was issued by the French Financial Markets Authority (AMF), enabling CoinShares to provide crypto asset portfolio management services within the 27 EU countries, and together with its existing MiFID and AIFM licenses, it constitutes a triple regulatory qualification. CoinShares said that this milestone is expected to promote the EU&apos;s $38.7 trillion asset management industry to further open up compliant crypto investment products. So far, the company has managed assets of more than $9 billion, and its stock price has risen by more than 46% this year. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946967392391168</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoPANewsCoinShares obtains EU MiCA license, becoming the first licensed crypto asset management companyOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, European crypto asset management company CoinShares announced that it had obtained the EU&apos;s &quot;Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation&quot; (MiCA) license, beco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946967392391168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$51.5214 millionOn July 23, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$51.5214 million. Among them:
The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$22.4015 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$23.3565 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$1.0478 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$0.9224 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$1.8167 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$1.9765 million.
Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946525744762880</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$51.5214 millionOn July 23, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$51.5214 million. Among them:
The tran</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946525744762880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Stock Exchange holds a symposium for companies in the Shanghai artificial intelligence industry chainOn July 23, the Shanghai Stock Exchange conducted a special survey on Shanghai&apos;s &quot;Model Speed Space&quot; and jointly held a symposium with the Xuhui District People&apos;s Government on Shanghai&apos;s artificial intelligence industry chain enterprises, and had in-depth face-to-face exchanges with key enterprises, investment institutions, and sponsors to accelerate the construction of a good ecology adapted to the era of artificial intelligence science and innovation. The Shanghai Stock Exchange said that it hopes that high-quality technology companies at different stages of development will seize the development opportunities of the capital market, make full use of policy reform tools, and use the capital market to become better and stronger, and win new advantages for future development with technological innovation. In the next step, the Shanghai Stock Exchange will follow the unified deployment of the China Securities Regulatory Commission, take the &quot;1+6&quot; policy of the Science and Technology Innovation Board reform as an opportunity, widely gather market consensus, and use cutting-edge technology fields such as artificial intelligence as strategic fulcrums to further strengthen the cultivation and service of high-quality technology companies throughout their life cycle, product lines, and business chains, accelerate the implementation of typical cases as soon as possible, and promote the development of new quality productivity to a new level. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945987372290048</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoPANewsShanghai Stock Exchange holds a symposium for companies in the Shanghai artificial intelligence industry chainOn July 23, the Shanghai Stock Exchange conducted a special survey on Shanghai&apos;s &quot;Model Speed Space&quot; and jointly held a symposium with the Xuhui District People&apos;s Governm</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945987372290048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address transferred 16.81M XRP, worth $58.37M, to CoinbaseOn July 23, according to Whale Alert monitoring, an address transferred 16,812,113 XRP to Coinbase, worth approximately $58,365,018.00. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945654059339776</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoTechFlowAn address transferred 16.81M XRP, worth $58.37M, to CoinbaseOn July 23, according to Whale Alert monitoring, an address transferred 16,812,113 XRP to Coinbase, worth approximately $58,365,018.00. [TechFlow]#Crypto Stocks$MAG7.SSI$XRP$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945654059339776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Now Lists COAThe official interface shows that Binance Alpha has listed COA. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947947571019845632</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha Now Lists COAThe official interface shows that Binance Alpha has listed COA. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947947571019845632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of stablecoin licensing regime next weekOn July 23, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, said that the Stablecoin Ordinance will take effect on August 1, when it will be illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoin to the Hong Kong public. He pointed out that there have been recent scams targeting stablecoins and digital assets in the market, causing losses to the public. In response to market concerns about the application process, the HKMA plans to publish a summary of the &quot;Licensing System for Stablecoin Issuers&quot; next week, which will detail the acceptance and processing arrangements for license applications. Eddie Yue called on interested parties to stay tuned. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944419080081408</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of stablecoin licensing regime next weekOn July 23, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, said that the Stablecoin Ordinance will take effect on August 1, when it will be illegal to promote any unlicensed s</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944419080081408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sygnum: Bitcoin network transaction volume surpasses VisaRegulated digital asset bank Sygnum said that the Bitcoin network&apos;s existing annual transaction volume is estimated at $20 trillion, exceeding Visa&apos;s $13 trillion. The report also highlighted other data, such as Bitcoin&apos;s liquid supply on exchanges falling to a near seven-year low, ETFs currently holding over $150.00 billion in Bitcoin, and publicly listed companies holding approximately $80.00 billion in Bitcoin. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944481038340096</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoForesightNewsSygnum: Bitcoin network transaction volume surpasses VisaRegulated digital asset bank Sygnum said that the Bitcoin network&apos;s existing annual transaction volume is estimated at $20 trillion, exceeding Visa&apos;s $13 trillion. The report also highlighted other data, such as Bitc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944481038340096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi to Mars, they are pioneering narratives! Sun, who is flying to space, and the women who are changing the industry.&quot; YIYI, Damei Una, Li Qian, Silvia Wanqing, Crayon Xiaomi and other crypto KOLs will gather together to discuss the female power unique to Web3. This event will be broadcast simultaneously via Huobi Live and X Space, with constant red envelope rain, so stay tuned. Book a live broadcast: https://www.htx.com.de/zh-cn/live/detail/h5?id=79115&amp;invite_code=ip549223&amp;inviter_id=11351630 [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoTechFlowHuobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure with native on-chain staking rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoForesightNewsREX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaito is postponing the Espresso launch to July 24th at 20:00.Due to KYC process issues, Kaito has postponed the launch of Espresso to 20:00 on July 24th. Kaito has partnered with identity platform Persona to update the KYC address verification section. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942693002350592</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoForesightNewsKaito is postponing the Espresso launch to July 24th at 20:00.Due to KYC process issues, Kaito has postponed the launch of Espresso to 20:00 on July 24th. Kaito has partnered with identity platform Persona to update the KYC address verification section. [Foresight News]Sha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942693002350592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side.The Ministry of Commerce stated that, as agreed upon by both China and the United States, He Lifeng, member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and Vice Premier of the State Council, will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the United States. The two sides will follow the important consensus reached by the two heads of state during their phone call on June 5th, give full play to the role of the China-U.S. economic and trade consultation mechanism, and continue to conduct consultations on economic and trade issues of mutual concern based on the principles of mutual respect, peaceful coexistence, and win-win cooperation. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942527096655872</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyHe Lifeng will travel to Sweden from July 27th to 30th to hold economic and trade talks with the US side.The Ministry of Commerce stated that, as agreed upon by both China and the United States, He Lifeng, member of the Political Bureau of the CPC Central Committee and Vice Premi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947942527096655872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2B PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address. A week ago, this portion of tokens was deposited into Binance and then transferred to the address &quot;9SnqX...seSGz&quot;, and half an hour ago, it was transferred back in batches from that address. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947937510591631360</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdaily2B PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947937510591631360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENGU surpasses BONK to become the meme coin with the highest market value on the Solana chain, and its market value ranking rises to 54th.On July 23, according to the latest data from coingecko, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) has surpassed Bonk (BONK) and ranked 54th in cryptocurrency market capitalization, becoming the Memecoin with the highest market capitalization in the Solana ecosystem. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947935295181230080</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsPENGU surpasses BONK to become the meme coin with the highest market value on the Solana chain, and its market value ranking rises to 54th.On July 23, according to the latest data from coingecko, Pudgy Penguins (PENGU) has surpassed Bonk (BONK) and ranked 54th in cryptocurrency marke</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947935295181230080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should Investors Buy Low-Cap Altcoins in Q3 2025? Analysts Weigh InCrypto investors are well aware of the risks involved in low-cap altcoins. However, this segment often delivers impressive returns, sometimes multiplying investments several times over. So, should investors start buying low-cap altcoins in July, especially now that experts believe altcoin season has begun? Opportunities and Risks for Low-Cap Altcoins in Q3 2025 Although the total market cap reached a new high in July, capital flows mainly into Bitcoin and major altcoins. TradingView data supports this. While the total crypto market cap nears $4 trillion, the market cap excluding the top 100 altcoins stands at just $15.4 billion. CoinMarketCap data shows that the top 100 altcoins each have a market cap above $700 million. Altcoins outside this group—those below $700 million—are categorized as mid-cap or low-cap. This capital disparity suggests that investors remain cautious. They prefer altcoins with high liquidity or those that institutional players and listed companies notice. However, another interpretation offers hope. Some analysts believe the current capital inflow is still in its early phase . Many analysts share the same view as investor Mister Crypto. According to them, the market is still in phase two. In this stage, investors mostly favor Ethereum . Capital will eventually rotate to large, mid, and low caps . This delay creates a window of opportunity for many investors to buy early and at a good price . It’s also a chance to get ahead of the broader capital flow. Still, analysts like João Wedson remain skeptical of ultra-low-cap altcoins—especially those outside the top 300. These coins usually have a market cap of less than $200 million. He cites the Open Interest to Market Cap Ratio as a warning signal for these coins. Data shows that open interest for coins outside the top 300 is unusually high compared to their market caps. When open interest significantly surpasses market capitalization, it indicates that traders are focusing on short-term movements in the derivatives market instead of actively trading the tokens in spot markets. Consequently, these altcoins experience low liquidity and encounter extreme volatility . On X, excitement about altcoin season is spreading fast in July. However, whether investors should buy low-cap altcoins in Q3/2025 still depends heavily on their personal risk appetite and investment strategy.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947940340698255360</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoShould Investors Buy Low-Cap Altcoins in Q3 2025? Analysts Weigh InCrypto investors are well aware of the risks involved in low-cap altcoins. However, this segment often delivers impressive returns, sometimes multiplying investments several times over. So, should investors start</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947940340698255360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>