<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:00:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>CertiK Stablecoin Report 2025: What are the top 5 most secure tokens in the stablecoin race?As stablecoin adoption grows more mainstream, so do the security risks associated with them. Which tokens are leading the race in terms of security? The first half of 2025 saw a surge in stablecoin use cases, with a monthly settlement volume rising by 43% to $1.39 trillion. According to the security firm, this rapidly increasing growth in adoption hides the widening gaps in security posture, compliance, and operational risk that still need to be addressed by the community. As a result, CertiK has managed to rank the top fiat-pegged tokens from a security and risk standpoint. The six-item Skynet rating framework assesses each token based on factors including operational resilience, governance strength, fundamental health, code security, market dynamic and community trust. According to the Skynet framework, Tether’s USDT ( USDT ) ranks at number one with an overall score of 94.72. The security firm highlighted USDT’s decision to increase its circulation from $138.00 billion to $154.00 billion in the first half of 2025. In second place is Circle’s USDC ( USDC ) with 93.37. Having secured a MiCA license and completed an IPO, Circle’s token supply increased from $41.00 billion to $61.00 billion. Although it is still slightly behind Tether, CertiK has dubbed it the “fastest growing” major stablecoin. Ranking in third place is the PayPal-Paxos jointly issued PYUSD ( PYUSD ) with a score of 91.47. The token’s market cap has doubled in the first half of 2025. Recent developments for the token include expansions into Solana ( SOL ) and Arbitrum ( ARB ) as well as a rewards program. In fourth place is USDS by Sky with 90.09. The rebranding of DAI into Sky has helped to expand the token into multiple chains. Since its launch on Solana, it has grown to become the fifth largest stablecoin. Ripple’s RLUSD ( RLUSD ) stands at number five with a Skynet framework score of 89.89. Although it still ranks below USDT and USDC in terms of supply and security mechanisms in place, CertiK noted that the token has experienced zero security incidents since its launch. Other notable tokens mentioned in the top 10 include First Digital USD ( FDUSD ), USDG by Paxos, Ethena’s USDe ( USDE ) and USDtb, as well as World Liberty Financial’s own USD1. According to blockchain security firm CertiK, as many as 344 crypto security incidents occurred in the past year. These incidents led to the theft of $2.47 billion worth of crypto assets industry-wide. Though these incidents are not always linked to stablecoins directly, they often bear the brunt of exploits, more so than regular tokens. For instance, First Digital USD saw its price plummet to $0.76 amid rumors about whether or not its reserves were secure. It was only able to recover its $1.00 value after the issuer disclosed audited holdings to prove that its reserves were safe. This case shows just how easily the cookie crumbles when it comes to stablecoins. Due to the nature of fiat-pegged tokens, its reserves are considered sacred in a way that differs to other tokens. One wrong move could result in the 1:1 ratio backed by real currencies to dip and lead to the token’s downfall. CertiK’s report showed that exploits in the crypto space, such as hacks, death spirals, and price depegs, were mostly caused by operational failures compared to technical flaws in the system. According to the study, vulnerabilities in systems where stablecoins are the primary asset made up a large portion of the losses. [CertiK]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947958189059805184</link>
      <description>6 minutes agocrypto.newsCertiK Stablecoin Report 2025: What are the top 5 most secure tokens in the stablecoin race?As stablecoin adoption grows more mainstream, so do the security risks associated with them. Which tokens are leading the race in terms of security? The first half of 2025 saw a surge</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947958189059805184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, continuing to set new all-time highsAccording to @sankin_eth&apos;s data dashboard, Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, reaching $5.074B USDC, continuously setting new historical highs. Since the beginning of this year, Hyperliquid AUM has grown by approximately $3.00B USDC. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947957019994034176</link>
      <description>10 minutes ago吴说Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, continuing to set new all-time highsAccording to @sankin_eth&apos;s data dashboard, Hyperliquid AUM has exceeded $5.00B, reaching $5.074B USDC, continuously setting new historical highs. Since the beginning of this year, Hyperliquid AUM has grown by ap</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947957019994034176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fartcoin derivatives open interest ranks among the top ten, speculative boom emergesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Fartcoin (FARTCOIN), a meme coin of the Solana ecosystem, has now become one of the top ten tokens in terms of open interest in cryptocurrency derivatives. Data shows that the nominal open interest of Fartcoin-related futures has exceeded $1.00 billion, surpassing mainstream currencies such as Litecoin, LINK, and AVAX. It is worth noting that Fartcoin&apos;s open interest has reached 65.00% of its market value, while its market value ranks 83rd in the world. This abnormally high open interest is considered a signal of overheated market speculation. Similar phenomena are also reflected in other small-cap currencies, which may lead to large-scale investor liquidation risks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947953345834061824</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoPANewsFartcoin derivatives open interest ranks among the top ten, speculative boom emergesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Fartcoin (FARTCOIN), a meme coin of the Solana ecosystem, has now become one of the top ten tokens in terms of open interest in cryptocurrency derivatives. Data</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947953345834061824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted on the X platform, saying, &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world economy (except for food and energy production) is essentially a status game, so how could the internet society be any different?&quot; [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955124432867328</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoOdailyArthur Hayes: Cryptopunks Will Outperform Ethereum This CycleBitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes posted on the X platform, saying, &quot;Cryptopunks will outperform ETH in USD terms this cycle because Ethereum holders will flex on NFTs, it&apos;s an internet status game. The entire world econom</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955124432867328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southeast Asian stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Philippine OTC institution Moneybees to optimize the remittance experience for overseas Filipino workers.Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Moneybees, the largest over-the-counter (OTC) institution in the Philippines. This collaboration optimizes the remittance experience for Overseas Filipino Workers (OFW) by combining stablecoin technology with offline exchange networks. Users who receive stablecoin remittances can convert APACX-incubated Philippine Peso stablecoin PHT into cash at Moneybees&apos; more than 1,000 offline locations in the Philippines. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952904685555712</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoForesightNewsSoutheast Asian stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic partnership with Philippine OTC institution Moneybees to optimize the remittance experience for overseas Filipino workers.Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX has reached a strategic p</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952904685555712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Companies’ Bitcoin Bet: Can They Weather the Bear Market Storm?Public companies worldwide have been going all-in on Bitcoin (BTC) this year. Whether it’s through equity or debt issuance, firms have accelerated their push to acquire BTC and add it to their balance sheets. While Bitcoin continues to appreciate in value, the firms have also benefited through their stock surge and paper gains. But the looming question is: What will happen if a bear market returns? Will institutional confidence hold steady, or will it waver in the face of  volatility ? BeInCrypto spoke to industry experts to examine the possibilities in a potential bear market and whether these firms will contribute to more stability or downfall. Is Institutional Interest in Bitcoin a Double-Edged Sword? Over the past few months,  BeInCrypto has extensively  reported on corporate Bitcoin acquisitions. The trend pioneered by Michael Saylor, co-founder of (Micro) Strategy, has inspired many others to follow suit. Dean Chen, an analyst at Bitunix, highlighted that the growing influx of institutional capital has solidified Bitcoin’s  position as ‘digital gold.’ Furthermore, John Glover, Ledn’s Chief Information Officer (CIO), attributed Bitcoin’s reputation for stability in recent years to the increasing involvement of institutions. Glover said that with Bitcoin’s volatility decreasing over time, it is increasingly behaving like a traditional asset.  Nonetheless, as with all traditional assets, the market experiences cycles, with bull markets typically followed by bear markets. He anticipates that any future bear market for Bitcoin will likely be less severe compared to past cycles. Still, corrections are inevitable. Notably, the executive  added that while institutes bring capital,  they also bring constraints. Chen pointed out that institutional investors tend to exit faster than retail investors. Thus, if the market moves in the opposite direction, high-frequency trading funds and quant strategies are likely to sell off their positions. However, Marcin Kazmierczak, the COO and Co-Founder of Redstone, offered an alternative viewpoint. He noted that while institutional investors might encounter difficulties during bear markets, their involvement has brought  advanced risk management practices  to the cryptocurrency space.  The Success of Corporate Financing Models for Bitcoin Acquisition Institutional investors use a mix of financing  methods to buy Bitcoin , with debt being the most common one. In a post on X, Redbox Global revealed that Bitcoin-focused companies are facing a significant $12.8 billion debt maturity wall by 2028. These concerns are not new.  Previously, Sygnum Bank  and  other market analysts  have also raised alarms about the sustainability of the strategies.  Chen highlighted that Strategy raised $42.87 billion since 2020 through zero-coupon convertible notes and equity issuances to buy over 600,000 BTC at an average cost of $71,268.00. This strategy boosts Bitcoin accumulation in bull markets. Nevertheless, it strains finances in bear markets with interest payments and falling stock prices.  Moreover,  Strategy’s debt makes up about 24.3%  of its capital structure. He added that its convertible bonds may trigger mandatory conversion or redemption if Bitcoin drops below a certain threshold. Other companies like Marathon Digital issue equity before bonds, lowering the leverage. Despite this, they have higher capital costs and limited resilience. Still, Glover emphasized that companies with strong capital structures—like staggered maturities and low-interest debt—will fare better. He stated that Strategy’s model can handle significant losses. However, new firms face a higher risk of forced sales in a downturn. Anthony Georgiades, Founder and General Partner at Innovating Capital, also called the strategies a ‘high-stakes play.’ Meanwhile, Kazmierczak noted that companies using convertible debt strategies have demonstrated innovative ways to balance growth with risk management. According to him, their effectiveness ultimately depends on the strength of their core business and their ability to service debt through operational cash flows, rather than relying purely on Bitcoin appreciation.  He believes  smart treasury strategies involve appropriately sizing positions  relative to overall balance sheets. Kazmierczak detailed that many public companies holding Bitcoin have demonstrated sound management by treating BTC allocations as a part of their overall reserves. What Will Happen to Bitcoin’s Price if Institutions Start Selling? While the experts showed cautious optimism regarding the financing strategies, centralization is more concerning. As of the latest  data  from Bitcoin Treasuries, the top three publicly listed Bitcoin treasury companies collectively hold about 695,000 BTC, accounting for  3.31% of the total  BTC supply. So, what happens  when or more decide to sell?  He elaborated that hedging options are available in the space, and the liquidity of markets like  futures  and options continues to grow. Therefore, Glover hopes that BTC treasury companies are strategic in managing their risk to withstand a bear market. Nonetheless, Bitcoin isn’t the only asset that will be impacted. The decline of the largest cryptocurrency could also lead to a broader market downfall.  The CIO of Ledn stressed that  ‘Bitcoin is still the  anchor  for the entire market.’ He noted that if large holders begin offloading, it sends a message that even the ‘safe’ end of crypto isn’t secure. Factors That Could Influence Companies’ Ability to Hold Bitcoin Bitcoin and the crypto sector aren’t immune to macroeconomic pressures. Whether it’s  President Trump’s tariffs  or  the Israel-Iran conflict , the market has reacted quickly by going into a free fall. The experts also outlined factors that are most likely to influence BTC treasury companies’ ability to hold Bitcoin through a bear market. Furthermore, Bitunix’s Chen also revealed that regulatory factors could play an important role. According to him, the  Clarity Act could reduce compliance costs  for institutions, thereby supporting long-term Bitcoin holdings by treasury firms. Besides this, shareholder pressure is another key factor to consider. Chen explained that if Bitcoin crashes, coordinated shareholder actions—such as calling a special meeting—could force the board to adopt a more conservative strategy and liquidate assets to reduce risk. Despite this, Glover stresses that a potential bear market wouldn’t erase Bitcoin. However, it will serve as a crucial test for  institutional conviction in the asset . [BeInCrypto]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955933849653248</link>
      <description>29 minutes agobeincryptoPublic Companies’ Bitcoin Bet: Can They Weather the Bear Market Storm?Public companies worldwide have been going all-in on Bitcoin (BTC) this year. Whether it’s through equity or debt issuance, firms have accelerated their push to acquire BTC and add it to their balance sheet</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947955933849653248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 0.31% in the past 1H, down 0.18% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952308594630656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoPANewsSouth Korean regulator urges asset managers to limit crypto exposureSouth Korea’s FSS advises fund managers to limit ETF exposure to crypto firms like Coinbase, citing caution as regulatory rules are still evolving.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951610113626112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that Galaxy Digital is well-positioned to capture upside opportunities in a favorable cryptocurrency regulatory environment. The investment bank noted that the passage of the U.S. GENIUS Act provides a &quot;favorable market structure&quot; for Galaxy&apos;s business. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoTechFlowJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a buy rating with a target price of $35.00On July 23, CoinDesk reported that investment bank Jefferies initiated coverage of cryptocurrency investment bank Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a buy rating and a price target of $35.00. Jefferies stated that</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947951242055061504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits.Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino posted that the Tether Group has invested in over 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. Relevant investment information has been published on the official Tether website. Paolo Ardoino stated that the source of funds is independent of USDT and other stablecoin reserves (reaching $13.70B in 2024) and falls within the business scope of Tether Investments investment division. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952604511801344</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoOdailyTether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits.Tether CEO Paolo Ardoino posted that the Tether Group has invested in over 120 companies, and this number is expected to grow significantly in the coming months and years. Relevant investm</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947952604511801344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Pastor Charged in $3.40M Crypto ScamA Denver, Colorado-based online pastor and his wife were indicted on Tuesday in connection with a cryptocurrency fraud scheme that raised over $3 million from faith-based investors. Between January 2022 and July 2023, the Regalados raised nearly $3.40 million by encouraging people in their religion to purchase INDXcoin through the Kingdom Wealth Exchange platform, with at least 300 people investing in the token and suffering losses. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947948979861393408</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsColorado Pastor Charged in $3.40M Crypto ScamA Denver, Colorado-based online pastor and his wife were indicted on Tuesday in connection with a cryptocurrency fraud scheme that raised over $3 million from faith-based investors. Between January 2022 and July 2023, the Regala</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947948979861393408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares obtains EU MiCA license, becoming the first licensed crypto asset management companyOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, European crypto asset management company CoinShares announced that it had obtained the EU&apos;s &quot;Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation&quot; (MiCA) license, becoming the first European crypto asset management company to obtain this license. The license was issued by the French Financial Markets Authority (AMF), enabling CoinShares to provide crypto asset portfolio management services within the 27 EU countries, and together with its existing MiFID and AIFM licenses, it constitutes a triple regulatory qualification. CoinShares said that this milestone is expected to promote the EU&apos;s $38.7 trillion asset management industry to further open up compliant crypto investment products. So far, the company has managed assets of more than $9 billion, and its stock price has risen by more than 46% this year. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946967392391168</link>
      <description>50 minutes agoPANewsCoinShares obtains EU MiCA license, becoming the first licensed crypto asset management companyOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, European crypto asset management company CoinShares announced that it had obtained the EU&apos;s &quot;Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation&quot; (MiCA) license, beco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946967392391168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$51.5214 millionOn July 23, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$51.5214 million. Among them:
The transaction volume of China Asset Management Bitcoin ETF (3042.HK/9042.HK/83042.HK) was HK$22.4015 million, and the transaction volume of China Asset Management Ethereum ETF (03046.HK/09046.HK/83046.HK) was HK$23.3565 million; The trading volume of Harvest Bitcoin ETF (03439.HK/09439.HK) was HK$1.0478 million, and the trading volume of Harvest Ethereum ETF (03179.HK/09179.HK) was HK$0.9224 million; The transaction volume of Bosera Bitcoin ETF (03008.HK/09008.HK) was HK$1.8167 million, and the transaction volume of Bosera Ethereum ETF (03009.HK/09009.HK) was HK$1.9765 million.
Note: All of the above virtual asset ETFs have Hong Kong dollar counters and US dollar counters, and only two of Hua Xia’s ETFs also have RMB counters. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946525744762880</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoPANewsData: Hong Kong virtual asset ETF today&apos;s transaction volume is about HK$51.5214 millionOn July 23, Hong Kong stock market data showed that as of the close, the transaction volume of all Hong Kong virtual asset ETFs today was approximately HK$51.5214 million. Among them:
The tran</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947946525744762880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Stock Exchange holds a symposium for companies in the Shanghai artificial intelligence industry chainOn July 23, the Shanghai Stock Exchange conducted a special survey on Shanghai&apos;s &quot;Model Speed Space&quot; and jointly held a symposium with the Xuhui District People&apos;s Government on Shanghai&apos;s artificial intelligence industry chain enterprises, and had in-depth face-to-face exchanges with key enterprises, investment institutions, and sponsors to accelerate the construction of a good ecology adapted to the era of artificial intelligence science and innovation. The Shanghai Stock Exchange said that it hopes that high-quality technology companies at different stages of development will seize the development opportunities of the capital market, make full use of policy reform tools, and use the capital market to become better and stronger, and win new advantages for future development with technological innovation. In the next step, the Shanghai Stock Exchange will follow the unified deployment of the China Securities Regulatory Commission, take the &quot;1+6&quot; policy of the Science and Technology Innovation Board reform as an opportunity, widely gather market consensus, and use cutting-edge technology fields such as artificial intelligence as strategic fulcrums to further strengthen the cultivation and service of high-quality technology companies throughout their life cycle, product lines, and business chains, accelerate the implementation of typical cases as soon as possible, and promote the development of new quality productivity to a new level. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945987372290048</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoPANewsShanghai Stock Exchange holds a symposium for companies in the Shanghai artificial intelligence industry chainOn July 23, the Shanghai Stock Exchange conducted a special survey on Shanghai&apos;s &quot;Model Speed Space&quot; and jointly held a symposium with the Xuhui District People&apos;s Governm</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945987372290048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An address transferred 16.81M XRP, worth $58.37M, to CoinbaseOn July 23, according to Whale Alert monitoring, an address transferred 16,812,113 XRP to Coinbase, worth approximately $58,365,018.00. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945654059339776</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoTechFlowAn address transferred 16.81M XRP, worth $58.37M, to CoinbaseOn July 23, according to Whale Alert monitoring, an address transferred 16,812,113 XRP to Coinbase, worth approximately $58,365,018.00. [TechFlow]#Crypto Stocks$MAG7.SSI$XRP$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947945654059339776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha Now Lists COAThe official interface shows that Binance Alpha has listed COA. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947947571019845632</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoOdailyBinance Alpha Now Lists COAThe official interface shows that Binance Alpha has listed COA. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 09:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947947571019845632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of stablecoin licensing regime next weekOn July 23, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, said that the Stablecoin Ordinance will take effect on August 1, when it will be illegal to promote any unlicensed stablecoin to the Hong Kong public. He pointed out that there have been recent scams targeting stablecoins and digital assets in the market, causing losses to the public. In response to market concerns about the application process, the HKMA plans to publish a summary of the &quot;Licensing System for Stablecoin Issuers&quot; next week, which will detail the acceptance and processing arrangements for license applications. Eddie Yue called on interested parties to stay tuned. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944419080081408</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsHong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of stablecoin licensing regime next weekOn July 23, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, said that the Stablecoin Ordinance will take effect on August 1, when it will be illegal to promote any unlicensed stabl</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944419080081408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sygnum: Bitcoin network transaction volume surpasses VisaRegulated digital asset bank Sygnum said that the Bitcoin network&apos;s existing annual transaction volume is estimated at $20 trillion, exceeding Visa&apos;s $13 trillion. The report also highlighted other data, such as Bitcoin&apos;s liquid supply on exchanges falling to a near seven-year low, ETFs currently holding over $150.00 billion in Bitcoin, and publicly listed companies holding approximately $80.00 billion in Bitcoin. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944481038340096</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsSygnum: Bitcoin network transaction volume surpasses VisaRegulated digital asset bank Sygnum said that the Bitcoin network&apos;s existing annual transaction volume is estimated at $20 trillion, exceeding Visa&apos;s $13 trillion. The report also highlighted other data, such as Bitcoin&apos;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944481038340096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi to Mars, they are pioneering narratives! Sun, who is flying to space, and the women who are changing the industry.&quot; YIYI, Damei Una, Li Qian, Silvia Wanqing, Crayon Xiaomi and other crypto KOLs will gather together to discuss the female power unique to Web3. This event will be broadcast simultaneously via Huobi Live and X Space, with constant red envelope rain, so stay tuned. Book a live broadcast: https://www.htx.com.de/zh-cn/live/detail/h5?id=79115&amp;invite_code=ip549223&amp;inviter_id=11351630 [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHuobi HTX joins hands with SunPump for a live broadcast at 20:00 tonight: Discussing the rise of female power in Web3According to official social media news on July 23, Huobi HTX will join hands with SunPump to hold a live broadcast at 20:00 today with the theme of &quot;From Huobi to M</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947944024039559168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure with native on-chain staking rewards. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsREX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF Surpasses $100 Million in AUMAsset management firm REX Shares announced that the REX-Osprey SOL Staking ETF, launched on July 2, has surpassed $100 million in assets under management. The ETF is the first U.S. ETF to combine spot Solana exposure with</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947943581607596032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>