<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:32:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>SenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsAccording to the Hong Kong Stock Exchange announcement, SenseTime Group announced the placement of 1.667B new Class B shares at a price of HK$1.5 per share to raise approximately HK$2.50B. The company intends to use part of the net proceeds from the placement to explore the technological integration and practice of artificial intelligence in innovative vertical fields, including but not limited to carrying out embodied intelligent robots, blockchain, Real World Assets (RWA), digital assets, stablecoins and other businesses independently or with strategic partners and obtaining relevant qualifications, as well as for general working capital. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948314449923870720</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoForesightNewsSenseTime Plans to Raise Approximately HK$2.5 Billion Through Share Placement to Develop RWA, Stablecoin, and Other Businesses and Obtain Relevant QualificationsAccording to the Hong Kong Stock Exchange announcement, SenseTime Group announced the placement of 1.667B new Cla</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948314449923870720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sky 联创 has repurchased 24.53M SKY and transferred it back to the staking address, worth approximately $2.08MAccording to @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, Sky (formerly MakerDAO) co-founder Rune continues to use SKY&apos;s staking rewards to repurchase SKY. An hour ago, he claimed SKY staking rewards: 1.90M USDS + 10.378M SPK (1.30M), then transferred them to his repurchase address, and has now repurchased 24.53M SKY (2.08M) and transferred them back to the staking address. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312952955801600</link>
      <description>8 minutes ago吴说Sky 联创 has repurchased 24.53M SKY and transferred it back to the staking address, worth approximately $2.08MAccording to @EmberCN&apos;s monitoring, Sky (formerly MakerDAO) co-founder Rune continues to use SKY&apos;s staking rewards to repurchase SKY. An hour ago, he claimed SKY staking rewards</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312952955801600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes: Cryptocurrency tax treatment remains unchanged after new US billReported on July 24 that, according to Forbes, despite the recent passage of the GENIUS Act and the CLARITY Act in the Senate, the U.S. Internal Revenue Service (IRS) still regards cryptocurrencies as &quot;intangible property&quot; for taxation, and the relevant tax regulations have not changed substantially for investors and traders. The GENIUS Act strengthens the compliance requirements for stablecoin issuers, but does not affect the tax classification of crypto assets. The CLARITY Act proposes a regulatory framework for digital asset securities and commodities, but also does not change the existing position of the IRS. Experts pointed out that currently cryptocurrency transactions do not need to comply with the wash sale rules of securities, and investors can flexibly carry forward losses, but they cannot enjoy the preferential tax treatment of some securities or commodity transactions. Unless the U.S. tax law is further revised, cryptocurrencies will still be taxed as property. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312559228096512</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoPANewsForbes: Cryptocurrency tax treatment remains unchanged after new US billReported on July 24 that, according to Forbes, despite the recent passage of the GENIUS Act and the CLARITY Act in the Senate, the U.S. Internal Revenue Service (IRS) still regards cryptocurrencies as &quot;intangi</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312559228096512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: Tether is ready to operate in the US market and will target the institutional marketTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated, &quot;Tether is ready to operate in the US market.&quot; A week ago, President Donald Trump signed the &quot;genius bill,&quot; regulating stablecoins in the US, and publicly thanked Ardoino for his work in the bill. Ardoino stated, &quot;We are developing an internal strategy for the US and plan to announce it in the next two months.&quot; The new US stablecoin will target the institutional market. Ardoino concluded by reiterating that Tether has no intention of going public like its US competitor Circle. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312580321251328</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoForesightNewsTether CEO: Tether is ready to operate in the US market and will target the institutional marketTether CEO Paolo Ardoino stated, &quot;Tether is ready to operate in the US market.&quot; A week ago, President Donald Trump signed the &quot;genius bill,&quot; regulating stablecoins in the US, an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948312580321251328</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese AI company Quantum to buy up to 3,000 Bitcoin within 12 monthsAccording to CoinDesk Japan, Japanese listed company Quantum Solutions has announced that it will purchase up to 3,000 Bitcoin (approximately 53.85B JPY) in the next 12 months, officially entering the cryptocurrency field. The company stated that this move is aimed at responding to the global crypto market expansion and the popularity of Bitcoin as &quot;digital gold,&quot; while also diversifying assets, reducing exchange rate risks, and hedging against inflation. Quantum plans to initially invest approximately 1.48B JPY and will gradually implement the plan using borrowed funds. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948311356540784640</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoForesightNewsJapanese AI company Quantum to buy up to 3,000 Bitcoin within 12 monthsAccording to CoinDesk Japan, Japanese listed company Quantum Solutions has announced that it will purchase up to 3,000 Bitcoin (approximately 53.85B JPY) in the next 12 months, officially entering the c</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948311356540784640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lido’s share of the ETH staking market has dropped to 25%, a three-year lowOn July 24, according to Tom Wan citing Dune data, Lido&apos;s share of the Ethereum staking market has dropped to 25%, the lowest point since March 2022. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948306003317035008</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsLido’s share of the ETH staking market has dropped to 25%, a three-year lowOn July 24, according to Tom Wan citing Dune data, Lido&apos;s share of the Ethereum staking market has dropped to 25%, the lowest point since March 2022. [PANews]#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSI$LDOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948306003317035008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forbes: US stablecoins still treated as property for tax purposes, GENIUS Act does not change tax rulesAccording to Forbes, although the US recently passed the GENIUS Act, the IRS still considers digital assets as property, and the key tax rules remain unchanged for traders and investors. The GENIUS Act imposes strict reserve, audit, and disclosure requirements on US stablecoin issuers, including 1:1 asset backing and monthly financial attestations; however, the bill does not reclassify stablecoins for tax purposes. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948305713092169728</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoForesightNewsForbes: US stablecoins still treated as property for tax purposes, GENIUS Act does not change tax rulesAccording to Forbes, although the US recently passed the GENIUS Act, the IRS still considers digital assets as property, and the key tax rules remain unchanged for trader</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948305713092169728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghana’s Central Bank plans to launch crypto regulatory framework to promote digital assetsOn July 24, the Central Bank of Ghana plans to introduce a licensing system for crypto platforms to regulate digital assets and capture related revenues. Central Bank Governor Johnson Asiama revealed that the regulatory framework is expected to be submitted to parliament for review in September this year. The new bill aims to use cryptocurrencies to promote cross-border trade, attract strategic investments, and collect financial data to advance the country’s digital asset sector. Earlier news, the Governor of the Central Bank of Ghana said: Ghana is finalizing the regulatory framework for cryptocurrency transactions. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302725002891264</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoPANewsGhana’s Central Bank plans to launch crypto regulatory framework to promote digital assetsOn July 24, the Central Bank of Ghana plans to introduce a licensing system for crypto platforms to regulate digital assets and capture related revenues. Central Bank Governor Johnson Asiama</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302725002891264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) raises over £100 million to promote AI and Bitcoin deploymentOn July 24, the listed company Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) announced that it had completed the fundraising of over £100 million of convertible bonds and started the third round of financing, with the minimum subscription threshold reduced to $100,000.00, which is expected to end on July 28. The funds will be used to expand the business and promote the construction of Bitcoin and decentralized AI infrastructure. CEO Henry Elder has officially joined the board of directors as executive director. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302120138117120</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsSatsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) raises over £100 million to promote AI and Bitcoin deploymentOn July 24, the listed company Satsuma (formerly Tao Alpha) announced that it had completed the fundraising of over £100 million of convertible bonds and started the third round of financing</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302120138117120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has launched U-margined perpetual contracts.On July 24, according to the official announcement, LBank has launched U-based perpetual contracts on July 24, 2025, at 14:30 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301297815457792</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoTechFlowLBank has launched U-margined perpetual contracts.On July 24, according to the official announcement, LBank has launched U-based perpetual contracts on July 24, 2025, at 14:30 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948301297815457792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EU approves a €93.00B counter-tariff plan against the USEU member states have voted in favor of a measure to impose retaliatory tariffs on a total of €93.00B worth of U.S. products. The day before, a European Commission spokesperson said on July 23 that the EU plans to merge two lists of retaliatory tariffs on U.S. exports into a single list totaling €93.00B. The list mainly involves high-value industrial products such as aircraft, automobiles, and electrical equipment. The total value of the package of retaliatory lists formed by the two lists amounts to €93.00B. European Commission spokesman Olof Gill said on July 23 that if negotiations (with the U.S.) break down, the countermeasures will take effect on August 7. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302422211891200</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoOdailyThe EU approves a €93.00B counter-tariff plan against the USEU member states have voted in favor of a measure to impose retaliatory tariffs on a total of €93.00B worth of U.S. products. The day before, a European Commission spokesperson said on July 23 that the EU plans to merge</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948302422211891200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: The current Bitcoin RSI index is close to 75, and it is expected that the RSI will be greater than 80 for several months during the bull market.PlanB posted that Bitcoin&apos;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently close to 75. In this bull market, it is expected that the RSI will reach above 80 for several months, similar to the bull market performance in 2021, 2017, 2013, and 2011. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948299890806820864</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyAnalyst: The current Bitcoin RSI index is close to 75, and it is expected that the RSI will be greater than 80 for several months during the bull market.PlanB posted that Bitcoin&apos;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) is currently close to 75. In this bull market, it is expected that the RS</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948299890806820864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoPlus launches a 500 million GPS security fund, divided into a token-based reward pool and a token bounty pool.GoPlus announces the launch of a 500 million GPS Security Fund (currently valued at approximately $10.00M USD). There are two ways for users to participate in the fund distribution: users who stake GPS can receive triple benefits (basic annualized + security incident lottery + GoPlus security ecosystem income repurchase); participate in the &quot;Security Bounty List&quot; to participate in obtaining a 100.00M GPS special bounty pool, for example: submit a malicious address / phishing website, with a maximum prize of 10,000 GPS. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948297740588486656</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsGoPlus launches a 500 million GPS security fund, divided into a token-based reward pool and a token bounty pool.GoPlus announces the launch of a 500 million GPS Security Fund (currently valued at approximately $10.00M USD). There are two ways for users to participate in the fu</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948297740588486656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users with App versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function starting July 28Binance Chinese announced, &quot;Starting July 28th, users of the Binance App with versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function. Please upgrade to the latest version in time to ensure normal use.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948296410767626240</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBinance: Users with App versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function starting July 28Binance Chinese announced, &quot;Starting July 28th, users of the Binance App with versions lower than 3.0.x will not be able to use the facial pre-check function</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948296410767626240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6% in pre-market trading, with Musk saying Tesla may face some difficult quarters.On July 24, according to data from Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network, Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6.00% in pre-market trading. Tesla&apos;s total revenue for the second quarter decreased by 12.00% year-on-year to $22.50B, and Musk said that Tesla may face several difficult quarters next. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294093439832064</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowTesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6% in pre-market trading, with Musk saying Tesla may face some difficult quarters.On July 24, according to data from Hithink RoyalFlush Information Network, Tesla&apos;s U.S. stock fell 6.00% in pre-market trading. Tesla&apos;s total revenue for the second quarter dec</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294093439832064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Meme tokens listed on JuCoin chain, expanding the JuCoin Preferred Zone lineupOn July 24, 2025, according to official sources, JuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection Preferred Zone officially launched three popular Memes: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, which are now fully open for trading. Users can enter through the &quot;Trading&quot; - &quot;On-chain Trading&quot; section on the JuCoin App or homepage. It is reported that memecoin emphasizes the community-driven pure Meme spirit; PYTHIA represents a pioneering experiment in the integration of AI and biotechnology; AOL Coin pays tribute to the America Online cultural heritage. This launch will further enrich the JuCoin on-chain ecosystem and meet users&apos; diversified asset allocation needs. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294852696936448</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyThree Meme tokens listed on JuCoin chain, expanding the JuCoin Preferred Zone lineupOn July 24, 2025, according to official sources, JuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection Preferred Zone officially launched three popular Memes: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, which are now fully open for tra</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294852696936448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huang Licheng closed his position of 1,229 ETH and lost $80,000. The long positions of ETH, PUMP and HYPE still had a floating loss of about $8.711 million.On July 24, according to Ai Yi’s monitoring, Huang Licheng closed 1,229 ETH positions in the past hour, with a loss of about $80,000. Currently, his long positions in ETH, PUMP and HYPE still have a floating loss of about $8.711 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948293552563359744</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsHuang Licheng closed his position of 1,229 ETH and lost $80,000. The long positions of ETH, PUMP and HYPE still had a floating loss of about $8.711 million.On July 24, according to Ai Yi’s monitoring, Huang Licheng closed 1,229 ETH positions in the past hour, with a loss of about $80</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948293552563359744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; has lost over $8.71M on Hyperliquid due to long positions.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi, &quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; closed 1,229 ETH in the past 1 hour and lost $80,000.00, and the remaining ETH, PUMP, and HYPE long positions are still at a floating loss of $8,711,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294861144264704</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdaily&quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; has lost over $8.71M on Hyperliquid due to long positions.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi, &quot;Machi Big Brother&quot; closed 1,229 ETH in the past 1 hour and lost $80,000.00, and the remaining ETH, PUMP, and HYPE long positions are still at a floating loss of $8,711,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948294861144264704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast at 8 PM today: How to Learn and Earn through BlumHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast today at 20:00, with the theme &quot;How to Learn and Earn through Blum.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292101573251072</link>
      <description>1 hour agoTechFlowHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast at 8 PM today: How to Learn and Earn through BlumHuobi HTX Growth Academy will hold a themed live broadcast today at 20:00, with the theme &quot;How to Learn and Earn through Blum.&quot;$BLUM$HTXShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948292101573251072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT platform Pixel Vault may cease operationsAccording to the official announcement, NFT platform Pixel Vault announced that after more than four years of development, the company has begun the process of potentially ceasing operations. The company had attempted to create a profitable and sustainable crypto entertainment business, but was unsuccessful. Currently, Pixel Vault is in discussions with multiple parties regarding the possibility of acquiring the company and its assets in order to continue serving the community. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948291599938686976</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说NFT platform Pixel Vault may cease operationsAccording to the official announcement, NFT platform Pixel Vault announced that after more than four years of development, the company has begun the process of potentially ceasing operations. The company had attempted to create a profitable an</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 08:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948291599938686976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 09:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>