<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Ethereum buyers took profits near $2,520.00, but still hold nearly 2.00M ETHA heatmap of Ethereum&apos;s cost basis distribution released by blockchain data analysis firm Glassnode shows that since July 1, buyers have been taking profits significantly around $2,520.00, and the red area is gradually weakening. However, these buyers still hold nearly 2.00M ETH. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947607674225184768</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoForesightNewsGlassnode: Ethereum buyers took profits near $2,520.00, but still hold nearly 2.00M ETHA heatmap of Ethereum&apos;s cost basis distribution released by blockchain data analysis firm Glassnode shows that since July 1, buyers have been taking profits significantly around $2,520.0</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947607674225184768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot tradingOn July 22, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot trading at 21:00 (UTC+8) on July 23. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605879021129728</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsGate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot tradingOn July 22, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch Codatta (XNY) spot trading at 21:00 (UTC+8) on July 23. [PANews]$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605879021129728</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWF Labs co-founder: Falcon Finance funds have all been withdrawn from CEX, and the new transparency page will be launched this weekOn July 22, Andrei Grachev, co-founder of DWF Labs and co-founder of Falcon Finance, wrote that Falcon Finance has withdrawn all funds from centralized exchanges and obtained a confirmation letter from the auditor. Currently, Falcon Finance is designing the structure of a new transparency page, which is expected to be launched this week. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605399893200896</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsDWF Labs co-founder: Falcon Finance funds have all been withdrawn from CEX, and the new transparency page will be launched this weekOn July 22, Andrei Grachev, co-founder of DWF Labs and co-founder of Falcon Finance, wrote that Falcon Finance has withdrawn all funds from centrali</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605399893200896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy&apos;s per-share equivalent of Bitcoin has increased by 20.8% since the beginning of the year, TD Cowen reiterates MSTR&apos;s target price of $680.00Investment bank TD Cowen stated that the premium for Strategy is reasonable. After increasing its holdings by another 6,220 BTC last week, one share of MSTR stock now corresponds to 20.8% more Bitcoin than on January 1. TD Cowen reiterated its $680.00 target price for MSTR stock and expects that by 2027, Strategy will hold nearly 900,000 BTC, and the flywheel strategy of Bitcoin treasury will continue to provide it with momentum. (The Block) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605308901969920</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoOdailyStrategy&apos;s per-share equivalent of Bitcoin has increased by 20.8% since the beginning of the year, TD Cowen reiterates MSTR&apos;s target price of $680.00Investment bank TD Cowen stated that the premium for Strategy is reasonable. After increasing its holdings by another 6,220 BTC las</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947605308901969920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate will list Uranium.io (XU3O8) for spot trading, and launch HODLer Airdrop and trading competition with a total prize pool of 10,962 XU3O8According to the official announcement, Gate will launch Uranium.io (XU3O8) spot trading on July 24 at 16:00 (UTC+8). To give back to platform users, XU3O8 HODLer Airdrop and trading competition are launched, with a total prize pool of 10,962 XU3O8. Gate has now launched the 272nd HODLer Airdrop, which will end on July 24 at 14:00 (UTC+8). Users holding 1 GT can participate in the free airdrop and share 4,474 XU3O8. Gate will launch the Uranium.io (XU3O8) trading competition from July 24 at 16:00 to July 31 at 16:00 (UTC+8). Users can share 6,488 XU3O8 by completing spot trading, inviting friends, and completing the first order exclusive task for new users. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602795083616256</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoOdailyGate will list Uranium.io (XU3O8) for spot trading, and launch HODLer Airdrop and trading competition with a total prize pool of 10,962 XU3O8According to the official announcement, Gate will launch Uranium.io (XU3O8) spot trading on July 24 at 16:00 (UTC+8). To give back to platf</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602795083616256</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts.On July 22, according to the official announcement, LBank launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts for the first time on July 22, 2025, at 16:10 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602141049016320</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoTechFlowLBank has launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts.On July 22, according to the official announcement, LBank launched SOLAMI USDT-margined perpetual contracts for the first time on July 22, 2025, at 16:10 (SGT), with a maximum leverage of 20x. [Techflow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602141049016320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernstein raises price targets for Meta and AlphabetOn July 22, Bernstein raised its target price for Alphabet (GOOG.O) from $185 to $195 and its target price for Meta Platforms (META.O) from $700 to $775. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947601609597145088</link>
      <description>31 minutes agoPANewsBernstein raises price targets for Meta and AlphabetOn July 22, Bernstein raised its target price for Alphabet (GOOG.O) from $185 to $195 and its target price for Meta Platforms (META.O) from $700 to $775. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947601609597145088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: US Treasury sustainability will be a key issue in the second half of this yearAramea Asset Management analyst Felix Herrmann said in a report that the debate over U.S. debt sustainability could dominate U.S. markets in the second half of this year. The chief economist said this would lead to upside risks for long-term U.S. Treasury yields. He said that the U.S. debt will increase significantly in the short term, partly due to the so-called &quot;Big, Beautiful Bill.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602803631607808</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoOdailyInstitutions: US Treasury sustainability will be a key issue in the second half of this yearAramea Asset Management analyst Felix Herrmann said in a report that the debate over U.S. debt sustainability could dominate U.S. markets in the second half of this year. The chief economi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947602803631607808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futu Launches ChinaAMC Tokenized Money Fund, Exploring On-Chain Subscription and Redemption with Stablecoin Application ScenariosFutu Holdings (FUTU) and China Asset Management (Hong Kong) have announced a partnership in the Web3.0 field. Futu will be the exclusive broker to list tokenized money market funds issued by China Asset Management (Hong Kong) on its platform, covering three currencies: HKD, RMB, and USD. Currently, the HKD product has been launched on the Futu platform, and the USD product is expected to be launched this week. The two parties plan to explore a &quot;on-chain&quot; and &quot;off-chain&quot; dual subscription and redemption mechanism in the future, and support 7×24-hour on-chain trading and receipt services. In addition, Zeng Yuchao, Managing Director of Futu Holdings, said that after the issuance of stablecoins, Futu will support the use of stablecoins on the platform. For example, users can use stablecoins as platform balances or holding assets to directly buy stocks, and Futu will handle the fiat currency clearing and settlement process for users. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947600484093415424</link>
      <description>39 minutes ago吴说Futu Launches ChinaAMC Tokenized Money Fund, Exploring On-Chain Subscription and Redemption with Stablecoin Application ScenariosFutu Holdings (FUTU) and China Asset Management (Hong Kong) have announced a partnership in the Web3.0 field. Futu will be the exclusive broker to list tok</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947600484093415424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance alpha is now live with ZKWASMOn July 22, the official page showed that Binance alpha is now live on ZKWASM. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022319751168</link>
      <description>41 minutes agoTechFlowBinance alpha is now live with ZKWASMOn July 22, the official page showed that Binance alpha is now live on ZKWASM. [TechFlow]#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022319751168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of England Governor Bailey: Stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank accountAccording to Zhitong Finance, Bank of England Governor Bailey stated that stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank account. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022751764480</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoForesightNewsBank of England Governor Bailey: Stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank accountAccording to Zhitong Finance, Bank of England Governor Bailey stated that stablecoins need to be as stable as pounds in a bank account. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599022751764480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMP falls below private placement price, nearly 30B PUMP from two major whales has flowed into exchangesAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, after the PUMP price fell below its private/public sale price of $0.004, the largest token holding address, which spent 100.00M USDC to purchase 25.00B PUMP in the private placement round, has deposited 17.00B PUMP to the exchange through FalconX, worth approximately $89.50M, and currently still holds 8.00B PUMP, worth approximately $29.58M. In addition, the second largest token holding address of PUMP previously spent 50.00M USDC to purchase 12.50B PUMP, worth approximately $71.37M, and has now transferred all of them to the exchange. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947598166060978176</link>
      <description>47 minutes ago吴说PUMP falls below private placement price, nearly 30B PUMP from two major whales has flowed into exchangesAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, after the PUMP price fell below its private/public sale price of $0.004, the largest token holding address, which spent 100.00M USDC to purcha</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947598166060978176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank Points System Officially LaunchedAccording to official news, LBank has announced the official launch of its points system, where users can earn points through various methods such as depositing assets, spot and margin trading, perpetual contracts, KYC verification, and inviting friends. The first phase of the program will last for 90 days, and users can accumulate points for daily active behaviors. The higher the trading volume and the more friends invited, the more points will be earned. As another innovative exploration of LBank&apos;s trading incentive mechanism, the points system integrates the multi-dimensional drivers of &quot;holding + trading + social fission,&quot; and is open and transparent. It aims to empower users at different levels, help asset growth, and promote a virtuous cycle of ecological co-construction. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597772366827520</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoOdailyLBank Points System Officially LaunchedAccording to official news, LBank has announced the official launch of its points system, where users can earn points through various methods such as depositing assets, spot and margin trading, perpetual contracts, KYC verification, and invi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597772366827520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: Dollar may fall further as US economic growth slowsInsight Investment analyst Francesca Fornasari said in a report that the dollar may weaken further in the second half of 2025 as U.S. economic growth slows. She said that economic weakness could pave the way for further interest rate cuts by the Federal Reserve. The dollar&apos;s continued decline as the world&apos;s reserve currency will also put pressure on the dollar. However, given the uncertainty of the U.S. policy outlook and the current aggressive short bets against the dollar, the dollar&apos;s decline should be gradual and moderate. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597780839321600</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailyInstitutions: Dollar may fall further as US economic growth slowsInsight Investment analyst Francesca Fornasari said in a report that the dollar may weaken further in the second half of 2025 as U.S. economic growth slows. She said that economic weakness could pave the way for fur</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947597780839321600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Public Companies Turn to Bitcoin This Week As Corporate Adoption RisesCorporate Bitcoin adoption is gaining momentum, as more publicly listed companies worldwide are shifting their treasury strategies from cash to digital assets. Although investor sentiment varies, the overall market is witnessing growing institutional alignment with Bitcoin as a reserve and strategic asset. Bitcoin Adoption Accelerates as Firms Embrace BTC MicroStrategy (MSTR) remains a notable leader in corporate Bitcoin adoption . The firm recently announced plans to issue 5.00 million Series A STRC preferred shares to raise capital for additional BTC purchases . The capital is intended for working capital needs and explicitly aligns with a long-term Bitcoin reserve strategy . Beyond MicroStrategy, other companies are actively adopting Bitcoin on their balance sheets. US-listed Profusa secured a $100.00 million equity credit line to build a Bitcoin reserve. Similarly, EV startup Volcon acquired over 280 BTC and completed a $500.00 million private funding round to support further accumulation. In Europe, Swedish-listed H100 Group increased its holdings to over 510 BTC after purchasing an additional 140 BTC. Perhaps the most symbolic move comes from Grupo Murano, a major real estate conglomerate in Mexico, which declared Bitcoin a “core strategic asset” with an initial investment of $1.00 billion. This shows a growing corporate consensus that Bitcoin is more than a speculative tool—it is becoming part of global financial policy. Market Signals Support Confidence Recent data shows that public companies’ net purchases of Bitcoin reached $953.00 million last week alone, with MSTR accounting for over $700.00 million. This surge coincides with a sharp increase in Google Trends searches for “ Buy Bitcoin ,” suggesting a revival of retail interest alongside institutional momentum. Overall, corporate Bitcoin adoption reflects a broader financial paradigm shift. Bitcoin is no longer treated as a fringe or experimental asset. From tech to real estate, businesses are increasingly incorporating Bitcoin into their treasury models, not only for diversification but also as a hedge and a symbol of forward-thinking strategy.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599073850970112</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoMore Public Companies Turn to Bitcoin This Week As Corporate Adoption RisesCorporate Bitcoin adoption is gaining momentum, as more publicly listed companies worldwide are shifting their treasury strategies from cash to digital assets. Although investor sentiment varies, the overa</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947599073850970112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ave.ai recently launched a series of tools to accelerate its expansion into the Southeast Asian market.On July 20th, Kuala Lumpur Blockchain Week 2025 in Kuala Lumpur, Southeast Asia, kicked off. Ave.ai, a leading on-chain aggregation trading platform, consecutively sponsored three high-profile side events: The MAGNE.AI Launch Night, the Holder Appreciation Reception, and the ANOME Pool Party. This series of events brought together many industry leaders to discuss in-depth cutting-edge topics such as on-chain transaction efficiency innovation, user-friendly product design, sustainable ecosystem construction, the survival status of P traders, and on-chain tool development. Attendees pointed out that current on-chain data analysis is evolving from professional tools to inclusive infrastructure, and Ave.ai&apos;s recently launched Signal Square and real-time monitoring system are accelerating this process. &quot;We are witnessing the explosive growth of the Southeast Asian Web3 market,&quot; said the Ave.ai BD representative in his speech at the ANOME pool party. &quot;By supporting community development and user education practices, Ave.ai will continue to empower the on-chain data transaction process.&quot; The blockchain week-related side events attracted more than 2,000 participants in total. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947595248305983488</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyAve.ai recently launched a series of tools to accelerate its expansion into the Southeast Asian market.On July 20th, Kuala Lumpur Blockchain Week 2025 in Kuala Lumpur, Southeast Asia, kicked off. Ave.ai, a leading on-chain aggregation trading platform, consecutively sponsored three h</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947595248305983488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai: Developing AI+AR, AI+MR and other multi-form eyewear productsOn July 22, the Shanghai Municipal Economic and Information Commission issued the &quot;Shanghai Next Generation Display Industry High-Quality Development Action Plan (2026-2030)&quot;. It pointed out that smart glasses will drive display technology innovation. Actively deploy smart glasses production capacity and build intelligent and unmanned production lines. Develop multi-form glasses products such as AI+AR and AI+MR, and cultivate a multi-technical micro-display ecosystem with terminal integration. Focusing on the actual needs of the consumer market, focusing on key technical indicators such as lightweight, low power consumption, high resolution, and large field of view, promote iterative innovation of key components such as display devices, waveguide lenses, and core chips, and continuously improve product performance. Encourage innovation in product models and glasses forms for the next generation of silicon-based micro-displays, and accelerate the development of full-color, portable smart glasses products. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947591188651724800</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsShanghai: Developing AI+AR, AI+MR and other multi-form eyewear productsOn July 22, the Shanghai Municipal Economic and Information Commission issued the &quot;Shanghai Next Generation Display Industry High-Quality Development Action Plan (2026-2030)&quot;. It pointed out that smart glasses wil</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947591188651724800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Figma plans to raise $1.0 billion in IPO, holds Bitcoin ETF, and plans to issue blockchain stocksAccording to the Financial Times, design software company Figma has officially submitted IPO documents to the US SEC, planning to issue approximately 40.00 million shares at a price of $25–28 per share, with a fundraising scale of up to $1.00 billion and a maximum valuation of $16.50 billion (fully diluted). Figma disclosed in the documents that it currently holds approximately $70.00 million in Bitcoin ETFs and plans to increase its investment in the coming months. In addition, the company has been authorized to issue Blockchain Common Stock. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947590146174242816</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Figma plans to raise $1.0 billion in IPO, holds Bitcoin ETF, and plans to issue blockchain stocksAccording to the Financial Times, design software company Figma has officially submitted IPO documents to the US SEC, planning to issue approximately 40.00 million shares at a price of $25–28</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947590146174242816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>071labs makes strategic investment in Bitcoin scaling project NubitOn July 22, 071labs announced a strategic investment in Nubit, a core infrastructure project for Bitcoin expansion. Nubit is committed to improving the scalability, usability and openness of the Bitcoin ecosystem, and as a core contributor, developed Thunderbolt, a native soft fork of Bitcoin. Thunderbolt significantly improves Bitcoin&apos;s transaction throughput through key technologies such as UTXO bundling and OP_CAT, and realizes native support for on-chain applications such as smart contracts, asset issuance and DeFi. As of July 2025, the Thunderbolt mainnet transaction volume has exceeded 4 million, with more than 5,000 daily active users. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947589180096008192</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANews071labs makes strategic investment in Bitcoin scaling project NubitOn July 22, 071labs announced a strategic investment in Nubit, a core infrastructure project for Bitcoin expansion. Nubit is committed to improving the scalability, usability and openness of the Bitcoin ecosystem, and</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947589180096008192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sidekick&apos;s China-Korea Web3 KOL League of Legends Tournament Has BegunSidekick announced on X that its first China-Korea KOL League of Legends competition has started. Currently, the group stage for the China region is underway, and the group stage for the Korea region will begin this Tuesday at 5 PM, with the final scheduled for this Saturday at 1 PM. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947590043753533440</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsSidekick&apos;s China-Korea Web3 KOL League of Legends Tournament Has BegunSidekick announced on X that its first China-Korea KOL League of Legends competition has started. Currently, the group stage for the China region is underway, and the group stage for the Korea region will be</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947590043753533440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 10:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>