<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:54:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>The number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, the number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000, with net redemptions reaching 271,000. On-chain data shows that in the past week, two HTX-related wallets have cumulatively redeemed 110,000 ETH, with a total value of over $400 million. In addition, institutions such as Abraxas Capital Mgmt have also carried out staking redemptions. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924910063554560</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyThe number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, the number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000, with net redemptions reaching 271,000. On-chain data shows that in the past week, two H</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924910063554560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport&apos;s custody platform, Cactus Custody, has entered into a strategic partnership with Bybit.Cactus Custody, a compliant digital asset custodian under Matrixport Group, has announced a strategic partnership with Bybit. Its over-the-counter (OTC) settlement system, Cactus Oasis, has been officially integrated into the Bybit platform and will be officially put into use on July 28th in the early morning. Cactus Custody and Bybit are working together to bring innovative OTC settlement solutions to the market and enhance the trading experience for crypto investors. Cactus Oasis is an OTC settlement system created by Cactus Custody specifically for institutional clients. After Bybit officially puts Cactus Oasis into use, institutional users can enjoy Bybit&apos;s smooth trading experience and liquidity, as well as independent asset custody, reducing counterparty risk. At the same time, institutional users do not need to deposit funds into the platform in advance, and can quickly participate in spot and contract market transactions through simple offline authorization. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924918494105600</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyMatrixport&apos;s custody platform, Cactus Custody, has entered into a strategic partnership with Bybit.Cactus Custody, a compliant digital asset custodian under Matrixport Group, has announced a strategic partnership with Bybit. Its over-the-counter (OTC) settlement system, Cactus Oa</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924918494105600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought 475 WBTC and established a long position of 434.6 BTC.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;0x3E38&quot; bought 475 WBTC ($56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 and went long on BTC by borrowing on Aave. He also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC ($51.60M) on Hyperliquid with 10x leverage. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924926937239552</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoOdailyA whale bought 475 WBTC and established a long position of 434.6 BTC.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;0x3E38&quot; bought 475 WBTC ($56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 and went long on BTC by borrowing on Aave. He also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC ($51.60</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924926937239552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch XNY spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Hotbit Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23: Spot trading pair XNY/USDT (July 23 21:20 UTC+8): $XNY is the native token of the Codatta project. Codatta is an open, decentralized, multi-chain protocol that combines blockchain-based data infrastructure with a collaborative network of human contributors and professional AI agents. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923761684090880</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch XNY spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Hotbit Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23: Spot trading pair XNY/USDT (July 23 21:20 UTC+8): $XNY is the native token of the Codatta project. Codatta is</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923761684090880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>edgeX 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.15BOn July 23, according to the official announcement, edgeX&apos;s 24-hour trading volume exceeded $1.15B, marking a major milestone in the platform&apos;s development. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923515503611904</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoTechFlowedgeX 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.15BOn July 23, according to the official announcement, edgeX&apos;s 24-hour trading volume exceeded $1.15B, marking a major milestone in the platform&apos;s development. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923515503611904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; Recruitment ProgramBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; recruitment campaign, which will recruit 300 users from the Chinese community to become &quot;Scan Chain Product Promoters&quot; by sharing their experiences using the Bitget Wallet scan chain function to discover meme potential coins. The event will run from July 23 to August 1. Participants need to use the Bitget Wallet scan chain function and publish tweets to share the process of screening potential coins and their personal experiences. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947922407586598912</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet Launches &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; Recruitment ProgramBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; recruitment campaign, which will recruit 300 users from the Chinese community to become &quot;Scan Chain Product Promot</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947922407586598912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainCatcher announces a partnership with Volcano Engine to drive the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure.ChainCatcher has announced a partnership with Volcengine to assist Volcengine in promoting its cloud computing services, including cloud servers, storage, and enterprise-level solutions. Through this collaboration, both parties will jointly promote the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure. As an influential media platform in the Web3 field, ChainCatcher&apos;s collaboration will combine its industry resources with Volcengine&apos;s technical advantages to provide Web3 companies with more efficient cloud service support. As a leading global cloud computing service provider, Volcengine&apos;s collaboration will further strengthen its presence in Web3 and emerging technology fields. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921955025391616</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoChainCatcherChainCatcher announces a partnership with Volcano Engine to drive the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure.ChainCatcher has announced a partnership with Volcengine to assist Volcengine in promoting its cloud computing services, including cloud servers, storage, and</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921955025391616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale starting with 0x3E3 is going long on BTC in Aave and Hyperliquid, with total profits exceeding $5.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale starting with 0x3E3 borrowed from Aave to purchase 475 WBTC (worth approximately $56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 to long BTC. The address also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC (worth approximately $51.60M) with 10x leverage on Hyperliquid. The total profit has now exceeded $5.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921620428984320</link>
      <description>25 minutes agoForesightNewsA whale starting with 0x3E3 is going long on BTC in Aave and Hyperliquid, with total profits exceeding $5.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale starting with 0x3E3 borrowed from Aave to purchase 475 WBTC (worth approximately $56.00M) at an average price of $115,7</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921620428984320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant analyst: Ethereum may experience a pullback in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too largeOn July 23, CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan said that Ethereum has recently risen sharply and may experience a correction in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too large. He pointed out that compared with the overheated market in March and November 2024, the current market is not high. Although Ethereum has performed slowly in this cycle, it has bottomed out and may continue to rise in the second half of 2025. He also mentioned that the rise of Ethereum often drives the performance of other currencies, and investors can pay attention to the subsequent market trends. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917982683959296</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoPANewsCryptoQuant analyst: Ethereum may experience a pullback in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too largeOn July 23, CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan said that Ethereum has recently risen sharply and may experience a correction in the short term, bu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917982683959296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has withdrawn a cumulative total of 12,341 ETH from Kraken over the past 8 days, equivalent to approximately $45.60M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,672 ETH, worth $9.87M, from Kraken. In the past 8 days, this whale has withdrawn 12,341 ETH, worth $45.60M, from Kraken. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947919876928114688</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoOdailyA whale has withdrawn a cumulative total of 12,341 ETH from Kraken over the past 8 days, equivalent to approximately $45.60M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,672 ETH, worth $9.87M, from Kraken. In the past 8 days, this whale has withdrawn 12,341 ETH, worth</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947919876928114688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walrus Announces Collaboration with Gata to Help Build Open AI Execution InfrastructureOn July 23, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced a partnership with Gata, which is dedicated to developing decentralized large model inference, training, and data technology, to become a core component of Gata AI&apos;s open execution infrastructure. With Walrus, Gata will solve the high data access costs that have long plagued decentralized AI. This integration directly empowers Gata&apos;s DataAgent, allowing anyone to contribute idle computing power with one click through a browser, collaboratively generating synthetic datasets needed for AI training. Walrus provides performance comparable to centralized cloud services and low-cost storage, and more importantly, eliminates download fees, allowing the Gata community to conduct large-scale data interaction in a permissionless manner without incurring unpredictable and unsustainable costs. In the future, Gata plans to leverage Walrus&apos;s unique on-chain data programmability to build an open, auditable pricing model. By storing verifiable computation proofs on Walrus, Gata can use Move-based smart contracts to transparently verify computation tasks and settle on-chain, creating a fairer pricing mechanism for service providers, which is a major improvement over the opaque models used by current centralized AI providers. It is reported that Walrus is a new generation storage protocol built for AI Agents, on-chain applications, and enterprises that process large-scale unstructured data. Whether it&apos;s images, videos, audio files, or dynamic metadata, Walrus can store them efficiently, securely, and economically through its distributed node network. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917150328524800</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoTechFlowWalrus Announces Collaboration with Gata to Help Build Open AI Execution InfrastructureOn July 23, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced a partnership with Gata, which is dedicated to developing decentralized large model inference, training, and</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917150328524800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance altcoin contract daily trading volume climbs to $100.70B, hitting its highest level since February 3According to Cointelegraph, Binance&apos;s altcoin contract daily trading volume climbed to $100.70B, reaching its highest level since February 3. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915833988157440</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoForesightNewsBinance altcoin contract daily trading volume climbs to $100.70B, hitting its highest level since February 3According to Cointelegraph, Binance&apos;s altcoin contract daily trading volume climbed to $100.70B, reaching its highest level since February 3. [Foresight News]Share t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915833988157440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huarong Securities and Guojin Securities jointly organized more than 50 Chinese and foreign institutions to visit OSL to jointly explore digital asset development opportunities.Hong Kong-listed OSL Group (863.HK), which focuses on crypto assets, exchanged views with a delegation of institutional investors organized by China Securities and Guojin Securities, who were visiting, to jointly explore the development trends and compliance paths of the digital asset industry. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915151629422592</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoForesightNewsHuarong Securities and Guojin Securities jointly organized more than 50 Chinese and foreign institutions to visit OSL to jointly explore digital asset development opportunities.Hong Kong-listed OSL Group (863.HK), which focuses on crypto assets, exchanged views with a dele</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915151629422592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Crypto market faces short-term volatility, but overall uptrend is not overMatrixport released a chart today stating that Bitcoin&apos;s open interest has increased significantly by $6.00B in the past two weeks, and the annualized funding rate has soared to 19.00%, indicating a large number of aggressive leveraged long positions in the market. At the same time, the activity of South Korean retail investors has increased significantly, and cryptocurrency trading volume has jumped from $1.00B to $6.00B, reflecting the dominant role of retail funds in this round of market conditions. However, as prices enter a sideways phase, these highly leveraged long positions may face the risk of passive liquidation, especially after next week&apos;s FOMC meeting, when the market will enter a relatively quiet August trading period. Despite short-term volatility pressure, multiple key positives are building momentum for after the summer, and the overall upward trend in the crypto market is not over. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947914855469617152</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoOdailyMatrixport: Crypto market faces short-term volatility, but overall uptrend is not overMatrixport released a chart today stating that Bitcoin&apos;s open interest has increased significantly by $6.00B in the past two weeks, and the annualized funding rate has soared to 19.00%, indicati</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947914855469617152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba Denies Reports of His ResignationAccording to Jinshi, Shigeru Ishiba, the Japanese Prime Minister, told the media on the afternoon of July 23 that the Japanese media&apos;s reports about his resignation were &quot;completely without factual basis.&quot; Ishiba said that he had just finished meetings with Taro Aso, the top advisor of the Liberal Democratic Party, former Prime Minister Yoshihide Suga, and Fumio Kishida, and &quot;the issue of resignation was not discussed.&quot; Media reports about his intention to resign are completely untrue. Ishiba reiterated that he will remain in office and continue to govern. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947913977199136768</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoForesightNewsJapanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba Denies Reports of His ResignationAccording to Jinshi, Shigeru Ishiba, the Japanese Prime Minister, told the media on the afternoon of July 23 that the Japanese media&apos;s reports about his resignation were &quot;completely without factual bas</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947913977199136768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000.00 Bitcoin and $10,000.00 EthereumIn his latest blog post, Arthur Hayes predicted a year-end target of $250,000.00 for Bitcoin and $10,000.00 for Ethereum. He stated that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market, and Maelstrom (his personal family office) is doing everything related to Ethereum, DeFi, and ERC-20 shitcoins. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912931039055872</link>
      <description>59 minutes ago吴说Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000.00 Bitcoin and $10,000.00 EthereumIn his latest blog post, Arthur Hayes predicted a year-end target of $250,000.00 for Bitcoin and $10,000.00 for Ethereum. He stated that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912931039055872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-Japan reach trade agreement, Japanese stocks close up 3.5%The Nikkei 225 index closed up 1,396.40 points, or 3.51%, at 41,171.32 on Wednesday, July 23. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912336437743616</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUS-Japan reach trade agreement, Japanese stocks close up 3.5%The Nikkei 225 index closed up 1,396.40 points, or 3.51%, at 41,171.32 on Wednesday, July 23. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912336437743616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scamFederal prosecutors in Seattle are looking to win forfeiture of millions worth of crypto tied to an investment scheme in the hope of distributing it to victims.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909733234577408</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUS looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scamFederal prosecutors in Seattle are looking to win forfeiture of millions worth of crypto tied to an investment scheme in the hope of distributing it to victims.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909733234577408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins are all over Twitter: From NFT project to Web3 multi-dimensional ecosystem IPPudgy Penguins has gone far beyond the scope of traditional NFT projects, and has evolved into a composite Web3 brand covering IP, physical products, games, and infrastructure.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947916240839839744</link>
      <description>1 hour agoBitMart ResearchPudgy Penguins are all over Twitter: From NFT project to Web3 multi-dimensional ecosystem IPPudgy Penguins has gone far beyond the scope of traditional NFT projects, and has evolved into a composite Web3 brand covering IP, physical products, games, and infrastructure.#NFTSh</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947916240839839744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Ecosystem Protocol Strata Opens Pre-DepositEthena ecosystem protocol Strata opens pre-deposits. The first phase of the campaign will accept two tokens, USDe and eUSDe, and depositing the corresponding funds will qualify users for Ethena rewards and Strata points. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908817592848384</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsEthena Ecosystem Protocol Strata Opens Pre-DepositEthena ecosystem protocol Strata opens pre-deposits. The first phase of the campaign will accept two tokens, USDe and eUSDe, and depositing the corresponding funds will qualify users for Ethena rewards and Strata points. [Fores</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908817592848384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>