<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:28:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -10.73%, SXP -7.69%, CRO -5.17%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132635099226112</link>
      <description>30seconds agoSSI Price BotssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -10.73%, SXP -7.69%, CRO -5.17%.$CRO$WOO$SXPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132635099226112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memecoin launchpad LetsBONK pledges 1% of revenue to buyback top tokensMemecoin launchpad LetsBONK, which supports the Solana-based memecoin BONK and its ecosystem, announced on Wednesday it would set aside 1% of total revenue towards buying back &quot;the top pairs within the BONK eco.&quot;

The revenue will be reassigned from the LetsBONK team&apos;s marketing fund, according to the team&apos;s announcement on X.

LetsBONK has made around $1.5 million in fees over the past 24 hours, according to a Dune dashboard that tracks rival memecoin platforms by Adam_Tehc. 1% of that revenue would equal to $15,000.00 of buying pressure on top token pairs, such as Useless Coin, which has a market capitalization of about $312 million, according to CoinGecko data.

&quot;[The buybacks] will happen once a week and any pair that reaches the high levels can be included,&quot; LetsBONK founder Tom wrote on X. &quot;More to come.&quot;

The total market capitalizations of tokens launched on LetsBONK recently surpassed $1 billion, according to a Dune dashboard. Useless Coin is the largest coin in the ecosystem, followed by ANI, a token representing xAI&apos;s recent Grok AI Companion.

Notably, rival platform Pump has integrated a revenue-sharing mechanism into its newly-launched PUMP token and a “community takeover” mechanism that will enable users to commandeer “abandoned” projects.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132536256892928</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoThe BlockMemecoin launchpad LetsBONK pledges 1% of revenue to buyback top tokensMemecoin launchpad LetsBONK, which supports the Solana-based memecoin BONK and its ecosystem, announced on Wednesday it would set aside 1% of total revenue towards buying back &quot;the top pairs within the BONK</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132536256892928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer2 index 24hr loss of 10.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer2 has fallen by 10.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OP -13.43%, TIA -12.98%, MOVE -12.74%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132198665117696</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer2 index 24hr loss of 10.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer2 has fallen by 10.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OP -13.43%, TIA -12.98%, MOVE -12.74%.$OP$TIA$MOVEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132198665117696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiDePIN index 24hr loss of 10.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDePIN has fallen by 10.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: GRASS -11.9%, AIOZ -10.9%, IOTA -10.52%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131117130276864</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiDePIN index 24hr loss of 10.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDePIN has fallen by 10.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: GRASS -11.9%, AIOZ -10.9%, IOTA -10.52%.$IOTA$AIOZ$GRASSShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131117130276864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: US market entry &apos;well underway&apos; amid plans for institutional stablecoinTether CEO Paolo Ardoino said the stablecoin issuer is well underway to do business in the U.S. in an interview with Bloomberg Television. The news comes less than a week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act into law to regulate stablecoins in the U.S.

&quot;We are well in progress of establishing our U.S. domestic strategy,&quot; Ardoino said on Wednesday.

In April, Tether&apos;s Ardoino told The Block that the stablecoin issuer had plans to launch a new U.S.-based stablecoin aimed specifically at institutional clients.

Tether&apos;s USDT is the world&apos;s largest stablecoin with a total market capitalization of $162 billion, according to The Block&apos;s price page. The new proposed stablecoin, however, would be geared toward institutions looking for faster settlements.

Ardoino told Bloomberg on Wednesday that Tether plans to make an announcement on the firm&apos;s plans for U.S. institutional markets.

&quot;That is well underway,&quot; Ardoino said. &quot;We plan to announce it in the next couple of months.&quot;

Tether has faced ongoing scrutiny for not providing a full independent audit of its stablecoin reserves, and instead has released quarterly attestations signed by BDO Italia. Last month, the company hired Simon McWilliams as its new chief financial officer to lead efforts toward securing a full audit. Ardoino has also said that obtaining a review from a Big Four audit firm — Deloitte, EY, PwC, or KPMG — is a &quot;top priority.&quot;

Ardoino appeared at Trump&apos;s signing of a bill to regulate stablecoins called GENIUS last week in Washington. The bill creates a federal regulatory framework for fiat-pegged tokens, including a requirement for stablecoins to be fully backed by U.S. dollars or similarly liquid assets, and mandating annual audits for issuers with a market capitalization of more than $50 billion. It also establishes guidelines for foreign issuance.

In the U.S., Tether is likely to face increased competition as more traditional banks begin to make plans to launch their stablecoins, including companies co-owned by JPMorgan, Bank of America, Citigroup, and Wells Fargo.

To that, Ardoino told Bloomberg that those competitors might be better than Tether in the short term in the U.S., but added that Tether has advantages. &quot;They can compete and be probably maybe, maybe, better than us in the short term in the United States just because it&apos;s a new market for us, but we have better technology,&quot; Ardoino said. &quot;We have a much better understanding of this market than anyone else.&quot;

Ardoino was also asked whether Tether planned to go public like its competitor, Circle. He said Tether was not interested. [Bloomberg Television]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131342176292864</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoThe BlockTether CEO: US market entry &apos;well underway&apos; amid plans for institutional stablecoinTether CEO Paolo Ardoino said the stablecoin issuer is well underway to do business in the U.S. in an interview with Bloomberg Television. The news comes less than a week after President Donald T</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131342176292864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to Initiate Next Round of Creditor Distributions on September 30, Releasing $1.90B in Disputed Reserve FundsFTX has announced that the record date for the next round of creditor distributions is August 15, 2025, with distributions expected to begin on September 30, applicable to approved Class 5 customer claims, Class 6 general unsecured claims, and previously undistributed convenience claims. Additionally, FTX has received court approval to reduce the disputed claims reserve from $6.50B to $4.30B, releasing nearly $1.90B in cash for this round of distributions. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131066270781440</link>
      <description>8 minutes ago吴说FTX to Initiate Next Round of Creditor Distributions on September 30, Releasing $1.90B in Disputed Reserve FundsFTX has announced that the record date for the next round of creditor distributions is August 15, 2025, with distributions expected to begin on September 30, applicable to a</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131066270781440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan: $2 Trillion Stablecoin Market Prediction Too Optimistic, Infrastructure Still Needs ImprovementJPMorgan says that market predictions of stablecoin&apos;s total market capitalization reaching $2 trillion by 2028 are &quot;slightly optimistic.&quot; Although Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent recently proposed this target at a hearing, saying it could be achieved with legislative support, JPMorgan believes that the stablecoin infrastructure is not yet perfect and it will be difficult to support such large-scale growth in the short term. JPMorgan expects the market to more likely double or triple in the coming years, rather than reach several times its current market capitalization of $260.00 billion. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948127867426115584</link>
      <description>20 minutes ago吴说JPMorgan: $2 Trillion Stablecoin Market Prediction Too Optimistic, Infrastructure Still Needs ImprovementJPMorgan says that market predictions of stablecoin&apos;s total market capitalization reaching $2 trillion by 2028 are &quot;slightly optimistic.&quot; Although Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948127867426115584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiGameFi index 24hr loss of 10.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiGameFi has fallen by 10.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: GALA -11.08%, IMX -10.67%, SAND -10.58%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948121008438206464</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiGameFi index 24hr loss of 10.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiGameFi has fallen by 10.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: GALA -11.08%, IMX -10.67%, SAND -10.58%.$SAND$IMX$GALAShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948121008438206464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily: Goldman-BNY tokenization push, Ethereum&apos;s &apos;demand shock&apos;, $50 trillion crypto forecast, and moreThe following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter,The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.

Happy Wednesday! Let’s take a look at the top stories.

Traditional finance is moving further onchain.BNY Mellon and Goldman Sachshave teamed up to tokenize money market fund records — a step toward bringing traditional assets onto blockchain rails.

Bitcoin miner MARA plans to raise $850.00 millionthrough a convertible note sale, with proceeds partially set aside to buy more BTC. Separately,Dan Tapiero has launched a new $500.00 million fundunder the &quot;50T&quot; brand, betting the crypto economy will hit $50.00 trillion.

Ethereum is leading the market.U.S. spot ETH ETFs pulled in $534.00 millionin single-day inflows — the third-largest on record — whileTrump-linked World Liberty Financial bought 3,400 ETHonchain.Bitwise CIO Matt Hougan saysETH is in the middle of a &quot;demand shock,&quot; with ETF and treasury buyers acquiring 32x more ETH than the network has minted since May.

Let’s get into it.

Never miss a beat with The Block&apos;sdaily digestof the most influential events happening across the digital assetecosystem. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119693365153792</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoThe BlockThe Daily: Goldman-BNY tokenization push, Ethereum&apos;s &apos;demand shock&apos;, $50 trillion crypto forecast, and moreThe following article is adapted from The Block’s newsletter,The Daily, which comes out on weekday afternoons.

Happy Wednesday! Let’s take a look at the top stories.

Tr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119693365153792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninth Circuit Rules NFTs Eligible for Trademark Protection, Yuga Labs Case RemandedThe U.S. Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals has ruled that NFTs can be considered &quot;goods&quot; under the Lanham Act and are therefore eligible for trademark protection, and has rejected most of artist Ryder Ripps&apos; legal defenses, but at the same time vacated the previous $9.00M damages and injunction against him, remanding the case to the district court for a new trial to determine whether ordinary consumers would confuse his RR/BAYC series with Yuga Labs&apos; genuine products. (The Block) [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119808649793536</link>
      <description>53 minutes ago吴说Ninth Circuit Rules NFTs Eligible for Trademark Protection, Yuga Labs Case RemandedThe U.S. Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals has ruled that NFTs can be considered &quot;goods&quot; under the Lanham Act and are therefore eligible for trademark protection, and has rejected most of artist Ryder Rip</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119808649793536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMeme index 24hr loss of 10.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMeme has fallen by 10.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BONK -11.79%, FLOKI -10.85%, SHIB -9.5%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119246511759360</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiMeme index 24hr loss of 10.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMeme has fallen by 10.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BONK -11.79%, FLOKI -10.85%, SHIB -9.5%.$SHIB$FLOKI$BONKShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119246511759360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: DOGE is now at $0.23616According to SoSoValue, DOGE (Dogecoin) is down 10.03% in the past 24h. Now at $0.23616.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119234247614464</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: DOGE is now at $0.23616According to SoSoValue, DOGE (Dogecoin) is down 10.03% in the past 24h. Now at $0.23616.$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119234247614464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: ADA is now at $0.79839According to SoSoValue, ADA (Cardano) is down 10.03% in the past 24h. Now at $0.79839.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119210767900672</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: ADA is now at $0.79839According to SoSoValue, ADA (Cardano) is down 10.03% in the past 24h. Now at $0.79839.$ADAShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948119210767900672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiPayFi index 24hr loss of 10.01%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiPayFi has fallen by 10.01% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: XLM -10.19%, XRP -10.07%, ACH -7.12%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948117434484350976</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiPayFi index 24hr loss of 10.01%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiPayFi has fallen by 10.01% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: XLM -10.19%, XRP -10.07%, ACH -7.12%.$XRP$XLM$ACHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948117434484350976</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of crypto, CBDC bills unclear as US Congress heads into recessLawmakers are expected to break in a matter of days, but there are still items on the legislative agenda to address, including two crypto bills passed by the House.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948108476080787456</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFate of crypto, CBDC bills unclear as US Congress heads into recessLawmakers are expected to break in a matter of days, but there are still items on the legislative agenda to address, including two crypto bills passed by the House.#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948108476080787456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise is &apos;actively evaluating&apos; the SEC&apos;s pause on its initially approved crypto index fundBitwise says it&apos;s &quot;actively evaluating&quot; the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&apos;s recent move to pause the conversion of its cryptocurrency index fund after initially approving it to list and trade.

In a statement, a Bitwise spokesperson said the crypto index fund manager was &quot;thrilled by the SEC&apos;s accelerated approval,&quot; and noted they&apos;re assessing the pause.

&quot;The subsequent stay is a new development that we’re actively evaluating,&quot; the spokesperson said in an email on Wednesday. &quot;We’ve been encouraged by the constructive engagement with the SEC under the new administration and remain committed to working productively to expand access to crypto — just as we’ve done over the last seven years.”

On Tuesday, the SEC&apos;s Division of Trading and Markets granted an &quot;accelerated approval&quot; of the Bitwise 10 Crypto Index ETF, according to a filing. However, SEC Assistant Secretary Sherry R. Haywood later stayed the action and said the commission would review it.

The Bitwise 10 Crypto Index Fund, which trades under the ticker “BITW,” currently consists of exposure to BTC, ETH, XRP, SOL, Polkadot, among others, on a market cap-weighted basis, according to its website.

This marks the second instance the SEC has hit pause on an initial approval to convert a fund to an ETF. A similar scenario occurred with Grayscale&apos;s proposed conversion of its Digital Large Cap Fund, which was initially approved and later put under review. Grayscale has said it &quot;remains committed&quot; to continue trying to list the fund.

This comes amid a broader shift as the SEC is also considering a wide array of crypto ETFs, from ones that track SOL to DOGE in the face of a friendlier regulatory environment for crypto following President Donald Trump&apos;s inauguration in January. [Bitwise]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948102244129378304</link>
      <description>2 hours agoThe BlockBitwise is &apos;actively evaluating&apos; the SEC&apos;s pause on its initially approved crypto index fundBitwise says it&apos;s &quot;actively evaluating&quot; the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission&apos;s recent move to pause the conversion of its cryptocurrency index fund after initially approving it to l</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948102244129378304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burwick Law Expands RICO Lawsuit Against Pump, Listing Solana and Jito Executives as Co-ConspiratorsBurwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against memecoin platform Pump, naming the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito Labs, and their executives as co-conspirators. The lawsuit alleges illegal gambling, wire fraud, securities fraud, intellectual property theft, and unlicensed money transmission, and invokes the Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO). [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948101169599025152</link>
      <description>2 hours ago吴说Burwick Law Expands RICO Lawsuit Against Pump, Listing Solana and Jito Executives as Co-ConspiratorsBurwick Law and Wolf Popper have expanded the scope of their lawsuit against memecoin platform Pump, naming the Solana Foundation, Solana Labs, Jito Labs, and their executives as co-consp</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 19:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948101169599025152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s AI plan eases data center rules, strips federal DEI guidelinesThe White House on Wednesday released its plan to make the United States a global leader in artificial intelligence research and development.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948085881256087552</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsTrump&apos;s AI plan eases data center rules, strips federal DEI guidelinesThe White House on Wednesday released its plan to make the United States a global leader in artificial intelligence research and development.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948085881256087552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standard Chartered-backed Zodia Custody joins Ondo’s Global Markets AllianceZodia Custody, a digital assets custody platform backed by Standard Chartered, has joined the Global Markets Alliance, an initiative by Ondo Finance aimed at promoting interoperability across the tokenized assets market. As the Global Markets Alliance’s newest member, Zodia Custody adds to a group of industry players that include Solana Foundation, LayerZero, BitGo, Fireblocks, Jupiter, Trust Wallet, 1inch, Alpaca, and Bitget. Ondo Finance announced the Zodia Custody move via X. Like the other members, Zodia Custody will leverage its infrastructure, security and compliance features to help advance the tokenization of capital markets. The on-chain efforts aligns with the institution-first digital assets custodian’s traction across the ecosystem, efforts that include the support for institutional decentralized finance on the TON blockchain, Berachain and RWA platform Polymesh. The Global Markets Alliance’s areas of focus across the real-world assets on-chain ecosystem includes tokenized stocks, exchange-traded funds, money market funds and private credit. RWA on-chain is a rapidly expanding market, with major players, including BlackRock, Franklin Templeton, and Fidelity Investments, driving adoption to the next level. The key to growing tokenization lies in its feature that enables the bridging of traditional finance and blockchain, with real-world assets wrapped into tokens issued on the blockchain. Investors taking positions with these assets benefit from 24/7 trading, fractional ownership and on-chain transparency and accessibility. With institutional clients eyeing the tokenization opportunity, major Wall Street banks have had no option but to consider launching their own tokenized assets initiatives. Zodia, which also offers a staking solution, counts asset managers, banks, crypto natives, governments, hedge funds, and private wealth firms among its partners.  The platform recently launched Zodia Rewards, its opt-in token rewards program targeted for institutional clients. Clients can enjoy rewards on supported stablecoins, including USDC ( USDC ), Ethena USDe ( USDE ) and the Global Dollar Network. “Stablecoins are being adopted far beyond crypto capital markets, emerging as a tool to complement traditional financial rails for cross-border payments. We see this value, and as a custodian, we want to play our part to help unlock further capital efficiencies,” Anoosh Arevshatian, chief product officer at Zodia Custody, said at the time. [Ondo Finance]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948086047681875968</link>
      <description>3 hours agocrypto.newsStandard Chartered-backed Zodia Custody joins Ondo’s Global Markets AllianceZodia Custody, a digital assets custody platform backed by Standard Chartered, has joined the Global Markets Alliance, an initiative by Ondo Finance aimed at promoting interoperability across the tokeni</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948086047681875968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: XRP is now at $3.16009According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 10.13% in the past 24h. Now at $3.16009.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948070918004629504</link>
      <description>4 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: XRP is now at $3.16009According to SoSoValue, XRP (Xrp) is down 10.13% in the past 24h. Now at $3.16009.$XRPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948070918004629504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 21:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>