<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs announces the launch of the first season of airdrops, 25% of the shares are now availableOn July 22, Sonic Labs published a post on the X platform saying that the first season of Sonic airdrop has officially started. Users can now claim 25% of the allocated shares, and the remaining 75% will be released linearly in the form of NFTs and gradually opened through the PaintSwap order book. The official specially reminded that this airdrop is based on the Sonic mainnet whitelist event and has nothing to do with pre-sales or TGE. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678554049499136</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoPANewsSonic Labs announces the launch of the first season of airdrops, 25% of the shares are now availableOn July 22, Sonic Labs published a post on the X platform saying that the first season of Sonic airdrop has officially started. Users can now claim 25% of the allocated shares, and</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678554049499136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machi Big Brother has accumulated losses of over $5.50M on PUMP spot and contracts, but continues to add to long positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother Huang Licheng (@machibigbrother) has lost more than $1.50M on PUMP spot and more than $3.90M on contracts. However, he continues to add to his PUMP long position. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678290018062336</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoOdailyMachi Big Brother has accumulated losses of over $5.50M on PUMP spot and contracts, but continues to add to long positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother Huang Licheng (@machibigbrother) has lost more than $1.50M on P</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678290018062336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneFootball to Launch Token Sale on CoinList on July 24On July 22, CoinList announced that the OneFootball (OFC) token sale will officially start at 17:00 UTC on July 24. The FDV of this token sale is $50.00 million, the token price is $0.05, 25% will be released at TGE, and the rest will be released linearly within 12 months, with a minimum purchase amount of $100.00. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947677332810780672</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoPANewsOneFootball to Launch Token Sale on CoinList on July 24On July 22, CoinList announced that the OneFootball (OFC) token sale will officially start at 17:00 UTC on July 24. The FDV of this token sale is $50.00 million, the token price is $0.05, 25% will be released at TGE, and the r</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947677332810780672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US DOJ drops probe into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell over nonprofit allegations: FortuneThe U.S. Justice Department has dropped its investigation into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell tied to a nonprofit group, according to reporting from Fortune.

Authorities searched Powell&apos;s Los Angeles home and took electronic devices in 2023 as part of an investigation into claims he hacked and cyber-stalked a nonprofit arts group, The New York Times previously reported.

In 2023, the nonprofit alleged that Powell interfered with its computer accounts, including blocking access to emails and other messages, according to people with knowledge of the matter who spoke to The New York Times.

Powell has said he did not stalk or hack anyone and alleged that the nonprofit Verge Center for the Arts executives tried to remove him from the board, Fortune reported on Tuesday.

The DOJ did not immediately respond to a request for comment. Powell told Fortune that the Federal Bureau of Investigation&apos;s raid was &quot;devastating both personally and professionally.&quot;

Powell, who co-founded the Kraken exchange, stepped down as CEO in 2022 and he is currently the chair of its board of directors.

The Justice Department&apos;s probe happened as crypto firms were being sued by federal regulators over charges related to not registering properly and fraud. A Kraken spokeswoman told the New York Times in 2023 that the investigation into Powell has nothing to do with the company and that it had no reason to believe that prosecutors were looking into other potential issues. [Fortune]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947676994187841536</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoThe BlockUS DOJ drops probe into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell over nonprofit allegations: FortuneThe U.S. Justice Department has dropped its investigation into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell tied to a nonprofit group, according to reporting from Fortune.

Authorities searched Powell&apos;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947676994187841536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fogo Launches High-Performance Layer 1 SVM Chain Public Testnet with 40 Millisecond Block TimeFogo, a Layer 1 blockchain created by former Wall Street executives, announced on Tuesday the official launch of its public testnet. Fogo aims to bring the execution speed of traditional finance to the decentralized finance space without sacrificing decentralization and composability. The team says the Fogo network can achieve 40 milliseconds block times and provide unique advantages for on-chain trading products through native infrastructure and vertical integration. Other innovations include reduced MEV risk, a co-located node architecture for real-time transaction execution, and an enhanced session-based account management experience. Fogo plans to be the first to fully deploy the Firedancer validator client, and has already adopted the Frankendancer hybrid client and will gradually transition to Firedancer. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678298461196288</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoOdailyFogo Launches High-Performance Layer 1 SVM Chain Public Testnet with 40 Millisecond Block TimeFogo, a Layer 1 blockchain created by former Wall Street executives, announced on Tuesday the official launch of its public testnet. Fogo aims to bring the execution speed of traditional</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678298461196288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Expects the Federal Reserve to hold rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2025.Goldman Sachs expects the Federal Reserve to hold interest rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2025, as a slowing job market puts pressure on policymakers. Private sector hiring is now close to &quot;stall speed,&quot; with the risk of further slowdowns; meanwhile, consumer spending has stalled for six consecutive months, a situation extremely rare outside of recessions. Goldman Sachs also expects the Fed to cut rates twice more in early 2026. (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675768805150720</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoOdailyGoldman Sachs: Expects the Federal Reserve to hold rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2025.Goldman Sachs expects the Federal Reserve to hold interest rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675768805150720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNC strikes deal with Coinbase to bring cryptocurrency services to banking customersPNC Bank said it has struck a partnership with Coinbase to let clients access cryptocurrencies through Coinbase’s Crypto‑as‑a‑Service platform, while PNC will provide select banking services to the exchange.

The companies framed the deal as a way to marry PNC’s compliance and distribution footprint with Coinbase’s institutional‑grade trading and custody stack.

&quot;Partnering with Coinbase accelerates our ability to bring innovative, crypto financial solutions to our clients,&quot; PNC Chairman and CEO William S. Demchak said in the announcement. Coinbase Institutional head Brett Tejpaul added that the CaaS toolkit will let the bank set up a scalable, security‑first crypto offering for PNC&apos;s 12 million customers.

The firms did not disclose any financial terms or a launch date for the offering.

The move lands as Wall Street banks edge deeper into digital assets. Standard Chartered recently launched spot bitcoin and ether trading for institutional clients. JPMorgan told clients that regulators outside the United States appear to prefer tokenized bank deposits — onchain versions of traditional balances that always settle at par — over privately issued stablecoins. JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon nevertheless said last week the bank &quot;will be involved&quot; with both deposit tokens and stablecoins to stay competitive, even as he questioned why anyone would use a stablecoin instead of a standard payment rail.

Meanwhile, the U.S. under President Donald Trump&apos;s pro-crypto administration has accelerated supportive legislation for the blockchain-powered industry. Trump recently signed the GENIUS Act into law, standardizing rules for a U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin industry with over $250 billion in circulation, according to The Block&apos;s data dashboard.

Senate Republicans also released a discussion draft on the crypto market structure, which they say expands on the Clarity bill passed in the House of Representatives last week. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675642506268672</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoThe BlockPNC strikes deal with Coinbase to bring cryptocurrency services to banking customersPNC Bank said it has struck a partnership with Coinbase to let clients access cryptocurrencies through Coinbase’s Crypto‑as‑a‑Service platform, while PNC will provide select banking services to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675642506268672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Gateway Launches Cross-Chain Unified USDC Balance FeatureCircle introduces Circle Gateway, a new primitive that enables cross-chain instant access to unified USDC balances. The feature is currently live on the Avalanche, Base, and Ethereum testnets, with a mainnet version coming soon and plans to expand to more blockchain networks. Circle Gateway provides instant access, allowing users to view and use their USDC balances. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673026309148672</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoForesightNewsCircle Gateway Launches Cross-Chain Unified USDC Balance FeatureCircle introduces Circle Gateway, a new primitive that enables cross-chain instant access to unified USDC balances. The feature is currently live on the Avalanche, Base, and Ethereum testnets, with a mainnet v</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673026309148672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank: Tariff costs are borne by Americans themselves, and the dollar faces downward pressureDeutsche Bank analyst George Saravelos wrote that the dollar is facing downward pressure as Americans bear the brunt of tariff costs. Saravelos noted that if tariff costs were borne by foreign countries, their selling prices should fall, but this trend has not emerged except in individual cases. However, he also said that since U.S. inflation is still under control, it is not consumers who mainly bear the tariff costs, but importers. Saravelos said, &quot;Since tariff costs are mainly borne by the United States, this is another negative factor for the dollar.&quot; (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673271277473792</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyDeutsche Bank: Tariff costs are borne by Americans themselves, and the dollar faces downward pressureDeutsche Bank analyst George Saravelos wrote that the dollar is facing downward pressure as Americans bear the brunt of tariff costs. Saravelos noted that if tariff costs were bor</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673271277473792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glassnode: Sui Futures Open Interest Nears All-Time High of $1.20BAccording to Glassnode data, Sui futures open interest remains near its all-time high of approximately $1.20B, making it the sixth-largest crypto asset by futures open interest. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673026489503744</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoForesightNewsGlassnode: Sui Futures Open Interest Nears All-Time High of $1.20BAccording to Glassnode data, Sui futures open interest remains near its all-time high of approximately $1.20B, making it the sixth-largest crypto asset by futures open interest. [Foresight News]#Layer1$SUISh</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673026489503744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin Supply on Polygon Surpasses $2.80B, Reaching a Three-Year HighPolygon officially announced that the supply of stablecoins on the Polygon network has exceeded $2.80B, reaching a three-year high. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947671774657531904</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoForesightNewsStablecoin Supply on Polygon Surpasses $2.80B, Reaching a Three-Year HighPolygon officially announced that the supply of stablecoins on the Polygon network has exceeded $2.80B, reaching a three-year high. [Foresight News]#Layer2Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947671774657531904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale with 3x leverage short on PENGU was liquidated, losing $13.16M, and has reopened a 2x leverage short on PENGU.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale was forced to liquidate its 3x leveraged PENGU short position, losing as much as $13.16M. The address has now re-established a small 2x leveraged short position, but is still losing approximately $10.60M overall. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947670747946438656</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoOdailyA whale with 3x leverage short on PENGU was liquidated, losing $13.16M, and has reopened a 2x leverage short on PENGU.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale was forced to liquidate its 3x leveraged PENGU short position, losing as much as $13.16M. The address has now re-est</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947670747946438656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Ends Investigation into Kraken Founder Jesse Powell and Returns EquipmentAccording to Fortune, the US FBI has concluded its investigation into Kraken founder Jesse Powell and returned the dozens of electronic devices that were previously seized. The investigation was not related to Kraken&apos;s operations, but to a management dispute between Powell and the non-profit organization Verge he founded. Powell stated that the FBI raid had a serious impact on his personal and professional life and plans to continue to pursue civil litigation against members of the Verge board. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947668636215037952</link>
      <description>43 minutes ago吴说FBI Ends Investigation into Kraken Founder Jesse Powell and Returns EquipmentAccording to Fortune, the US FBI has concluded its investigation into Kraken founder Jesse Powell and returned the dozens of electronic devices that were previously seized. The investigation was not related</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947668636215037952</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Botic Named Acting Chairman of Public Company Accounting Oversight BoardOn July 22, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced that George R. Botic will serve as the acting chairman of the Public Company Accounting Oversight Board (PCAOB) starting July 23, 2025. The current chairman, Erica Y. Williams, resigned on July 22. Botic has been a member of the PCAOB board of directors since October 2023. He has served as director of the Registration and Inspection Division and has held several key positions. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947668362004025344</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoPANewsGeorge Botic Named Acting Chairman of Public Company Accounting Oversight BoardOn July 22, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced that George R. Botic will serve as the acting chairman of the Public Company Accounting Oversight Board (PCAOB) starting July 23,</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947668362004025344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Atlantic’s Kotzin Sees IPOs Taking Off in 2026Hi, it’s Swetha Gopinath in London, getting a global IPO outlook from a senior executive at private equity investor General Atlantic. Also today, the billionaire owner of the LA Times plans to take the newspaper public. Today’s top stories</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678188285218816</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoBloombergGeneral Atlantic’s Kotzin Sees IPOs Taking Off in 2026Hi, it’s Swetha Gopinath in London, getting a global IPO outlook from a senior executive at private equity investor General Atlantic. Also today, the billionaire owner of the LA Times plans to take the newspaper public. Tod</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678188285218816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Senator Lummis calls for digital asset legislation, saying bipartisan collaboration will protect innovation and consumer rightsOn July 22, U.S. Senator Cynthia Lummis tweeted that the United States has been leading the world in financial innovation and has not slowed down. Lummis said that she looks forward to working with the industry and both parties to develop market structure legislation that is conducive to digital assets, encourages innovation, and protects consumers. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947664551013273600</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoPANewsU.S. Senator Lummis calls for digital asset legislation, saying bipartisan collaboration will protect innovation and consumer rightsOn July 22, U.S. Senator Cynthia Lummis tweeted that the United States has been leading the world in financial innovation and has not slowed down. L</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947664551013273600</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consensys plans to lay off 49 people, about 7% of its total workforceAccording to Bloomberg, Consensys, the software company founded by Ethereum co-founder Joseph Rubin, is currently planning to lay off 49 employees, representing approximately 7% of its total workforce. A company spokesperson stated that the restructuring is to drive overall profitability improvements. Previously, Consensys acquired a startup with approximately 30 employees, who will remain with the company. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947663316835127296</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Consensys plans to lay off 49 people, about 7% of its total workforceAccording to Bloomberg, Consensys, the software company founded by Ethereum co-founder Joseph Rubin, is currently planning to lay off 49 employees, representing approximately 7% of its total workforce. A company spokesp</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947663316835127296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1 Trillion Capital Is All It Takes for Bitcoin to Hit $1 Million | US Crypto NewsWelcome to the US Crypto News Morning Briefing—your essential rundown of the most important developments in crypto for the day ahead. Grab your coffee and settle in because the numbers behind Bitcoin’s future are starting to get serious. As global liquidity surges and the pace of money creation accelerates, some investors believe we are entering a new phase for the pioneer crypto. Crypto News of the Day: Bitcoin Hitting $1 Million Seen as Inevitable with Global Money Supply Set to Double In a recent US Crypto News publication, Davinci Jeremie urged viewers to spend just a dollar to buy Bitcoin. According to the Bitcoin maxi, BTC price could reach $500,000 per coin before 2030. Now, a growing number of analysts believe Bitcoin could go well beyond $500,000, ultimately reaching $1 million. This, they say, may be inevitable. Analysts point to a macroeconomic backdrop that heavily favors Bitcoin, citing surging global liquidity and the money supply, which is on track to double in the next decade. The sentiment echoes broader concerns about monetary debasement, especially as global central banks maintain loose fiscal policies and governments continue large-scale deficit spending. In the past year, the money supply has grown at its fastest pace in recent history, adding credence to the Bitcoin bull case. According to River, a Bitcoin-focused platform, anyone who has held Bitcoin since July 2024 has outperformed against money debasement tenfold. That outperformance reinforces Bitcoin’s positioning as a hedge against fiat dilution, particularly in an environment of rising global debt and systemic liquidity injections. Further supporting the bullish thesis, global M2 money supply per Bitcoin has reached a 12-year high. This liquidity-to-scarcity ratio reflects just how little capital is needed, in relative terms, to send Bitcoin dramatically higher. With only 21 million BTC coins ever existing, and significantly fewer in active circulation, Bitcoin’s fixed supply makes it increasingly responsive to institutional or sovereign capital inflows. Chart of the Day Byte-Sized Alpha Here’s a summary of more US crypto news to follow today: Crypto Equities Pre-Market Overview [US Crypto News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947664756060213248</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincrypto$1 Trillion Capital Is All It Takes for Bitcoin to Hit $1 Million | US Crypto NewsWelcome to the US Crypto News Morning Briefing—your essential rundown of the most important developments in crypto for the day ahead. Grab your coffee and settle in because the numbers behind Bitcoi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947664756060213248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Agriculture Committee Postpones Vote on CFTC Chair Nominee, Coordinating to RescheduleCrypto reporter Eleanor Terrett revealed that after the Senate Agriculture Committee removed CFTC Chairman nominee Brian Quintenz and another nominee from the voting list yesterday, committee members are working to reschedule the vote. A staff member said they are seeking to get all 12 Republican members together to push Quintenz&apos;s nomination to a full Senate vote. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947660685928583168</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySenate Agriculture Committee Postpones Vote on CFTC Chair Nominee, Coordinating to RescheduleCrypto reporter Eleanor Terrett revealed that after the Senate Agriculture Committee removed CFTC Chairman nominee Brian Quintenz and another nominee from the voting list yesterday, committee</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947660685928583168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr loss of 3.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has fallen by 3.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.24%, ETH -4.61%, DOGE -4.57%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658988425273344</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr loss of 3.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has fallen by 3.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ADA -7.24%, ETH -4.61%, DOGE -4.57%.$ETH$ADA$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947658988425273344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>