<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Sui is now integrated with the Fireblocks platform and will support native custody and staking services.Sui officially announced that the Sui network has formally connected to the enterprise-grade digital asset infrastructure platform Fireblocks, aiming to provide services to institutional users seeking high performance and security. Currently, Fireblocks supports native custody of SUI and Sui ecosystem tokens, MPC wallet strategy control, and will subsequently support access to DeFi via WalletConnect, as well as integrate Fireblocks Trust&apos;s staking services. Sui stated that its high throughput and scalability are becoming the preferred path for financial institutions and game studios to access the next generation of digital asset world. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947892198208507904</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoOdailySui is now integrated with the Fireblocks platform and will support native custody and staking services.Sui officially announced that the Sui network has formally connected to the enterprise-grade digital asset infrastructure platform Fireblocks, aiming to provide services to inst</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947892198208507904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasuryOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, DMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, announced that it is evaluating the institutional-level fund management strategy of its subsidiary Systemic Trust Company and plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasury. At this stage, the company&apos;s digital asset portfolio consists only of Bitcoin. It has begun to evaluate the use of existing mining income and additional funds to acquire other digital assets besides Bitcoin. DMG Blockchain Solutions currently holds approximately 341 Bitcoins, ranking 54th among listed Bitcoin treasury companies. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947889317124313088</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsDMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, plans to establish a diversified digital asset treasuryOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, DMG Blockchain Solutions, a listed Bitcoin mining company, announced that it is evaluating the institutional-level fund manage</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947889317124313088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listed company SEALSQ plans to set up a $30.00 million cryptocurrency investment fundOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, SEALSQ Corp, a Nasdaq-listed public key infrastructure development company, announced that it is setting up a cryptocurrency investment fund of approximately US$30.00 million and plans to use the funds to purchase digital assets, including BTC, ETH, HBAR, etc. In addition, the company also stated that its cryptocurrency investment fund will serve as a strategic funding tool responsible for developing strategies for purchasing and holding cryptocurrencies, similar to how companies invest in traditional assets such as bonds or stocks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947887286087127040</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoPANewsListed company SEALSQ plans to set up a $30.00 million cryptocurrency investment fundOn July 23, according to Globenewswire, SEALSQ Corp, a Nasdaq-listed public key infrastructure development company, announced that it is setting up a cryptocurrency investment fund of approximate</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947887286087127040</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX into Bybit, worth $4.53 millionOn July 23, according to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX worth $4.53 million into Bybit. The whale deposited 2.53 million SPX worth $4.55 million into Bybit on the 20th, earning a profit of $4.46 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947886982985748480</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsA whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX into Bybit, worth $4.53 millionOn July 23, according to OnchainLens monitoring, a whale deposited another 2.35 million SPX worth $4.53 million into Bybit. The whale deposited 2.53 million SPX worth $4.55 million into Bybit on the 20th, e</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947886982985748480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changpeng Zhao: The alt season index is rising, and the FOMO season is comingOn July 23, Zhao Changpeng posted on the X platform at noon that although the accuracy of the Altcoin Season Index on CoinMarketCap is uncertain, it is indeed rising and &quot;FOMO season is coming.&quot; [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947886390775189504</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoPANewsChangpeng Zhao: The alt season index is rising, and the FOMO season is comingOn July 23, Zhao Changpeng posted on the X platform at noon that although the accuracy of the Altcoin Season Index on CoinMarketCap is uncertain, it is indeed rising and &quot;FOMO season is coming.&quot; [PANews]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947886390775189504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PayPal to launch global platform PayPal World to connect payment systems and digital walletsOn July 23, according to official news, PayPal announced that it will launch the global platform PayPal World. Some of the world&apos;s largest payment systems and digital wallets, including Mercado Pago, NCPI International Payments Limited (UPI) and Tenpay Global, are working with PayPal and Venmo to connect millions of users and businesses around the world. Consumers will be able to make international purchases and quickly make global remittances through their existing wallets. Businesses can also accept payments from new customers around the world without expensive integration fees. More wallets will be added in the coming months. PayPal World is expected to go live this fall, and all partners will be interoperable with PayPal and Venmo. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947885829896081408</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoPANewsPayPal to launch global platform PayPal World to connect payment systems and digital walletsOn July 23, according to official news, PayPal announced that it will launch the global platform PayPal World. Some of the world&apos;s largest payment systems and digital wallets, including Me</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947885829896081408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale ETF Global Head David LaValle departs, having led key work in GBTC&apos;s conversion to an ETF.Summary: ChainCatcher news, according to Unchained, David LaValle, Global Head of ETFs at crypto asset management firm Grayscale, will leave the company at the end of July, weeks after the company secretly filed for an IPO on July 14. LaValle joined in 2021 and led the key behind-the-scenes work of GBTC&apos;s ETF conversion. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947885837324193792</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoForesightNewsGrayscale ETF Global Head David LaValle departs, having led key work in GBTC&apos;s conversion to an ETF.Summary: ChainCatcher news, according to Unchained, David LaValle, Global Head of ETFs at crypto asset management firm Grayscale, will leave the company at the end of July,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947885837324193792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BNB +7.13%, ADA +2.99%, SOL +2.97%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947883607564443648</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.08%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.08% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BNB +7.13%, ADA +2.99%, SOL +2.97%.$BNB$ADA$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947883607564443648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.21%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.21% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BNB +7.13%, HYPE +3.78%, ADA +2.99%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947883585796005888</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr gain of 3.21%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has risen by 3.21% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BNB +7.13%, HYPE +3.78%, ADA +2.99%.$BNB$ADA$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947883585796005888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21Shares files with SEC for spot ONDO ETF21Shares has filed a preliminary application with the US Securities and Exchange Commission for an ETF tracking the token of the DeFi platform Ondo Finance.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947875155065245696</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANews21Shares files with SEC for spot ONDO ETF21Shares has filed a preliminary application with the US Securities and Exchange Commission for an ETF tracking the token of the DeFi platform Ondo Finance.#ETF$ONDOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947875155065245696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three wallets suspected to be owned by a whale transferred out a total of 10,606 BTC after being dormant for three yearsOn July 23, according to Lookonchain monitoring, three wallets (possibly belonging to the same whale) had just transferred out 10,606 BTC (US$126.00 million) after being idle for 3-5 years. All 3 wallets received BTC on December 13, 2020, when the price of BTC was $18,807.00. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869910515912704</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsThree wallets suspected to be owned by a whale transferred out a total of 10,606 BTC after being dormant for three yearsOn July 23, according to Lookonchain monitoring, three wallets (possibly belonging to the same whale) had just transferred out 10,606 BTC (US$126.00 million) after</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869910515912704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance VIP Borrowing adds KAIA, LA, C, ERA as loanable assets, and adds EURI as collateral assetOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Binance VIP lending has added KAIA, LA, C, and ERA borrowable assets, and added EURI collateral assets. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869706366554112</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBinance VIP Borrowing adds KAIA, LA, C, ERA as loanable assets, and adds EURI as collateral assetOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Binance VIP lending has added KAIA, LA, C, and ERA borrowable assets, and added EURI collateral assets. [PANews]$ERA$C$KAIAShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869706366554112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX Hearing: Creditors in restricted jurisdictions may choose to transfer their claims to non-restricted jurisdictions for claimsOn July 23, FTX Historian, an account that tracks FTX&apos;s bankruptcy and compensation, summarized the key points of last night&apos;s hearing: Previously, if a creditor was in a &quot;restricted jurisdiction&quot; (such as China or Russia), his funds would be immediately confiscated according to the initial proposal of FTX&apos;s asset recovery party. Now the situation has changed, and creditors may be able to transfer their claims to non-restricted countries. The initial motion was &quot;If the creditor is in a restricted jurisdiction, his claims or compensation will be immediately confiscated&quot;, and the updated motion is expected to limit or delete this clause. Creditors can move to non-restricted areas (such as from China to Singapore and the UAE) and receive a distribution of funds, and the jurisdiction can be changed before the distribution. Affected creditors (such as those who have completed KYC in China but live in other countries) may be able to recover their funds through this, but they need to update information and seize the opportunity. In addition, the hearing reduced the risk of debt buyers, and they are likely to increase their bids. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947868718134005760</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsFTX Hearing: Creditors in restricted jurisdictions may choose to transfer their claims to non-restricted jurisdictions for claimsOn July 23, FTX Historian, an account that tracks FTX&apos;s bankruptcy and compensation, summarized the key points of last night&apos;s hearing: Previously, if a cr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947868718134005760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Espresso to Launch First Community Initial Offering via Kaito Capital LaunchpadThe Espresso Foundation has partnered with Kaito to launch its first community initial offering through the Kaito Capital Launchpad platform. The Espresso Foundation will sell $4.00M worth of ESP tokens, with subscription prices lower than Espresso&apos;s latest $600.00M valuation. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947866541483167744</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsEspresso to Launch First Community Initial Offering via Kaito Capital LaunchpadThe Espresso Foundation has partnered with Kaito to launch its first community initial offering through the Kaito Capital Launchpad platform. The Espresso Foundation will sell $4.00M worth of ESP to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947866541483167744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday, with only Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC achieving a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 22th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net inflow yesterday was Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC, with a daily net inflow of 7.51M USD, and the total historical net outflow of GBTC currently stands at 23.54B USD.The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net outflow yesterday was Bitwise&apos;s ETF BITB, with a daily net outflow of 42.27M USD, and the total historical net inflow of BITB currently stands at 2.28B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 154.77B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.5%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.55B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865801859092480</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday, with only Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC achieving a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 22th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highe</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865801859092480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development: Stablecoins will form a new interconnected model with fiat currenciesLi Yang, Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development, recently analyzed stablecoins from five perspectives at a seminar on &quot;The Development Prospects of RMB Stablecoins&quot;: He pointed out that stablecoins are not real currencies, but rather intermediary tools for payment and clearing driven by technology, which will form a new interconnected model with legal tender; he emphasized that sovereign currency is irreplaceable, and stablecoins cannot bypass exchange and the national right to issue currency; he believes that technological innovation should not challenge national monetary sovereignty, but should coordinate and evolve with central bank digital currencies and private payment systems; he suggested promoting the internationalization of the RMB, both internally and externally, exploring the development path of onshore and offshore RMB stablecoins, and establishing a fusion mechanism with digital RMB and the central bank custody system to guide stablecoins and legal tender to jointly build the future payment landscape. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865054979887104</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development: Stablecoins will form a new interconnected model with fiat currenciesLi Yang, Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development, recently analyzed stablecoins from five perspectives at a seminar on &quot;The Deve</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865054979887104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lotte Card applies for trademark rights related to Korean won stablecoinOn July 23, according to Yonhap News Agency, Lotte Card has applied for a total of 36 trademark rights related to the Korean won stablecoin. Lotte Card explained that in addition to applying for trademark rights around &quot;token symbols&quot;, it also simultaneously registered &quot;brand name trademark rights&quot; mainly expressed in Korean. The Korean Intellectual Property Information Retrieval System shows that Lotte Card has applied for 12 brand name trademarks such as &quot;WONBIT&quot;, &quot;KTOKEN&quot;, and &quot;LOCAMONEY&quot;, as well as 24 token symbol trademarks such as &quot;WONBIT&quot;, &quot;KTOKEN&quot;, and &quot;LOCAMONEY&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863899616907264</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsLotte Card applies for trademark rights related to Korean won stablecoinOn July 23, according to Yonhap News Agency, Lotte Card has applied for a total of 36 trademark rights related to the Korean won stablecoin. Lotte Card explained that in addition to applying for trademark rights</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863899616907264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Official: State Should Confiscate Crypto from Illegal MinersAccording to Cryptonews, Yevgeny Masharov, a member of the Russian Public Chamber and a policymaker, said that authorities should be given the power to confiscate cryptocurrencies from illegal or quasi-legal Bitcoin miners. Masharov believes that this proposal will deter &quot;gray&quot; miners by &quot;making illegal mining unprofitable.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863746390593536</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsRussian Official: State Should Confiscate Crypto from Illegal MinersAccording to Cryptonews, Yevgeny Masharov, a member of the Russian Public Chamber and a policymaker, said that authorities should be given the power to confiscate cryptocurrencies from illegal or quasi-legal B</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863746390593536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: 31.6% of PUMP pre-sale buyers have sold on DEX, and 53.0% have been transferred to new walletsOn July 23, according to Spot On Chain statistics, among the 10,145 successful pre-sale buyers of PUMP tokens, 12.7% still hold them; 31.6% have been sold on DEX; only 2.7% of users choose to increase their positions; the remaining 53.0% transferred tokens to new wallets (including those who deposited them on CEX for sale). In addition, the largest buyer who spent $100.0 million to purchase 25.00 billion PUMPs in the pre-sale has now recharged 17.10 billion ($89.5 million) tokens to CEX through FalconX, and currently holds 7.99 billion ($29.5 million). Expected profit, $19.0 million. The largest buyer of PUMP spent $50.0 million to purchase 12.50 billion PUMP and has deposited all tokens ($71.4 million) into CEX. Estimated profit: $21.4 million (+43.0%). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862326023098368</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsData: 31.6% of PUMP pre-sale buyers have sold on DEX, and 53.0% have been transferred to new walletsOn July 23, according to Spot On Chain statistics, among the 10,145 successful pre-sale buyers of PUMP tokens, 12.7% still hold them; 31.6% have been sold on DEX; only 2.7% of users c</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862326023098368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX Hearing Minutes: Allowing Creditors in Restricted Jurisdictions to Transfer Claims to Non-Restricted JurisdictionsThe account FTX Historian, which tracks FTX bankruptcy and compensation, posted a summary of last night&apos;s FTX hearing minutes on X. The core content of the hearing was: For creditors in &quot;restricted jurisdictions&quot; (such as China), their funds will not be immediately confiscated as proposed in the original FTX recovery plan, but creditors will be allowed to transfer to non-restricted jurisdictions. FTX Historian added that for affected creditors, such as those who completed KYC in China but now reside in other jurisdictions such as Singapore, this may be a way to realize claims, although it may require further information updates and more time costs. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862523511902208</link>
      <description>2 hours agoForesightNewsFTX Hearing Minutes: Allowing Creditors in Restricted Jurisdictions to Transfer Claims to Non-Restricted JurisdictionsThe account FTX Historian, which tracks FTX bankruptcy and compensation, posted a summary of last night&apos;s FTX hearing minutes on X. The core content of the he</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862523511902208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>