<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:00:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 08:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches ETH Recurring Buy Event, Enjoy Recurring Buy Cashback and 10% APR SubsidyOn July 23, to celebrate the 10th anniversary of ETH, Bitget launched an ETH fixed investment activity. During the event, new users who create a fixed investment plan for the first time and invest no less than 100 USDT in ETH can receive a 10% cashback on the fixed investment amount, with a maximum cashback amount of 100 USDT and a total prize pool of 10,000 USDT. In addition, if new and existing users invest in ETH and hold it until 0:00 (UTC+8) on August 6, they can enjoy an ETH wealth management interest rate hike coupon of 10% APR based on the fixed investment amount. The interest rate hike period is 2 days, and the maximum interest rate hike amount is 20 ETH. Rewards are given on a first-come, first-served basis while supplies last. The event time is from 15:00 on July 22 to 15:00 on August 5 (UTC+8). [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947929340443955200</link>
      <description>1 minute agoTechFlowBitget Launches ETH Recurring Buy Event, Enjoy Recurring Buy Cashback and 10% APR SubsidyOn July 23, to celebrate the 10th anniversary of ETH, Bitget launched an ETH fixed investment activity. During the event, new users who create a fixed investment plan for the first time and i</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947929340443955200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bybit and Cactus Custody announced a strategic partnership, Cactus Oasis officially connected to the Bybit platformOn July 23, according to official news, Bybit announced today that it has established a strategic partnership with Cactus Custody, Asia&apos;s leading compliant and licensed digital asset custodian under the Matrixport Group. The two parties will launch a new over-the-counter settlement solution through the Cactus Oasis platform, aiming to enhance the asset security, capital utilization efficiency, and operational control capabilities of institutional clients. The integration will be officially launched on July 28, 2025.
This collaboration allows institutional and professional clients to trade directly without having to pre-fund their Bybit exchange accounts. Clients can deposit collateral assets into Cactus Custody, which is securely stored in a fully isolated and regulated custody environment, and the assets are only transferred to Bybit when the transaction is settled. This effectively reduces counterparty risk while ensuring that clients still have full access to market liquidity.
Through Cactus Oasis, institutional clients can safely store their collateral assets in independent custody accounts while trading on Bybit. Assets are always properly kept by Cactus Custody before transaction settlement, which not only improves capital utilization efficiency, but also meets the strict internal governance requirements of institutions.
Cactus Custody adopts a bank-level security system, equipped with a layered hot wallet and cold wallet system, combining hardware security module (HSM) encryption technology with institutional-level cold storage solutions. The company has obtained SOC 1 Type 1 and SOC 2 Type 2 certifications issued by Deloitte, and holds a trust company and trust or corporate service provider (TCSP) license issued by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, fully meeting the compliance standards of mainstream financial institutions. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947928162054246400</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoPANewsBybit and Cactus Custody announced a strategic partnership, Cactus Oasis officially connected to the Bybit platformOn July 23, according to official news, Bybit announced today that it has established a strategic partnership with Cactus Custody, Asia&apos;s leading compliant and licens</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947928162054246400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Citigroup eyeing stablecoin issuance? Here’s what we knowCitigroup claims to be exploring stablecoin adoption amidst accelerated regulations in the United States and Hong Kong to accommodate. How far are they willing to dive? Major financial institutions are now seeking opportunities to benefit from the current stablecoin wave that’s been sweeping the globe. Companies in Hong Kong and the United States have expressed interest in issuing their own stablecoins pegged to local currencies. The global banking firm Citigroup is no exception. In a recent earnings call, CEO Jane Fraser said to stakeholders that the bank is currently aiming to delve deeper into stablecoins and digital assets in order to fulfill clients’ needs. In addition, the bank also hopes to attract new clients and unlock new revenue streams through stablecoins. These comments are reaffirmed by New York-based head of services at Citigroup, Shahmir Khaliq in an interview with South China Morning Post. The executive called stablecoins a “global phenomenon,” especially with recent developments in the United States and Hong Kong’s own Stablecoin Ordinance bill that is scheduled to come into effect on August 1. “We welcome regulators providing us guidance and insight on the stablecoin landscape, allowing us to continue developing new services that help our clients run their businesses every day,” said Khaliq. How far do you think banks are willing to go to embrace stablecoins? Earlier this year, the banking group expressed interest in offering technology-based services and the issuance of what they called a “Citi stablecoin.” Recently, it has also stated that its plans to help clients navigate reserve management as stablecoins require backing its value in reserves. It would also offer services that could convert stablecoins into fiat currencies and vice versa. “Consumers and companies will have multiple payment options, and ultimately, the adoption of stablecoins will depend on factors like cost and ease of access,” he said, adding that banks are able to provide the bridge between stablecoins and fiat. Although the bank is undoubtedly curious about stablecoins and how they will be able to make use of them, it is also taking a cautious stance as it observes the need for “clear accounting rules regarding stablecoins and their impact on balance sheets and liquidity” according to Khaliq. He believes that there is still a long way to go before true regulatory clarity can be achieved in terms of stablecoins, stating that it is still “very early” in its development. Back in April 2025, Citigroup’s latest report showed that stablecoin issuers are poised to become some of the largest holders of U.S. Treasuries by 2030 if the U.S. adopts a regulatory framework. Now that it has, only time will tell if it will reach the predicted $1 trillion surge in additional demand for U.S. Treasuries. Most recently, the Trump Administration passed the Guiding and Establishing National Innovation for U.S. Stablecoins Act or GENIUS Act. It received majority vote from the House of Representatives on July 18. The bill is aimed at providing the first federal framework for stablecoins. Hong Kong is next in line. The special administrative region recently passed the Stablecoin Ordinance, which mandates companies to register for a stablecoin issuance license in order to offer services and issue stablecoins pegged to the Hong Kong dollar. It is scheduled to come into effect on August 1. Even China has begun to mull over softening its stance on digital assets as more and more countries are competing to issue their own stablecoins linked to local currencies, in an attempt to overthrow USD-pegged stablecoin dominance. [Citigroup]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947927496934100992</link>
      <description>9 minutes agocrypto.newsIs Citigroup eyeing stablecoin issuance? Here’s what we knowCitigroup claims to be exploring stablecoin adoption amidst accelerated regulations in the United States and Hong Kong to accommodate. How far are they willing to dive? Major financial institutions are now seeking op</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947927496934100992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, the number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000, with net redemptions reaching 271,000. On-chain data shows that in the past week, two HTX-related wallets have cumulatively redeemed 110,000 ETH, with a total value of over $400 million. In addition, institutions such as Abraxas Capital Mgmt have also carried out staking redemptions. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924910063554560</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoOdailyThe number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, the number of ETH queued for unstaking has increased to nearly 620,000, with net redemptions reaching 271,000. On-chain data shows that in the past week, two H</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924910063554560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale bought 475 WBTC and established a long position of 434.6 BTC.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;0x3E38&quot; bought 475 WBTC ($56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 and went long on BTC by borrowing on Aave. He also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC ($51.60M) on Hyperliquid with 10x leverage. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924926937239552</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoOdailyA whale bought 475 WBTC and established a long position of 434.6 BTC.According to Lookonchain monitoring, the whale &quot;0x3E38&quot; bought 475 WBTC ($56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 and went long on BTC by borrowing on Aave. He also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC ($51.60</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947924926937239552</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch XNY spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Hotbit Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23: Spot trading pair XNY/USDT (July 23 21:20 UTC+8): $XNY is the native token of the Codatta project. Codatta is an open, decentralized, multi-chain protocol that combines blockchain-based data infrastructure with a collaborative network of human contributors and professional AI agents. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923761684090880</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch XNY spot tradingOn July 23, according to official news, Hotcoin Hotbit Exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 23: Spot trading pair XNY/USDT (July 23 21:20 UTC+8): $XNY is the native token of the Codatta project. Codatta is</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923761684090880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>edgeX 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.15BOn July 23, according to the official announcement, edgeX&apos;s 24-hour trading volume exceeded $1.15B, marking a major milestone in the platform&apos;s development. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923515503611904</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoTechFlowedgeX 24-hour trading volume exceeds $1.15BOn July 23, according to the official announcement, edgeX&apos;s 24-hour trading volume exceeded $1.15B, marking a major milestone in the platform&apos;s development. [TechFlow]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947923515503611904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; Recruitment ProgramBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; recruitment campaign, which will recruit 300 users from the Chinese community to become &quot;Scan Chain Product Promoters&quot; by sharing their experiences using the Bitget Wallet scan chain function to discover meme potential coins. The event will run from July 23 to August 1. Participants need to use the Bitget Wallet scan chain function and publish tweets to share the process of screening potential coins and their personal experiences. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947922407586598912</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet Launches &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; Recruitment ProgramBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a &quot;Scan Chain Product Experience Officer&quot; recruitment campaign, which will recruit 300 users from the Chinese community to become &quot;Scan Chain Product Promot</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947922407586598912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainCatcher announces a partnership with Volcano Engine to drive the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure.ChainCatcher has announced a partnership with Volcengine to assist Volcengine in promoting its cloud computing services, including cloud servers, storage, and enterprise-level solutions. Through this collaboration, both parties will jointly promote the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure. As an influential media platform in the Web3 field, ChainCatcher&apos;s collaboration will combine its industry resources with Volcengine&apos;s technical advantages to provide Web3 companies with more efficient cloud service support. As a leading global cloud computing service provider, Volcengine&apos;s collaboration will further strengthen its presence in Web3 and emerging technology fields. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921955025391616</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoChainCatcherChainCatcher announces a partnership with Volcano Engine to drive the efficient development of Web3 infrastructure.ChainCatcher has announced a partnership with Volcengine to assist Volcengine in promoting its cloud computing services, including cloud servers, storage, and</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921955025391616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale starting with 0x3E3 is going long on BTC in Aave and Hyperliquid, with total profits exceeding $5.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale starting with 0x3E3 borrowed from Aave to purchase 475 WBTC (worth approximately $56.00M) at an average price of $115,733.00 to long BTC. The address also opened a long position of 434.6 BTC (worth approximately $51.60M) with 10x leverage on Hyperliquid. The total profit has now exceeded $5.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921620428984320</link>
      <description>32 minutes agoForesightNewsA whale starting with 0x3E3 is going long on BTC in Aave and Hyperliquid, with total profits exceeding $5.00MAccording to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale starting with 0x3E3 borrowed from Aave to purchase 475 WBTC (worth approximately $56.00M) at an average price of $115,7</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947921620428984320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CryptoQuant analyst: Ethereum may experience a pullback in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too largeOn July 23, CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan said that Ethereum has recently risen sharply and may experience a correction in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too large. He pointed out that compared with the overheated market in March and November 2024, the current market is not high. Although Ethereum has performed slowly in this cycle, it has bottomed out and may continue to rise in the second half of 2025. He also mentioned that the rise of Ethereum often drives the performance of other currencies, and investors can pay attention to the subsequent market trends. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917982683959296</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsCryptoQuant analyst: Ethereum may experience a pullback in the short term, but the magnitude and duration are not expected to be too largeOn July 23, CryptoQuant analyst Crypto Dan said that Ethereum has recently risen sharply and may experience a correction in the short term, bu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917982683959296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale has withdrawn a cumulative total of 12,341 ETH from Kraken over the past 8 days, equivalent to approximately $45.60M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,672 ETH, worth $9.87M, from Kraken. In the past 8 days, this whale has withdrawn 12,341 ETH, worth $45.60M, from Kraken. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947919876928114688</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoOdailyA whale has withdrawn a cumulative total of 12,341 ETH from Kraken over the past 8 days, equivalent to approximately $45.60M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale withdrew 2,672 ETH, worth $9.87M, from Kraken. In the past 8 days, this whale has withdrawn 12,341 ETH, worth</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947919876928114688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walrus Announces Collaboration with Gata to Help Build Open AI Execution InfrastructureOn July 23, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced a partnership with Gata, which is dedicated to developing decentralized large model inference, training, and data technology, to become a core component of Gata AI&apos;s open execution infrastructure. With Walrus, Gata will solve the high data access costs that have long plagued decentralized AI. This integration directly empowers Gata&apos;s DataAgent, allowing anyone to contribute idle computing power with one click through a browser, collaboratively generating synthetic datasets needed for AI training. Walrus provides performance comparable to centralized cloud services and low-cost storage, and more importantly, eliminates download fees, allowing the Gata community to conduct large-scale data interaction in a permissionless manner without incurring unpredictable and unsustainable costs. In the future, Gata plans to leverage Walrus&apos;s unique on-chain data programmability to build an open, auditable pricing model. By storing verifiable computation proofs on Walrus, Gata can use Move-based smart contracts to transparently verify computation tasks and settle on-chain, creating a fairer pricing mechanism for service providers, which is a major improvement over the opaque models used by current centralized AI providers. It is reported that Walrus is a new generation storage protocol built for AI Agents, on-chain applications, and enterprises that process large-scale unstructured data. Whether it&apos;s images, videos, audio files, or dynamic metadata, Walrus can store them efficiently, securely, and economically through its distributed node network. [深潮 TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917150328524800</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoTechFlowWalrus Announces Collaboration with Gata to Help Build Open AI Execution InfrastructureOn July 23, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced a partnership with Gata, which is dedicated to developing decentralized large model inference, training, and</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947917150328524800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance altcoin contract daily trading volume climbs to $100.70B, hitting its highest level since February 3According to Cointelegraph, Binance&apos;s altcoin contract daily trading volume climbed to $100.70B, reaching its highest level since February 3. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915833988157440</link>
      <description>55 minutes agoForesightNewsBinance altcoin contract daily trading volume climbs to $100.70B, hitting its highest level since February 3According to Cointelegraph, Binance&apos;s altcoin contract daily trading volume climbed to $100.70B, reaching its highest level since February 3. [Foresight News]Share t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915833988157440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huarong Securities and Guojin Securities jointly organized more than 50 Chinese and foreign institutions to visit OSL to jointly explore digital asset development opportunities.Hong Kong-listed OSL Group (863.HK), which focuses on crypto assets, exchanged views with a delegation of institutional investors organized by China Securities and Guojin Securities, who were visiting, to jointly explore the development trends and compliance paths of the digital asset industry. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915151629422592</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoForesightNewsHuarong Securities and Guojin Securities jointly organized more than 50 Chinese and foreign institutions to visit OSL to jointly explore digital asset development opportunities.Hong Kong-listed OSL Group (863.HK), which focuses on crypto assets, exchanged views with a dele</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947915151629422592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrixport: Crypto market faces short-term volatility, but overall uptrend is not overMatrixport released a chart today stating that Bitcoin&apos;s open interest has increased significantly by $6.00B in the past two weeks, and the annualized funding rate has soared to 19.00%, indicating a large number of aggressive leveraged long positions in the market. At the same time, the activity of South Korean retail investors has increased significantly, and cryptocurrency trading volume has jumped from $1.00B to $6.00B, reflecting the dominant role of retail funds in this round of market conditions. However, as prices enter a sideways phase, these highly leveraged long positions may face the risk of passive liquidation, especially after next week&apos;s FOMC meeting, when the market will enter a relatively quiet August trading period. Despite short-term volatility pressure, multiple key positives are building momentum for after the summer, and the overall upward trend in the crypto market is not over. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947914855469617152</link>
      <description>59 minutes agoOdailyMatrixport: Crypto market faces short-term volatility, but overall uptrend is not overMatrixport released a chart today stating that Bitcoin&apos;s open interest has increased significantly by $6.00B in the past two weeks, and the annualized funding rate has soared to 19.00%, indicati</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947914855469617152</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba Denies Reports of His ResignationAccording to Jinshi, Shigeru Ishiba, the Japanese Prime Minister, told the media on the afternoon of July 23 that the Japanese media&apos;s reports about his resignation were &quot;completely without factual basis.&quot; Ishiba said that he had just finished meetings with Taro Aso, the top advisor of the Liberal Democratic Party, former Prime Minister Yoshihide Suga, and Fumio Kishida, and &quot;the issue of resignation was not discussed.&quot; Media reports about his intention to resign are completely untrue. Ishiba reiterated that he will remain in office and continue to govern. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947913977199136768</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsJapanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba Denies Reports of His ResignationAccording to Jinshi, Shigeru Ishiba, the Japanese Prime Minister, told the media on the afternoon of July 23 that the Japanese media&apos;s reports about his resignation were &quot;completely without factual basis.&quot;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947913977199136768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000.00 Bitcoin and $10,000.00 EthereumIn his latest blog post, Arthur Hayes predicted a year-end target of $250,000.00 for Bitcoin and $10,000.00 for Ethereum. He stated that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market, and Maelstrom (his personal family office) is doing everything related to Ethereum, DeFi, and ERC-20 shitcoins. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912931039055872</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000.00 Bitcoin and $10,000.00 EthereumIn his latest blog post, Arthur Hayes predicted a year-end target of $250,000.00 for Bitcoin and $10,000.00 for Ethereum. He stated that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market, and</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912931039055872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-Japan reach trade agreement, Japanese stocks close up 3.5%The Nikkei 225 index closed up 1,396.40 points, or 3.51%, at 41,171.32 on Wednesday, July 23. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912336437743616</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUS-Japan reach trade agreement, Japanese stocks close up 3.5%The Nikkei 225 index closed up 1,396.40 points, or 3.51%, at 41,171.32 on Wednesday, July 23. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912336437743616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scamFederal prosecutors in Seattle are looking to win forfeiture of millions worth of crypto tied to an investment scheme in the hope of distributing it to victims.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909733234577408</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsUS looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scamFederal prosecutors in Seattle are looking to win forfeiture of millions worth of crypto tied to an investment scheme in the hope of distributing it to victims.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909733234577408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>