<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of STRC perpetual preferred stock to increase its Bitcoin holdings.Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) announced on July 21, 2025, that it plans to conduct an initial public offering of 5,000,000 shares of STRC Variable Rate Series A Perpetual Preferred Stock under the Securities Act of 1933. The funds raised will be used for general corporate purposes, including the purchase of Bitcoin and supplementing working capital. The preferred stock has an initial annualized dividend rate of 9.00%, which the company can adjust monthly, but the adjustment range is limited. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947394474577776640</link>
      <description>22 minutes ago吴说Strategy plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of STRC perpetual preferred stock to increase its Bitcoin holdings.Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) announced on July 21, 2025, that it plans to conduct an initial public offering of 5,000,000 shares of STRC Variable Rate Series A Perpetual P</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947394474577776640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameSquare Ups Crypto Asset Mandate to $250.0M, Launches Ethereum and NFT Yield StrategyGameSquare Holdings has announced an increase in its crypto asset management authorization from $100.00M to $250.00M, and the addition of an Ethereum ecosystem NFT yield strategy, initially allocating $10.00M with a target annualized yield of 6%–10%. The company recently increased its holdings by 8,352 ETH at an average price of approximately $3,592.00, with total holdings of approximately 10,171 ETH currently valued at approximately $38.00M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947387410853941248</link>
      <description>51 minutes ago吴说GameSquare Ups Crypto Asset Mandate to $250.0M, Launches Ethereum and NFT Yield StrategyGameSquare Holdings has announced an increase in its crypto asset management authorization from $100.00M to $250.00M, and the addition of an Ethereum ecosystem NFT yield strategy, initially alloca</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947387410853941248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street rallies as AI hype meets earnings realityStocks climbed toward record highs on Monday as investors looked past tariff tensions and focused on upcoming tech earnings. The Dow rose 220 points (0.52%), while the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq gained 0.58% and 0.75%, respectively. Traders are piling into tech shares ahead of key results from Alphabet and Tesla, both set to report on Wednesday. Optimism is high—but so are valuations, drawing warnings from economists who see signs of a growing AI-fueled bubble. Apollo’s chief economist, Torsten Slok, said valuations for top S&amp;P 500 firms, such as Nvidia, Microsoft, and Apple, now exceed their peaks from the dot-com era. Traders are bidding up tech stocks ahead of key earnings reports. Notably, both Alphabet and Tesla will release their earnings on Wednesday, the first among the major tech giants this quarter. Strong results could validate the market’s optimism and high valuations. Still, the market’s focus on the AI sector is increasingly drawing comparisons to the 1999 tech bubble. Torsten Slok, the chief economist at Apollo Global Management, stated that the AI bubble could be even worse than the dot-com bubble. Torsten Slok: &quot;The difference between the IT bubble in the 1990s and the AI bubble today is that the top 10 companies in the S&amp;P 500 today are more overvalued than they were in the 1990s&quot; pic.twitter.com/OEervHU4WG Slok explained that the top 10 companies in the S&amp;P 500 are now more overvalued than they were in the 1990s. Specifically, he compared the P/E ratios of major firms such as Nvidia, Microsoft, and Apple, and found they were higher than at the absolute peak of the dot-com bubble. Moreover, traders remain concerned over U.S. trade policy, as tensions with the EU escalate. The European Union is preparing for a trade reprisal if it doesn’t get a deal with the U.S. “If they want war, they will get war,” WSJ quoted one German official referencing the trade negotiations. This is a response to President Donald Trump’s escalating demands toward the EU and other trading partners. Earlier, Trump pushed for a 20% minimum tariff on EU goods, up from 15% proposed earlier. On the other hand, the EU aims to obtain a 10% baseline tariff, with special consideration for certain industries.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947361750357921792</link>
      <description>2 hours agocrypto.newsWall Street rallies as AI hype meets earnings realityStocks climbed toward record highs on Monday as investors looked past tariff tensions and focused on upcoming tech earnings. The Dow rose 220 points (0.52%), while the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq gained 0.58% and 0.75%, respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947361750357921792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.13% in the past 1H, down 0.12% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947360209566392320</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.13% in the past 1H, down 0.12% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947360209566392320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin or CBDC? Tether’s latest freeze adds fuel to decentralization debateFollowing its latest freeze of nearly $86,000.00 in stolen USDt, Tether’s enforcement capabilities are again in the spotlight — raising questions about centralized control in stablecoin ecosystems.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947351046577999872</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsStablecoin or CBDC? Tether’s latest freeze adds fuel to decentralization debateFollowing its latest freeze of nearly $86,000.00 in stolen USDt, Tether’s enforcement capabilities are again in the spotlight — raising questions about centralized control in stablecoin ecosystems.#DeFi$U</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947351046577999872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Chair Jerome Powell Accused of Lying Twice, Congressman Requests Criminal ReferralU.S. Representative Anna Paulina Luna has submitted a criminal referral to the Department of Justice, accusing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell of twice making false statements in testimony and written statements regarding the Fed building renovation project. The move comes as conservatives continue to pressure Trump to replace Powell as soon as possible, but Trump has said it is &quot;highly unlikely&quot; he will remove him from office at this time. [Fox News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947337030577180672</link>
      <description>4 hours ago吴说Fed Chair Jerome Powell Accused of Lying Twice, Congressman Requests Criminal ReferralU.S. Representative Anna Paulina Luna has submitted a criminal referral to the Department of Justice, accusing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell of twice making false statements in testimony and w</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947337030577180672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lido Discloses RageQuit Vulnerability That Could Cause Withdrawal Delays, User Funds Not AffectedLido officially disclosed that the RageQuit mechanism in its Dual Governance (DG) system has a vulnerability that can be used for griefing, potentially causing delays in ETH withdrawals under certain conditions. The vulnerability was reported by an anonymous white hat through Immunefi and does not pose a risk to user funds. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330628689350656</link>
      <description>4 hours ago吴说Lido Discloses RageQuit Vulnerability That Could Cause Withdrawal Delays, User Funds Not AffectedLido officially disclosed that the RageQuit mechanism in its Dual Governance (DG) system has a vulnerability that can be used for griefing, potentially causing delays in ETH withdrawals unde</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330628689350656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s allies in the House level criminal accusations against Federal Reserve Chairman PowellFox News reported that Fed Chair Powell is facing criminal charges from Trump&apos;s allies in the House of Representatives. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330998970896384</link>
      <description>4 hours agoOdailyTrump&apos;s allies in the House level criminal accusations against Federal Reserve Chairman PowellFox News reported that Fed Chair Powell is facing criminal charges from Trump&apos;s allies in the House of Representatives. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330998970896384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US SEC Chairman: ETH is not a securityIn an interview with CNBC, the new U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman Paul Atkins stated that ETH is not a security. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947328480475893760</link>
      <description>4 hours agoOdailyUS SEC Chairman: ETH is not a securityIn an interview with CNBC, the new U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman Paul Atkins stated that ETH is not a security. [Odaily Planet Daily]$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947328480475893760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company DeFi Development Corp increases holdings by 141,383 SOL, total holdings near 1.00M SOLAccording to the official announcement, US-listed company DeFi Development Corp announced today that it has increased its holdings of SOL by another 141,383, bringing its total holdings to 999,999, equivalent to approximately $192.00 million. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947325753159077888</link>
      <description>4 hours agoForesightNewsUS-listed company DeFi Development Corp increases holdings by 141,383 SOL, total holdings near 1.00M SOLAccording to the official announcement, US-listed company DeFi Development Corp announced today that it has increased its holdings of SOL by another 141,383, bringing its t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947325753159077888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish listed company H100 Group increased its holdings by 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC.According to official sources, Swedish listed company H100 Group announced an increase of 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947323456203018240</link>
      <description>5 hours agoOdailySwedish listed company H100 Group increased its holdings by 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC.According to official sources, Swedish listed company H100 Group announced an increase of 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTC$MAG</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947323456203018240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury to review scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in futureOn July 21, the US Treasury Department will review the scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in the future. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947322448647311360</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsU.S. Treasury to review scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in futureOn July 21, the US Treasury Department will review the scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in the future. [PANews]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947322448647311360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercurity Fintech and Solana Ventures reach $200.00 million SOL funding agreementOn July 21, according to The Block, Nasdaq-listed Mercurity Fintech Holding signed a $200.00 million equity credit agreement with Solana Ventures to advance its Solana funding strategy. Mercurity plans to accumulate a large number of Solana (SOL) tokens through the agreement, and earn income through staking, validating nodes and Solana DeFi protocols, while investing in Solana-based projects, including tokenized assets and real-world asset platforms. Wilfred Daye, the company&apos;s chief strategy officer, said that the Solana strategy is a new plan and does not replace the previous $800.00 million Bitcoin reserve plan. The two have different fund management and income characteristics. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947321361768927232</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsMercurity Fintech and Solana Ventures reach $200.00 million SOL funding agreementOn July 21, according to The Block, Nasdaq-listed Mercurity Fintech Holding signed a $200.00 million equity credit agreement with Solana Ventures to advance its Solana funding strategy. Mercurity plans</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947321361768927232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tron founder Justin Sun to fly on Blue Origin four years after bidding nearly $30 million for a seatTron founder Justin Sun&apos;s big-money bet is paying for itself with a ride on Jeff Bezos&apos; next space exploration rocket.Blue Origin announced Monday the six-person crew for New Shepard’s 34th mission, which will be the 14th human flight for the New Shepard program and the 34th overall. Since Bezos took off on its inaugural mission in 2021, Blue Origin has flown 70 people above the Kármán line, the internationally recognized boundary of space.Sun placed the winning $28 million bid for the first seat on New Shepard in June 2021. Those proceeds were donated to Blue Origin’s foundation, Club for the Future, which selected 19 space-focused nonprofits to each receive a $1 million grant.&quot;Proud to join Blue Origin’s NS-34 mission and continue encouraging youth to pursue their dreams in science and space!&quot; Sun said Monday in a post on X. The flight date will be announced soon.Tron is one of the leading blockchain-based operating systems, particularly for stablecoins. Before founding Tron, Sun was formerly a chief representative for the Greater China Area at Ripple.As one of the top holders of the Original Trump memecoin, Sun said earlier this month he&apos;s committed to buying $100 million worth of President Donald Trump&apos;s memecoin. He previously invested $75 million into the Trump-linked World Liberty Financial, which in turn bought millions of dollars worth of Tron&apos;s TRX token.Last week, SRM Entertainment announced a rebrand to Tron Inc. after staking 365 million TRX for its crypto treasury and brought on Sun as an adviser.Last November, Sun bought Maurizio Cattelan’s infamous duct-taped banana artwork for $6.24 million. [Unknown]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318635173531648</link>
      <description>5 hours agoThe BlockTron founder Justin Sun to fly on Blue Origin four years after bidding nearly $30 million for a seatTron founder Justin Sun&apos;s big-money bet is paying for itself with a ride on Jeff Bezos&apos; next space exploration rocket.Blue Origin announced Monday the six-person crew for New Shepa</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318635173531648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the total network contract liquidation was $424.00 million, with both long and short positions being liquidated.On July 21, Coinglass data showed that in the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency market had a total contract liquidation of $424.00 million, of which $230.00 million was for long orders and $194.00 million was for short orders. The total amount of BTC liquidation was $59.8037 million, and the total amount of ETH liquidation was $130.00 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318218767224832</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsIn the past 24 hours, the total network contract liquidation was $424.00 million, with both long and short positions being liquidated.On July 21, Coinglass data showed that in the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency market had a total contract liquidation of $424.00 million, of which</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318218767224832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Based Fellowship Round 3 based on the Farcaster ecosystem is now open for applications.Farcaster Builders International has announced the third edition of its Based Fellowship program, scheduled for August 11-19, 2025, in Goa, India. Applications are now open. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318314988752896</link>
      <description>5 hours agoForesightNewsBased Fellowship Round 3 based on the Farcaster ecosystem is now open for applications.Farcaster Builders International has announced the third edition of its Based Fellowship program, scheduled for August 11-19, 2025, in Goa, India. Applications are now open. [Foresight News</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318314988752896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: SOL is now at $199.18According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 10.14% in the past 24h. Now at $199.18.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947315840318660608</link>
      <description>5 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: SOL is now at $199.18According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 10.14% in the past 24h. Now at $199.18.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947315840318660608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chu Tianlong: Plan to provide cross-border settlement solutions combining stablecoins and SIM cards for partner banksOn July 21, Chu Tianlong held an online exchange meeting for investors. An institutional investor asked: What progress has the company made in the digital currency business in the first half of this year? Chu Tianlong replied that, first, the company&apos;s system development business related to digital currency has grown rapidly, and some system platforms have been delivered to a bank for operation; second, the company continues to consolidate its market position in advantageous fields such as digital currency hard wallets, issuance and acceptance terminals; third, it will work with outstanding partners to promote cooperation in the field of cross-border payments of digital RMB. In addition, the company seizes the industry opportunities brought about by the legalization of virtual asset transactions in Hong Kong, and plans to build an eSIM management platform for operators and provide cross-border settlement solutions combining stablecoins and SIM cards for cooperative banks. So far, the company&apos;s digital currency business revenue has increased to a certain extent compared with previous years, but it accounts for a relatively low proportion of the company&apos;s revenue. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947312336201338880</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsChu Tianlong: Plan to provide cross-border settlement solutions combining stablecoins and SIM cards for partner banksOn July 21, Chu Tianlong held an online exchange meeting for investors. An institutional investor asked: What progress has the company made in the digital currency bu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947312336201338880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives are losing the crypto futureAs US conservatives rapidly shape the crypto landscape through policy, funding and grassroots adoption, progressives remain divided and hesitant. Progressives lack a unified strategy and risk losing relevance.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947311376066433024</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsProgressives are losing the crypto futureAs US conservatives rapidly shape the crypto landscape through policy, funding and grassroots adoption, progressives remain divided and hesitant. Progressives lack a unified strategy and risk losing relevance.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947311376066433024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Sun to travel to space on a Blue Origin rocketOn July 21, according to zoomer, Justin Sun is about to take a Blue Origin rocket to participate in a space launch mission. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947310222897074176</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsJustin Sun to travel to space on a Blue Origin rocketOn July 21, according to zoomer, Justin Sun is about to take a Blue Origin rocket to participate in a space launch mission. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947310222897074176</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 20:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>