<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:29:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Minsheng Securities: Stablecoin applications range from cross-border payments to on-chain asset management, as Chinese securities firms accelerate their deployment in the new digital finance arena.On July 21, according to Sina Finance, Minsheng Securities pointed out that in the short term, cross-border payment scenarios are expected to become an important application scenario for stablecoin adoption. Stablecoins are expected to help improve the efficiency of cross-border payments and reduce cross-border payment costs. Fintech targets related to cross-border payments are expected to continue to benefit, and it is recommended to focus on LianLian DigiTech. In the long term, stablecoins are expected to promote virtual asset trading and RWA, STO. Stablecoins are expected to help traditional financial assets conduct &quot;on-chain&quot; transactions. Chinese securities firms are accelerating their layout. For example, Guotai Junan International has upgraded its virtual asset trading license, and GF Securities (Hong Kong) has fully connected to HashKey Chain as the core on-chain issuance network and issued the first daily redeemable tokenized security &quot;GF Token&quot;. Leading securities firms and exchange targets are expected to benefit more from the development of stablecoins. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947196996804956160</link>
      <description>59seconds agoTechFlowMinsheng Securities: Stablecoin applications range from cross-border payments to on-chain asset management, as Chinese securities firms accelerate their deployment in the new digital finance arena.On July 21, according to Sina Finance, Minsheng Securities pointed out that in the</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947196996804956160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch CSKY spot tradingOn July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will list the following trading pairs on July 21: Spot trading pair CSKY/USDT (July 21, 20:20 UTC+8): $CSKY is the native token of the CoreSky project. Coresky is a new generation Web3 meme incubation platform that aims to discover, empower, and launch community-driven meme projects. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195954121953280</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch CSKY spot tradingOn July 21, according to official news, the Hotcoin exchange will list the following trading pairs on July 21: Spot trading pair CSKY/USDT (July 21, 20:20 UTC+8): $CSKY is the native token of the CoreSky project. Coresky is a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195954121953280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTX-sponsored ChainCatcher &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party in Hanoi, Vietnam will be held on July 31.The &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party, sponsored by HTX and hosted by ChainCatcher, will be grandly held in Hanoi, Vietnam on July 31st from 19:30 - 22:30 (GMT+7). As the third time this brand event has been held in Vietnam, previous events have successfully brought together leading local Vietnamese Web3 project teams, top investors, well-known KOLs, and core community members, creating a highly influential communication platform in the industry. This event will further promote in-depth cooperation and resource docking within the Vietnamese Web3 ecosystem. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195150010961920</link>
      <description>8 minutes agoChainCatcherHTX-sponsored ChainCatcher &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party in Hanoi, Vietnam will be held on July 31.The &quot;Web3 Future Night&quot; themed cocktail party, sponsored by HTX and hosted by ChainCatcher, will be grandly held in Hanoi, Vietnam on July 31st from 19:30 - 22:30 (</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947195150010961920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aave community vote approves ARFC proposal to &quot;Deploy a white-label version of Aave 3 on the Ink chain&quot;The Aave community has voted to pass the ARFC proposal for &quot;Deploying a White-Label Version of Aave 3 on the Ink Chain,&quot; with an approval rate of 99.8%. The proposal suggests deploying Aave 3 on Ink, and unlike Aave deployments on other chains, the proposal states that Ink will have a white-label version centrally managed by the Ink Foundation, without the need for governance tokens. The name is to be determined, but it will adopt the &quot;Powered by Aave&quot; branding. The Ink Foundation has committed to providing incentives, including liquidity mining, to bring in over $250.0 million in supply. 4% of the &quot;future governance token&quot; supply will initially be used for these incentives. The Ink Foundation will make this its sole on-chain lending focus and will avoid partnering with other lending protocols for at least 12 months. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947191096622993408</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoForesightNewsAave community vote approves ARFC proposal to &quot;Deploy a white-label version of Aave 3 on the Ink chain&quot;The Aave community has voted to pass the ARFC proposal for &quot;Deploying a White-Label Version of Aave 3 on the Ink Chain,&quot; with an approval rate of 99.8%. The proposal sugg</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 07:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947191096622993408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinTax Founder: Web3-related crypto income may become a focus of taxation in the futureIn recent years, the data analysis capabilities of tax authorities have significantly improved, and tax bureaus have begun to proactively analyze CRS data. As a Chinese tax resident, if your overseas assets and income are conspicuous enough, you are likely to come into the view of the tax bureau. In the long run, these overseas assets will sooner or later face the attention and management of tax authorities. This reflects the upgrading of the collection and management mechanism—based on specific risk indicators, using internal &quot;five-step work method&quot; and other means to conduct a systematic assessment of the overseas income of natural persons. Currently, common targets of verification include those who invest in Hong Kong and US stocks, and those who realize overseas equity in Internet companies. However, Web3-related crypto income may become one of the focuses in the future. [Securities Times]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947189008828485632</link>
      <description>33 minutes ago吴说FinTax Founder: Web3-related crypto income may become a focus of taxation in the futureIn recent years, the data analysis capabilities of tax authorities have significantly improved, and tax bureaus have begun to proactively analyze CRS data. As a Chinese tax resident, if your overse</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947189008828485632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish listed company H100 Group plans to raise $1.50M to increase its holdings of BitcoinPublicly listed company H100 Group announced that its board of directors has decided to conduct a directed issue of up to 1,523,089 new shares to certain qualified investors at a price of SEK 9.30 per share, with total proceeds expected to be approximately SEK 14.10 million (approximately $1.50 million). The announcement stated that the net proceeds from this fundraising will be used to seek new investment opportunities within its Bitcoin reserve strategy framework. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947190076857667584</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoOdailySwedish listed company H100 Group plans to raise $1.50M to increase its holdings of BitcoinPublicly listed company H100 Group announced that its board of directors has decided to conduct a directed issue of up to 1,523,089 new shares to certain qualified investors at a price of S</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947190076857667584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank and credit union groups in the US are asking the OCC to delay decisions on bank charter applications submitted by crypto firmsAccording to Cointelegraph, banking and credit union groups in the United States have asked the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) to delay decisions on bank charter applications submitted by crypto companies, citing &quot;significant policy and procedural issues.&quot; &quot;There are significant policy and legal questions regarding whether the business plans proposed by the applicants involve the types of fiduciary activities conducted by national trust banks. The public portions of the applications fail to provide sufficient information for the public to assess or meaningfully comment on the applicants’ proposed business models and operations. If the OCC approves these applications, the public should also be able to review the OCC’s decisions.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947188615226609664</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoForesightNewsBank and credit union groups in the US are asking the OCC to delay decisions on bank charter applications submitted by crypto firmsAccording to Cointelegraph, banking and credit union groups in the United States have asked the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947188615226609664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate Will Launch TA Perpetual Contract TradingAccording to the official announcement, Gate will launch TA perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement) at 15:30 (UTC+8) on July 21, supporting 1-20x leverage. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947187563383246848</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoOdailyGate Will Launch TA Perpetual Contract TradingAccording to the official announcement, Gate will launch TA perpetual contract trading (USDT settlement) at 15:30 (UTC+8) on July 21, supporting 1-20x leverage. [Odaily]$USDT$GTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947187563383246848</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has premiered PsyopCoin (PSYOP)On July 21, according to official news, LBank has launched PsyopCoin (PSYOP) for the first time on July 21, 2025, at 13:30 (SGT), and opened the PSYOP/USDT trading pair. Deposits are now open, and withdrawals will be open on July 22 at 13:00 (SGT). [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182627861843968</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoTechFlowLBank has premiered PsyopCoin (PSYOP)On July 21, according to official news, LBank has launched PsyopCoin (PSYOP) for the first time on July 21, 2025, at 13:30 (SGT), and opened the PSYOP/USDT trading pair. Deposits are now open, and withdrawals will be open on July 22 at 13:00</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182627861843968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.69% in the past 1H, up 1.06% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182453138350080</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $119,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.69% in the past 1H, up 1.06% in the last 24H. Now at $119,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182453138350080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: Users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha Points can claim TA token airdropOn July 21, according to the official announcement, Binance released an update on the launch of Trusta AI (TA), stating that after the start of trading, users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha points can apply for a 750 TA token airdrop. First come, first served, until the airdrop pool is full or the event ends. Please note that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha points. Users must confirm the claim within 24 hours on the Alpha event page, otherwise it will be deemed to have given up the airdrop.
Starting today, the risk pre-check for airdrop activities will be opened 5 minutes before the start, please prepare in advance. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947181839848591360</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsBinance: Users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha Points can claim TA token airdropOn July 21, according to the official announcement, Binance released an update on the launch of Trusta AI (TA), stating that after the start of trading, users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha points</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947181839848591360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Alpha: The TA airdrop claim threshold is 210 points, and claiming will consume 15 points.Binance has announced that TA trading will be available on Binance Alpha on July 21, 2025 at 7:00 (UTC), and futures trading will begin at 7:30. At that time, users holding at least 210 Binance Alpha points can get an airdrop of 750 TA tokens on a first-come, first-served basis, which will end when the airdrop pool is exhausted or the event expires. Claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Alpha points, and users need to confirm the application on the Alpha event page within 24 hours, otherwise it will be deemed as a waiver. Binance will conduct an airdrop risk pre-check 5 minutes before the start of the event, so please be prepared in advance. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182537009025024</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance Alpha: The TA airdrop claim threshold is 210 points, and claiming will consume 15 points.Binance has announced that TA trading will be available on Binance Alpha on July 21, 2025 at 7:00 (UTC), and futures trading will begin at 7:30. At that time, users holding at least 210 B</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182537009025024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Launches Trading Lucky Draw with Up to 3 ETH to be WonTo celebrate Ethereum&apos;s strong comeback, Bitget is launching a trading lucky draw event, open to both new and existing users. During the event, complete the corresponding contract trading volume tasks to get a specific number of chances to win a prize, up to 11 times. Each additional draw increases the chance of winning a grand prize, with a maximum of 3 ETH per draw. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182349267783680</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitget Launches Trading Lucky Draw with Up to 3 ETH to be WonTo celebrate Ethereum&apos;s strong comeback, Bitget is launching a trading lucky draw event, open to both new and existing users. During the event, complete the corresponding contract trading volume tasks to get a specif</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947182349267783680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Blockchain Group Increases Holdings by 22 BitcoinEuropean listed company The Blockchain Group officially announced on Twitter that it spent approximately 2.20 million euros (approximately $2.56 million) to increase its holdings by 22 Bitcoin, and its total holdings have now reached 1955. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180695894118400</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说The Blockchain Group Increases Holdings by 22 BitcoinEuropean listed company The Blockchain Group officially announced on Twitter that it spent approximately 2.20 million euros (approximately $2.56 million) to increase its holdings by 22 Bitcoin, and its total holdings have now reached 1</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180695894118400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyStonks and BIT Reach Strategic Partnership to Accelerate Deep Integration of Digital Assets and Traditional SecuritiesMyStonks announces a deep strategic partnership with global professional digital asset trading platform BIT. MyStonks is a leading global decentralized US stock token platform, and BIT focuses on providing digital asset services to global users. This collaboration marks an important upgrade to the on-chain securities and crypto asset trading ecosystem. This round of cooperation will cover multiple levels, including API integration, traffic referral, joint construction of agent channels, and dual community linkage. The two parties will bring users a convenient cross-platform jump experience, exclusive transaction discounts, and diverse interactive activities, and plan to integrate MyStonks digital securities products on the BIT platform in the future to promote the continuous implementation of one-stop on-chain financial services. This strong alliance will not only help both parties improve service coverage and market influence, but also accelerate the deep integration of digital assets and traditional securities, bringing investors more efficient and diverse asset allocation choices and innovative experiences. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180005536845824</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMyStonks and BIT Reach Strategic Partnership to Accelerate Deep Integration of Digital Assets and Traditional SecuritiesMyStonks announces a deep strategic partnership with global professional digital asset trading platform BIT. MyStonks is a leading global decentralized US stock tok</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180005536845824</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaultz Capital increased its holdings by 20 BTC, and currently holds a total of 70 BTCAccording to NLNico monitoring, UK-listed company Vaultz Capital increased its holdings by 20 BTC, and currently holds a total of 70 BTC. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180013984174080</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyVaultz Capital increased its holdings by 20 BTC, and currently holds a total of 70 BTCAccording to NLNico monitoring, UK-listed company Vaultz Capital increased its holdings by 20 BTC, and currently holds a total of 70 BTC. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTC$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180013984174080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has integrated xStocks to enable coin-stock tradingAccording to official news, LBank has integrated xStocks and launched tokenized stock asset trading. The first batch of popular targets, MSTRX and CRCLX, have been listed in the XSTOCKS trading area, and users can directly trade with USDT. The coin-stock trading provided by LBank supports 24/7 trading, breaking through the trading time and geographical restrictions of traditional stock markets, allowing global users to participate at any time, making asset allocation more flexible. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180022435696640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyLBank has integrated xStocks to enable coin-stock tradingAccording to official news, LBank has integrated xStocks and launched tokenized stock asset trading. The first batch of popular targets, MSTRX and CRCLX, have been listed in the XSTOCKS trading area, and users can directly trad</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947180022435696640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: In the past 24 hours, Top figures have been following projects such as polycule, Hyperbeat, and DubDub.According to RootData X dynamic data, in the past 24 hours: The Polymarket event trading platform polycule has been followed by a16z co-founder Marc Andreessen, Electric Capital co-founder Avichal Garg, CoinFund founder Jake Brukhman, and others. The Hyperliquid-based expansion protocol Hyperbeat has been followed by angel investor DCF GOD, Aperture founding partner Kay Fong, crypto influencer Stephen, and others. The cryptocurrency mobile wallet HaHa has been followed by the Web3 hackathon ETHDenver. The Meme launch platform DubDub has been followed by Taproot Wizards co-founder Udi Wertheimer. The DeFi lending protocol Takara Lend has been followed by crypto trader Yuyue, crypto KOL spark, and others. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947177230925058048</link>
      <description>1 hour agoChainCatcherData: In the past 24 hours, Top figures have been following projects such as polycule, Hyperbeat, and DubDub.According to RootData X dynamic data, in the past 24 hours: The Polymarket event trading platform polycule has been followed by a16z co-founder Marc Andreessen, Electric</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947177230925058048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiNFT index 24hr gain of 10.02%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has risen by 10.02% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BLUR +25.47%, PENGU +12.78%, SUPER +5.07%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947175260561301504</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiNFT index 24hr gain of 10.02%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiNFT has risen by 10.02% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: BLUR +25.47%, PENGU +12.78%, SUPER +5.07%.$BLUR$SUPER$PENGUShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947175260561301504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAOMAO Launches Token Airdrop, Community Users Can Claim MAOMAO for FreeMeme project MAOMAO has announced the launch of an airdrop campaign, where users can participate by filling out a form to receive early distribution tokens of MAOMAO. According to the official introduction, the airdrop does not require a whitelist and is open to all users. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947174968962076672</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMAOMAO Launches Token Airdrop, Community Users Can Claim MAOMAO for FreeMeme project MAOMAO has announced the launch of an airdrop campaign, where users can participate by filling out a form to receive early distribution tokens of MAOMAO. According to the official introduction, the a</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947174968962076672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>