<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:57:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trial</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948143686927323136</link>
      <description>22:09Crypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trial</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948143686927323136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trialWith the trial of the Tornado Cash co-founder ending its eighth day, a witness testified Roman Storm had control over some of the funds connected to the mixing service.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948144352076828672</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoPANewsCrypto &apos;control&apos; takes center stage at Roman Storm trialWith the trial of the Tornado Cash co-founder ending its eighth day, a witness testified Roman Storm had control over some of the funds connected to the mixing service.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948144352076828672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX to Initiate Next Round of Creditor Distributions on September 30, Releasing $1.90B in Disputed Reserve FundsFTX has announced that the record date for the next round of creditor distributions is August 15, 2025, with distributions expected to begin on September 30, applicable to approved Class 5 customer claims, Class 6 general unsecured claims, and previously undistributed convenience claims. Additionally, FTX has received court approval to reduce the disputed claims reserve from $6.50B to $4.30B, releasing nearly $1.90B in cash for this round of distributions. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131066270781440</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说FTX to Initiate Next Round of Creditor Distributions on September 30, Releasing $1.90B in Disputed Reserve FundsFTX has announced that the record date for the next round of creditor distributions is August 15, 2025, with distributions expected to begin on September 30, applicable to appr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131066270781440</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan: $2 Trillion Stablecoin Market Prediction Too Optimistic, Infrastructure Still Needs ImprovementJPMorgan says that market predictions of stablecoin&apos;s total market capitalization reaching $2 trillion by 2028 are &quot;slightly optimistic.&quot; Although Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent recently proposed this target at a hearing, saying it could be achieved with legislative support, JPMorgan believes that the stablecoin infrastructure is not yet perfect and it will be difficult to support such large-scale growth in the short term. JPMorgan expects the market to more likely double or triple in the coming years, rather than reach several times its current market capitalization of $260.00 billion. [Bloomberg]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948127867426115584</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说JPMorgan: $2 Trillion Stablecoin Market Prediction Too Optimistic, Infrastructure Still Needs ImprovementJPMorgan says that market predictions of stablecoin&apos;s total market capitalization reaching $2 trillion by 2028 are &quot;slightly optimistic.&quot; Although Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent rec</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948127867426115584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Agent Links Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm to Binance Funds and Offshore DealingsFederal prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm moved millions through Binance and coordinated with co-founders to send funds and buy offshore real estate. IRS-CI Special Agent Stephan George told the jury he traced over $533,000.00 in USDT from a Binance account allegedly controlled by Storm. He said the funds were moved on August 9, 2022, and distributed across three wallet addresses. Storm Allegedly Sent $2.6 Million Each to Co-Founders Prosecutors showed chat logs between Tornado Cash’s founding trio: Roman Storm, Roman Semenov, and Alexey Pertsev. In one message, Storm wrote: “I overloaded 8 million yesterday.” Another message stated: “I sent you guys 2.6 million each.” Agent George said these communications indicated Storm had access to the funds and decision-making power over the wallet in question. In a separate message, Storm reportedly told a colleague to: “Give her a task to f **ing open various offshores… and to buy real estate.” Prosecutors also read a message from Semenov stating: “I will send some TORN later, to avoid getting busted.” The prosecution argued these messages revealed intent to obscure transactions and profit from Tornado Cash’s operations. 96% of Tornado Cash Users Relied on Web Interface Earlier in the day, prosecution expert Philip Werlau of AnChain.AI testified that 96.2% of users accessed Tornado Cash through its user interface (UI), not the command line. He said Lazarus Group shifted to CLI usage only after US sanctions were imposed. Werlau said this behavior suggested a deliberate attempt to avoid detection. During cross-examination, Roman Storm’s defense challenged Werlau’s conclusions. He emphasized that Tornado Cash’s smart contract pools became immutable in May 2020, meaning neither Storm nor the DAO could change them. Klein also clarified that Tornado’s UI did not handle transactions directly. Deposits and withdrawals required interacting with Ethereum’s smart contracts, not any centralized interface. Meanwhile, prosecutors presented an email from an earlier witness, Ms. Lin, addressed to Tornado Cash’s public inbox. Judge Failla warned the jury not to treat its content as fact. The email’s inclusion may relate to the defense’s previously stated mistrial concerns, though no motion was filed. What’s Next in the Tornado Cash Trial The prosecution is expected to rest its case tomorrow morning. A separate hearing on the Chainalysis expert testimony is still pending. Storm’s defense is preparing to present its side, focusing on the immutability of Tornado Cash and Storm’s lack of control after deployment. [Wu Shuo]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948140146783752192</link>
      <description>1 hour agobeincryptoIRS Agent Links Tornado Cash’s Roman Storm to Binance Funds and Offshore DealingsFederal prosecutors presented evidence suggesting Tornado Cash founder Roman Storm moved millions through Binance and coordinated with co-founders to send funds and buy offshore real estate. IRS-CI S</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948140146783752192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Trump administration did not deny Trump&apos;s name appearing in Epstein documentsA White House official stated that the Trump administration did not deny that Trump&apos;s name appeared in the (Epstein) documents. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133802961866752</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyWhite House: Trump administration did not deny Trump&apos;s name appearing in Epstein documentsA White House official stated that the Trump administration did not deny that Trump&apos;s name appeared in the (Epstein) documents. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133802961866752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiAI index 24hr loss of 10.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiAI has fallen by 10.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: KAITO -13.08%, AI16Z -12.44%, VIRTUAL -12.18%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132827357732864</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiAI index 24hr loss of 10.04%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiAI has fallen by 10.04% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: KAITO -13.08%, AI16Z -12.44%, VIRTUAL -12.18%.$VIRTUAL$AI16Z$KAITOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132827357732864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&apos;s Q2 net profit increased by 19%, raising its full-year capital expenditure forecast to $850.00BAlphabet, the parent company of Google (GOOG.O), reported a 19% year-over-year increase in net profit to $28.196B in the second quarter, and a 14% increase in revenue to $96.43B, better than the market&apos;s expected $94.00B. Q2 Google service revenue increased by 12% to $82.5B, of which YouTube advertising revenue was $9.79B; Google Cloud revenue increased by 32% to $13.6B, higher than the expected $13.11B. The company expects capital expenditures to reach $85.00B this year with increased investment in artificial intelligence, compared to earlier estimates of $75.00B this year. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133811400806400</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGoogle&apos;s Q2 net profit increased by 19%, raising its full-year capital expenditure forecast to $850.00BAlphabet, the parent company of Google (GOOG.O), reported a 19% year-over-year increase in net profit to $28.196B in the second quarter, and a 14% increase in revenue to $96.43B, be</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133811400806400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -10.73%, SXP -7.69%, CRO -5.17%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132635099226112</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -10.73%, SXP -7.69%, CRO -5.17%.$CRO$WOO$SXPShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132635099226112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla&apos;s Q2 net profit was $1.172B, a 20.7% year-on-year decrease.Tesla&apos;s second-quarter revenue was $22.50B, a year-on-year decrease of 12%, with an estimated $22.64B. Second-quarter net profit was $1.172B, a year-on-year decrease of 20.7%, with market expectations of $1.136B. Adjusted earnings per share for the second quarter were $0.40, compared to $0.52 in the same period last year, with an estimated $0.42. Second-quarter gross margin was 17.2%, compared to 18% in the same period last year, with an estimated 16.5%. Second-quarter free cash flow (FCF) was $146.00M, compared to $664.00M in the first quarter, with analysts expecting $760.00M. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133819839746048</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTesla&apos;s Q2 net profit was $1.172B, a 20.7% year-on-year decrease.Tesla&apos;s second-quarter revenue was $22.50B, a year-on-year decrease of 12%, with an estimated $22.64B. Second-quarter net profit was $1.172B, a year-on-year decrease of 20.7%, with market expectations of $1.136B. Adjust</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133819839746048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Trump does not support Musk&apos;s artificial intelligence company receiving federal contractsWhite House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said Wednesday that she believes U.S. President Donald Trump does not support federal agencies contracting with Elon Musk&apos;s artificial intelligence company. When asked if Trump wants to cancel recent contracts with Musk&apos;s AI ventures, Jean-Pierre said she would discuss the matter with the president. About a week ago, Musk&apos;s xAI, along with three other major tech companies, was awarded a Department of Defense contract worth up to $200.00M. Trump and Musk have been in a heated feud since Musk resigned as a government special employee at the end of May. Trump said he could retaliate against Musk by canceling federal contracts with Musk&apos;s businesses. (The Hill) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133828282880000</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyWhite House: Trump does not support Musk&apos;s artificial intelligence company receiving federal contractsWhite House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said Wednesday that she believes U.S. President Donald Trump does not support federal agencies contracting with Elon Musk&apos;s artificial</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133828282880000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memecoin launchpad LetsBONK pledges 1% of revenue to buyback top tokensMemecoin launchpad LetsBONK, which supports the Solana-based memecoin BONK and its ecosystem, announced on Wednesday it would set aside 1% of total revenue towards buying back &quot;the top pairs within the BONK eco.&quot;

The revenue will be reassigned from the LetsBONK team&apos;s marketing fund, according to the team&apos;s announcement on X.

LetsBONK has made around $1.5 million in fees over the past 24 hours, according to a Dune dashboard that tracks rival memecoin platforms by Adam_Tehc. 1% of that revenue would equal to $15,000.00 of buying pressure on top token pairs, such as Useless Coin, which has a market capitalization of about $312 million, according to CoinGecko data.

&quot;[The buybacks] will happen once a week and any pair that reaches the high levels can be included,&quot; LetsBONK founder Tom wrote on X. &quot;More to come.&quot;

The total market capitalizations of tokens launched on LetsBONK recently surpassed $1 billion, according to a Dune dashboard. Useless Coin is the largest coin in the ecosystem, followed by ANI, a token representing xAI&apos;s recent Grok AI Companion.

Notably, rival platform Pump has integrated a revenue-sharing mechanism into its newly-launched PUMP token and a “community takeover” mechanism that will enable users to commandeer “abandoned” projects.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132536256892928</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockMemecoin launchpad LetsBONK pledges 1% of revenue to buyback top tokensMemecoin launchpad LetsBONK, which supports the Solana-based memecoin BONK and its ecosystem, announced on Wednesday it would set aside 1% of total revenue towards buying back &quot;the top pairs within the BONK eco</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132536256892928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Florida judge rejects request to unseal Epstein case grand jury recordsOn Wednesday, a federal judge in Florida rejected a request from the Department of Justice to release grand jury records from the Epstein investigation. Attorney General Bondi pushed for the release of the Epstein case&apos;s grand jury materials in an effort to quell the anger of Trump&apos;s MAGA base, who have urged the government to disclose Epstein&apos;s alleged &quot;client list.&quot; Earlier this month, Trump&apos;s Justice Department and the FBI said that no such client list exists, and Bondi said she would not release any further materials. Despite the rejection in Florida, the Justice Department has another opportunity, as they have also asked two federal judges in New York to unseal grand jury transcripts, where prosecutors filed lawsuits against Epstein and his accomplice Ghislaine Maxwell. Federal courts in New York generally take a less strict approach to grand jury secrecy. (Politico) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133836788928512</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUS Florida judge rejects request to unseal Epstein case grand jury recordsOn Wednesday, a federal judge in Florida rejected a request from the Department of Justice to release grand jury records from the Epstein investigation. Attorney General Bondi pushed for the release of the Epst</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133836788928512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer2 index 24hr loss of 10.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer2 has fallen by 10.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OP -13.43%, TIA -12.98%, MOVE -12.74%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132198665117696</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiLayer2 index 24hr loss of 10.06%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer2 has fallen by 10.06% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: OP -13.43%, TIA -12.98%, MOVE -12.74%.$OP$TIA$MOVEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948132198665117696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary: There may be 1 to 2 interest rate cuts this yearUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: There may be 1 to 2 rate cuts this year. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133845253033984</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUS Treasury Secretary: There may be 1 to 2 interest rate cuts this yearUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: There may be 1 to 2 rate cuts this year. [Odaily]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133845253033984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents.The U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents. (Wall Street Journal) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133853717139456</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyThe U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents.The U.S. Department of Justice informed Trump in May that his name appeared in the Epstein documents. (Wall Street Journal) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133853717139456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Decide How to Use $550.00B in Japanese Investment in the U.S.White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt stated that President Trump will decide how to use Japan&apos;s $550.00B investment in the United States himself. She stated that Japan&apos;s investment is part of the US-Japan trade agreement. Leavitt stated that Trump will use the investment for key industries such as energy, semiconductors, critical minerals, pharmaceuticals, and shipbuilding. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133862151884800</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyTrump to Decide How to Use $550.00B in Japanese Investment in the U.S.White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt stated that President Trump will decide how to use Japan&apos;s $550.00B investment in the United States himself. She stated that Japan&apos;s investment is part of the US-Japan t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133862151884800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House Speaker: House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing Epstein case recordsLocal time July 23, it was learned that U.S. House Speaker Mike Johnson said that the House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing records related to the Jeffrey Epstein case, because the Trump administration &quot;has done everything it can to release these records.&quot; It is reported that the Democratic Party is constantly trying to force a vote on the matter, saying that it concerns trust in the government. Republican leaders also released a resolution that has no legal effect, but would urge the Justice Department to provide more documents. (CCTV) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133870590824448</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyUS House Speaker: House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing Epstein case recordsLocal time July 23, it was learned that U.S. House Speaker Mike Johnson said that the House of Representatives does not need to vote this week on releasing records related to t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133870590824448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank: Firing Powell wouldn&apos;t save much in debt costsU.S. President Trump last month cited the cost of federal debt as a new reason to urge Powell to cut interest rates. But a new analysis shows that firing the Fed chairman and forcing him to lower interest rates would not help. Deutsche Bank chief U.S. economist Matthew Luzzetti and others wrote that replacing Powell would not change the Treasury&apos;s debt interest costs. Trump has repeatedly called for a 3 percentage point rate cut, saying it would save more than $1 trillion. But according to the Deutsche Bank team&apos;s calculations, while short-term Treasury yields would fall, long-term Treasury yields would rise due to concerns that a more compliant Fed would mean higher inflation. Specifically, if Trump fired Powell, the Treasury would only save $12.00 billion to $15.00 billion by 2027. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133879042347008</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyDeutsche Bank: Firing Powell wouldn&apos;t save much in debt costsU.S. President Trump last month cited the cost of federal debt as a new reason to urge Powell to cut interest rates. But a new analysis shows that firing the Fed chairman and forcing him to lower interest rates would not he</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948133879042347008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiDePIN index 24hr loss of 10.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDePIN has fallen by 10.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: GRASS -11.9%, AIOZ -10.9%, IOTA -10.52%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131117130276864</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSSI Price BotssiDePIN index 24hr loss of 10.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDePIN has fallen by 10.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: GRASS -11.9%, AIOZ -10.9%, IOTA -10.52%.$IOTA$AIOZ$GRASSShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131117130276864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tether CEO: US market entry &apos;well underway&apos; amid plans for institutional stablecoinTether CEO Paolo Ardoino said the stablecoin issuer is well underway to do business in the U.S. in an interview with Bloomberg Television. The news comes less than a week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act into law to regulate stablecoins in the U.S.

&quot;We are well in progress of establishing our U.S. domestic strategy,&quot; Ardoino said on Wednesday.

In April, Tether&apos;s Ardoino told The Block that the stablecoin issuer had plans to launch a new U.S.-based stablecoin aimed specifically at institutional clients.

Tether&apos;s USDT is the world&apos;s largest stablecoin with a total market capitalization of $162 billion, according to The Block&apos;s price page. The new proposed stablecoin, however, would be geared toward institutions looking for faster settlements.

Ardoino told Bloomberg on Wednesday that Tether plans to make an announcement on the firm&apos;s plans for U.S. institutional markets.

&quot;That is well underway,&quot; Ardoino said. &quot;We plan to announce it in the next couple of months.&quot;

Tether has faced ongoing scrutiny for not providing a full independent audit of its stablecoin reserves, and instead has released quarterly attestations signed by BDO Italia. Last month, the company hired Simon McWilliams as its new chief financial officer to lead efforts toward securing a full audit. Ardoino has also said that obtaining a review from a Big Four audit firm — Deloitte, EY, PwC, or KPMG — is a &quot;top priority.&quot;

Ardoino appeared at Trump&apos;s signing of a bill to regulate stablecoins called GENIUS last week in Washington. The bill creates a federal regulatory framework for fiat-pegged tokens, including a requirement for stablecoins to be fully backed by U.S. dollars or similarly liquid assets, and mandating annual audits for issuers with a market capitalization of more than $50 billion. It also establishes guidelines for foreign issuance.

In the U.S., Tether is likely to face increased competition as more traditional banks begin to make plans to launch their stablecoins, including companies co-owned by JPMorgan, Bank of America, Citigroup, and Wells Fargo.

To that, Ardoino told Bloomberg that those competitors might be better than Tether in the short term in the U.S., but added that Tether has advantages. &quot;They can compete and be probably maybe, maybe, better than us in the short term in the United States just because it&apos;s a new market for us, but we have better technology,&quot; Ardoino said. &quot;We have a much better understanding of this market than anyone else.&quot;

Ardoino was also asked whether Tether planned to go public like its competitor, Circle. He said Tether was not interested. [Bloomberg Television]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131342176292864</link>
      <description>1 hour agoThe BlockTether CEO: US market entry &apos;well underway&apos; amid plans for institutional stablecoinTether CEO Paolo Ardoino said the stablecoin issuer is well underway to do business in the U.S. in an interview with Bloomberg Television. The news comes less than a week after President Donald Trum</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 21:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948131342176292864</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 22:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>