<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:40:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Polymarket set to reenter US with $112.00M acquisition of QCEX derivitives exchange</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947410600883933184</link>
      <description>21:36Polymarket set to reenter US with $112.00M acquisition of QCEX derivitives exchange</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947410600883933184</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StablecoinX to go public via SPAC merger, raising $360.00M for ENA treasury</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947400549133733888</link>
      <description>20:56StablecoinX to go public via SPAC merger, raising $360.00M for ENA treasury</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947400549133733888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jito Introduces BAM Architecture, Restructuring the Solana Block Building ProcessJito Foundation and Jito Labs have jointly launched the Solana block building architecture Block Assembly Marketplace (BAM), which implements verifiable transaction sequencing, programmable execution logic, and a new revenue distribution mechanism through a trusted execution environment (TEE), aiming to mitigate harmful MEV and improve on-chain transparency. BAM consists of scheduling nodes (BAM Nodes), upgraded validator clients (BAM Validators), and a plug-in system, supporting custom transaction sequencing logic. Developers can charge fees through plug-ins, and node operators, validators, and stakers share revenue according to the built-in model. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947400252785184768</link>
      <description>44 minutes ago吴说Jito Introduces BAM Architecture, Restructuring the Solana Block Building ProcessJito Foundation and Jito Labs have jointly launched the Solana block building architecture Block Assembly Marketplace (BAM), which implements verifiable transaction sequencing, programmable execution log</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947400252785184768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of STRC perpetual preferred stock to increase its Bitcoin holdings.Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) announced on July 21, 2025, that it plans to conduct an initial public offering of 5,000,000 shares of STRC Variable Rate Series A Perpetual Preferred Stock under the Securities Act of 1933. The funds raised will be used for general corporate purposes, including the purchase of Bitcoin and supplementing working capital. The preferred stock has an initial annualized dividend rate of 9.00%, which the company can adjust monthly, but the adjustment range is limited. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947394474577776640</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Strategy plans to issue 5,000,000 shares of STRC perpetual preferred stock to increase its Bitcoin holdings.Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy) announced on July 21, 2025, that it plans to conduct an initial public offering of 5,000,000 shares of STRC Variable Rate Series A Perpetual Prefe</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947394474577776640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameSquare Ups Crypto Asset Mandate to $250.0M, Launches Ethereum and NFT Yield StrategyGameSquare Holdings has announced an increase in its crypto asset management authorization from $100.00M to $250.00M, and the addition of an Ethereum ecosystem NFT yield strategy, initially allocating $10.00M with a target annualized yield of 6%–10%. The company recently increased its holdings by 8,352 ETH at an average price of approximately $3,592.00, with total holdings of approximately 10,171 ETH currently valued at approximately $38.00M. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947387410853941248</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说GameSquare Ups Crypto Asset Mandate to $250.0M, Launches Ethereum and NFT Yield StrategyGameSquare Holdings has announced an increase in its crypto asset management authorization from $100.00M to $250.00M, and the addition of an Ethereum ecosystem NFT yield strategy, initially allocating</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947387410853941248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dream of Banking the Third World is Still Alive with AztecoAzteco, the international Bitcoin gift card company, has announced a series of partnerships with digital gift card distributors that unlock 598 million new potential buyers, with an expected 1.3 billion potential customers as the rollout of distribution deals continues. “We’re turning Bitcoin from being a noun into a verb so that you can Bitcoin it,” Akin Fernandez, founder of Azteco, told Bitcoin Magazine in an exclusive interview. The company, whose brand first appeared in Bitcoin in 2014, has been focused on banking the unbanked throughout the developing world for over a decade, with Bitcoin gift cards or vouchers as the technology of choice. The new partnerships include Razor, the video game software and hardware company, which today has 240 million tech-savvy customers, according to Fernandez. Focused on Brazil, Europe, the Middle East and Africa, other distribution partnerships include Enterative®LIVE, with an estimated 30 million customers; DTOne, a global estimate of 190 million customers; KaBum!, with 8 million; and PicPay, having just cleared compliance and is expected to unlock another 60 million users in Brazil, per data shared by Fernandez. “Bitcoin has all the utility of money and that’s an absolutely enormous market, the size of which makes the current price of bitcoin completely irrational,” Fernandez added when discussing the potential market size of Bitcoin. Azteco, who originally raised $6 million in seed funding from various angel investors, including Jack Dorsey, has now launched a new seed extension raise, targeting $4 million to fund the expansion. “My contribution to Azteco comes out of a deep respect for their mission. The unbanked population is immense. We have the technology and resources to close this gap, but until now, no one has taken that important next step. Azteco is providing so much more than just access to a secure financial system; it is building an ecosystem of financial self-determination that is secure and supported by local communities. I am honored to support them.” — Jack Dorsey, Block. Banking the unbanked, a popular slogan of an older generation of Bitcoiners, is still alive and well in Azteco. Popularized by Andreas Antonopoulos around 2014, this mission statement for Bitcoin highlighted the vast gap in access to financial services and technologies between the Western elite — be it in New York or London — to that of the rest of the world. The unbanked often lack the to basic access to long-distance financial rails, reasonably priced credit and the relative security of a normal bank account. Proponents of banking the unbanked as a clear use case of Bitcoin argued that, as a technology, it could go a lot further than banks since it doesn’t need to identify its users; bitcoin simply works as a bearer asset regardless of who controls or or where in the world it is sent from. Access to cheap mobile phones and basic telecommunications infrastructure like text messages, allowed novel implementations of Bitcoin to exist and function in environments where traditional Western banks simply could not justify the administration and onboarding costs. “To experience the future of money. To gain a glimpse into an exciting technology. To learn about how money could be in the future and also become aware of how limited money and banks are today. For the ‘other 6 billion’ who don’t enjoy international, control-free banking as we do, bitcoin represents an opportunity to become part of a global economy which up till now did not exist. For those users, bitcoin is more than just a curiosity, it might be a doorway to connect to the world.” — Antonoplous, 2015. This vision for Bitcoin began to struggle as the transaction fees of sending BTC on-chain started to spike around 2017, leading to the infamous Blocksize wars and, as a consequence, the build-out of the Lightning Network. Azteco vouchers could be purchased as early as 2014. Fast-forward to 2025, and Azteco has upgraded its technology from natively using Bitcoin on-chain addresses in its vouchers in 2014 to adding Lightning Network support via the LNURL standard via compatible apps like Wallet of Satoshi, Muun or Blink. The deep experience Azteco has with the Bitcoin technology stack is self-evident in their design today, which removes an incredible amount of friction from normal ways of buying bitcoin and delivers it in a beautiful package. Going further than the economic argument for servicing an unbanked and underbanked population, out of reach of the legacy banking system, Fernandez differentiates between ethical and unethical bitcoin along the same lines. In an unpublished document on the matter, shared with Bitcoin Magazine, Fernandez writes: “What is ‘Ethical Bitcoin’? This can best be described by stating what it is not. It is not ethical to connect a user’s identity to the money they use, or the content of the messages they send on a network. It is unethical to cut people off from being able to use their money. It is unethical to surveil people and then use that information to control them. It is unethical to arbitrarily block people from selling goods and services.” With this statement, Fernandez strikes at the fundamental, structural difference between legacy finance and Bitcoin. Censorship resistance; confidence that users can access their accounts and transfer value without the need for personal information, despite the way the political winds are blowing — that is Bitcoin’s killer app. A very different mindset than popular generations of Bitcoiners who, in internet parlance, seem to mostly just care about NGU (“number go up), even if it’s in the form of an ETF or bitcoin treasury company. Nothing wrong with that, but perhaps this generation of Bitcoiners has either forgotten or not been exposed to enough content by Andreas Antonopoulos. They might not realize how big a portion of the global market is cut off from legacy finance, how many are unbanked. Azteco’s thesis is far from just ideological; there’s a big market at play. Focusing on the prepaid phone data market, Fernandez points out that “there are 3.4 billion users of prepaid mobile smartphones” worldwide. Which means that almost half of the global population has access to smartphones and is already used to topping up their phones “on an ad hoc basis,” including via digital vouchers of various kinds. Every one of these users of the internet network is capable of installing “Wallet of Satoshi, Proton Wallet, Blockstream App or BitKey; all they have to do is take 30 seconds to put it on their Android or iPhone,” he adds. The utility of bitcoin to them is not that different from sending a WhatsApp message, says Fernandez, which, for near-zero cost, allows billions of people in the developing world to coordinate across great distances every day. Bitcoin unlocks the same velocity but for the transfer of monetary value, be it in the form of payments or remittances, while also serving as an accessible safe-haven asset from their local fiat currencies — most of which are trending to zero compared to bitcoin. Fernandez notes that “The remittances market is very, very, very large, it is worth $782 billion a year. Imagine we take, I don’t know, 12% of that, or 15% of that and switch them all onto bitcoin. That would be a super disruptive event.” He added that “just like in WhatsApp, if you have a family of 15 people and you put them all onto Wallet of Satoshi or Blockstream Wallet then all of a sudden you have a lot of people who are moving bitcoin from and to, and they all need to be fed with bitcoin.” The problem is, of course: How will they acquire the bitcoin? “If they’re not Americans or they’re not Europeans, getting bitcoin through an exchange, first of all, is very difficult. And secondly, it’s very slow and privacy-invading. Azteco vouchers are much better for them because they can go to a place where they’re already buying their video games and stuff like that, they can buy a $25 voucher or go to the supermarket and buy a $25 voucher. And then they have their bitcoin that they can send to wherever it is they want. The use case, once again, is money.” This is not just theoretical. Fernandez shared some of Azteco’s sales numbers with Bitcoin Magazine, having sold roughly “500,000 vouchers over the last couple of years” with a rough average $280-$315 in value transferred and many purchases of $20-$30. In Q1 of 2024, Bitcoin Magazine reported that Azteco had sold vouchers to a million people worldwide since their inception, suggesting an acceleration of interest throughout the developing world in recent years. Fernandez believes these numbers can be a lot bigger and the key obstacle to developing that market is user experience. “I mean we’re all at an all-time high now of what it is, $123,034 but just imagine if the whole world, just people who are on mobile phones are using bitcoin as money to send to each other, to save money and to spend online; that 123,034 is a pittance compared to the size of the market. But none of this can happen if bitcoin is hard to get. It must be trivially easy to get, as easy as topping up your mobile phone to make phone calls,” Fernandez concluded. [Bitcoin Magazine]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947401027741569024</link>
      <description>2 hours agobitcoinmagazineThe Dream of Banking the Third World is Still Alive with AztecoAzteco, the international Bitcoin gift card company, has announced a series of partnerships with digital gift card distributors that unlock 598 million new potential buyers, with an expected 1.3 billion potentia</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947401027741569024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street rallies as AI hype meets earnings realityStocks climbed toward record highs on Monday as investors looked past tariff tensions and focused on upcoming tech earnings. The Dow rose 220 points (0.52%), while the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq gained 0.58% and 0.75%, respectively. Traders are piling into tech shares ahead of key results from Alphabet and Tesla, both set to report on Wednesday. Optimism is high—but so are valuations, drawing warnings from economists who see signs of a growing AI-fueled bubble. Apollo’s chief economist, Torsten Slok, said valuations for top S&amp;P 500 firms, such as Nvidia, Microsoft, and Apple, now exceed their peaks from the dot-com era. Traders are bidding up tech stocks ahead of key earnings reports. Notably, both Alphabet and Tesla will release their earnings on Wednesday, the first among the major tech giants this quarter. Strong results could validate the market’s optimism and high valuations. Still, the market’s focus on the AI sector is increasingly drawing comparisons to the 1999 tech bubble. Torsten Slok, the chief economist at Apollo Global Management, stated that the AI bubble could be even worse than the dot-com bubble. Torsten Slok: &quot;The difference between the IT bubble in the 1990s and the AI bubble today is that the top 10 companies in the S&amp;P 500 today are more overvalued than they were in the 1990s&quot; pic.twitter.com/OEervHU4WG Slok explained that the top 10 companies in the S&amp;P 500 are now more overvalued than they were in the 1990s. Specifically, he compared the P/E ratios of major firms such as Nvidia, Microsoft, and Apple, and found they were higher than at the absolute peak of the dot-com bubble. Moreover, traders remain concerned over U.S. trade policy, as tensions with the EU escalate. The European Union is preparing for a trade reprisal if it doesn’t get a deal with the U.S. “If they want war, they will get war,” WSJ quoted one German official referencing the trade negotiations. This is a response to President Donald Trump’s escalating demands toward the EU and other trading partners. Earlier, Trump pushed for a 20% minimum tariff on EU goods, up from 15% proposed earlier. On the other hand, the EU aims to obtain a 10% baseline tariff, with special consideration for certain industries.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947361750357921792</link>
      <description>3 hours agocrypto.newsWall Street rallies as AI hype meets earnings realityStocks climbed toward record highs on Monday as investors looked past tariff tensions and focused on upcoming tech earnings. The Dow rose 220 points (0.52%), while the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq gained 0.58% and 0.75%, respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947361750357921792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.13% in the past 1H, down 0.12% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947360209566392320</link>
      <description>3 hours agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $118,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is up 0.13% in the past 1H, down 0.12% in the last 24H. Now at $118,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947360209566392320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin or CBDC? Tether’s latest freeze adds fuel to decentralization debateFollowing its latest freeze of nearly $86,000.00 in stolen USDt, Tether’s enforcement capabilities are again in the spotlight — raising questions about centralized control in stablecoin ecosystems.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947351046577999872</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsStablecoin or CBDC? Tether’s latest freeze adds fuel to decentralization debateFollowing its latest freeze of nearly $86,000.00 in stolen USDt, Tether’s enforcement capabilities are again in the spotlight — raising questions about centralized control in stablecoin ecosystems.#DeFi$U</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947351046577999872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Chair Jerome Powell Accused of Lying Twice, Congressman Requests Criminal ReferralU.S. Representative Anna Paulina Luna has submitted a criminal referral to the Department of Justice, accusing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell of twice making false statements in testimony and written statements regarding the Fed building renovation project. The move comes as conservatives continue to pressure Trump to replace Powell as soon as possible, but Trump has said it is &quot;highly unlikely&quot; he will remove him from office at this time. [Fox News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947337030577180672</link>
      <description>4 hours ago吴说Fed Chair Jerome Powell Accused of Lying Twice, Congressman Requests Criminal ReferralU.S. Representative Anna Paulina Luna has submitted a criminal referral to the Department of Justice, accusing Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell of twice making false statements in testimony and w</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947337030577180672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lido Discloses RageQuit Vulnerability That Could Cause Withdrawal Delays, User Funds Not AffectedLido officially disclosed that the RageQuit mechanism in its Dual Governance (DG) system has a vulnerability that can be used for griefing, potentially causing delays in ETH withdrawals under certain conditions. The vulnerability was reported by an anonymous white hat through Immunefi and does not pose a risk to user funds. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330628689350656</link>
      <description>5 hours ago吴说Lido Discloses RageQuit Vulnerability That Could Cause Withdrawal Delays, User Funds Not AffectedLido officially disclosed that the RageQuit mechanism in its Dual Governance (DG) system has a vulnerability that can be used for griefing, potentially causing delays in ETH withdrawals unde</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330628689350656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s allies in the House level criminal accusations against Federal Reserve Chairman PowellFox News reported that Fed Chair Powell is facing criminal charges from Trump&apos;s allies in the House of Representatives. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330998970896384</link>
      <description>5 hours agoOdailyTrump&apos;s allies in the House level criminal accusations against Federal Reserve Chairman PowellFox News reported that Fed Chair Powell is facing criminal charges from Trump&apos;s allies in the House of Representatives. [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947330998970896384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US SEC Chairman: ETH is not a securityIn an interview with CNBC, the new U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman Paul Atkins stated that ETH is not a security. [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947328480475893760</link>
      <description>5 hours agoOdailyUS SEC Chairman: ETH is not a securityIn an interview with CNBC, the new U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission Chairman Paul Atkins stated that ETH is not a security. [Odaily Planet Daily]$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947328480475893760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-listed company DeFi Development Corp increases holdings by 141,383 SOL, total holdings near 1.00M SOLAccording to the official announcement, US-listed company DeFi Development Corp announced today that it has increased its holdings of SOL by another 141,383, bringing its total holdings to 999,999, equivalent to approximately $192.00 million. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947325753159077888</link>
      <description>5 hours agoForesightNewsUS-listed company DeFi Development Corp increases holdings by 141,383 SOL, total holdings near 1.00M SOLAccording to the official announcement, US-listed company DeFi Development Corp announced today that it has increased its holdings of SOL by another 141,383, bringing its t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947325753159077888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish listed company H100 Group increased its holdings by 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC.According to official sources, Swedish listed company H100 Group announced an increase of 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947323456203018240</link>
      <description>5 hours agoOdailySwedish listed company H100 Group increased its holdings by 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC.According to official sources, Swedish listed company H100 Group announced an increase of 140.25 BTC, bringing its total holdings to 510.28 BTC. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTC$MAG</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947323456203018240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury to review scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in futureOn July 21, the US Treasury Department will review the scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in the future. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947322448647311360</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsU.S. Treasury to review scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in futureOn July 21, the US Treasury Department will review the scope of anti-money laundering rules at some point in the future. [PANews]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947322448647311360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercurity Fintech and Solana Ventures reach $200.00 million SOL funding agreementOn July 21, according to The Block, Nasdaq-listed Mercurity Fintech Holding signed a $200.00 million equity credit agreement with Solana Ventures to advance its Solana funding strategy. Mercurity plans to accumulate a large number of Solana (SOL) tokens through the agreement, and earn income through staking, validating nodes and Solana DeFi protocols, while investing in Solana-based projects, including tokenized assets and real-world asset platforms. Wilfred Daye, the company&apos;s chief strategy officer, said that the Solana strategy is a new plan and does not replace the previous $800.00 million Bitcoin reserve plan. The two have different fund management and income characteristics. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947321361768927232</link>
      <description>5 hours agoPANewsMercurity Fintech and Solana Ventures reach $200.00 million SOL funding agreementOn July 21, according to The Block, Nasdaq-listed Mercurity Fintech Holding signed a $200.00 million equity credit agreement with Solana Ventures to advance its Solana funding strategy. Mercurity plans</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947321361768927232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Based Fellowship Round 3 based on the Farcaster ecosystem is now open for applications.Farcaster Builders International has announced the third edition of its Based Fellowship program, scheduled for August 11-19, 2025, in Goa, India. Applications are now open. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318314988752896</link>
      <description>6 hours agoForesightNewsBased Fellowship Round 3 based on the Farcaster ecosystem is now open for applications.Farcaster Builders International has announced the third edition of its Based Fellowship program, scheduled for August 11-19, 2025, in Goa, India. Applications are now open. [Foresight News</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318314988752896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: SOL is now at $199.18According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 10.14% in the past 24h. Now at $199.18.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947315840318660608</link>
      <description>6 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: SOL is now at $199.18According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 10.14% in the past 24h. Now at $199.18.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947315840318660608</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chu Tianlong: Plan to provide cross-border settlement solutions combining stablecoins and SIM cards for partner banksOn July 21, Chu Tianlong held an online exchange meeting for investors. An institutional investor asked: What progress has the company made in the digital currency business in the first half of this year? Chu Tianlong replied that, first, the company&apos;s system development business related to digital currency has grown rapidly, and some system platforms have been delivered to a bank for operation; second, the company continues to consolidate its market position in advantageous fields such as digital currency hard wallets, issuance and acceptance terminals; third, it will work with outstanding partners to promote cooperation in the field of cross-border payments of digital RMB. In addition, the company seizes the industry opportunities brought about by the legalization of virtual asset transactions in Hong Kong, and plans to build an eSIM management platform for operators and provide cross-border settlement solutions combining stablecoins and SIM cards for cooperative banks. So far, the company&apos;s digital currency business revenue has increased to a certain extent compared with previous years, but it accounts for a relatively low proportion of the company&apos;s revenue. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947312336201338880</link>
      <description>6 hours agoPANewsChu Tianlong: Plan to provide cross-border settlement solutions combining stablecoins and SIM cards for partner banksOn July 21, Chu Tianlong held an online exchange meeting for investors. An institutional investor asked: What progress has the company made in the digital currency bu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947312336201338880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tron founder Justin Sun to fly on Blue Origin four years after bidding nearly $30 million for a seatTron founder Justin Sun&apos;s big-money bet is paying for itself with a ride on Jeff Bezos&apos; next space exploration rocket.Blue Origin announced Monday the six-person crew for New Shepard’s 34th mission, which will be the 14th human flight for the New Shepard program and the 34th overall. Since Bezos took off on its inaugural mission in 2021, Blue Origin has flown 70 people above the Kármán line, the internationally recognized boundary of space.Sun placed the winning $28 million bid for the first seat on New Shepard in June 2021. Those proceeds were donated to Blue Origin’s foundation, Club for the Future, which selected 19 space-focused nonprofits to each receive a $1 million grant.&quot;Proud to join Blue Origin’s NS-34 mission and continue encouraging youth to pursue their dreams in science and space!&quot; Sun said Monday in a post on X. The flight date will be announced soon.Tron is one of the leading blockchain-based operating systems, particularly for stablecoins. Before founding Tron, Sun was formerly a chief representative for the Greater China Area at Ripple.As one of the top holders of the Original Trump memecoin, Sun said earlier this month he&apos;s committed to buying $100 million worth of President Donald Trump&apos;s memecoin. He previously invested $75 million into the Trump-linked World Liberty Financial, which in turn bought millions of dollars worth of Tron&apos;s TRX token.Last week, SRM Entertainment announced a rebrand to Tron Inc. after staking 365 million TRX for its crypto treasury and brought on Sun as an adviser.Last November, Sun bought Maurizio Cattelan’s infamous duct-taped banana artwork for $6.24 million. [Unknown]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318635173531648</link>
      <description>6 hours agoThe BlockTron founder Justin Sun to fly on Blue Origin four years after bidding nearly $30 million for a seatTron founder Justin Sun&apos;s big-money bet is paying for itself with a ride on Jeff Bezos&apos; next space exploration rocket.Blue Origin announced Monday the six-person crew for New Shepa</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318635173531648</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 24 hours, the total network contract liquidation was $424.00 million, with both long and short positions being liquidated.On July 21, Coinglass data showed that in the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency market had a total contract liquidation of $424.00 million, of which $230.00 million was for long orders and $194.00 million was for short orders. The total amount of BTC liquidation was $59.8037 million, and the total amount of ETH liquidation was $130.00 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318218767224832</link>
      <description>6 hours agoPANewsIn the past 24 hours, the total network contract liquidation was $424.00 million, with both long and short positions being liquidated.On July 21, Coinglass data showed that in the past 24 hours, the cryptocurrency market had a total contract liquidation of $424.00 million, of which</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947318218767224832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</link>
      <description>Updated  1 day agoSoSo Daily | Jul. 21: Ethereum Soars as Treasury Arms Race Heats Up00:00 / 04:13View</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947143958375706624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>