<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:20:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America Merrill Lynch: Stablecoins will have a disruptive impact on traditional bank deposits and payment systemsOn July 21, according to Phoenix.com, the latest research report from Bank of America Merrill Lynch shows that as the US stablecoin regulatory framework gradually takes effect, stablecoins will have a disruptive impact on traditional bank deposits and payment systems in the next 2-3 years. The US President has signed the GENIUS Act to set a preliminary framework for stablecoin regulation. In the short term, the stablecoin market is expected to grow by $25-75 billion, which will boost demand for US short-term Treasury bonds. Although major banks are cautious about domestic payment applications, they generally believe that cross-border payments are a feasible scenario and have begun to deploy related businesses, including JPMorgan Chase&apos;s deposit tokens and Bank of New York Mellon&apos;s custody services. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947134063324450816</link>
      <description>1 minute agoPANewsBank of America Merrill Lynch: Stablecoins will have a disruptive impact on traditional bank deposits and payment systemsOn July 21, according to Phoenix.com, the latest research report from Bank of America Merrill Lynch shows that as the US stablecoin regulatory framework graduall</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947134063324450816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consensys to release fix for MetaMask browser extensionAccording to Cointelegraph, Consensys stated that it has noticed some MetaMask users reporting &quot;abnormally high disk activity&quot; and will release a fix soon. Previously, user ripper31337 pointed out in a GitHub bug report on June 24 that after reinstalling the MetaMask extension on Chromium-based browsers (such as Chrome, Edge, and Opera), the program was found to be continuously writing data to the solid-state drive (SSD) in the background without user interaction. This &quot;abnormal disk writing&quot; occurs at a rate of 5M per second, totaling 500G bytes per day, accumulating to 25 TB in three months. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947133222802706432</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoForesightNewsConsensys to release fix for MetaMask browser extensionAccording to Cointelegraph, Consensys stated that it has noticed some MetaMask users reporting &quot;abnormally high disk activity&quot; and will release a fix soon. Previously, user ripper31337 pointed out in a GitHub bug repor</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947133222802706432</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: SOL is now at $186.28According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 5.02% in the past 24h. Now at $186.28.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947131047962435584</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: SOL is now at $186.28According to SoSoValue, SOL (Solana) is up 5.02% in the past 24h. Now at $186.28.$SOLShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947131047962435584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sui ecosystem launches BTCFi series of events, participate to win rich rewardsOn July 21, the Sui ecosystem launched a BTCFi series of activities where users holding any BTC-backed assets can earn rewards by completing tasks, including: SatLayer platform xBTC event: From July 9 to October 1, 2025, deposit xBTC on SatLayer to earn satXBTC and earn more rewards; Bluefin tBTC Galxe event: From July 9 to July 23, 2025, complete tasks to win a $5,000.00 prize pool; OKX Wallet Cryptopedia event (Season 36): From June 26 to August 24, 2025, participate in the event to learn how Sui native DeFi works, and complete some simple tasks to get rewards; xBTC Phase 1: From June 24 to August 27, 2025, deposit xBTC, USDC, or SUI on the NAVI or Momentum platform to receive specific event rewards; Lombard Luminary Program: Users can stake BTC on the Lombard platform to earn LBTC and earn rewards; wBTC: Bridge wBTC to Sui via Sui Bridge and participate in Sui DeFi to earn income. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947129640829341696</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoTechFlowSui ecosystem launches BTCFi series of events, participate to win rich rewardsOn July 21, the Sui ecosystem launched a BTCFi series of activities where users holding any BTC-backed assets can earn rewards by completing tasks, including: SatLayer platform xBTC event: From July 9</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947129640829341696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Token Unlocks This WeekAccording to Tokenomist, single large unlocks (unlock amount greater than $5.00M) in the next 7 days include AVAIL, VENOM, ALT, SAHARA, SOON, etc.; linear large unlocks (single-day unlock amount greater than $1.00M) in the next 7 days include SOL, WLD, Trump, TIA, DOGE, TAO, AVAX, SUI, DOT, IP, MORPHO, SEI, ETHFI, JTO, NEAR, ENS, FIL, etc., with a total unlock value of over $442.00M.
 [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130627933622272</link>
      <description>20 minutes ago吴说Large Token Unlocks This WeekAccording to Tokenomist, single large unlocks (unlock amount greater than $5.00M) in the next 7 days include AVAIL, VENOM, ALT, SAHARA, SOON, etc.; linear large unlocks (single-day unlock amount greater than $1.00M) in the next 7 days include SOL, WLD, Tr</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130627933622272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: $372.00 million liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with $208.00 million in short positions liquidatedAccording to Coinglass data, approximately $372.00M was liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with long positions accounting for $164.00M and short positions accounting for $208.00M. Among them, Bitcoin liquidations amounted to $41.50M, and Ethereum liquidations amounted to $150.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130718052438016</link>
      <description>20 minutes agoForesightNewsData: $372.00 million liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with $208.00 million in short positions liquidatedAccording to Coinglass data, approximately $372.00M was liquidated across the entire network in the past 24 hours, with long positions account</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947130718052438016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Rich Dad Poor Dad&quot; Author: Bubbles Always Burst, Will Continue to Buy if BTC Falls&quot;Rich Dad Poor Dad&quot; author Robert Kiyosaki posted on the X platform, saying: Bubbles always burst, and when they do, gold, silver, and Bitcoin may also fall. However, if the prices of gold, silver, and Bitcoin plummet, he will continue to buy, but reminds investors to be cautious. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947129676300570624</link>
      <description>22 minutes agoOdaily&quot;Rich Dad Poor Dad&quot; Author: Bubbles Always Burst, Will Continue to Buy if BTC Falls&quot;Rich Dad Poor Dad&quot; author Robert Kiyosaki posted on the X platform, saying: Bubbles always burst, and when they do, gold, silver, and Bitcoin may also fall. However, if the prices of gold, silver,</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947129676300570624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet withdrew 400 BTC from Binance, worth $47.22 millionOn July 21, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, another newly created wallet withdrew 400 BTC worth $47.22 million from Binance 9 hours ago. In the past 4 days, a total of 4 newly created wallets withdrew 1,800 BTC worth $212.38 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947125630323937280</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoPANewsA new wallet withdrew 400 BTC from Binance, worth $47.22 millionOn July 21, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, another newly created wallet withdrew 400 BTC worth $47.22 million from Binance 9 hours ago. In the past 4 days, a total of 4 newly created wallets withdrew 1,800 BTC</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947125630323937280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance to Remove Seed Tags From BONK, EIGEN, ETHFI, PENGU, and PEPE on July 21Binance has announced that it will remove the seed tags from Bonk (BONK), EigenLayer (EIGEN), ether fi (ETHFI), Pudgy Penguins (PENGU), and Pepe (PEPE) on July 21, 2025. Seed tags are typically used to identify emerging innovative projects with higher volatility and risk. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124892571029504</link>
      <description>38 minutes ago吴说Binance to Remove Seed Tags From BONK, EIGEN, ETHFI, PENGU, and PEPE on July 21Binance has announced that it will remove the seed tags from Bonk (BONK), EigenLayer (EIGEN), ether fi (ETHFI), Pudgy Penguins (PENGU), and Pepe (PEPE) on July 21, 2025. Seed tags are typically used to ide</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124892571029504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Bonk Attracts $198.00M in Funding Over the Past Week, Meme Series Performs WellOn July 21, according to HolderScan data, capital inflows into the crypto market have been significant in the past 7 days. Bonk leads the way with $198.29 million, followed by Uniswap and Pepe, attracting $112.08 million and $99.63 million, respectively. Chainlink ($94.53 million), Pengu ($70.91 million), and Fartcoin ($55.30 million) also performed strongly. [Techflow TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124782726402048</link>
      <description>38 minutes agoTechFlowReport: Bonk Attracts $198.00M in Funding Over the Past Week, Meme Series Performs WellOn July 21, according to HolderScan data, capital inflows into the crypto market have been significant in the past 7 days. Bonk leads the way with $198.29 million, followed by Uniswap and Pep</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124782726402048</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong stocks of stablecoin concept stocks are strengthening, with China Inspection &amp; Certification Healthcare rising more than 30%.Hong Kong stock stablecoin concept stocks collectively strengthened, with China Inspection Medical surging over 30%, Linklogis Technology rising over 8%, Victory Securities up 7.1%, OSL Group up 1.43%, Bright Smart Securities up 5.60%, and Alibaba also rising. Regarding news, U.S. President Trump recently formally signed the &quot;Guidance and Establishment of National Innovation Act for Stablecoins in the United States&quot; (GENIUS Act) at the White House, marking the entry of U.S. stablecoin regulatory legislation into the implementation phase. In addition, Hong Kong&apos;s &quot;Stablecoin Ordinance&quot; was officially published in the Gazette on May 30 and will take effect on August 1. From an ecological chain perspective, the stablecoin ecosystem can be specifically divided into three levels: primary market issuance, secondary market circulation, and application scenarios. In terms of individual stocks, China Inspection Medical has initiated the application for a U.S. stablecoin license and is actively promoting the Web3 exchange ecosystem; Yunfeng Financial recently announced on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange that it will strategically focus on areas such as Web 3, Real World Assets (RWA), digital currencies, ESG zero-carbon assets, and artificial intelligence. [Sina Finance] [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124650790375424</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoOdailyHong Kong stocks of stablecoin concept stocks are strengthening, with China Inspection &amp; Certification Healthcare rising more than 30%.Hong Kong stock stablecoin concept stocks collectively strengthened, with China Inspection Medical surging over 30%, Linklogis Technology rising</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124650790375424</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created wallet withdrew 400 BTC from Binance, worth approximately $47.22MAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet withdrew 400 BTC from Binance, worth approximately $47.22M. In the past 4 days, 4 newly created wallets have withdrawn a total of 1800 BTC from Binance, worth approximately $212.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124427208806400</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoForesightNewsA newly created wallet withdrew 400 BTC from Binance, worth approximately $47.22MAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet withdrew 400 BTC from Binance, worth approximately $47.22M. In the past 4 days, 4 newly created wallets have withdrawn a total of 1</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124427208806400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linea, Consensys, and Nile Collaborate to Launch Decentralized Trading Platform EtherexLinea, Consensys, and Nile have partnered to launch the decentralized trading platform Etherex, aiming to achieve true user alignment and a full-chain infrastructure. Etherex is an upgraded version of Nile Exchange, built on Ramses v3 technology, and adopts the x33 token economic model. The native token REX will be distributed to LP users as a liquidity reward. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124667668254720</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoOdailyLinea, Consensys, and Nile Collaborate to Launch Decentralized Trading Platform EtherexLinea, Consensys, and Nile have partnered to launch the decentralized trading platform Etherex, aiming to achieve true user alignment and a full-chain infrastructure. Etherex is an upgraded ver</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947124667668254720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wallet spent approximately $8.00 million to purchase 45 CryptoPunks and 1 Chromie SquiggleAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet has spent 2,082 ETH (approximately $7.79 million) to purchase 45 CryptoPunks NFTs. In addition, the whale also spent 60.5 ETH (approximately $227,000) to purchase 1 Chromie Squiggle. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947120651180273664</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoForesightNewsA new wallet spent approximately $8.00 million to purchase 45 CryptoPunks and 1 Chromie SquiggleAccording to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet has spent 2,082 ETH (approximately $7.79 million) to purchase 45 CryptoPunks NFTs. In addition, the whale also spent</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947120651180273664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 21Today in 2022, the total transaction volume of ENS domains exceeded $100 million.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947114353009319936</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 21Today in 2022, the total transaction volume of ENS domains exceeded $100 million.#NFTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947114353009319936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMorgan Chase data-charging plan could &quot;destroy&quot; crypto and fintech startups, executive warnsOn July 21, according to Fortune magazine, last month, when JPMorgan Chase informed fintech companies that it planned to charge them for accessing its customers&apos; bank account data, the move caused a strong reaction in many areas of the financial industry. According to four industry executives, the move is a blow to the fintech industry and may have a devastating impact on early startups, including those in the cryptocurrency industry. However, analysts believe that mature fintech companies such as PayPal and Block (formerly Square) may not be greatly affected by this fee adjustment.
Under the plan, the bank could charge data aggregators fees every time a consumer moves money from JPMorgan to a cryptocurrency account or a third-party service like Robinhood. Crypto and fintech companies often use aggregators like Plaid or MX to access customer accounts at major financial institutions like JPMorgan. So far, banks haven’t charged fintech companies, but that could change. Aggregators are widely expected to pass on the new fees to fintech customers, and some may even pass the costs on to consumers. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947112882226290688</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsJPMorgan Chase data-charging plan could &quot;destroy&quot; crypto and fintech startups, executive warnsOn July 21, according to Fortune magazine, last month, when JPMorgan Chase informed fintech companies that it planned to charge them for accessing its customers&apos; bank account data, the move</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947112882226290688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market news: pump.fun may airdrop PUMP on July 24According to market news, pump.fun co-founder and CEO Alon Cohen appeared to disclose on the X platform that he plans to start distributing PUMP airdrops to eligible active Solana wallets at 23:00 Beijing time on July 24, 2025. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947114570953744384</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMarket news: pump.fun may airdrop PUMP on July 24According to market news, pump.fun co-founder and CEO Alon Cohen appeared to disclose on the X platform that he plans to start distributing PUMP airdrops to eligible active Solana wallets at 23:00 Beijing time on July 24, 2025. [Odaily</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947114570953744384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will deliver a speech on July 22 at 20:30.According to Cointelegraph, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will attend the regulatory capital framework conference and deliver a speech at 20:30 Beijing time on July 22. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947111875454918656</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsFederal Reserve Chairman Powell will deliver a speech on July 22 at 20:30.According to Cointelegraph, Federal Reserve Chairman Powell will attend the regulatory capital framework conference and deliver a speech at 20:30 Beijing time on July 22. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947111875454918656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale transferred 400 BTC to Binance, realizing a profit of over $100 million, and still holds a position of over $128 million.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale transferred 400.1 Bitcoin (worth approximately $47.23 million) to Binance, realizing a profit of approximately $107.08 million. The whale initially withdrew 1,500 Bitcoin from Binance 8 to 9 months ago (worth approximately $69.01 million at the time), and currently still holds 1,100 Bitcoin, worth approximately $128.87 million. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947111284775280640</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说A whale transferred 400 BTC to Binance, realizing a profit of over $100 million, and still holds a position of over $128 million.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale transferred 400.1 Bitcoin (worth approximately $47.23 million) to Binance, realizing a profit of approximately $1</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947111284775280640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum will pass The Torch NFT to commemorate its tenth anniversary and will open up commemorative NFT minting to everyone.Ethereum has launched The Torch NFT, designed to commemorate the people and values that shaped Ethereum&apos;s first decade and will help build its future. In the 10 days leading up to Ethereum&apos;s tenth anniversary, the NFT will be symbolically passed between wallets. On July 30th, the NFT will be burned to commemorate the tenth anniversary of Ethereum&apos;s founding. In addition, everyone can mint a commemorative NFT. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947109345136173056</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsEthereum will pass The Torch NFT to commemorate its tenth anniversary and will open up commemorative NFT minting to everyone.Ethereum has launched The Torch NFT, designed to commemorate the people and values that shaped Ethereum&apos;s first decade and will help build its future. I</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947109345136173056</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</link>
      <description>Updated  23 hours agoJul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜So</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>