<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:55:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000.00 Bitcoin and $10,000.00 EthereumIn his latest blog post, Arthur Hayes predicted a year-end target of $250,000.00 for Bitcoin and $10,000.00 for Ethereum. He stated that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market, and Maelstrom (his personal family office) is doing everything related to Ethereum, DeFi, and ERC-20 shitcoins. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912931039055872</link>
      <description>1 minute ago吴说Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000.00 Bitcoin and $10,000.00 EthereumIn his latest blog post, Arthur Hayes predicted a year-end target of $250,000.00 for Bitcoin and $10,000.00 for Ethereum. He stated that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market, an</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912931039055872</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba refutes reports of his resignationJuly 23 news, according to Jinshi, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba told the media this afternoon (July 23) that the Japanese media reports that he would resign &quot;have no factual basis.&quot; Shigeru Ishiba said that he had just finished a meeting with Liberal Democratic Party&apos;s top adviser Taro Aso, former Prime Minister Yoshihide Suga and Fumio Kishida, &quot;no resignation was discussed.&quot; Media reports that he intends to resign are completely untrue. Shigeru Ishiba once again stated that he will stay in office and continue to govern. Justin Low, an analyst at US financial media, commented that Shigeru Ishiba has not yet officially admitted defeat, but at present, his fate is a foregone conclusion. The ruling Liberal Democratic Party of Japan will hold a party meeting on July 31, and it can be foreseen that this will be the last straw for Shigeru Ishiba. The sentiment in Japan&apos;s asset markets is clearly mixed, with stocks rising, bonds selling, and the yen fluctuating up and down, trying to balance the impact of trade news and political uncertainty. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947911679546822656</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsJapanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba refutes reports of his resignationJuly 23 news, according to Jinshi, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba told the media this afternoon (July 23) that the Japanese media reports that he would resign &quot;have no factual basis.&quot; Shigeru Ishiba s</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947911679546822656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-Japan reach trade agreement, Japanese stocks close up 3.5%The Nikkei 225 index closed up 1,396.40 points, or 3.51%, at 41,171.32 on Wednesday, July 23. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912336437743616</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyUS-Japan reach trade agreement, Japanese stocks close up 3.5%The Nikkei 225 index closed up 1,396.40 points, or 3.51%, at 41,171.32 on Wednesday, July 23. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947912336437743616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scamFederal prosecutors in Seattle are looking to win forfeiture of millions worth of crypto tied to an investment scheme in the hope of distributing it to victims.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909733234577408</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsUS looks to grab $7.1M in crypto from oil and gas investment scamFederal prosecutors in Seattle are looking to win forfeiture of millions worth of crypto tied to an investment scheme in the hope of distributing it to victims.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909733234577408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethena Ecosystem Protocol Strata Opens Pre-DepositEthena ecosystem protocol Strata opens pre-deposits. The first phase of the campaign will accept two tokens, USDe and eUSDe, and depositing the corresponding funds will qualify users for Ethena rewards and Strata points. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908817592848384</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoForesightNewsEthena Ecosystem Protocol Strata Opens Pre-DepositEthena ecosystem protocol Strata opens pre-deposits. The first phase of the campaign will accept two tokens, USDe and eUSDe, and depositing the corresponding funds will qualify users for Ethena rewards and Strata points. [F</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947908817592848384</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kled AI founder and Believe founder accuse each other, escalating the conflictBelieve ecosystem project Kled AI founder Avi Patel has expressed disappointment with the current handling of the Believe ecosystem, claiming a complete lack of support and communication. Believe founder Ben Pasternak accuses Avi of being a founder lacking integrity, alleging that Avi secretly sold $500,000.00 worth of KLED and lied that the sale was at Ben&apos;s direction. However, it is worth noting that yesterday, the official Believe Twitter account praised Kled for becoming a major data platform on Solana in just three months. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909407035166720</link>
      <description>19 minutes ago吴说Kled AI founder and Believe founder accuse each other, escalating the conflictBelieve ecosystem project Kled AI founder Avi Patel has expressed disappointment with the current handling of the Believe ecosystem, claiming a complete lack of support and communication. Believe founder Be</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909407035166720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backed.fi&apos;s xStocks on-chain trading volume exceeds $300 million.Backed.fi&apos;s tokenized U.S. stock product, xStocks, has surpassed $300.00M in on-chain trading volume within four weeks of launching on Bybit, Kraken, and the Solana decentralized finance (DeFi) platform, indicating growing demand for tokenized U.S. stocks. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947907675509035008</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoForesightNewsBacked.fi&apos;s xStocks on-chain trading volume exceeds $300 million.Backed.fi&apos;s tokenized U.S. stock product, xStocks, has surpassed $300.00M in on-chain trading volume within four weeks of launching on Bybit, Kraken, and the Solana decentralized finance (DeFi) platform, indi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947907675509035008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: The US economy has not declined as expected, and AI may be the main contributorAccording to foreign media analysis reports, for the second time in three years, concerns about a US economic recession have once again been refuted by reality. This time, the artificial intelligence (AI) boom may be the main contributor. As generative AI enters its third year, its financial impact is no longer limited to the stock prices of chip manufacturers. The surge in data center construction and overall capital expenditure is &quot;beautifying&quot; US GDP data in a surprising way. Carlyle Group&apos;s chief investment strategist Jason Thomas pointed out that this capital expenditure is an effective reindustrialization of American companies, shifting their focus from software and intangible assets to factories, machinery, and energy investments, which is unprecedented. This has a huge impact on GDP. Thomas estimates that AI-related spending alone may have contributed one-third of the US GDP growth in the second quarter of this year. And orders in related industries are still expanding at an annual growth rate of more than 40%. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909827807744000</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoOdailyInstitutions: The US economy has not declined as expected, and AI may be the main contributorAccording to foreign media analysis reports, for the second time in three years, concerns about a US economic recession have once again been refuted by reality. This time, the artificial</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947909827807744000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pi Coin Teases a Quick 40% Burst If This One EMA Cross ConfirmsPi Coin is steady around $0.47 after the “Buy Pi” fiat on‑ramp announcement kicked price up to $0.52; the first real push in days. Two technical signals on the lower timeframe hint this may not be a one-off bounce: trend strength is back, and a second moving‑average trigger is close. Trend Strength Returns, But Needs Confirmation The Average Directional Index (ADX) on the 4‑hour chart is back above 30. That tells us the price move has strength behind it, not just random sentiment. However, the current ADX peak is lower than the last one. In plain terms, the Pi Coin price trend is there, but it is not yet stronger than the previous swing. A new ADX high, or simply keeping ADX above the mid‑20s, would firm up confidence. The 4‑hour view is prioritized here because Tuesday’s jump happened inside the day; signals show up there first before the daily chart reacts. ADX measures how strong a trend is (0 to 100). It does not say up or down, so it must be read with price action. Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here . One EMA Trigger Still Pending The fast (20-period) Exponential Moving Average (EMA) has already crossed above the medium (50-period) EMA, and that lined up with the move from $0.45 to $0.52. The same thing happened in late June when the price ran from about $0.56 to $0.66. Back then, the fast EMA failed to clear the next slower (100-period) EMA, and the Pi Coin rally faded. That second cross is now getting close again, almost waiting to happen. If it happens this time while ADX stays firm, the odds of a bigger PI price rally improve. The 200‑period EMA (blue line) on the 4‑hour chart was briefly crossed by the price yesterday, before experiencing resistance. A clean close above it would match the price structure with momentum. EMAs weigh recent prices more than older ones, so when the shorter lines climb over the longer ones, it signals rising speed in the move. Key Pi Coin Price Levels to Watch The daily chart sets the main levels for the bigger picture. A trend‑based Fibonacci extension is used here. It links three points: the late‑June low at $0.47, the swing high near $0.66, and the mid‑July pullback to $0.42. Tuesday’s candle pushed through three Fibonacci bands in one day: 0.236 at $0.46, 0.382 at $0.49, and 0.5 at $0.51. PI Price is now pausing in the $0.46–$0.49 range. A daily close above that range opens $0.54 first (0.618) and then $0.66, the prior swing high, roughly 40% above current levels if momentum carries on and the much-awaited EMA cross finally happens. An inverted bullish hammer formed on the rebound (Tuesday candle), showing buyers stepped in near the lows. Invalidation is clear: a close back under $0.46, ADX dropping under the mid‑20s, and the 20-period EMA failing to clear the 100-period line would likely send Pi Coin’s price back toward $0.42.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947911621564764160</link>
      <description>24 minutes agobeincryptoPi Coin Teases a Quick 40% Burst If This One EMA Cross ConfirmsPi Coin is steady around $0.47 after the “Buy Pi” fiat on‑ramp announcement kicked price up to $0.52; the first real push in days. Two technical signals on the lower timeframe hint this may not be a one-off bounce</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947911621564764160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 0.61% in the past 1H, down 0.07% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947904108332539904</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,700According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 0.61% in the past 1H, down 0.07% in the last 24H. Now at $3,700.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947904108332539904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web3 AI engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB ChainSummary: According to official news, Web3 artificial intelligence engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB Chain. It is reported that Orbofi is an AI agent creation platform where users can easily create exclusive, multimodal, personalized, socialized, and tokenized agents. Previously, Orbofi AI completed $2.80M in financing through private placements and public token sales, with participation from Cogitent Ventures, OIG Capital, CSP DAO, Zephyrus Capital, and Halvings Capital, among others. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902359694282752</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoForesightNewsWeb3 AI engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB ChainSummary: According to official news, Web3 artificial intelligence engine Orbofi AI has been deployed to BNB Chain. It is reported that Orbofi is an AI agent creation platform where users can easily create exclusive, mu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902359694282752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DogeOS proposes to enable ZKP native verification capabilities on the Dogecoin network by introducing new opcodesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Dogecoin&apos;s ecological application development layer DogeOS officially submitted a technical proposal to Dogecoin Core, intending to implement zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) native verification function through a new opcode (OP_CHECKZKP). The upgrade will support off-chain applications such as Rollup and smart contracts, while maintaining the lightweight and high-speed characteristics of the main chain. The proposal adopts a modular design, and the first version supports Groth16 proof verification, and old version nodes can be compatible. To avoid performance risks, it is initially set that only one zero-knowledge proof (ZKP) can be used for each script and only five zero-knowledge proofs can be used for each block. DogeOS simultaneously develops a zk virtual machine compatible with EVM, allowing Ethereum native applications to run directly on Dogecoin infrastructure. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900229071736832</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoPANewsDogeOS proposes to enable ZKP native verification capabilities on the Dogecoin network by introducing new opcodesOn July 23, according to CoinDesk, Dogecoin&apos;s ecological application development layer DogeOS officially submitted a technical proposal to Dogecoin Core, intending to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900229071736832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merlin Founder: 2.0 Upgrade Officially Released, Aiming to Create &quot;Yield-Generating and Tradable&quot; BTCIn an exclusive interview with Odaily, Jeff, the founder of the Bitcoin Layer2 project Merlin Chain, stated that the Merlin 2.0 upgrade plan has been officially released. This version will focus on &quot;BTC&apos;s yield-generating and cross-chain trading capabilities,&quot; aiming to upgrade Bitcoin from a single store-of-value asset to an on-chain currency with profitability and liquidity. Jeff pointed out that Merlin Chain&apos;s core goals in the future will revolve around two directions: first, to enhance the practicality of BTC, making it available for multi-chain interaction, DeFi investment, and asset trading; and second, to lower the barriers for retail and institutional investors to enter the BTC ecosystem, so that BTC can not only outperform the market but also participate in new narratives and new projects, capturing higher potential returns. He also revealed that Merlin will continue to optimize the BTCfi ecosystem, expand AI-driven chain abstraction technology, and launch a series of user-friendly products in the next stage to promote BTC as a true &quot;universal currency&quot; on the chain. Click to read the original interview: &quot;Odaily Exclusive Interview with Merlin Founder Jeff: I Want to Give Up Every Day, But I Still Look Forward to Crossing the Cycle&quot; [Odaily].</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902272100438016</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoOdailyMerlin Founder: 2.0 Upgrade Officially Released, Aiming to Create &quot;Yield-Generating and Tradable&quot; BTCIn an exclusive interview with Odaily, Jeff, the founder of the Bitcoin Layer2 project Merlin Chain, stated that the Merlin 2.0 upgrade plan has been officially released. This ver</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902272100438016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-linked World Liberty Financial buys over 3,400 ETH for $13.00 million, onchain data showsWorld Liberty Financial, a crypto project linked to U.S. President Donald Trump, spent millions to acquire more Ethereum on Tuesday as the cryptocurrency sees surging institutional demand.

Citing Arkham Intelligence data, onchain researcher Lookonchain reported that World Liberty added 3,473 ETH at an average price of $3,743 across a number of wallets during Tuesday evening. It appears to have staked some of the newly acquired ether.

The project currently owns roughly 73,616 ETH, worth about $275.9 million at current market prices, according to Lookonchain.

World Liberty&apos;s move comes amid rising institutional demand for ether. On Tuesday, spot Ethereum exchange-traded funds recorded $533.9 million in net inflows, while spot bitcoin ETFs saw a net outflow of $67.9 million, according to SoSoValue data.

The Block&apos;s price page shows that ether remained flat in the past 24 hours at $3,729. However, the second-largest cryptocurrency rose 20% in the past week and 67.1% in the past 30 days.

Meanwhile, World Liberty is preparing for the upcoming unlock of its WLFI token. The team said last week that it is aiming to have WLFI to officially begin trading within the next two months.

&quot;We&apos;re targeting 6 to 8 weeks for the full awakening — strategic alignments (alliances, grand stages, smart unlocks) take time to realize full potential,&quot; the project said last week. [Lookonchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900415118479360</link>
      <description>52 minutes agoThe BlockTrump-linked World Liberty Financial buys over 3,400 ETH for $13.00 million, onchain data showsWorld Liberty Financial, a crypto project linked to U.S. President Donald Trump, spent millions to acquire more Ethereum on Tuesday as the cryptocurrency sees surging institutional d</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947900415118479360</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance Will Launch PENGU, CVX, and SLP Perpetual ContractsAccording to the official announcement, Binance Futures will launch PENGU/USDC, CVX/USDT, and SLP/USDT perpetual contracts successively on July 23, 2025, with up to 75x leverage. Among them, the PENGU/USDC contract will be launched at 7:30 (UTC), and the CVX/USDT and SLP/USDT contracts will be launched at 11:30 and 11:45 (UTC) respectively. (This news was generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902280547766272</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoOdailyBinance Will Launch PENGU, CVX, and SLP Perpetual ContractsAccording to the official announcement, Binance Futures will launch PENGU/USDC, CVX/USDT, and SLP/USDT perpetual contracts successively on July 23, 2025, with up to 75x leverage. Among them, the PENGU/USDC contract will b</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947902280547766272</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches Sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Event, Jointly Airdropping SYRUP with Maple FinanceBitget Wallet&apos;s sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event will officially start on July 23 at 21:00. This time, it will be jointly launched with Maple Finance to distribute a total of approximately 228,000 SYRUP tokens, with 120,000 participation slots available. This event features a special &quot;Super Lucky Koi Award,&quot; where one individual can win SYRUP worth $6,666.00.
&quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; is a brand airdrop event launched by Bitget Wallet. Users only need to stake $10.00 to participate, and the staked amount will be 100% returned afterward. Users can participate in the event through the Bitget Wallet App, explore on-chain staking gameplay, and receive airdrops. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899760412790784</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoOdailyBitget Wallet Launches Sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; Event, Jointly Airdropping SYRUP with Maple FinanceBitget Wallet&apos;s sixth &quot;FOMO Thursday&quot; event will officially start on July 23 at 21:00. This time, it will be jointly launched with Maple Finance to distribute a total of approximately</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 06:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899760412790784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polymarket forecasts a 67% probability that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot;According to Polymarket platform data, the probability of predicting that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot; has reached 67%, and the total prize pool is currently over $129,000.00. Prior news stated that Polymarket spent $112.00M to acquire the US compliant exchange QCX, and will legally return to the US market. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899768897867776</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoOdailyPolymarket forecasts a 67% probability that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot;According to Polymarket platform data, the probability of predicting that &quot;Polymarket US version will be launched in 2025&quot; has reached 67%, and the total prize pool is currently over $129,</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899768897867776</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance: At least 200 Alpha points users can claim 1,500 COA token airdropAccording to official sources, Binance will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23, 2025, at 17:00 (UTC+8). After trading begins, users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha points can claim an airdrop of 1,500 COA tokens. First come, first served. If the event has not ended, the score threshold will automatically decrease by 10 points every hour. Please note that claiming the airdrop will consume 15 Binance Alpha points. Users need to confirm the claim on the Alpha activity page within 24 hours, otherwise they will be deemed to have given up receiving the airdrop. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899777374556160</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBinance: At least 200 Alpha points users can claim 1,500 COA token airdropAccording to official sources, Binance will list Alliance Games (COA) on July 23, 2025, at 17:00 (UTC+8). After trading begins, users holding at least 200 Binance Alpha points can claim an airdrop of 1,500 COA</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899777374556160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Expects Trump administration to raise base tariff rate to 15%Goldman Sachs&apos; chief U.S. economist, David Mericle, expects the U.S.&apos;s base &quot;like-for-like&quot; tariff rate to increase from 10% to 15%, with tariffs on copper and critical minerals reaching 50% - a move that could exacerbate inflationary pressures and dampen economic growth. To reflect the new tariff assumptions and incorporate the impact of import tariffs in an &quot;initial observation,&quot; Goldman Sachs has adjusted its forecasts for U.S. inflation and GDP growth accordingly. Goldman Sachs lowered its core inflation forecast for 2025 from 3.4% to 3.3%, raised its 2026 forecast from 2.6% to 2.7%, and raised its 2027 forecast from 2.0% to 2.4%. Mericle said tariffs are expected to cumulatively push up core prices by 1.7% over 2-3 years. He added that tariffs would reduce GDP growth by 1 percentage point this year, 0.4 percentage points in 2026, and 0.3 percentage points in 2027. Goldman Sachs has accordingly lowered its GDP growth forecast for 2025 to 1.0%. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899785813495808</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyGoldman Sachs: Expects Trump administration to raise base tariff rate to 15%Goldman Sachs&apos; chief U.S. economist, David Mericle, expects the U.S.&apos;s base &quot;like-for-like&quot; tariff rate to increase from 10% to 15%, with tariffs on copper and critical minerals reaching 50% - a move that cou</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947899785813495808</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.5 billion.According to validatorqueue.com data, there are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.50 billion, which accounts for 29.50% of the circulating supply of Ethereum. Charts show that while the amount of ETH staked has recently decreased, it remains at a historical high. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947897233889890304</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyThere are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.5 billion.According to validatorqueue.com data, there are currently over 35.67 million ETH staked, worth approximately $132.50 billion, which accounts for 29.50% of the circulating supply of Ethereum. Charts</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 05:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947897233889890304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 06:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>