<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Voltage CEO: By 2028, Lightning Network may handle at least 5% of global stablecoin transactionsOn July 25, according to Cointelegraph, Graham Krizek, founder and CEO of Voltage, a Lightning Network payment service provider, said in an interview that with the popularity of the Layer 2 network, by 2028, the Lightning Network will handle at least 5% of the world&apos;s stablecoin transactions. He said that stablecoins will accelerate the popularity of the Lightning Network because it is the best expansion tool for stablecoins, and the network&apos;s stablecoin transactions may reach billions of dollars. At present, there are few stablecoin trading activities on the Lightning Network, but the situation may change soon. &quot;Stablecoins have just entered the Lightning Network, and major participants such as Tether have not yet been launched. The transaction volume accounts for almost zero, but it will grow in the second half of this year.&quot; Tether announced in January this year that it will launch USDT that supports the native Lightning Network. Changes may have begun since then. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948615208263553024</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoPANewsVoltage CEO: By 2028, Lightning Network may handle at least 5% of global stablecoin transactionsOn July 25, according to Cointelegraph, Graham Krizek, founder and CEO of Voltage, a Lightning Network payment service provider, said in an interview that with the popularity of the La</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948615208263553024</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Digital deposited another 2,850 BTC worth $330 million to major exchanges in the past 10 minutesOn July 25, according to on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, Galaxy Digital has recharged 2,850 BTC worth $330.00 million to major exchanges in the past 10 minutes. The cumulative number of BTC transferred to exchanges in the past 12 hours has increased to 17,123. Previously, 14,273 BTC suspected to be &quot;Fossil Hand Whale&quot; were recharged by Galaxy Digital to major exchanges in batches in the past 12 hours. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948615208376799232</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoPANewsGalaxy Digital deposited another 2,850 BTC worth $330 million to major exchanges in the past 10 minutesOn July 25, according to on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, Galaxy Digital has recharged 2,850 BTC worth $330.00 million to major exchanges in the past 10 minutes. The cumulative nu</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948615208376799232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 巨鲸 deposited 3.26 million USDC into HyperLiquid and opened multiple long positionsOn July 25, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited 3.26 million USDC into HyperLiquid and opened multiple long positions: BTC and SOL long positions with 20x leverage, and ETH and AAVE long positions with 10x leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948612687394574336</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsA 巨鲸 deposited 3.26 million USDC into HyperLiquid and opened multiple long positionsOn July 25, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited 3.26 million USDC into HyperLiquid and opened multiple long positions: BTC and SOL long positions with 20x leverage, and ETH and</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948612687394574336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ark Invest sold $12 million worth of Coinbase shares yesterdayJuly 25 news, according to CoinDesk, Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest sold $12.00 million worth of Coinbase (COIN) shares on Thursday, continuing its trend of cashing out profits from Coinbase investments. Ark Invest sold a total of 30,501 Coinbase shares from its two funds. In addition, Ark Invest also sold 11,262 Robinhood (HOOD) shares, worth about $1.10 million; and sold 123,169 Block Inc (XYZ) shares, worth about $10.00 million, and 28,906 shares of its own Bitcoin ETF (ARKB), worth about $1.10 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948607655999770624</link>
      <description>43 minutes agoPANewsArk Invest sold $12 million worth of Coinbase shares yesterdayJuly 25 news, according to CoinDesk, Cathie Wood&apos;s Ark Invest sold $12.00 million worth of Coinbase (COIN) shares on Thursday, continuing its trend of cashing out profits from Coinbase investments. Ark Invest sold a to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948607655999770624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fofund fund wealth management products under Hengfeng International are shut downAccording to Caixin.com, Fofund, a fund management product platform under Hengfeng International Web3 ecosystem FO-X (fo.com), issued a service change notice to investors on July 23, announcing the closure and refund of the fund management products &quot;Duo Duo No. 1&quot; and &quot;Duo Duo No. 2,&quot; managed by Fofund. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948605470880632832</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoForesightNewsFofund fund wealth management products under Hengfeng International are shut downAccording to Caixin.com, Fofund, a fund management product platform under Hengfeng International Web3 ecosystem FO-X (fo.com), issued a service change notice to investors on July 23, announcin</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948605470880632832</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the past 12 hours, 14,273 BTC suspected to be from a &quot;Fossil Hand Whale&quot; were recharged to major exchanges in batches by Galaxy Digital.On July 25, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, 14,273 BTC suspected to belong to the &quot;14-year BTC holder&quot; were recharged by Galaxy Digital in batches to major exchanges (about 1.67 billion US dollars) in the past 12 hours, of which 5,690 BTC were transferred in the past hour. Two sets of data show that this time there is a high probability that they are really selling: Binance BTC spot trading has traded more than 10,000 in 4 hours; Galaxy Digital has withdrawn some USDT from the exchange after recharging BTC. At noon today, Galaxy has withdrawn 200.00 million USDT from Binance and OKX, and then distributed 140.00 million of them to 5 new addresses. It should be that some of them are being sold and sorted out. At present, Galaxy still holds 33,763 BTC (about 3.90 billion US dollars) on the chain. Subsequently, the analyst released an update saying that the seven new addresses that received USDT should be Coinbase recharge addresses, and a total of 200.00 million USDT tokens have been recharged into hot wallets. It seems that the “Fossil Hand Whale” has chosen to settle at Coinbase. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948607656100433920</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoPANewsIn the past 12 hours, 14,273 BTC suspected to be from a &quot;Fossil Hand Whale&quot; were recharged to major exchanges in batches by Galaxy Digital.On July 25, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, 14,273 BTC suspected to belong to the &quot;14-year BTC holder&quot; were rec</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948607656100433920</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong’s OSL Group secures $300 million in equity funding to fuel global expansionHong Kong-based OSL Group has secured $300.00 million in equity financing to support its global expansion.

In a filing with the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, OSL said that it has entered into an equity purchase agreement to raise approximately HK$2,355.00 million ($300.00 million).

The company said it plans to use the proceeds to fuel global expansion through strategic acquisitions. OSL also intends to use the newly raised capital for the development of payment initiatives that integrate fiat currencies, stablecoins, and major cryptocurrencies.

&quot;This $300.00 million equity raise marks a major milestone in our journey and reflects strong conviction in OSL’s digital asset strategy and execution,&quot; said Ivan Wong, chief financial officer of OSL Group. &quot;The funding will accelerate our global buildout — particularly in regulated payment infrastructure and access points.&quot;

OSL&apos;s latest funding move comes as Hong Kong&apos;s new stablecoin licensing regime is expected to take effect on Aug. 1. The upcoming framework mandates licensing from the Hong Kong Monetary Authority for issuers of fiat-referenced stablecoins.

Global expansion appears to be at the forefront of OSL&apos;s agenda. Last month, OSL announced a $15.00 million deal to acquire Evergreen Crest, the operator of a cryptocurrency exchange in Indonesia. In February, the company completed its acquisition of the Japanese crypto exchange CoinBest and renamed it OSL Japan.

OSL&apos;s stock fell 7.40% in Hong Kongas of Friday, according to Yahoo Financedata, with the market still open. The stock, however, has risen 14.00% over the past month and 104.00% year-to-date.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948603849815691264</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoThe BlockHong Kong’s OSL Group secures $300 million in equity funding to fuel global expansionHong Kong-based OSL Group has secured $300.00 million in equity financing to support its global expansion.

In a filing with the Hong Kong Stock Exchange, OSL said that it has entered into an</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948603849815691264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Galaxy Digital withdrew 200.00M USDT from Binance and OKX, and still holds 33,800 BTC on-chain.According to on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa)&apos;s monitoring, Galaxy Digital has withdrawn 200.00M USDT from Binance and OKX in the past 13 minutes, and distributed 140.00M of them to 5 new addresses. Currently, Galaxy still holds 33,763 BTC on-chain, worth approximately $3.90B. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948603137492848640</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoChainCatcherData: Galaxy Digital withdrew 200.00M USDT from Binance and OKX, and still holds 33,800 BTC on-chain.According to on-chain analyst AI Auntie (@ai_9684xtpa)&apos;s monitoring, Galaxy Digital has withdrawn 200.00M USDT from Binance and OKX in the past 13 minutes, and distributed 1</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948603137492848640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC, suspected to belong to a &quot;whale holding BTC for 14 years,&quot; was deposited in batches into various exchanges by Galaxy Digital in the past 12 hours, with a value of approximately $1.67B.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, 14,273 BTC, suspected to belong to a &quot;BTC whale holding for 14 years,&quot; were recharged into various exchanges in batches by Galaxy Digital in the past 12 hours, worth approximately $1.67B, of which 5,690 BTC were transferred in the past 1 hour alone. The two sets of data show that this is likely a real sell-off. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948600115597479936</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBTC, suspected to belong to a &quot;whale holding BTC for 14 years,&quot; was deposited in batches into various exchanges by Galaxy Digital in the past 12 hours, with a value of approximately $1.67B.According to @ai_9684xtpa monitoring, 14,273 BTC, suspected to belong to a &quot;BTC whale ho</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948600115597479936</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOO X: The attack was caused by a phishing attack on a team member&apos;s device, which gave the attacker access to the development environmentOn July 25, cryptocurrency trading platform WOO X released an update on the X platform saying that the attack originated from a team member&apos;s device being hacked in a targeted phishing attack, allowing the attacker to access the development environment. Although multiple security measures restricted access rights, it still gave the attacker time to coordinate a series of withdrawal operations from the user account mentioned in the previous message. The team is conducting a comprehensive forensic review and is prioritizing the reopening of withdrawal services for all users. Once the relevant work is completed, the progress will be updated here immediately. Previously, WOO X said that the attack has caused a loss of $14.00 million and promised to fully compensate the affected users. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948595074769686528</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsWOO X: The attack was caused by a phishing attack on a team member&apos;s device, which gave the attacker access to the development environmentOn July 25, cryptocurrency trading platform WOO X released an update on the X platform saying that the attack originated from a team member&apos;s devi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948595074769686528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net inflow of 226.61M USD yesterday, with none of the twelve ETFs experiencing a net outflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net inflow of 226.61M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 24th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net inflow yesterday was Fidelity&apos;s ETF FBTC, with a daily net inflow of 106.58M USD, and the total historical net inflow of FBTC currently stands at 12.43B USD.The second highest was VanEck&apos;s ETF HODL, with a daily net inflow of 46.36M USD, and the total historical net inflow of HODL currently stands at 1.12B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 154.45B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.54%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.69B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948591611410731008</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net inflow of 226.61M USD yesterday, with none of the twelve ETFs experiencing a net outflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net inflow of 226.61M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 24th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the hig</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948591611410731008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoSoMacro|U.S. Mixed PMI Data Signals Fed Caution as Trump Pressures PowellU.S. releases July Markit PMI; ECB holds rates as expected; U.S.-Japan trade deal details emerge; Trump continues pressuring Powell.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948591521046949888</link>
      <description>1 hour agoSoSoValueSoSoMacro|U.S. Mixed PMI Data Signals Fed Caution as Trump Pressures PowellU.S. releases July Markit PMI; ECB holds rates as expected; U.S.-Japan trade deal details emerge; Trump continues pressuring Powell.#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948591521046949888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea&apos;s KB Kookmin Bank Applies for Trademarks Related to USD and JPY StablecoinsAccording to the Korea Economic Daily, KB Kookmin Bank recently applied for 27 trademarks related to USD and JPY stablecoins, including &quot;KBUSD&quot; and &quot;JPYKB,&quot; for a total of 49 trademark rights, covering categories such as stablecoin electronic financial platform software. Previously, KB Kookmin Bank applied for trademarks related to KRW stablecoins last month, and its current layout has expanded to the USD and JPY fields, intending to seize the trademark rights for foreign currency stablecoins. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948589097920040960</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说South Korea&apos;s KB Kookmin Bank Applies for Trademarks Related to USD and JPY StablecoinsAccording to the Korea Economic Daily, KB Kookmin Bank recently applied for 27 trademarks related to USD and JPY stablecoins, including &quot;KBUSD&quot; and &quot;JPYKB,&quot; for a total of 49 trademark rights, covering</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948589097920040960</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Drop: BTC is now at $115,557According to SoSoValue, BTC (Bitcoin) is down 3.01% in the past 24h. Now at $115,557.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948587159110770688</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Drop: BTC is now at $115,557According to SoSoValue, BTC (Bitcoin) is down 3.01% in the past 24h. Now at $115,557.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948587159110770688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: SOL -7.17%, HYPE -6.33%, HBAR -5.19%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948586886216769536</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSSI Price BotssiLayer1 index 24hr loss of 3.03%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiLayer1 has fallen by 3.03% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: SOL -7.17%, HYPE -6.33%, HBAR -5.19%.$SOL$HBAR$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948586886216769536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,600According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 2.27% in the past 1H, down 1.72% in the last 24H. Now at $3,600.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948586865031340032</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,600According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 2.27% in the past 1H, down 1.72% in the last 24H. Now at $3,600.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948586865031340032</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manta: RPC endpoint communication issue resolved, user funds not affectedModular L2 Manta Network tweeted that Manta Atlantic experienced a brief issue communicating with RPC endpoints, which has now been resolved. Network activity was not interrupted, and user wallets or funds were not affected. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948584396335943680</link>
      <description>2 hours agoForesightNewsManta: RPC endpoint communication issue resolved, user funds not affectedModular L2 Manta Network tweeted that Manta Atlantic experienced a brief issue communicating with RPC endpoints, which has now been resolved. Network activity was not interrupted, and user wallets or fun</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948584396335943680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTC is now at $116,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 1.14% in the past 1H, down 2.60% in the last 24H. Now at $116,000.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948580548896055296</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotBTC is now at $116,000According to SoSoValue, BTC(Bitcoin) is down 1.14% in the past 1H, down 2.60% in the last 24H. Now at $116,000.$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948580548896055296</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch LMEOW, ASP, and LN spot trading and SLP contract trading.On July 25, according to official news, Hotcoin will launch the following trading pairs on July 25:
Spot trading pairs
LMEOW/USDT (July 25 12:00 UTC+8): $LMEOW is the native token of the LMEOW project.
ASP/USDT (July 25 12:00 UTC+8): $ASP is the native token of the Aspecta project. Aspecta fills a fundamental gap in capital markets: early-stage or locked assets often enter the public market without transparent pricing, creating volatility and distrust.
LN/USDT (July 25 18:20 UTC+8): $LN is the native token of the LNFI Network project. Lnfi Network unlocks multi-asset DeFi on the Lightning Network through next-generation financial infrastructure, enabling users to trade, earn, and manage Bitcoin, Taproot assets, and RGB assets through LightningFi.
Contract trading pairs
SLP/USDT (July 25 12:00 UTC+8): $SLP is a contract transaction for the Smooth Love Potion project, with a maximum leverage of 25x. Play the Axie Infinity game to earn Smooth Love Potion (SLP) tokens. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948576502173470720</link>
      <description>2 hours agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch LMEOW, ASP, and LN spot trading and SLP contract trading.On July 25, according to official news, Hotcoin will launch the following trading pairs on July 25:
Spot trading pairs
LMEOW/USDT (July 25 12:00 UTC+8): $LMEOW is the native token of the L</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948576502173470720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.01%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.01% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -7.57%, MNT -6.42%, HYPE -6.11%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948575843977486336</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSSI Price BotssiCeFi index 24hr loss of 3.01%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiCeFi has fallen by 3.01% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: WOO -7.57%, MNT -6.42%, HYPE -6.11%.$WOO$MNT$HYPEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948575843977486336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>