<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:15:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean authorities tell asset managers to limit exposure to Coinbase, Strategy: reportSouth Korea&apos;s Financial Supervisory Service (FSS) recently instructed local asset management firms to adjust their exchange-traded funds to limit exposure to crypto-related companies such as Coinbase and Strategy, a report from The Korea Herald said.The Korea Herald reported Wednesday that the FSS gave such directions verbally to a number of companies earlier this month. The regulator reportedly said that asset managers need to comply with the Financial Services Commission&apos;s (FSC) administrative guidelines issued in 2017, which prohibit regulated financial institutions from holding, purchasing, or making equity investments in virtual assets.The report stated that this directive from the local regulator sparked complaints among domestic financial players, who argue it creates an uneven playing field, as retail investors can access U.S. ETFs with exposure to crypto companies.An FSS official reportedly said that institutions need to abide by the existing guidelines until the adoption of new regulations, even if there are regulatory changes being made in the U.S. and in South Korea.The FSS regulates the country&apos;s financial sector, focusing on practical, day-to-day oversight of various financial entities. It acts as the executive arm of the FSC, South Korea&apos;s top financial regulator.Since the U.S. government shifted to a friendlier stance to crypto under President Donald Trump, South Korea has been discussing similar measures to ease some of its strict regulations on crypto and institutional involvement.Earlier this year, the country began to phase out its de facto ban on institutional trading. The election of pro-crypto President Lee Jae Myung accelerated the paradigm shift, as Lee pushes to enable the local issuance and launch of spot crypto ETFs and strengthen the Korean won market with local currency-based stablecoins.South Korea houses one of the largest crypto markets in the world, with its retail investors known for their altcoin-heavy trading strategies. As of the end of last year, South Korea had 18.25 million crypto investors, according to the Bank of Korea. [The Korea Herald]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947871321286840320</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoThe BlockSouth Korean authorities tell asset managers to limit exposure to Coinbase, Strategy: reportSouth Korea&apos;s Financial Supervisory Service (FSS) recently instructed local asset management firms to adjust their exchange-traded funds to limit exposure to crypto-related companies suc</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947871321286840320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMG Blockchain Solutions Plans to Establish a Diverse Digital Asset Treasury Including BTCPublicly listed Bitcoin mining company DMG Blockchain Solutions has announced that it is evaluating the institutional-grade fund management strategy of its subsidiary, Systemic Trust Company, with a view to establishing a diversified digital asset treasury. Currently, the company&apos;s digital asset portfolio consists only of Bitcoin. It has now begun to assess the possibility of using existing mining revenue and additional raised funds to acquire digital assets other than Bitcoin. According to BitcoinTreasuries data, DMG Blockchain Solutions currently holds approximately 341 Bitcoins, ranking 54th among publicly listed Bitcoin holding companies. (Globenewswire) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947872059555647488</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoOdailyDMG Blockchain Solutions Plans to Establish a Diverse Digital Asset Treasury Including BTCPublicly listed Bitcoin mining company DMG Blockchain Solutions has announced that it is evaluating the institutional-grade fund management strategy of its subsidiary, Systemic Trust Company</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947872059555647488</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three wallets suspected to be owned by a whale transferred out a total of 10,606 BTC after being dormant for three yearsOn July 23, according to Lookonchain monitoring, three wallets (possibly belonging to the same whale) had just transferred out 10,606 BTC (US$126.00 million) after being idle for 3-5 years. All 3 wallets received BTC on December 13, 2020, when the price of BTC was $18,807.00. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869910515912704</link>
      <description>12 minutes agoPANewsThree wallets suspected to be owned by a whale transferred out a total of 10,606 BTC after being dormant for three yearsOn July 23, according to Lookonchain monitoring, three wallets (possibly belonging to the same whale) had just transferred out 10,606 BTC (US$126.00 million) af</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869910515912704</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binance VIP Borrowing adds KAIA, LA, C, ERA as loanable assets, and adds EURI as collateral assetOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Binance VIP lending has added KAIA, LA, C, and ERA borrowable assets, and added EURI collateral assets. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869706366554112</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsBinance VIP Borrowing adds KAIA, LA, C, ERA as loanable assets, and adds EURI as collateral assetOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Binance VIP lending has added KAIA, LA, C, and ERA borrowable assets, and added EURI collateral assets. [PANews]$ERA$C$KAIAShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947869706366554112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX Hearing: Creditors in restricted jurisdictions may choose to transfer their claims to non-restricted jurisdictions for claimsOn July 23, FTX Historian, an account that tracks FTX&apos;s bankruptcy and compensation, summarized the key points of last night&apos;s hearing: Previously, if a creditor was in a &quot;restricted jurisdiction&quot; (such as China or Russia), his funds would be immediately confiscated according to the initial proposal of FTX&apos;s asset recovery party. Now the situation has changed, and creditors may be able to transfer their claims to non-restricted countries. The initial motion was &quot;If the creditor is in a restricted jurisdiction, his claims or compensation will be immediately confiscated&quot;, and the updated motion is expected to limit or delete this clause. Creditors can move to non-restricted areas (such as from China to Singapore and the UAE) and receive a distribution of funds, and the jurisdiction can be changed before the distribution. Affected creditors (such as those who have completed KYC in China but live in other countries) may be able to recover their funds through this, but they need to update information and seize the opportunity. In addition, the hearing reduced the risk of debt buyers, and they are likely to increase their bids. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947868718134005760</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoPANewsFTX Hearing: Creditors in restricted jurisdictions may choose to transfer their claims to non-restricted jurisdictions for claimsOn July 23, FTX Historian, an account that tracks FTX&apos;s bankruptcy and compensation, summarized the key points of last night&apos;s hearing: Previously, if</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947868718134005760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Espresso to Launch First Community Initial Offering via Kaito Capital LaunchpadThe Espresso Foundation has partnered with Kaito to launch its first community initial offering through the Kaito Capital Launchpad platform. The Espresso Foundation will sell $4.00M worth of ESP tokens, with subscription prices lower than Espresso&apos;s latest $600.00M valuation. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947866541483167744</link>
      <description>26 minutes agoForesightNewsEspresso to Launch First Community Initial Offering via Kaito Capital LaunchpadThe Espresso Foundation has partnered with Kaito to launch its first community initial offering through the Kaito Capital Launchpad platform. The Espresso Foundation will sell $4.00M worth of ES</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947866541483167744</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday, with only Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC achieving a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 22th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net inflow yesterday was Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC, with a daily net inflow of 7.51M USD, and the total historical net outflow of GBTC currently stands at 23.54B USD.The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the highest net outflow yesterday was Bitwise&apos;s ETF BITB, with a daily net outflow of 42.27M USD, and the total historical net inflow of BITB currently stands at 2.28B USD.As of the time of publication, the total net asset value of Bitcoin Spot ETFs is 154.77B USD, with an ETF net asset ratio (market capitalization relative to the total Bitcoin market cap) of 6.5%. The historical cumulative net inflow has reached 54.55B USD.Source: https://sosovalue.com/zh/assets/etf/us-btc-spot</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865801859092480</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoSoSo ETF TrackerBitcoin Spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday, with only Grayscale&apos;s ETF GBTC achieving a net inflowAccording to SoSoValue data, Bitcoin spot ETF saw a total net outflow of 67.93M USD yesterday (Eastern Time, July 22th).The Bitcoin Spot ETF with the h</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865801859092480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development: Stablecoins will form a new interconnected model with fiat currenciesLi Yang, Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development, recently analyzed stablecoins from five perspectives at a seminar on &quot;The Development Prospects of RMB Stablecoins&quot;: He pointed out that stablecoins are not real currencies, but rather intermediary tools for payment and clearing driven by technology, which will form a new interconnected model with legal tender; he emphasized that sovereign currency is irreplaceable, and stablecoins cannot bypass exchange and the national right to issue currency; he believes that technological innovation should not challenge national monetary sovereignty, but should coordinate and evolve with central bank digital currencies and private payment systems; he suggested promoting the internationalization of the RMB, both internally and externally, exploring the development path of onshore and offshore RMB stablecoins, and establishing a fusion mechanism with digital RMB and the central bank custody system to guide stablecoins and legal tender to jointly build the future payment landscape. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865054979887104</link>
      <description>32 minutes ago吴说Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development: Stablecoins will form a new interconnected model with fiat currenciesLi Yang, Chairman of the National Institution for Finance and Development, recently analyzed stablecoins from five perspectives at a seminar on &quot;The</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947865054979887104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lotte Card applies for trademark rights related to Korean won stablecoinOn July 23, according to Yonhap News Agency, Lotte Card has applied for a total of 36 trademark rights related to the Korean won stablecoin. Lotte Card explained that in addition to applying for trademark rights around &quot;token symbols&quot;, it also simultaneously registered &quot;brand name trademark rights&quot; mainly expressed in Korean. The Korean Intellectual Property Information Retrieval System shows that Lotte Card has applied for 12 brand name trademarks such as &quot;WONBIT&quot;, &quot;KTOKEN&quot;, and &quot;LOCAMONEY&quot;, as well as 24 token symbol trademarks such as &quot;WONBIT&quot;, &quot;KTOKEN&quot;, and &quot;LOCAMONEY&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863899616907264</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsLotte Card applies for trademark rights related to Korean won stablecoinOn July 23, according to Yonhap News Agency, Lotte Card has applied for a total of 36 trademark rights related to the Korean won stablecoin. Lotte Card explained that in addition to applying for trademark rig</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863899616907264</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Official: State Should Confiscate Crypto from Illegal MinersAccording to Cryptonews, Yevgeny Masharov, a member of the Russian Public Chamber and a policymaker, said that authorities should be given the power to confiscate cryptocurrencies from illegal or quasi-legal Bitcoin miners. Masharov believes that this proposal will deter &quot;gray&quot; miners by &quot;making illegal mining unprofitable.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863746390593536</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoForesightNewsRussian Official: State Should Confiscate Crypto from Illegal MinersAccording to Cryptonews, Yevgeny Masharov, a member of the Russian Public Chamber and a policymaker, said that authorities should be given the power to confiscate cryptocurrencies from illegal or quasi-leg</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947863746390593536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: 31.6% of PUMP pre-sale buyers have sold on DEX, and 53.0% have been transferred to new walletsOn July 23, according to Spot On Chain statistics, among the 10,145 successful pre-sale buyers of PUMP tokens, 12.7% still hold them; 31.6% have been sold on DEX; only 2.7% of users choose to increase their positions; the remaining 53.0% transferred tokens to new wallets (including those who deposited them on CEX for sale). In addition, the largest buyer who spent $100.0 million to purchase 25.00 billion PUMPs in the pre-sale has now recharged 17.10 billion ($89.5 million) tokens to CEX through FalconX, and currently holds 7.99 billion ($29.5 million). Expected profit, $19.0 million. The largest buyer of PUMP spent $50.0 million to purchase 12.50 billion PUMP and has deposited all tokens ($71.4 million) into CEX. Estimated profit: $21.4 million (+43.0%). [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862326023098368</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoPANewsData: 31.6% of PUMP pre-sale buyers have sold on DEX, and 53.0% have been transferred to new walletsOn July 23, according to Spot On Chain statistics, among the 10,145 successful pre-sale buyers of PUMP tokens, 12.7% still hold them; 31.6% have been sold on DEX; only 2.7% of user</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862326023098368</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTX Hearing Minutes: Allowing Creditors in Restricted Jurisdictions to Transfer Claims to Non-Restricted JurisdictionsThe account FTX Historian, which tracks FTX bankruptcy and compensation, posted a summary of last night&apos;s FTX hearing minutes on X. The core content of the hearing was: For creditors in &quot;restricted jurisdictions&quot; (such as China), their funds will not be immediately confiscated as proposed in the original FTX recovery plan, but creditors will be allowed to transfer to non-restricted jurisdictions. FTX Historian added that for affected creditors, such as those who completed KYC in China but now reside in other jurisdictions such as Singapore, this may be a way to realize claims, although it may require further information updates and more time costs. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862523511902208</link>
      <description>42 minutes agoForesightNewsFTX Hearing Minutes: Allowing Creditors in Restricted Jurisdictions to Transfer Claims to Non-Restricted JurisdictionsThe account FTX Historian, which tracks FTX bankruptcy and compensation, posted a summary of last night&apos;s FTX hearing minutes on X. The core content of the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862523511902208</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEX Exchange Will List LIMO and MIU Spot TradingOn July 23, according to an announcement by WEEX Exchange, the platform will launch spot trading for Limoverse (LIMO) and MIU coin (MIU) on July 24 at 16:00 (UTC+8). In addition, WEEX recently officially launched spot trading for Opulous (OPUL), The Nation Token (NATO), peaq (PEAQ), Yala (YALA), and ZKWASM (ZKWASM). Limoverse is a comprehensive blockchain-based health and wellness ecosystem that rewards individuals for maintaining healthy lifestyles through its utility token LIMO. MIU is a Meme cat coin on the Sui Network. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947861743694319616</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoTechFlowWEEX Exchange Will List LIMO and MIU Spot TradingOn July 23, according to an announcement by WEEX Exchange, the platform will launch spot trading for Limoverse (LIMO) and MIU coin (MIU) on July 24 at 16:00 (UTC+8). In addition, WEEX recently officially launched spot trading for</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947861743694319616</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyst: Bitcoin Unlikely to Reach $200,000 in the Short TermOn July 23, Cointelegraph reported that Glassnode&apos;s chief analyst, James Check, said that Bitcoin reaching $200,000.00 this year is &quot;highly unlikely&quot; due to insufficient trading volume, but he expects it will definitely break this price level within five years. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947861280185978880</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoTechFlowAnalyst: Bitcoin Unlikely to Reach $200,000 in the Short TermOn July 23, Cointelegraph reported that Glassnode&apos;s chief analyst, James Check, said that Bitcoin reaching $200,000.00 this year is &quot;highly unlikely&quot; due to insufficient trading volume, but he expects it will definite</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947861280185978880</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The UK may ban its public sector from paying ransomware.The UK released a proposal on July 22 to ban its public sector (such as healthcare services and local councils) from paying ransomware. The proposal requires victims to submit a report to the government containing key details within 72 hours of an attack, and a more in-depth analysis within 28 days. Ransomware typically demands ransom payments in cryptocurrency. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947860642597244928</link>
      <description>49 minutes agoForesightNewsThe UK may ban its public sector from paying ransomware.The UK released a proposal on July 22 to ban its public sector (such as healthcare services and local councils) from paying ransomware. The proposal requires victims to submit a report to the government containing key</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947860642597244928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10K Announces Project Failure, Airdrops Over $2.30M in Tokens to Presale UsersWatch-to-earn project 10kdotworld has announced that the project has failed due to presale pressure, bot abuse, and creator access issues. The project team stated that it has used the WATCHCOIN vault, which was originally intended for incentives, to airdrop WATCHCOIN tokens worth over $2.30M to presale participants. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862263276310528</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdaily10K Announces Project Failure, Airdrops Over $2.30M in Tokens to Presale UsersWatch-to-earn project 10kdotworld has announced that the project has failed due to presale pressure, bot abuse, and creator access issues. The project team stated that it has used the WATCHCOIN vault, which</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862263276310528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX &quot;ETH 50% Off Carnival&quot; event goes live for 15 hours, with the number of participants exceeding 43,000.According to official OKX data, within 15 hours of the launch of the &quot;ETH 50% Off Carnival&quot; event, 43,916 people have participated, a total of 5,156 treasure boxes have been opened, and 151 new users have received interest rate hike coupons with an annualized rate of 26.08%. This event is one of OKX&apos;s 50% off coin purchase series and coincides with the tenth anniversary of Ethereum. During the event, users have the opportunity to win 0.5 ETH rewards for every 1 ETH traded, with a maximum of 10 participations per person; new users can receive an interest rate hike coupon with an annualized rate of 26.08% for their first transaction of 100 USDT or more; they can also receive 100 USDT contract experience bonus by publishing the event content and successfully inviting 1 new user to trade. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862156845846528</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyOKX &quot;ETH 50% Off Carnival&quot; event goes live for 15 hours, with the number of participants exceeding 43,000.According to official OKX data, within 15 hours of the launch of the &quot;ETH 50% Off Carnival&quot; event, 43,916 people have participated, a total of 5,156 treasure boxes have been open</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862156845846528</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ping An Securities: Hong Kong May Adopt Dual-Track Regulation for StablecoinsAccording to Hong Kong Wenhui Net, Ping An Securities released a report pointing out that Hong Kong is accelerating the promotion of stablecoin regulation and application, forming a &quot;USD stablecoin connecting to the international market, HKD stablecoin connecting to the mainland&quot; dual-track regulatory pattern, which not only strengthens the financial attributes of the HKD, but also provides experimental space for the internationalization of the RMB. The report mentioned that the Hong Kong &quot;Stablecoin Ordinance&quot; has clearly defined the regulatory scope of &quot;specified stablecoins,&quot; and guides institutions to test compliance solutions in scenarios such as HKD stablecoin cross-border payments and embedded financial products through regulatory sandboxes and stress testing mechanisms. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862153242939392</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Ping An Securities: Hong Kong May Adopt Dual-Track Regulation for StablecoinsAccording to Hong Kong Wenhui Net, Ping An Securities released a report pointing out that Hong Kong is accelerating the promotion of stablecoin regulation and application, forming a &quot;USD stablecoin connecting to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862153242939392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean blockchain infrastructure provider DSRV completes approximately $11.60M Series B first round of fundingKorean blockchain infrastructure service provider DSRV announced the completion of its Series B first round of financing, raising approximately 16.00 billion South Korean won (approximately $11.60 million USD). This round of financing was participated in by mainstream Korean investment institutions such as Intervest and NH-SK Securities. The second round of financing is expected to start at the end of next month, at which time more financial institutions will join. DSRV currently provides node and infrastructure services for more than 70 blockchain networks worldwide, managing assets of more than 4.00 trillion South Korean won. The company&apos;s sales in 2023 reached 10.70 billion South Korean won, with a net profit of 3.00 billion South Korean won. In the future, it will focus on expanding new business areas such as stablecoins and custody, and accelerate its global expansion plans in the United States, Japan, Africa and other regions. (edaily) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862162441048064</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailySouth Korean blockchain infrastructure provider DSRV completes approximately $11.60M Series B first round of fundingKorean blockchain infrastructure service provider DSRV announced the completion of its Series B first round of financing, raising approximately 16.00 billion South Kore</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862162441048064</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet Launches $50,000 KOKOK Trading Event to Support Solana Meme Ecosystem DevelopmentBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a KOKOK trading event with a total prize pool of $50,000.00, running from July 22nd to July 29th. Rewards will be distributed based on users&apos; total KOKOK trading volume, with higher trading volumes earning more rewards. The top 10 traders will also share an exclusive prize pool. Participants can also receive additional lottery tickets for the weekly FOMO Thursdays staking event. KOKOK is one of the fastest-growing meme coins in the Solana ecosystem recently. According to on-chain data, the total market capitalization of Solana meme coins has exceeded $14.00B, and daily protocol fees on platforms such as Bonk.fun exceed $1.00M. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862168682172416</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBitget Wallet Launches $50,000 KOKOK Trading Event to Support Solana Meme Ecosystem DevelopmentBitget Wallet has announced the launch of a KOKOK trading event with a total prize pool of $50,000.00, running from July 22nd to July 29th. Rewards will be distributed based on users&apos; total</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947862168682172416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>