<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:17:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +5.5%, ADA +5.06%, DOGE +5.03%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932904691982336</link>
      <description>18 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr gain of 3.00%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has risen by 3.00% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ETH +5.5%, ADA +5.06%, DOGE +5.03%.$ETH$ADA$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932904691982336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US pension fund OPERS increased its holdings of Palantir and MicroStrategy in the second quarterOne of the largest public pension funds in the United States, OPERS (Ohio Public Employees Retirement System), revealed in its 13F filing for the second quarter of 2025 that it increased its holdings in Palantir by 171,441 shares and Strategy by 21,499 shares, while reducing its holdings in Lyft by 58,881 shares. As of June 30, it held a total of 908,712 shares of Palantir, 101,880 shares of Strategy, and 166,628 shares of Lyft. [Barron&apos;s]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932792012005376</link>
      <description>19 minutes ago吴说US pension fund OPERS increased its holdings of Palantir and MicroStrategy in the second quarterOne of the largest public pension funds in the United States, OPERS (Ohio Public Employees Retirement System), revealed in its 13F filing for the second quarter of 2025 that it increased i</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946932792012005376</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum stablecoin USDe supply returns to 6 billion after early FebruaryAccording to the @EntropyAdvisors data panel, as the sUSDe APR reached 10%, the supply of Ethereum stablecoin USDe returned to 6 billion after early February. On July 17, the net minting volume of USDe on a single day reached $267.00 million, the third highest single day in history, and the net minting volume exceeded $160.00 million in the following two days. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946931162306797568</link>
      <description>25 minutes ago吴说Ethereum stablecoin USDe supply returns to 6 billion after early FebruaryAccording to the @EntropyAdvisors data panel, as the sUSDe APR reached 10%, the supply of Ethereum stablecoin USDe returned to 6 billion after early February. On July 17, the net minting volume of USDe on a sing</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946931162306797568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDC Treasury Burned 60,000,000 USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, the USDC Treasury destroyed 60,000,000 USDC on the Ethereum chain approximately five minutes ago. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946930867765993472</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoOdailyUSDC Treasury Burned 60,000,000 USDC on EthereumAccording to Whale Alert monitoring, the USDC Treasury destroyed 60,000,000 USDC on the Ethereum chain approximately five minutes ago. [Odaily Planet Daily News]#DeFi$USDC$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946930867765993472</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba says he will continue to governLocal time on the 20th, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba expressed his desire to continue governing. Ishiba stated, &quot;We must be clearly aware of the responsibility we bear to the country and the mission of being the largest party in the Diet. I will continue to fulfill my duties.&quot; The latest exit poll results released by Japanese media on the 20th show that the ruling coalition formed by the Liberal Democratic Party and the Komeito Party will find it difficult to maintain a majority of seats in the House of Councillors. According to previous news, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba stated that he would resolve the US tariff issue before the deadline of August 1st. (Golden Ten Data APP) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946928343470268416</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdailyJapanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba says he will continue to governLocal time on the 20th, Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba expressed his desire to continue governing. Ishiba stated, &quot;We must be clearly aware of the responsibility we bear to the country and the mission o</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946928343470268416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale spent 50.000 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours agoOn July 20, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale spent 50 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours ago, with an average purchase price of US$3,715. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946927948110426112</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoPANewsA whale spent 50.000 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours agoOn July 20, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a whale spent 50 million USDT to buy 13,462 ETH four hours ago, with an average purchase price of US$3,715. [PANews]#Layer1$ETH$MAG7.SSI$USDTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946927948110426112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Hot Project Updates: WLFI token to open for trading, Aave TVL exceeds 50 billion, Ondo Finance announces acceleration of full-stack RWA platform development, etc. (0713–0719)1. World Liberty Financial Community Vote Passes WLFI Token Open Trading Proposal linkWorld Liberty Financial released a proposal on July 9, suggesting opening WLFI token trading. The voting started on July 10 and ended on July 17, and it was finally passed with a 99.94% approval rate. The proposal aims to promote the transition of WLFI from a closed ecosystem to an open ecosystem, allowing tokens to be traded through peer-to-peer and secondary markets, thereby expanding the community&apos;s participation channels in the governance process.2. Aave TVL Exceeds $50 Billion for the First Time in History linkAave TVL exceeded $50 billion for the first time in history, with a growth of 13.93% in the past 7 days, continuing to consolidate its position as the DeFi protocol with the largest TVL. Currently, the overall DeFi TVL reaches $2,843.9 billion, further moving towards the previous high (slightly above $3,000 billion).3. Eclipse Announces Tokenomics: 15% for Airdrops and Liquidity linkEthereum SVM Layer2 network Eclipse announced its tokenomics. The total amount of ES tokens is 1 billion. Among them: 15% is used for airdrops + liquidity; 35% is used for ecosystem + development; 19% is given to contributors (current and future); 31% is given to early supporters/investors. ES tokens can be used as Gas tokens for the Eclipse chain through Eclipse&apos;s native payment mechanism.4. Pudgy Penguins Announces Cooperation with Chinese Toy Company Suplay linkPudgy Penguins announced a cooperation with Chinese toy company Suplay. The specific cooperation content will be announced later. According to public information, Suplay was established at the end of 2019 and is a trendy consumer goods company covering the entire industry chain of IP and channels. It has signed cooperation agreements with IP in various fields such as the Palace Museum Culture, Sanrio, Genshin Impact, and Disney. In early 2021, Suplay received millions of US dollars in Series A financing from Jixiang Capital. In October 2021, it received tens of millions of US dollars in Series A+ financing led by miHoYo.Previously, Alex, the former Binance community leader, announced that he had officially joined Coinbase as the head of crypto Twitter (CT) communication. In the future, he will be committed to promoting more direct, transparent, and interactive communication on social platforms to improve external perception and strengthen connections with the community. At the same time, Coinbase has changed its Twitter avatar to Pengu NFT.5. Kaito AI May Launch Project Launch Platform Capital Launchpad linkKaito AI tweeted, &quot;Capital Launchpad loading…&quot; Kaito official 0xWenMoon said that Capital Launchpad is not a Meme token issuance platform, but a chain-based crypto angel investment platform similar to Echo, which may support investors in participating in early high-potential crypto projects. Since Capital Launchpad is currently in the pre-release stage, the specific details are not yet clear. The community speculates that Capital Launchpad will allow KAITO stakers and top Yappers to participate in private token sales of new projects.6. Sonic Labs Announces Plans to Launch AI Development Platform Spark, Supporting Users to Deploy Web3 Applications with One Click linkSonic Labs announced plans to launch AI development platform Spark, which supports users to build and deploy Web3 applications through natural language without programming knowledge. Users will be able to complete smart contracts, front-end and deployment processes in the browser at one time. Spark is based on the Google Gemini large model and has a built-in risk scoring mechanism and self-debugging agent, which can optimize code in real time and prompt potential security risks before going live. It also has context-aware UI, development teaching and full-stack generation capabilities.7. Ondo Finance Announces Acquisition of Strangelove Labs to Accelerate the Development of its Full-Stack RWA Platform linkOndo Finance announced that it has acquired blockchain infrastructure development team Strangelove Labs to accelerate the development of its full-stack RWA platform. Strangelove has participated in the construction of key technologies such as multi-chain interoperability protocols, SDK frameworks, and customized chain deployment. Its former CEO Jack Zampolin will join Ondo as Vice President of Product.8. Polkadot Founder Gavin Wood Calls for an End to Staking Security Spending linkPolkadot founder Gavin Wood called for an end to the $500 million in annual Staking security spending under the NPoS model at the recent Web3 Summit event, believing that this structure causes capital outflow and incentive misalignment. He proposed short-term reforms including substantial incentive cuts, setting validator fiat salaries, and intermediate fund pool governance allocations. In addition, Gavin also suggested launching a Polkadot native stablecoin and shifting the treasury expenditure structure to this stablecoin settlement.9. Third-Party Layer1 Blockchain Network Tac Announces Mainnet Launch linkThird-party Layer1 blockchain network Tac announced the launch of its mainnet, dedicated to seamlessly connecting EVM DApps to the TON and Telegram ecosystems. The network allows Telegram users to directly use DeFi protocols such as Curve, Morpho, and Euler in the messaging application, while providing developers with a deployment method that does not require rewriting code. Tac has completed a total of $11.50 million in financing, with the latest round led by Hack VC.10. PumpFun Launches Creator Fees Redirection Mechanism to Support Community Takeover of Abandoned Projects linkPumpFun has launched a Creator Fees redirection mechanism that allows qualified community takeover parties (CTOs) to apply to redirect the project creator&apos;s profit-sharing address to the core contributor wallet. It is suitable for projects that are still in the Bonding Curve or have been migrated to PumpSwap, while projects that have been migrated to Raydium are not eligible. [World Liberty Financial]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946922383435034624</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说Weekly Hot Project Updates: WLFI token to open for trading, Aave TVL exceeds 50 billion, Ondo Finance announces acceleration of full-stack RWA platform development, etc. (0713–0719)1. World Liberty Financial Community Vote Passes WLFI Token Open Trading Proposal linkWorld Liberty Financi</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946922383435034624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Every 10,000 BTC increase in ETF holdings could push the average price up by 1.8%, potentially reaching $150,000 in OctoberA report released by research firm Cooper Research points out that the rise in Bitcoin prices seems inevitable as investors pour large amounts of capital into Bitcoin exchange-traded funds. Data shows that for every 10,000 BTC increase in ETF holdings, the price of Bitcoin can increase by an average of 1.8%. Analysts point out that, based on a series of data indicators, Bitcoin seems ready to rise sharply again. The leverage-driven market frenzy is gradually subsiding, and the price trend of Bitcoin may take a more moderate path, and is expected to reach $140,000 in September, and may rise to $150,000 as early as the beginning of October. (Decrypt) [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946918284903772160</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyAnalysis: Every 10,000 BTC increase in ETF holdings could push the average price up by 1.8%, potentially reaching $150,000 in OctoberA report released by research firm Cooper Research points out that the rise in Bitcoin prices seems inevitable as investors pour large amounts of capit</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946918284903772160</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>decrypt</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780.According to the official zorateam panel, possibly benefiting from the launch of Base APP, on July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780, of which 6,371 were new creators, both hitting all-time highs. A total of 20,732 tokens were created that day, with a trading volume of $12.45 million. At the same time, Zora Coins captured $229,000.00 in revenue that day, setting a new single-day record, with $120,600.00 allocated to creators, $72,600.00 in revenue captured by the protocol, and $36,000.00 in referral rewards. It is worth mentioning that the number of tokens launched through Zora Coins on July 17 exceeded Pumpfun for the first time in history. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946917862696742912</link>
      <description>1 hour ago吴说On July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780.According to the official zorateam panel, possibly benefiting from the launch of Base APP, on July 17, the number of Zora Coins creators reached 7,780, of which 6,371 were new creators, both hitting all-time highs. A total of 20</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946917862696742912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple regions warn of the risk of illegal fundraising through virtual currenciesRecently, the collapse of the &quot;Xinkangjia&quot; Ponzi scheme, which claimed &quot;2% daily interest&quot; and involved tens of billions of funds, has aroused widespread social concern and vigilance regarding new types of online fraud. Regulators have been issuing frequent warnings. According to incomplete statistics, since July, financial regulatory authorities in various regions, including Guangdong, Yunnan, Hunan, Liaoning, Heilongjiang, Zhejiang, and Fujian, have issued intensive warnings about the risks of illegal fundraising and new types of online fraud in the name of &quot;virtual currency&quot; (Yicai). [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946915773350342656</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMultiple regions warn of the risk of illegal fundraising through virtual currenciesRecently, the collapse of the &quot;Xinkangjia&quot; Ponzi scheme, which claimed &quot;2% daily interest&quot; and involved tens of billions of funds, has aroused widespread social concern and vigilance regarding new type</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946915773350342656</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Saylor has once again released Bitcoin Tracker information, and may disclose increased holdings data next week.Strategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor once again released Bitcoin Tracker-related information on the X platform, stating, &quot;Stay humble, stack Sats.&quot; He usually discloses Strategy&apos;s Bitcoin holdings data the day after he releases Bitcoin Tracker information. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946908222147719168</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyMichael Saylor has once again released Bitcoin Tracker information, and may disclose increased holdings data next week.Strategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor once again released Bitcoin Tracker-related information on the X platform, stating, &quot;Stay humble, stack Sats.&quot; He usually</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946908222147719168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Financial Secretary Paul Chan Mo-po: The HKSAR Government will position artificial intelligence as a key industryHong Kong Financial Secretary Paul Chan Mo-po published a Secretary&apos;s blog post, in which he pointed out: The 35th Hong Kong Book Fair, lasting for seven consecutive days, opened on the 16th at the Hong Kong Convention and Exhibition Centre, with the &quot;Hong Kong Innovation and Technology Special Flash Exhibition Zone&quot; set up for the first time. The SAR government has positioned artificial intelligence as a key industry, from strongly supporting basic research to promoting the transformation of results, from nurturing local start-ups to attracting global cutting-edge technology companies to settle down, from accelerating the construction of the Northern Metropolis to strengthening innovation and technology collaboration with brother cities in the Guangdong-Hong Kong-Macao Greater Bay Area, Hong Kong&apos;s innovation and technology industry development already has a solid blueprint. The SAR government will lock in the goals and not relax, draw the blueprint to the end, and the innovation and technology industry will provide Hong Kong&apos;s young people with more diverse and high-quality career development opportunities. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946905709751234560</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyHong Kong Financial Secretary Paul Chan Mo-po: The HKSAR Government will position artificial intelligence as a key industryHong Kong Financial Secretary Paul Chan Mo-po published a Secretary&apos;s blog post, in which he pointed out: The 35th Hong Kong Book Fair, lasting for seven consec</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946905709751234560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: AVAIL, VENOM, ALT and other tokens will be unlocked in large amounts next week, of which AVAIL unlocks about $18.9 millionOn July 20, Token Unlocks data showed that AVAIL, VENOM, ALT and other tokens will be unlocked in large amounts next week, including:
Avail (AVAIL) will unlock approximately 972 million tokens at 4:00 pm Beijing time on July 23, accounting for 38.23% of the current circulation, with a value of approximately US$18.9 million;
Venom (VENOM) will unlock approximately 59.26 million tokens at 4:00 pm Beijing time on July 25, accounting for 2.84% of the current circulation, with a value of approximately US$13.4 million;
AltLayer (ALT) will unlock approximately 240 million tokens at 6:00 pm Beijing time on July 25, accounting for 6.39% of the current circulation, with a value of approximately US$8.9 million;
Sahara AI (SAHARA) will unlock approximately 84.27 million tokens at 8:00 pm Beijing time on July 26, accounting for 4.13% of the current circulation, with a value of approximately US$6.9 million;
SOON (SOON) will unlock approximately 41.88 million tokens at 4:30 pm Beijing time on July 23, accounting for 22.41% of the current circulation and worth approximately US$6.1 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946904161528770560</link>
      <description>2 hours agoPANewsData: AVAIL, VENOM, ALT and other tokens will be unlocked in large amounts next week, of which AVAIL unlocks about $18.9 millionOn July 20, Token Unlocks data showed that AVAIL, VENOM, ALT and other tokens will be unlocked in large amounts next week, including:
Avail (AVAIL) will un</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946904161528770560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price Surge: LINK is now at $19.52According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is up 10.03% in the past 24h. Now at $19.52.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946900431283118080</link>
      <description>2 hours agoSoSo Price BotPrice Surge: LINK is now at $19.52According to SoSoValue, LINK (Chainlink) is up 10.03% in the past 24h. Now at $19.52.$LINKShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946900431283118080</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants Protocol: In discussions with multiple USD funds and listed companies to seek the next round of financing and cooperationAccording to official sources, Giants Protocol is currently seeking the next round of financing and cooperation with several USD funds and listed companies. It is reported that Giants Planet is an RWA + AI project supported by the Singapore sovereign wealth fund, dedicated to solving the Asian financing dilemma by building an AI-driven DeFAI engine. Through the on-chaining of RWA assets on the B2B side and the closed-loop AI intelligent agent investment on the B2C side, it aims to create a self-operating tokenized ecosystem. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946895639357353984</link>
      <description>2 hours agoOdailyGiants Protocol: In discussions with multiple USD funds and listed companies to seek the next round of financing and cooperationAccording to official sources, Giants Protocol is currently seeking the next round of financing and cooperation with several USD funds and listed companies</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 12:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946895639357353984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Financial Services Development Council Chairman Hong Pi-Cheng: Stablecoins are a long-term battle, regulatory regime to be launched in AugustHong Kong Financial Services Development Council Chairman Fred Hu said in an exclusive interview with the Hong Kong Economic Times that stablecoins should not be used as short-term speculative tools, but rather as a long-term battle, with the key being to promote payment infrastructure and the digitalization of asset markets. Hong Kong will officially implement a stablecoin regulatory regime on August 1, providing a clear compliance framework that will help attract global institutions to conduct issuance, custody, and trading businesses in Hong Kong. Hong Kong does not intend to compete with U.S. dollar stablecoins, but rather focuses on consolidating its strategic position in financial technology infrastructure.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946889787565076480</link>
      <description>3 hours ago吴说Hong Kong Financial Services Development Council Chairman Hong Pi-Cheng: Stablecoins are a long-term battle, regulatory regime to be launched in AugustHong Kong Financial Services Development Council Chairman Fred Hu said in an exclusive interview with the Hong Kong Economic Times that</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946889787565076480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts say ‘just a starting point’ as Crypto Week ends on a high noteThe GENIUS Act marks a turning point for crypto regulation, but experts say true integration with finance and identity systems is only beginning.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946889307669590016</link>
      <description>3 hours agoPANewsExperts say ‘just a starting point’ as Crypto Week ends on a high noteThe GENIUS Act marks a turning point for crypto regulation, but experts say true integration with finance and identity systems is only beginning.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946889307669590016</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBank has launched MarsMi (MARSMI)On July 20, according to official news, LBank officially launched MarsMi (MARSMI) on July 20 at 16:00 (SGT) and opened the MARSI/USDT trading pair. Currently, the deposit service is open, and the withdrawal service will be opened on July 21 at 16:00. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946888621011693568</link>
      <description>3 hours agoTechFlowLBank has launched MarsMi (MARSMI)On July 20, according to official news, LBank officially launched MarsMi (MARSMI) on July 20 at 16:00 (SGT) and opened the MARSI/USDT trading pair. Currently, the deposit service is open, and the withdrawal service will be opened on July 21 at 16:</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946888621011693568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Chain on-chain transactions exceed 100 millionAbstract core contributor cygaar posted on the X platform that the transaction volume on the Abstract Chain has officially exceeded 100 million, with a current cumulative transaction volume of 100,001,152. He said that this is an important moment for the chain itself, the community, and all participants, marking the phased achievement of Abstract&apos;s continued development and user activity. According to previous news, Abstract posted a message asking &quot;How much is CA?&quot; suspected of implying the issuance of coins. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946885565134073856</link>
      <description>3 hours agoOdailyAbstract Chain on-chain transactions exceed 100 millionAbstract core contributor cygaar posted on the X platform that the transaction volume on the Abstract Chain has officially exceeded 100 million, with a current cumulative transaction volume of 100,001,152. He said that this is a</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946885565134073856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LD Capital founder Yi Lihua: Insisting ETH will continue to outperform BTCOn July 20, Yi Lihua, founder of LD Capital, posted on social media that the weakness of the past few years has made the market forget Ethereum&apos;s strength in outperforming Bitcoin in the bull markets of 2017 and 2020. The current market has validated his judgment that &quot;Ethereum will continue to outperform Bitcoin,&quot; and he advises investors not to short in a bull market, and to at least hold Ethereum to avoid missing out on this round of market conditions. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946878165442293760</link>
      <description>3 hours agoTechFlowLD Capital founder Yi Lihua: Insisting ETH will continue to outperform BTCOn July 20, Yi Lihua, founder of LD Capital, posted on social media that the weakness of the past few years has made the market forget Ethereum&apos;s strength in outperforming Bitcoin in the bull markets of 2017</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946878165442293760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</link>
      <description>Updated  10 hours agoJul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜SoSo Daily Jul. 20: GENIUS Act Reshapes Crypto &amp; Crypto Security Alerts｜So</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 04:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1946774111265845248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>