<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:28:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>A whale PENGU short position was liquidated last night and lost $13.15 million, and then reopened the short positionOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the PENGU 3x short position at address 0x670...af6e0 was liquidated at 9 o&apos;clock last night and lost $13.15 million. He then opened an ant position of 2x PENGU short position, worth $520,000, with a current floating loss of $100,000. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947845428804603904</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoPANewsA whale PENGU short position was liquidated last night and lost $13.15 million, and then reopened the short positionOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the PENGU 3x short position at address 0x670...af6e0 was liquidated at 9 o&apos;clock last night</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947845428804603904</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eddie Yue: Avoid over-hyping stablecoins; only a few stablecoin licenses will be issued in the initial phase.According to Jinshi, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, spoke again about stablecoins, saying that with the recent hype surrounding the concept of stablecoins, the market has seen excessive excitement. Some listed companies, regardless of whether their main business is related to stablecoins or digital assets, have seen their share prices rise and stock trading volume increase significantly as soon as they announce their intention to develop stablecoin business, which is like turning stone into gold, and the company&apos;s visibility has also been greatly improved. In fact, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority has made it clear earlier that it will only issue a few stablecoin licenses at most in the initial stage, which means that there will be many disappointed parties. Even if a license is obtained, based on our desire for steady development, coupled with the resources required in the initial stage, the contribution to the company&apos;s short-term profits will be uncertain to a certain extent. We hope that investors will remain calm when digesting the market&apos;s &quot;positive&quot; news. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947843966460514304</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsEddie Yue: Avoid over-hyping stablecoins; only a few stablecoin licenses will be issued in the initial phase.According to Jinshi, Eddie Yue, Chief Executive of the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, spoke again about stablecoins, saying that with the recent hype surrounding the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947843966460514304</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiko Partners with Dune for Real-Time On-Chain Data AnalyticsOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Taiko announced a partnership with data analysis platform Dune to provide users with open and easily accessible on-chain data analysis services. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947843005730017280</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoTechFlowTaiko Partners with Dune for Real-Time On-Chain Data AnalyticsOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Taiko announced a partnership with data analysis platform Dune to provide users with open and easily accessible on-chain data analysis services. [TechFlow]#Layer2Sh</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947843005730017280</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of rules for stablecoin issuers next weekOn July 23, according to Zhitong Finance, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority will release a summary of the rules for stablecoin issuers next week. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842454397145088</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsHong Kong Monetary Authority to release summary of rules for stablecoin issuers next weekOn July 23, according to Zhitong Finance, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority will release a summary of the rules for stablecoin issuers next week. [PANews]#DeFiShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842454397145088</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoSoMacro | Trump Secures Asia Trade Wins as China Talks LoomTrump secures Japan, Philippines trade deals; China-U.S. talks expected Monday; Powell addresses regulatory meeting.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842386927316992</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoSoSoValueSoSoMacro | Trump Secures Asia Trade Wins as China Talks LoomTrump secures Japan, Philippines trade deals; China-U.S. talks expected Monday; Powell addresses regulatory meeting.#Macro$SOSOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947842386927316992</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Data Exchange held a closed-door seminar on &quot;New Opportunities in the Capital Market: RDA&quot; to discuss topics such as RWA.On July 23, according to the WeChat public account of Shanghai Data Exchange, as introduced by Jinshi, on July 21, Shanghai Data Exchange held a closed-door seminar on &quot;New Opportunities in the Capital Market: RDA&quot;. More than ten financial institutions including Cathay Haitong Securities, CITIC Construction Investment Securities, CICC, Orient Securities, Ping An Securities, Huaxin Securities, Shanxi Securities, Zheshang Securities, Tianfeng Asset Management, Huatai Asset Management, and Debang Asset Management attended the seminar to discuss key topics such as data value, RWA and RDA. Shanghai Data Exchange proposed the new RDA paradigm for the first time, emphasizing the anchoring of real-number integrated physical assets, and the role of data in authenticity verification and value enhancement of other physical assets. On the one hand, RDA can help accelerate the process of marketization and value of data elements, and on the other hand, it can promote the coordinated development of data elements and other elements, improve the docking efficiency of physical assets and capital, promote the development of new quality productivity, and promote the implementation of the deep integration system of the real economy and the digital economy. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947841779663654912</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoPANewsShanghai Data Exchange held a closed-door seminar on &quot;New Opportunities in the Capital Market: RDA&quot; to discuss topics such as RWA.On July 23, according to the WeChat public account of Shanghai Data Exchange, as introduced by Jinshi, on July 21, Shanghai Data Exchange held a close</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947841779663654912</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hut 8 Subsidiary Obtains Dubai International Financial Centre LicenseBitcoin mining firm Hut 8 Corp. has announced that its subsidiary, Hut 8 Investment Ltd, has obtained a commercial license from the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC). The license authorizes it to conduct proprietary investments and certain non-financial commercial activities within the DIFC&apos;s legal and regulatory framework based on international standards and common law principles. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947840403621564416</link>
      <description>23 minutes agoForesightNewsHut 8 Subsidiary Obtains Dubai International Financial Centre LicenseBitcoin mining firm Hut 8 Corp. has announced that its subsidiary, Hut 8 Investment Ltd, has obtained a commercial license from the Dubai International Financial Centre (DIFC). The license authorizes it t</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947840403621564416</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today in History | July 23Today in 2024, the Ethereum spot ETF was officially approved for listing and trading.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123314462720</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoForesightNewsToday in History | July 23Today in 2024, the Ethereum spot ETF was officially approved for listing and trading.#ETF$ETH$MAG7.SSIShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123314462720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A newly created wallet received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet further received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M. Currently, the wallet holds 105,977 ETH, worth approximately $396.00M. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123511595008</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoForesightNewsA newly created wallet received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, a newly created wallet further received 33,644 ETH from FalconX, worth approximately $126.00M. Currently, the wallet holds 105,977 ETH, worth approxi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123511595008</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Traded MEI Pharma Completes $100.00M Private Placement for Litecoin Strategic ReservePublicly traded MEI Pharma completes $100 million private placement, selling 29,239,767 shares of common stock at $3.42 per share (or in lieu thereof, pre-funded warrants). MEI has appointed Litecoin founder and PIPE lead investor Charlie Lee to its board of directors and GSR as its digital asset and treasury management advisor to oversee the implementation of its Litecoin strategic reserve. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123356405760</link>
      <description>28 minutes agoForesightNewsPublicly Traded MEI Pharma Completes $100.00M Private Placement for Litecoin Strategic ReservePublicly traded MEI Pharma completes $100 million private placement, selling 29,239,767 shares of common stock at $3.42 per share (or in lieu thereof, pre-funded warrants). MEI ha</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947839123356405760</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whale shorted 1,817.69 BTC with a margin of 36.200 million USDOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;10 big targets first&quot; whale made another move, starting with a short position of 1,817.69 BTC (about $217.00 million), with a margin of $36.20 million and an opening price of $119,425.00. According to the position screenshot of @Jason60704294, the position may have been opened on Binance, but it was not displayed in &quot;Contract Smart Money&quot;. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837422796820480</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoPANewsA whale shorted 1,817.69 BTC with a margin of 36.200 million USDOn July 23, according to the monitoring of on-chain analyst @ai_9684xtpa, the &quot;10 big targets first&quot; whale made another move, starting with a short position of 1,817.69 BTC (about $217.00 million), with a margin of $</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837422796820480</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eigen Labs: The redistribution mechanism is now live on the mainnetOn July 23, according to the official blog, Eigen Labs announced that the redistribution mechanism has been launched on the mainnet. The redistribution mechanism is the next generation iteration of the EigenLayer slashing function. Redistribution unlocks new use cases for AVS, providing AVS and its customers with more options for liquidity management and risk tolerance. Under the redistribution mechanism, the slashed funds can now be redistributed according to their specific use cases instead of being destroyed. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947836805101670400</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoPANewsEigen Labs: The redistribution mechanism is now live on the mainnetOn July 23, according to the official blog, Eigen Labs announced that the redistribution mechanism has been launched on the mainnet. The redistribution mechanism is the next generation iteration of the EigenLayer</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947836805101670400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARK Invest Acquires $182 Million of BMNR Common Stock to Help BitMine Advance Its Ethereum Treasury StrategyOn July 23, according to PR Newswire, BitMine announced on Tuesday that ARK Invest has acquired 4,773,444 shares of BitMine common stock BMNR, with a total value of US$182.00 million. BitMine plans to use all net proceeds (approximately US$177.00 million) to purchase Ethereum. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947835661302386688</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoPANewsARK Invest Acquires $182 Million of BMNR Common Stock to Help BitMine Advance Its Ethereum Treasury StrategyOn July 23, according to PR Newswire, BitMine announced on Tuesday that ARK Invest has acquired 4,773,444 shares of BitMine common stock BMNR, with a total value of US$182.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947835661302386688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean Regulators Verbally Instruct ETFs in the Country to Stop Increasing Their Holdings of Crypto Company Stocks Like CoinbaseAccording to The Korea Herald, South Korea&apos;s Financial Supervisory Service recently issued verbal guidance to domestic asset management companies, asking them not to increase the proportion of their holdings in ETFs of crypto companies such as Coinbase and Strategy. The regulator reiterated that the &quot;Emergency Countermeasures Related to Virtual Currency&quot; promulgated in 2017 are still valid. This administrative guidance clearly prohibits formal financial institutions from holding or purchasing virtual assets, obtaining related collateral, and making equity investments. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947834604178395136</link>
      <description>45 minutes agoForesightNewsSouth Korean Regulators Verbally Instruct ETFs in the Country to Stop Increasing Their Holdings of Crypto Company Stocks Like CoinbaseAccording to The Korea Herald, South Korea&apos;s Financial Supervisory Service recently issued verbal guidance to domestic asset management com</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947834604178395136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitfarms Launches Stock Buyback Program, Can Repurchase Up to 10% of Outstanding SharesOn July 23, global energy and computing infrastructure company Bitfarms Ltd. (NASDAQ/TSX code: BITF) announced that its board of directors has approved the immediate launch of a company stock repurchase program. Under the program, Bitfarms is authorized to repurchase up to 49,943,031 common shares between July 28, 2025, and July 27, 2026, representing 10% of the company&apos;s outstanding shares. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947833886834970624</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoTechFlowBitfarms Launches Stock Buyback Program, Can Repurchase Up to 10% of Outstanding SharesOn July 23, global energy and computing infrastructure company Bitfarms Ltd. (NASDAQ/TSX code: BITF) announced that its board of directors has approved the immediate launch of a company stock</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947833886834970624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Finance has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission to provide digital asset deposit and withdrawal servicesOn July 23, according to PR Newswire, Eddid Financial announced that its Eddid Securities and Futures has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission to provide digital asset deposit and withdrawal services, laying the foundation for the group to further develop digital asset transactions in the future, including stablecoins and tokenized physical asset (RWA) product distribution. The group&apos;s flagship trading application Eddid ONE will also be upgraded, and investors will be able to directly deposit and withdraw a variety of cryptocurrencies, including BTC, ETH, USDC, USDT, and USDT-TRC. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825589260144640</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsEd Finance has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission to provide digital asset deposit and withdrawal servicesOn July 23, according to PR Newswire, Eddid Financial announced that its Eddid Securities and Futures has been approved by the Hong Kong Securities a</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825589260144640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmine Announces It Will Use All Net Proceeds from ARK Invest Share Acquisition to Purchase EthereumBitmine announced that it will use all net proceeds ($177.00M) from the $182.00M ARK Invest share acquisition deal to purchase more Ethereum and deposit it into its vault. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825286804688896</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitmine Announces It Will Use All Net Proceeds from ARK Invest Share Acquisition to Purchase EthereumBitmine announced that it will use all net proceeds ($177.00M) from the $182.00M ARK Invest share acquisition deal to purchase more Ethereum and deposit it into its vault. [For</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947825286804688896</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitwise CIO Predicts: ETPs and Financial Firms Will Purchase $20.00B Worth of ETH Next YearBitwise CIO Matt Hougan said that since May 15, the Ethereum spot ETP market has seen inflows of over $5.00B, and listed companies such as Bitmine and SharpLink have announced Ethereum strategic reserves. ETPs and corporate treasuries have collectively purchased 2.83M ETH, worth over $10.00B, equivalent to 32 times the net new supply over the same period. He predicts that ETPs and financial companies will purchase $20.00B worth of ETH next year, equivalent to 5.33M ETH at current prices, equivalent to 7 times the net new supply over the same period. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947824307405344768</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsBitwise CIO Predicts: ETPs and Financial Firms Will Purchase $20.00B Worth of ETH Next YearBitwise CIO Matt Hougan said that since May 15, the Ethereum spot ETP market has seen inflows of over $5.00B, and listed companies such as Bitmine and SharpLink have announced Ethereum s</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947824307405344768</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pudgy Penguins NFTs Genesis 4th AnniversaryPudgy Penguins NFTs officially opened for minting 4 years ago today. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947821523054383104</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsPudgy Penguins NFTs Genesis 4th AnniversaryPudgy Penguins NFTs officially opened for minting 4 years ago today. [Foresight News]#NFTShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947821523054383104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is currently about 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024On July 23, according to CoinDesk, the size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is about 519,000 ETH (worth about $1.9 billion), a record high since January 2024, and the current exit waiting time exceeds 9 days. Analysis pointed out that this is mainly related to the profit-taking of stakers after the ETH price rose 160% from the low point in April. Data shows that despite the exit wave, the demand for Ethereum staking remains strong - there are currently 357,000 ETH (worth $1.3 billion) waiting to enter the staking queue, with a waiting time of more than 6 days. This phenomenon is partly due to the continued increase in holdings by Ethereum treasury companies such as SharpLink Gaming, and the increase in institutional participation after the SEC clarified at the end of May that staking does not violate securities laws. Since late May, the number of active validators has increased by 54,000, reaching a historical peak of 1.1 million. Industry insiders pointed out that the surge in exit queues may also include institutional investors who have unstaked their shares to participate in ETH treasury company fundraising. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947819458152386560</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsThe size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is currently about 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024On July 23, according to CoinDesk, the size of the Ethereum validator exit queue is about 519,000 ETH (worth about $1.9 billion), a record high since January 2024, and the curre</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947819458152386560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 02:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>