<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:51:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Hotcoin Exchange is about to launch BNKR spot trading
According to official news on July 24, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs


BNKR/USDT (July 24, 17:00 UTC+8): $BNKR is the native token of the Bankr project. Bankr is an advanced AI agent that can help you with swaps, research, and more.


 [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289446029365248</link>
      <description>58seconds agoTechFlowHotcoin Exchange is about to launch BNKR spot trading
According to official news on July 24, the Hotcoin exchange will launch the following trading pairs on July 24:
Spot trading pairs


BNKR/USDT (July 24, 17:00 UTC+8): $BNKR is the native token of the Bankr project. Bankr is a</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289446029365248</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZachXBT: Ripple co-founder-linked address transferred 50,000,000 XRP, approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchangesAccording to on-chain detective ZachXBT, starting on July 17, 2025, wallet addresses associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen transferred 50,000,000 XRP (approximately $175,000,000.00) to four addresses, of which approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchanges or related service platforms. Some of the funds also flowed into two new addresses, each receiving 5,000,000 XRP. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289501415149568</link>
      <description>1 minute ago吴说ZachXBT: Ripple co-founder-linked address transferred 50,000,000 XRP, approximately $140,000,000.00 flowed into exchangesAccording to on-chain detective ZachXBT, starting on July 17, 2025, wallet addresses associated with Ripple co-founder Chris Larsen transferred 50,000,000 XRP (appro</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948289501415149568</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitget Wallet adds new crypto payment channels, supporting mainstream consumer platforms including Hema, Honor of Kings, Sinopec, and JD.comBitget Wallet has added support for crypto payment functions in various daily consumption scenarios, covering e-commerce shopping, digital entertainment, game top-ups, global travel, and other fields. Users can use crypto assets in the wallet to complete one-stop consumption. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288504903045120</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsBitget Wallet adds new crypto payment channels, supporting mainstream consumer platforms including Hema, Honor of Kings, Sinopec, and JD.comBitget Wallet has added support for crypto payment functions in various daily consumption scenarios, covering e-commerce shopping, dig</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288504903045120</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amended class action calls Pump.fun a ‘slot machine cabinet’ in $5.5B caseAn amended lawsuit accuses Pump.fun and key Solana partners of operating an unlicensed digital casino that funneled billions through deceptive memecoin schemes.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288055307210752</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoPANewsAmended class action calls Pump.fun a ‘slot machine cabinet’ in $5.5B caseAn amended lawsuit accuses Pump.fun and key Solana partners of operating an unlicensed digital casino that funneled billions through deceptive memecoin schemes.#Layer1Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288055307210752</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Congress to Advance Veterans Affairs Blockchain Pilot BillThe U.S. Congress is considering the &quot;Department of Veterans Affairs Distributed Ledger Technology Innovation Act of 2025&quot; (H.R. 3455), which aims to promote the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) to study the application of blockchain technology in the claims process to improve transparency, traceability, and reduce the risk of fraud and abuse. The bill passed a hearing by the House Veterans Affairs Subcommittee on June 11 and is awaiting a full House vote. If passed, the VA will submit a feasibility study and pilot recommendation report within one year. [CryptoSlate]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288300611080192</link>
      <description>7 minutes ago吴说US Congress to Advance Veterans Affairs Blockchain Pilot BillThe U.S. Congress is considering the &quot;Department of Veterans Affairs Distributed Ledger Technology Innovation Act of 2025&quot; (H.R. 3455), which aims to promote the Department of Veterans Affairs (VA) to study the application o</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288300611080192</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JuCoin Lists Three Meme Coins for On-Chain Trading, Expanding the Selection Zone LineupJuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection zone has launched three tokens: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, and is now fully open for trading. Users can access &quot;Trading&quot; — &quot;On-chain Trading&quot; on the JuCoin App or website homepage to start trading on-chain assets with one click. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948287623658803200</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoForesightNewsJuCoin Lists Three Meme Coins for On-Chain Trading, Expanding the Selection Zone LineupJuCoin&apos;s on-chain trading Selection zone has launched three tokens: memecoin, PYTHIA, and AOL, and is now fully open for trading. Users can access &quot;Trading&quot; — &quot;On-chain Trading&quot; on the Ju</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948287623658803200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Ventures to Support AI Platform Bankr Through Base Ecosystem FundCoinbase Ventures announced that it will support AI agent platform Bankr through the Base ecosystem fund. Bankr is one of the agent platforms integrated into Coinbase&apos;s newly launched Base app. Trading agents react faster than humans, operate 24/7, and have the potential to make more data-driven decisions. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948287303650185216</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoOdailyCoinbase Ventures to Support AI Platform Bankr Through Base Ecosystem FundCoinbase Ventures announced that it will support AI agent platform Bankr through the Base ecosystem fund. Bankr is one of the agent platforms integrated into Coinbase&apos;s newly launched Base app. Trading agen</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948287303650185216</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Pi Coin Be Listed on Binance? New Developments in Pi Wallet Spark SpeculationSpeculation is growing that Pi Network’s Pi Coin (PI) could potentially be listed on Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange. This comes following reports from several Pioneers who noticed Binance support options appearing in the Pi Wallet. However, neither Binance nor the Pi Core Team has confirmed or commented on the development, leaving the rumor mill to run wild. Pi Coin on Binance? Rumors Grow Stronger Amid New Wallet Features The listing of Pi Coin on Binance has been a longstanding concern for the Pi Network community, known as Pioneers. Since the launch of the open network, Pioneers have consistently advocated for Pi to be listed on the exchange. However, this has not yet materialized. Recently, the integration of Binance-related support options within the Pi Wallet has renewed the community’s optimism. This has raised hopes that a partnership between Pi Network and Binance may soon be realized. In a recent post on X (formerly Twitter), a prominent Pioneer, Mr Spock, highlighted that ‘Binance Connect Support’ and ‘Binance P2P Support ‘ options now appear under the Help &amp; Support tab of the Pi Wallet. For context, Binance Connect is the exchange’s fiat-to-crypto service. It facilitates the easy purchase and conversion of fiat currencies into cryptocurrencies through various payment methods. The exchange shut the service down in 2023. Nevertheless, Binance later relaunched in 2024. Meanwhile, Binance P2P enables direct peer-to-peer transactions with more than 800 payment methods and over 100 fiat currencies. However, Mr Spock added that the development doesn’t directly confirm that Pi Network will be available to trade on Binance immediately. Nonetheless, he noted that it strongly suggests that ‘something big is coming.’ Furthermore, PiScan data revealed that a mysterious wallet address has accumulated over 336 million Pi. This has fueled theories that it might belong to an exchange preparing for listing. Despite the circulating reports on X, it is also worth noting that Binance is not a part of KYB-verified businesses on Pi Network. Moreover, besides the exchange, Pi Wallet also lists support for other payment processors like MoonPay and Stripe. These businesses are also not KYB-verified. The Pi Core Team has remained silent on the matter, leaving the community to grapple with unverified reports. Premature speculation has historically led to community disappointment. Until an official announcement from Pi Network or Binance materializes, the current developments remain rumors.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288863688003584</link>
      <description>24 minutes agobeincryptoCould Pi Coin Be Listed on Binance? New Developments in Pi Wallet Spark SpeculationSpeculation is growing that Pi Network’s Pi Coin (PI) could potentially be listed on Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange. This comes following reports from several Pioneers who noticed</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948288863688003584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 巨鲸 deposited about $7.00M in HyperLiquid to go long on PEPE, BONK, POPCAT, etc.On July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited about 6,998,000.000 USDC into the HyperLiquid platform and opened or increased long positions in multiple tokens, including: PEPE, BONK, WIF, POPCAT, Trump with 10x leverage, ZK, PUMP with 5x leverage, and LDO, PURR, CHILLGUY with 3x leverage. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282208929779712</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoPANewsA 巨鲸 deposited about $7.00M in HyperLiquid to go long on PEPE, BONK, POPCAT, etc.On July 24, according to Onchain Lens monitoring, a whale deposited about 6,998,000.000 USDC into the HyperLiquid platform and opened or increased long positions in multiple tokens, including: PEPE,</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282208929779712</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday and deposited into Bybit.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address yesterday. This address is marked by Solscan as &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2,&quot; i.e., a private placement investor. After receiving the returned funds from Binance yesterday, these 2 billion tokens have been deposited into Bybit, with a value reduced by $6.00M compared to when they were deposited into Binance. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282276646817792</link>
      <description>36 minutes agoOdaily2 billion PUMP tokens were withdrawn from Binance&apos;s hot wallet yesterday and deposited into Bybit.According to on-chain analyst Ai Yi&apos;s monitoring, 2 billion PUMP tokens were suspected of being transferred from Binance&apos;s hot wallet back to the project&apos;s associated address yesterd</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948282276646817792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walrus Announces Quilt Bulk Storage Solution, Reshaping How Small Files Are Stored at ScaleOn July 24, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced the release of Quilt, a batch storage solution equipped with an intuitive API that allows developers to conveniently, efficiently, and cost-effectively store and access large numbers of small files, such as NFT series, documents, AI communication data, logs, etc. Instead of storing each file separately, Quilt groups multiple small files into one unit, reducing the overhead and cost of a 100KB blob by approximately 106 times and the overhead and cost of a 10KB blob by approximately 420 times. Using Quilt can also reduce any SUI-denominated Gas fees associated with Walrus storage transactions. Currently, several projects, including Tusky and Gata, have adopted Quilt to optimize their storage architecture. Currently, Quilt has been launched on the Walrus testnet (version 1.29) and will be officially launched with the mainnet version 1.29 on July 30, 2025. It is reported that as a global data infrastructure for on-chain developers, Walrus has carried 800+ TB of encoded data and 14.00 million blobs since its mainnet launch more than three months ago, supporting hundreds of projects built on it. [Techflow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948280347678019584</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoTechFlowWalrus Announces Quilt Bulk Storage Solution, Reshaping How Small Files Are Stored at ScaleOn July 24, Walrus Protocol, a blockchain storage protocol built on Sui, announced the release of Quilt, a batch storage solution equipped with an intuitive API that allows developers to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948280347678019584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Espresso Foundation has completed the snapshot.The blockchain infrastructure Espresso Foundation tweeted that it has completed taking a snapshot. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278173883502592</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoForesightNewsEspresso Foundation has completed the snapshot.The blockchain infrastructure Espresso Foundation tweeted that it has completed taking a snapshot. [Foresight News]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278173883502592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic cooperation with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron.According to official sources, Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX recently reached a strategic partnership with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron. Through this collaboration, Safeheron will assist APACX in building a decentralized protocol for stablecoin trading and settlement targeting the Southeast Asian market, constructing a value network for the interconnection and application of multiple stablecoins, especially providing APACX with top-tier security and risk control capabilities. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948279780838805504</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoOdailyStablecoin operation service provider APACX has reached a strategic cooperation with digital asset self-custody service provider Safeheron.According to official sources, Southeast Asian stablecoin operator APACX recently reached a strategic partnership with digital asset self-cus</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948279780838805504</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizen Completes Token Migration, ZEN Converted to Base Chain ERC-20 Token, Launches Three-Layer Privacy Application ChainThe Horizen blockchain has migrated its native token ZEN from the original L1 mainnet to the Base chain and converted it to a standard ERC-20 token as part of its Horizen 2.0 three-layer privacy application chain deployment. The total supply of ZEN remains unchanged at 21.00 million. The project team stated that this is the first step in Horizen&apos;s privacy-focused restart of its ecosystem. Previously, Coinbase issued a statement saying that it would automatically complete the conversion of mainnet ZEN to Base chain ERC-20 tokens for users. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948277528602415104</link>
      <description>48 minutes agoChainCatcherHorizen Completes Token Migration, ZEN Converted to Base Chain ERC-20 Token, Launches Three-Layer Privacy Application ChainThe Horizen blockchain has migrated its native token ZEN from the original L1 mainnet to the Base chain and converted it to a standard ERC-20 token as</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948277528602415104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Bankers Association Opposes Circle and Others Applying to Establish National Trust Banks in the USRecently, five major US banking associations, including the American Bankers Association, jointly sent a letter to the US Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) opposing the applications of four crypto and stablecoin companies—Circle, Fidelity Digital Assets, Protego Trust, and Ripple—for national trust bank charters. The banking associations stated that although the OCC allows the public to comment on the applications, the application documents of the aforementioned companies have serious disclosure deficiencies, with over 90% of the content being redacted, making it difficult for the public to conduct an effective assessment. [Ledger Insights]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276591079002112</link>
      <description>52 minutes ago吴说American Bankers Association Opposes Circle and Others Applying to Establish National Trust Banks in the USRecently, five major US banking associations, including the American Bankers Association, jointly sent a letter to the US Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) opposin</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276591079002112</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A private placement investor missed the best time to sell PUMP due to mistakenly recharging it to Binance, and is expected to lose $6.00 millionOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a PUMP private equity investor &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2&quot; mistakenly recharged 2 billion PUMPs to Binance 8 days ago, when the price of PUMP was $0.0064. Since Binance did not launch PUMP spot trading, the 2 billion PUMPs (worth $6.93 million today) were likely returned to him 23 hours ago. He immediately transferred the 2 billion PUMPs to Bybit after receiving them. This operational error caused him to miss the best time to sell, and if he chose to sell now, he might have lost about $6 million. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276150249263104</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoPANewsA private placement investor missed the best time to sell PUMP due to mistakenly recharging it to Binance, and is expected to lose $6.00 millionOn July 24, according to Lookonchain monitoring, a PUMP private equity investor &quot;PUMP Top Fund 2&quot; mistakenly recharged 2 billion PUMPs t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948276150249263104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiDeFi index 24hr loss of 10.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDeFi has fallen by 10.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ONDO -12.5%, CAKE -11.54%, LDO -11.01%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948275391981379584</link>
      <description>56 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiDeFi index 24hr loss of 10.05%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiDeFi has fallen by 10.05% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: ONDO -12.5%, CAKE -11.54%, LDO -11.01%.$LDO$CAKE$ONDOShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948275391981379584</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC Shanghai Headquarters: Actively Explore the Application of Digital Yuan in Offshore Trade SettlementAccording to Jinshi, the Shanghai Headquarters of the People&apos;s Bank of China held a press conference for the third quarter of 2025 on July 24. Shi Jiandong, Deputy Director of the Macro-Prudential Management Department of the Shanghai Headquarters of the People&apos;s Bank of China, stated that the next step for the People&apos;s Bank of China Shanghai Headquarters is to continue to steadily and orderly promote financial reform tasks. First, it will promote comprehensive reform pilots for offshore trade financial services for banks and enterprises with mature conditions, continuously expand the scope of policy benefits, and actively explore the application of digital RMB in offshore trade settlement. Second, based on feedback from public comments, it will revise and improve the &quot;Implementation Measures for Upgrading the Free Trade Account Function in the Shanghai Free Trade Zone&quot; and formally release it to the public after reporting it to the head office of the People&apos;s Bank of China for approval. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273784611475456</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsPBOC Shanghai Headquarters: Actively Explore the Application of Digital Yuan in Offshore Trade SettlementAccording to Jinshi, the Shanghai Headquarters of the People&apos;s Bank of China held a press conference for the third quarter of 2025 on July 24. Shi Jiandong, Deputy Director</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273784611475456</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 63, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 63 (66 &quot;high risk&quot; yesterday), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273099958456320</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsData: Today&apos;s crypto derivatives risk index is 63, still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range.According to CoinGlass data, the crypto derivatives risk index today is 63 (66 &quot;high risk&quot; yesterday), still in the &quot;high risk&quot; range. [Foresight News]#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948273099958456320</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Bull Market Cycle Quick View: When Will This Bull Market End?The market FOMO caused by the RWA narrative may be the profit-taking signal for this cycle.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278589916516352</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCrypto Bull Market Cycle Quick View: When Will This Bull Market End?The market FOMO caused by the RWA narrative may be the profit-taking signal for this cycle.Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 06:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948278589916516352</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</link>
      <description>Updated  4 days agoSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | Crypto Market Sinks as DeFi Liquidity Shrinks and TradFi Embraces BlockchainSoSo Daily | C</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 07:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948197090280296448</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>