<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:34:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Evening News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses BONK, becoming the largest Solana ecosystem Meme coin by market cap;
2. Analyst: Ethereum faces short-term pullback risk, but the current increase is still relatively small from a large cycle perspective;
3. Matrixport: The crypto market faces short-term volatility, but the overall upward trend is not over;
4. Merlin Founder: 2.0 upgrade officially released, aiming to create a &quot;yield-generating, tradable&quot; BTC;
5. Tether CEO: Has invested in over 120 companies, with funds coming from Tether&apos;s own profits;
6. Arthur Hayes: Cryptopunks will outperform Ethereum this cycle;
7. Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach a $15.80M financing agreement to increase Bitcoin holdings;
8. Crypto mining company MARA to issue $850.00M in convertible notes to purchase more Bitcoin.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982797888622592</link>
      <description>3 minutes agoOdailyPlanet Evening News1. PENGU&apos;s market cap surpasses BONK, becoming the largest Solana ecosystem Meme coin by market cap;
2. Analyst: Ethereum faces short-term pullback risk, but the current increase is still relatively small from a large cycle perspective;
3. Matrixport: The crypto</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982797888622592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Trump says he will not fire PowellAccording to Jinshi, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent said, &quot;We are not in a hurry to nominate the Federal Reserve Chairman. Frustration with the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. Trump has said he will not fire Powell. Powell has also not indicated that he will leave his board position.&quot; [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981973129072640</link>
      <description>5 minutes agoForesightNewsUS Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: Trump says he will not fire PowellAccording to Jinshi, U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent said, &quot;We are not in a hurry to nominate the Federal Reserve Chairman. Frustration with the Fed&apos;s mission puts monetary policy independence at risk. T</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981973129072640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Bessent: Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off&quot;US Treasury Secretary Bessent says the Federal Reserve&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off,&quot; and (regarding interest rate decisions) he doesn&apos;t know what the Federal Reserve is considering. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982806327562240</link>
      <description>6 minutes agoOdailyTreasury Secretary Bessent: Fed&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off&quot;US Treasury Secretary Bessent says the Federal Reserve&apos;s tariff analysis is &quot;a bit off,&quot; and (regarding interest rate decisions) he doesn&apos;t know what the Federal Reserve is considering. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982806327562240</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gate launches the second round of VIP financial carnival, complete the task and win a box of MaotaiOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch the second phase of the &quot;VIP Financial Management Summer Carnival&quot; for a limited time. The registration period is from 18:00 on July 22 to 18:00 on August 5 (UTC+8). After VIP users complete the registration, participate in Yubibao Financial Management and complete the challenge to win a whole box of Feitian Moutai. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981438208512000</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsGate launches the second round of VIP financial carnival, complete the task and win a box of MaotaiOn July 23, according to the official announcement, Gate will launch the second phase of the &quot;VIP Financial Management Summer Carnival&quot; for a limited time. The registration period is</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947981438208512000</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Bessent: Trump Said He Would Not Fire PowellTreasury Secretary Bessent said that Trump has already said that he will not fire Powell. We are not in a hurry on the issue of nominating the Federal Reserve Chairman. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982814766501888</link>
      <description>9 minutes agoOdailyTreasury Secretary Bessent: Trump Said He Would Not Fire PowellTreasury Secretary Bessent said that Trump has already said that he will not fire Powell. We are not in a hurry on the issue of nominating the Federal Reserve Chairman. (Golden Ten) [Odaily Planet Daily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947982814766501888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) on Binance Smart Chain (BSC), causing losses of more than $600,000. Since the contract is not open source, investigations show that the vulnerability stems from the lack of slippage protection, and the attacker used a fake liquidity pool to harvest TA tokens (0x539ae81a166e5e80aed211731563e549c411b140) and sold them in a legitimate pool for profit. BlockSec Phalcon strongly recommends that users who have authorized the contract immediately revoke permissions to prevent further losses. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</link>
      <description>14 minutes agoPANewsSecurity agency: A BSC unverified contract was attacked, with losses exceeding $600,000.On July 23, blockchain security agency BlockSec Phalcon issued a warning that its system detected a series of malicious transactions against an unverified contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947979636591366144</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto mining firm MARA to issue $850.0M in convertible notes to purchase more BitcoinCrypto mining firm MARA Holdings has announced the issuance of $850.00M of 0% convertible notes to purchase more Bitcoin (as well as repay $50.00M of old notes and for general corporate purposes). [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947980278416347136</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoOdailyCrypto mining firm MARA to issue $850.0M in convertible notes to purchase more BitcoinCrypto mining firm MARA Holdings has announced the issuance of $850.00M of 0% convertible notes to purchase more Bitcoin (as well as repay $50.00M of old notes and for general corporate purposes</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947980278416347136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly impose a 30% tariff on US products worth about 100.00 billion euros (about 117.00 billion US dollars). A spokesman for the European Commission said on Wednesday that as part of the first wave of countermeasures, the EU will combine the already approved tariff list for 21.00 billion euros of US goods and the previously proposed tariff list for another 72.00 billion euros of US products into a package. According to people familiar with the matter, US exports, including Boeing aircraft, US-made cars and industrial products such as bourbon whiskey, will face tariffs matching Trump&apos;s threat of 30%. These people said that the tariffs will be ready to take effect next month, but only if the negotiations break down and the United States implements its tax measures after the August deadline. An unnamed government official said that in the absence of an agreement, Berlin is even willing to support the activation of the EU&apos;s &quot;anti-coercion tool&quot; (ACI). This tool will only be activated if an agreement cannot be reached. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoPANewsEU prepares 100 billion euro &quot;no deal&quot; plan to deal with 30% US tariffsJuly 23 news, according to foreign media reports, if the negotiations break down and US President Trump fulfills his threat to impose a 30% tariff on most EU exports after August 1, the EU plans to quickly imp</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947975856311308288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+8) on July 23. At the same time, the relevant tokens will no longer support Simple Earn and flexible lending services. (This news was generated with the assistance of AI) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</link>
      <description>30 minutes agoOdailyOKX to Delist Multiple Margin Trading PairsAccording to the official announcement, OKX will delist the RDNT/USDT, ID/USDT, AIDOGE/USDT, XCH/USDT, CSPR/USDT, CTC/USDT, and JOE/USDT margin trading pairs from July 30 to 31, 2025. The lending function will be stopped at 7:00 PM (UTC+</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947977763520057344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stellar (XLM) Risks a 40% Drop as Bearish Divergence ReturnsStellar’s (XLM) price trades near $0.47 after a 103% month-on-month. The rally has stalled into small daily candles (mostly indecisive Doji candles) . And two daily signals now lean lower: a heavy block of leveraged longs sits under price, and slipping momentum. Key support levels might be at risk. Leverage Pocket Below $0.40 Raises Cascade Risk Price is hovering above $0.45, but Bitget’s 30‑day XLM/USDT liquidation map shows roughly $79.8 million of long exposure compared with about $42.1 million in shorts , with the cumulative cluster highlighted under $0.40. Each step down would trigger smaller pockets first, then the dense area under $0.40 can amplify selling as forced closures hit the order book. A liquidation map plots where leveraged positions get auto-closed; when the largest clusters sit below spot, even a modest drop can snowball. Daily RSI Divergence Mirrors December Slide Since July 14, the price has held near the highs while the Relative Strength Index ( RSI ) on the daily chart has made lower highs. The last time XLM showed this pattern, in late December, the price fell over 40%. RSI measures the strength of recent price movements on a 0–100 scale. When price is steady or rising but RSI eases, momentum is not confirming the move, and pullback risk increases. With leverage and liquidation risks waiting below, that loss of momentum becomes more dangerous, supporting the “ XLM price correction ” logic. Want more token insights like this? Sign up for Editor Harsh Notariya’s Daily Crypto Newsletter  here . XLM Price Now Eyes Key Support Levels A Fibonacci retracement drawn from the $0.21 low to the $0.52 high frames the likely supports if selling starts: $0.44 (0.236) being the strongest level will multiple support hits. Fibonacci levels mark common pullback areas, and when they overlap with liquidation clusters, reactions tend to be sharper. XLM is currently sitting above $0.44. A daily close beneath that level would put $0.40 in focus. Below $0.40, the liquidation hypothesis wins, so a break there could speed a move toward $0.33. A 40% decline (inspired by the December 2024 pattern) from the $0.52 high lands under $0.33. Under $0.28 (if the $0.33 level breaks), the entire XLM price structure could turn bearish in the short term. Invalidation is straightforward: a firm daily close back above $0.52, with RSI turning up and liquidation risk thinning out, would neutralize this bearish setup and restore the upside case.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947980641638879232</link>
      <description>32 minutes agobeincryptoStellar (XLM) Risks a 40% Drop as Bearish Divergence ReturnsStellar’s (XLM) price trades near $0.47 after a 103% month-on-month. The rally has stalled into small daily candles (mostly indecisive Doji candles) . And two daily signals now lean lower: a heavy block of leveraged</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947980641638879232</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinShares secures MiCA license in France to cement EU presenceIn addition to its leadership in the EU, CoinShares has been actively expanding in the US market since officially entering in 2023, aiming to compete with major industry peers.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974271371907072</link>
      <description>35 minutes agoPANewsCoinShares secures MiCA license in France to cement EU presenceIn addition to its leadership in the EU, CoinShares has been actively expanding in the US market since officially entering in 2023, aiming to compete with major industry peers.#Crypto Stocks$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974271371907072</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Pastor Couple Charged in $3.40M Crypto Token ScamProsecutors in Denver, Colorado, have announced that online pastor Eli Regalado and his wife, Kaitlyn, have been indicted on a total of 40 counts for allegedly orchestrating a fraud involving the INDXcoin crypto token. The couple is accused of raising over $3.40 million between 2022 and 2023 by promoting the token to religious communities through their self-built Kingdom Wealth Exchange platform. At least $1.30 million of this amount was allegedly used for personal expenses, including home renovations. The indictment states that approximately 300 investors suffered total losses as a result. [Cointelegraph]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974177159450624</link>
      <description>37 minutes ago吴说Colorado Pastor Couple Charged in $3.40M Crypto Token ScamProsecutors in Denver, Colorado, have announced that online pastor Eli Regalado and his wife, Kaitlyn, have been indicted on a total of 40 counts for allegedly orchestrating a fraud involving the INDXcoin crypto token. The cou</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947974177159450624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferies gives Galaxy Digital a &quot;buy&quot; rating with a target price of $35.00.According to CoinDesk, Jefferies initiated coverage of Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a &quot;buy&quot; rating and a price target of $35.00 in its latest research report. The report noted that the passage of the GENIUS Act in the United States has improved the crypto regulatory environment, providing a favorable market structure for Galaxy. Galaxy is also expected to benefit from the growing demand for AI data centers by leasing a 393 megawatt data center in Texas. Currently, approximately two-thirds of its company value comes from its data center business. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947973963057008640</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoForesightNewsJefferies gives Galaxy Digital a &quot;buy&quot; rating with a target price of $35.00.According to CoinDesk, Jefferies initiated coverage of Galaxy Digital (GLXY) with a &quot;buy&quot; rating and a price target of $35.00 in its latest research report. The report noted that the passage of the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947973963057008640</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximately $1.9 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $1.3 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to join.Data shows that the Ethereum validator exit queue has surged in the past week, with approximately 521,000 ETH (worth approximately $1.9 billion at current prices) waiting to exit the Ethereum network. The number of ETH requested to exit has increased significantly since July 16, and the exit waiting time has been extended to 8 to 9 days, the longest waiting time since the beginning of 2024. At the same time, more than 359,500 ETH are queued to join the network, worth approximately $1.3 billion, with an expected activation delay of approximately 6 days. This situation reflects two opposing forces in the market: on the one hand, some stakers may be choosing to take profits after Ethereum rebounded 162.00% from its April low, leading to a surge in the exit queue; on the other hand, new deposits driven by regulatory benefits and institutional demand are also pushing up the entry queue, such as listed companies like SharpLink Gaming and BitMine Immersion increasing their ETH holdings and staking. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947972733899444224</link>
      <description>47 minutes agoOdailyApproximately $1.9 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to exit the Ethereum PoS network, while approximately $1.3 billion USD worth of ETH is queuing to join.Data shows that the Ethereum validator exit queue has surged in the past week, with approximately 521,000 ETH (worth appro</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947972733899444224</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value foundation of the ecosystem, Giants Protocol will advance its originally scheduled phased lock-up plan, locking 90% of the circulating tokens through smart contracts to ensure market stability and token value support. Giants Protocol stated that several international listed luxury goods groups have recently taken the initiative to contact the project team, intending to obtain priority access to its RWA asset on-chain services by holding G tokens. The official statement said: &quot;As traditional luxury assets accelerate on-chain, G is gradually becoming a key bridge connecting Web2 luxury assets and the Web3 protocol layer.&quot; [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoOdailyGiants Protocol accelerates 90% token lock-up plan and is in talks with international luxury brands for in-depth cooperationGiants Protocol officially announced a major development: To cooperate with upcoming institutional-level partnerships and enhance the long-term value founda</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970221368741888</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been partially liquidated, and there is still a floating loss of $266,000.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoOdailyJames Wynn&apos;s Bitcoin and PEPE long positions were partially liquidated, and are currently still showing an unrealized loss of $266,000.00.According to Onchain Lens monitoring, trader James Wynn&apos;s 40x leveraged Bitcoin long position and 10x leveraged PEPE long position have been p</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947970238259204096</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Capital to support its Bitcoin funding strategy. The ATM-style financing tool allows Hilbert Group to flexibly withdraw funds in the next 36 months to purchase more Bitcoin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoPANewsHilbert Group and LDA Capital reach SEK 150 million financing agreement to support Bitcoin funding strategyOn July 23, according to NLNico, Sweden&apos;s Hilbert Group signed a 150.00 million Swedish kronor (about 15.80 million U.S. dollars) structured financing agreement with LDA Cap</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947968586844278784</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadian dollars, with funds coming from the company&apos;s existing cash reserves. As of July 22, 2025, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings increased to 28.89, equivalent to 2,889,000,000.00 satoshis. Based on the company&apos;s 206 million outstanding shares, the number of bitcoins held per share increased to 14.01 satoshis, an increase of more than 8.49 times from 1.65 satoshis / share on June 26, an increase of 750.00%. The company&apos;s cumulative investment in bitcoins reached 4.5 million Canadian dollars, with an average holding cost of 155,800.00 Canadian dollars per coin. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</link>
      <description>1 hour agoPANewsCanadian listed company Planet Ventures increased its holdings by 3.06 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 28.89 bitcoinsOn July 23, according to TheNewswire, Planet Ventures Inc. (CSE: PXI) recently purchased another 3.06 bitcoins for a transaction amount of 500,000 Canadian do</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947967088475312128</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart money betting on FET? Price presses against key resistance after stealth accumulationArtificial Intelligence Alliance’s FET token is showing signs of strength as it tests a critical resistance zone after a period of accumulation, setting sights on the $1 target. Artificial Intelligence Alliance (FET) token has spent several weeks in a tight range after bottoming out at $0.56 on June 22, forming what appears to be an accumulation base on the daily chart. Recent price action has turned bullish, with FET now coiling just below a key horizontal resistance zone between $0.80 and $0.90 — a level that has rejected multiple breakout attempts in the past. A confirmed break above this area could pave the way toward the psychological $1.00 milestone, which also marked the peak of the previous rally on May 23. Technical indicators support a potential breakout. Despite a recent pullback from the local high of $0.89 reached two days ago, the price remains firmly above the 20-day EMA ($0.79), which appears to have acted as dynamic support during the accumulation phase. Additionally, the momentum indicator MACD has maintained a bullish crossover since June 2025, with the histogram consistently printing green bars. For context, the FET token is the unified native asset of the ASI Alliance, which includes SingularityNET, Fetch.ai, Ocean Protocol, and most recent addition CUDOS. FET’s accumulation may signal that smart money is eyeing the token as a strategic entry point ahead of key product rollouts. Notably, Singularity Finance, the financial arm of the ASI Alliance, recently released its H2 2025 roadmap outlining several key product launches, including AI-powered portfolio tools, diversified yield vaults, and autonomous trading agents that execute trades automatically without requiring users to write code.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965739838803968</link>
      <description>1 hour agocrypto.newsSmart money betting on FET? Price presses against key resistance after stealth accumulationArtificial Intelligence Alliance’s FET token is showing signs of strength as it tests a critical resistance zone after a period of accumulation, setting sights on the $1 target. Artificial</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965739838803968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bedrock Week 4 BR Trading Challenge is now live with a $50,000.00 prize poolAccording to official sources, the fourth week of the Bedrock BR trading challenge is now live, with a prize pool of $50,000. This challenge simplifies the process, allowing users to trade on Pancake&apos;s BR/USDT pool. The event lasts for 7 consecutive days, earning $16,000.00 per day, totaling $160,000.00, but is only available to the first 5000 claimants. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965174387904512</link>
      <description>1 hour agoOdailyBedrock Week 4 BR Trading Challenge is now live with a $50,000.00 prize poolAccording to official sources, the fourth week of the Bedrock BR trading challenge is now live, with a prize pool of $50,000. This challenge simplifies the process, allowing users to trade on Pancake&apos;s BR/USD</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 10:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947965174387904512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 11:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>