<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:00:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Lists BNKR, JITOSOL, MPLX on Listing RoadmapAccording to the official announcement, Coinbase has listed BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX on its listing roadmap. [ChainCatcher]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687852980850688</link>
      <description>39seconds agoChainCatcherCoinbase Lists BNKR, JITOSOL, MPLX on Listing RoadmapAccording to the official announcement, Coinbase has listed BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX on its listing roadmap. [ChainCatcher]#Crypto Stocks$JITOSOL$MPLX$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687852980850688</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Announces Addition of BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX to Listing RoadmapOn July 22, according to the official announcement, Coinbase has listed BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX on its listing roadmap. [TechFlow]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687763948359680</link>
      <description>59seconds agoTechFlowCoinbase Announces Addition of BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX to Listing RoadmapOn July 22, according to the official announcement, Coinbase has listed BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX on its listing roadmap. [TechFlow]#Crypto Stocks$JITOSOL$MPLX$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687763948359680</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>techflow</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase Adds BankrCoin, Jito Staked SOL, and Metaplex to Listing RoadmapCoinbase has added BankrCoin (BNKR), Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL), and Metaplex (MPLX) to its listing roadmap. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687847352094720</link>
      <description>1 minute agoForesightNewsCoinbase Adds BankrCoin, Jito Staked SOL, and Metaplex to Listing RoadmapCoinbase has added BankrCoin (BNKR), Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL), and Metaplex (MPLX) to its listing roadmap. [Foresight News]#Crypto Stocks$MPLX$JITOSOL$COINShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687847352094720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coinbase adds BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX to its asset roadmapOn July 22, Coinbase Assets released a message on the X platform, saying that today, three assets, BankrCoin (BNKR), Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL) and Metaplex (MPLX), have been added to the Coinbase asset roadmap, and the relevant contract addresses have been announced. Officials said that the trading of these assets will be launched after market-making support and technical infrastructure are in place, and the specific launch time will be announced separately. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687425908428800</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoPANewsCoinbase adds BNKR, JITOSOL, and MPLX to its asset roadmapOn July 22, Coinbase Assets released a message on the X platform, saying that today, three assets, BankrCoin (BNKR), Jito Staked SOL (JITOSOL) and Metaplex (MPLX), have been added to the Coinbase asset roadmap, and the rele</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947687425908428800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Research withdrew 203,000 ENS from Binance, worth approximately $5.50MAccording to Ember Monitoring, Trend Research transferred 1.50M FORM (worth approximately $5.12M) to Binance, and then withdrew 203.00K ENS from Binance 40 minutes ago, worth approximately $5.50M. Trend Research&apos;s current portfolio includes a variety of tokens with a total value of approximately $570.00M, including 108.00K ETH (approximately $402.00M), and these investments currently appear to be profitable. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947685761495355392</link>
      <description>10 minutes agoForesightNewsTrend Research withdrew 203,000 ENS from Binance, worth approximately $5.50MAccording to Ember Monitoring, Trend Research transferred 1.50M FORM (worth approximately $5.12M) to Binance, and then withdrew 203.00K ENS from Binance 40 minutes ago, worth approximately $5.50M.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947685761495355392</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the US GENIUS Act mean for stablecoins?The Genius Act is a US law aimed at establishing federal oversight for stablecoin issuers, setting rules for reserves, redemption rights, and licensing requirements.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684746545090560</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoPANewsWhat does the US GENIUS Act mean for stablecoins?The Genius Act is a US law aimed at establishing federal oversight for stablecoin issuers, setting rules for reserves, redemption rights, and licensing requirements.#MacroShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684746545090560</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump on Powell: Anyway, he&apos;ll be out soonPresident Trump on Powell: Anyway, he will be out soon. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947685838259507200</link>
      <description>13 minutes agoOdailyTrump on Powell: Anyway, he&apos;ll be out soonPresident Trump on Powell: Anyway, he will be out soon. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947685838259507200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former AWS CEO Adam Selipsky Officially Joins Circle&apos;s Board of DirectorsCircle CEO Jeremy Allaire tweeted that former Amazon Web Services (AWS) CEO Adam Selipsky has officially joined Circle&apos;s board of directors. Allaire said Selipsky will provide important support for Circle&apos;s efforts to promote global on-chain operations and financial system construction. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684246198177792</link>
      <description>15 minutes ago吴说Former AWS CEO Adam Selipsky Officially Joins Circle&apos;s Board of DirectorsCircle CEO Jeremy Allaire tweeted that former Amazon Web Services (AWS) CEO Adam Selipsky has officially joined Circle&apos;s board of directors. Allaire said Selipsky will provide important support for Circle&apos;s effo</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947684246198177792</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sources: Apple is expected to get EU antitrust approval for its App Store fees and rulesOn July 22, Apple (AAPL.O) is expected to receive approval from the European Union&apos;s antitrust agency for its App Store fees and rules, which will help Apple avoid daily fines. A decision is expected to be made in the coming weeks. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683511305785344</link>
      <description>17 minutes agoPANewsSources: Apple is expected to get EU antitrust approval for its App Store fees and rulesOn July 22, Apple (AAPL.O) is expected to receive approval from the European Union&apos;s antitrust agency for its App Store fees and rules, which will help Apple avoid daily fines. A decision is e</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683511305785344</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local timeOn July 22, the White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local time. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683241972748288</link>
      <description>19 minutes agoPANewsThe White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local timeOn July 22, the White House plans to visit the Federal Reserve headquarters on Thursday local time. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947683241972748288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TON Wallet Announces Launch in the United StatesTON Wallet announces that it is now live in the United States. U.S. users can now use TON Wallet directly in Telegram, supporting the purchase and trading of USDT, TON and other tokens, private message transfers, 0% fee fiat currency exchange, credit card withdrawals, and token holding benefits. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680359261163520</link>
      <description>30 minutes ago吴说TON Wallet Announces Launch in the United StatesTON Wallet announces that it is now live in the United States. U.S. users can now use TON Wallet directly in Telegram, supporting the purchase and trading of USDT, TON and other tokens, private message transfers, 0% fee fiat currency ex</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680359261163520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitalik: The paradox of utilitarianism is that the setting of &quot;utility is infinite&quot; does not match the upper limit of human emotionsOn July 22, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin wrote on a social media platform that the reason why many paradoxes of utilitarianism are confusing is that its &quot;unlimited utility&quot; setting conflicts with human emotional mechanisms. He pointed out that humans actually have an upper limit to their positive and negative emotional experience of a situation, so the &quot;unlimited utility&quot; assumption in theoretical models is often contrary to intuition. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947679409423273984</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoPANewsVitalik: The paradox of utilitarianism is that the setting of &quot;utility is infinite&quot; does not match the upper limit of human emotionsOn July 22, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin wrote on a social media platform that the reason why many paradoxes of utilitarianism are confusing</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947679409423273984</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneFootball to Launch Token Sale on CoinList on July 24According to the official announcement from CoinList, the OneFootball (OFC) token sale will officially begin on July 24th at 17:00 UTC. The fully diluted valuation (FDV) for this token sale is $50.00M, the token price is $0.05, 25% will be released at TGE, and the remaining portion will be released linearly over 12 months, with a minimum purchase amount of $100.00. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680819560861696</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoOdailyOneFootball to Launch Token Sale on CoinList on July 24According to the official announcement from CoinList, the OneFootball (OFC) token sale will officially begin on July 24th at 17:00 UTC. The fully diluted valuation (FDV) for this token sale is $50.00M, the token price is $0.0</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947680819560861696</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs announces the launch of the first season of airdrops, 25% of the shares are now availableOn July 22, Sonic Labs published a post on the X platform saying that the first season of Sonic airdrop has officially started. Users can now claim 25% of the allocated shares, and the remaining 75% will be released linearly in the form of NFTs and gradually opened through the PaintSwap order book. The official specially reminded that this airdrop is based on the Sonic mainnet whitelist event and has nothing to do with pre-sales or TGE. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678554049499136</link>
      <description>37 minutes agoPANewsSonic Labs announces the launch of the first season of airdrops, 25% of the shares are now availableOn July 22, Sonic Labs published a post on the X platform saying that the first season of Sonic airdrop has officially started. Users can now claim 25% of the allocated shares, and</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678554049499136</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machi Big Brother has accumulated losses of over $5.50M on PUMP spot and contracts, but continues to add to long positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother Huang Licheng (@machibigbrother) has lost more than $1.50M on PUMP spot and more than $3.90M on contracts. However, he continues to add to his PUMP long position. [Odaily Planet Daily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678290018062336</link>
      <description>40 minutes agoOdailyMachi Big Brother has accumulated losses of over $5.50M on PUMP spot and contracts, but continues to add to long positions.According to Lookonchain monitoring, as the price of PUMP continues to fall, Machi Big Brother Huang Licheng (@machibigbrother) has lost more than $1.50M on</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678290018062336</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US DOJ drops probe into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell over nonprofit allegations: FortuneThe U.S. Justice Department has dropped its investigation into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell tied to a nonprofit group, according to reporting from Fortune.

Authorities searched Powell&apos;s Los Angeles home and took electronic devices in 2023 as part of an investigation into claims he hacked and cyber-stalked a nonprofit arts group, The New York Times previously reported.

In 2023, the nonprofit alleged that Powell interfered with its computer accounts, including blocking access to emails and other messages, according to people with knowledge of the matter who spoke to The New York Times.

Powell has said he did not stalk or hack anyone and alleged that the nonprofit Verge Center for the Arts executives tried to remove him from the board, Fortune reported on Tuesday.

The DOJ did not immediately respond to a request for comment. Powell told Fortune that the Federal Bureau of Investigation&apos;s raid was &quot;devastating both personally and professionally.&quot;

Powell, who co-founded the Kraken exchange, stepped down as CEO in 2022 and he is currently the chair of its board of directors.

The Justice Department&apos;s probe happened as crypto firms were being sued by federal regulators over charges related to not registering properly and fraud. A Kraken spokeswoman told the New York Times in 2023 that the investigation into Powell has nothing to do with the company and that it had no reason to believe that prosecutors were looking into other potential issues. [Fortune]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947676994187841536</link>
      <description>44 minutes agoThe BlockUS DOJ drops probe into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell over nonprofit allegations: FortuneThe U.S. Justice Department has dropped its investigation into Kraken co-founder Jesse Powell tied to a nonprofit group, according to reporting from Fortune.

Authorities searched Powell&apos;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947676994187841536</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fogo Launches High-Performance Layer 1 SVM Chain Public Testnet with 40 Millisecond Block TimeFogo, a Layer 1 blockchain created by former Wall Street executives, announced on Tuesday the official launch of its public testnet. Fogo aims to bring the execution speed of traditional finance to the decentralized finance space without sacrificing decentralization and composability. The team says the Fogo network can achieve 40 milliseconds block times and provide unique advantages for on-chain trading products through native infrastructure and vertical integration. Other innovations include reduced MEV risk, a co-located node architecture for real-time transaction execution, and an enhanced session-based account management experience. Fogo plans to be the first to fully deploy the Firedancer validator client, and has already adopted the Frankendancer hybrid client and will gradually transition to Firedancer. (The Block) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678298461196288</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoOdailyFogo Launches High-Performance Layer 1 SVM Chain Public Testnet with 40 Millisecond Block TimeFogo, a Layer 1 blockchain created by former Wall Street executives, announced on Tuesday the official launch of its public testnet. Fogo aims to bring the execution speed of traditional</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947678298461196288</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Expects the Federal Reserve to hold rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2025.Goldman Sachs expects the Federal Reserve to hold interest rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2025, as a slowing job market puts pressure on policymakers. Private sector hiring is now close to &quot;stall speed,&quot; with the risk of further slowdowns; meanwhile, consumer spending has stalled for six consecutive months, a situation extremely rare outside of recessions. Goldman Sachs also expects the Fed to cut rates twice more in early 2026. (Golden Ten) [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675768805150720</link>
      <description>51 minutes agoOdailyGoldman Sachs: Expects the Federal Reserve to hold rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2025.Goldman Sachs expects the Federal Reserve to hold interest rates steady next week and begin cutting rates at the remaining three meetings in 2</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675768805150720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNC strikes deal with Coinbase to bring cryptocurrency services to banking customersPNC Bank said it has struck a partnership with Coinbase to let clients access cryptocurrencies through Coinbase’s Crypto‑as‑a‑Service platform, while PNC will provide select banking services to the exchange.

The companies framed the deal as a way to marry PNC’s compliance and distribution footprint with Coinbase’s institutional‑grade trading and custody stack.

&quot;Partnering with Coinbase accelerates our ability to bring innovative, crypto financial solutions to our clients,&quot; PNC Chairman and CEO William S. Demchak said in the announcement. Coinbase Institutional head Brett Tejpaul added that the CaaS toolkit will let the bank set up a scalable, security‑first crypto offering for PNC&apos;s 12 million customers.

The firms did not disclose any financial terms or a launch date for the offering.

The move lands as Wall Street banks edge deeper into digital assets. Standard Chartered recently launched spot bitcoin and ether trading for institutional clients. JPMorgan told clients that regulators outside the United States appear to prefer tokenized bank deposits — onchain versions of traditional balances that always settle at par — over privately issued stablecoins. JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon nevertheless said last week the bank &quot;will be involved&quot; with both deposit tokens and stablecoins to stay competitive, even as he questioned why anyone would use a stablecoin instead of a standard payment rail.

Meanwhile, the U.S. under President Donald Trump&apos;s pro-crypto administration has accelerated supportive legislation for the blockchain-powered industry. Trump recently signed the GENIUS Act into law, standardizing rules for a U.S. dollar-pegged stablecoin industry with over $250 billion in circulation, according to The Block&apos;s data dashboard.

Senate Republicans also released a discussion draft on the crypto market structure, which they say expands on the Clarity bill passed in the House of Representatives last week. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675642506268672</link>
      <description>53 minutes agoThe BlockPNC strikes deal with Coinbase to bring cryptocurrency services to banking customersPNC Bank said it has struck a partnership with Coinbase to let clients access cryptocurrencies through Coinbase’s Crypto‑as‑a‑Service platform, while PNC will provide select banking services to</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947675642506268672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circle Gateway Launches Cross-Chain Unified USDC Balance FeatureCircle introduces Circle Gateway, a new primitive that enables cross-chain instant access to unified USDC balances. The feature is currently live on the Avalanche, Base, and Ethereum testnets, with a mainnet version coming soon and plans to expand to more blockchain networks. Circle Gateway provides instant access, allowing users to view and use their USDC balances. [Foresight News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673026309148672</link>
      <description>1 hour agoForesightNewsCircle Gateway Launches Cross-Chain Unified USDC Balance FeatureCircle introduces Circle Gateway, a new primitive that enables cross-chain instant access to unified USDC balances. The feature is currently live on the Avalanche, Base, and Ethereum testnets, with a mainnet versi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947673026309148672</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>foresightnews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</link>
      <description>Updated  2 days agoSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo Daily | Solana Leads Altcoin Rally, NFTs Stage Explosive ReboundSoSo</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947510790600814592</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>