<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crypto News - SosoValue Research</title>
    <link>https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml</link>
    <description>Latest crypto news from SosoValue Research</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:47:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <category>crypto</category>
    <atom:link href="https://damon1002.github.io/news-scraper/feeds/crypto/sosovalue-research.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Multi-Source News Aggregator</generator>
    <managingEditor>noreply@github.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>noreply@github.com</webMaster>
    <item>
      <title>Trusta.AI responds to third-party contract fraud incident, official $TA tokens are safeOn July 23, Trusta.AI reported that an external fraud incident involving an unverified third-party contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) recently occurred on the blockchain. Trusta and the official $TA tokens remain safe and intact, and no vulnerabilities or problems have been found. The attack was caused by the failure of the non-open source contract to verify user input, which allowed the attacker to use the WBNB tokens of authorized users to exchange through the self-built WBNB-TA pool and sell their own $TA tokens to illegally obtain WBNB. Trusta.AI recommends that users immediately revoke their authorization to the contract and promises to repurchase $TA worth $200,000.00 to protect user interests. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031398367006720</link>
      <description>2 minutes agoPANewsTrusta.AI responds to third-party contract fraud incident, official $TA tokens are safeOn July 23, Trusta.AI reported that an external fraud incident involving an unverified third-party contract (0x16d7c6f43df19778e382b7a84bcb8c763971a551) recently occurred on the blockchain. Trus</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031398367006720</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nature&apos;s Miracle Announces Launch of Company-Level XRP Treasury Program of Up to $20.00MNature’s Miracle Holding Inc (OTCQB: NMHI) has announced the launch of a corporate-level XRP treasury program of up to $20.00M. The company will use equity financing funds under an S-1 registration statement already approved by the SEC to purchase XRP for long-term strategic reserves, staking yields, and participation in the Ripple ecosystem. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031358676307968</link>
      <description>4 minutes ago吴说Nature&apos;s Miracle Announces Launch of Company-Level XRP Treasury Program of Up to $20.00MNature’s Miracle Holding Inc (OTCQB: NMHI) has announced the launch of a corporate-level XRP treasury program of up to $20.00M. The company will use equity financing funds under an S-1 registration</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948031358676307968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. House Speaker Johnson: Legal compliance of firing Fed chairman unclearOn July 23, U.S. House Speaker Johnson said he was &quot;disappointed&quot; with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell, and the legal compliance of firing the Federal Reserve Chairman was unclear. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948030421631045632</link>
      <description>7 minutes agoPANewsU.S. House Speaker Johnson: Legal compliance of firing Fed chairman unclearOn July 23, U.S. House Speaker Johnson said he was &quot;disappointed&quot; with Federal Reserve Chairman Powell, and the legal compliance of firing the Federal Reserve Chairman was unclear. [PANews]Share to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948030421631045632</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaia Labs raises $20 million to launch first AI-native smartphoneOn July 23, Gaia Labs, a decentralized AI infrastructure developer, announced the completion of a total of $20.00 million in seed and Series A financing. This round of financing was led by ByteTrade/SIG Capital (Susquehanna) and Mirana/Mantle Eco Fund, and participated by EVM Capital, Taisu Ventures, NGC Ventures and other institutions. Gaia Labs currently supports more than 700,000 active nodes, with a cumulative inference time of more than 17.00 trillion times, and the network covers thousands of App-Chain domains and blockchain ecosystems. The new round of funds will be used to launch decentralized AI smartphones, expand node capacity, improve development toolkits and promote Web3 integration. Gaia Labs plans to release a limited number of smartphones equipped with local AI inference capabilities this year. The Gaia AI Phone is based on the Galaxy S25 Edge hardware and can run decentralized AI inference locally without relying on the cloud or data extraction, enabling users to fully control the agent. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948029236043911168</link>
      <description>11 minutes agoPANewsGaia Labs raises $20 million to launch first AI-native smartphoneOn July 23, Gaia Labs, a decentralized AI infrastructure developer, announced the completion of a total of $20.00 million in seed and Series A financing. This round of financing was led by ByteTrade/SIG Capital (Sus</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948029236043911168</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNY, Goldman Sachs ink tokenized money market fund deal to bring $7.1 trillion industry onchainBank of New York Mellon and Goldman Sachs on Wednesday launched a blockchain-based system that issues “mirror” tokens of money market fund shares, letting institutional investors subscribe and redeem through BNY’s LiquidityDirect platform while ownership is recorded on Goldman’s GS DAP ledger, marking the first U.S. rollout of tokenized MMF shares by major lenders.

Under the initiative, BNY will keep the official books and settlement records for participating funds, which reportedly already includes products from BlackRock, Fidelity, Federated Hermes, BNY’s Dreyfus unit, and Goldman Sachs Asset Management. BNY will also create digital token representations simultaneously, designed to boost collateral mobility and transferability.

The project targets a $7.1 trillion money market industry and arrives a week after President Donald Trump signed the GENIUS Act, establishing the first federal framework for U.S. stablecoins. Policymakers are also working on a crypto market structure bill that they say should broaden access to regulated digital asset services.

Unlike traditional money markets that trade during limited market hours, tokenized funds enjoy round-the-clock availability and expansive liquidity features because they sit on a blockchain network.

Mathew McDermott, Goldman Sachs&apos; global head of digital assets, said tokenizing MMF shares could unlock their use as collateral and pave the way for faster, more seamless moves across markets. The Goldman exec sees it as part of a longer-term push to modernize market plumbing, while BNY framed the project as a step toward a real-time financial architecture. &quot;Mirrored tokenization of MMF shares is a first step in this transition,&quot; Laide Majiyagbe, global head of liquidity, financing, and collateral at BNY, said.

It’s the first time major banks have ventured into blockchain-based money markets, but the tokenization trend has already attracted notable traditional finance players. Onchain products like BlackRock’s BUIDL and Franklin Templeton’s BENJI collectively command over $3 billion in assets, while the total real-world asset value in DeFi has exceeded $10.7 billion according to The Block’s data dashboard. [The Block]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028347660963840</link>
      <description>15 minutes agoThe BlockBNY, Goldman Sachs ink tokenized money market fund deal to bring $7.1 trillion industry onchainBank of New York Mellon and Goldman Sachs on Wednesday launched a blockchain-based system that issues “mirror” tokens of money market fund shares, letting institutional investors sub</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028347660963840</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>the block</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House launches AI.Gov website to strengthen US leadership in artificial intelligenceSpecial Assistant to the President and White House Principal Deputy Press Secretary Harrison Fields posted on the X platform that the White House has launched AI.Gov to strengthen the United States&apos; leadership in the field of artificial intelligence. Thanks to David Sacks and Michael Kratsios for their dedication and commitment. Trump is committed to promoting innovation and competition to win the global artificial intelligence race. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028100910059520</link>
      <description>16 minutes agoOdailyThe White House launches AI.Gov website to strengthen US leadership in artificial intelligenceSpecial Assistant to the President and White House Principal Deputy Press Secretary Harrison Fields posted on the X platform that the White House has launched AI.Gov to strengthen the Un</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948028100910059520</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H100 Group increased its holdings by 117.93 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 628.22 bitcoinsOn July 23, H100 Group announced that the company purchased 117.93 bitcoins according to its bitcoin vault strategy, with an average purchase price of about 1,120,000.00 Swedish kronor per bitcoin, with a total investment of about 132,000,000.00 kronor. Part of the purchase came from convertible bond financing. As of now, the company&apos;s total bitcoin holdings are 628.22. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025861294329856</link>
      <description>24 minutes agoPANewsH100 Group increased its holdings by 117.93 bitcoins, bringing its total holdings to 628.22 bitcoinsOn July 23, H100 Group announced that the company purchased 117.93 bitcoins according to its bitcoin vault strategy, with an average purchase price of about 1,120,000.00 Swedish kr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025861294329856</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperion announces the official launch of RION Utility, initiating the first phase of the native staking mechanism, RION Staking.Aptos&apos; largest decentralized trading platform, Hyperion, has announced the official launch of the RION Utility prologue, taking the lead in opening the native staking Staking Phase Ⅰ. Users can now lock up $RION to participate in the native staking mechanism, entering the first stage of network construction and value sharing. The total duration of the Staking Phase Ⅰ event is 1 month, and the user&apos;s staking time is based on the actual participation time. The rewards come from part of the platform&apos;s transaction fee revenue. This mechanism is intended to identify and incentivize real contributors, and lay the foundation for more RION application scenarios in the future, while reflecting Hyperion&apos;s high emphasis on real interaction and positive ecological cycles. Hyperion stated that this stage is the first step in unlocking RION Utility, and more utility scenarios based on real revenue will continue to be released in the future. [Odaily News]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025606058348544</link>
      <description>27 minutes agoOdailyHyperion announces the official launch of RION Utility, initiating the first phase of the native staking mechanism, RION Staking.Aptos&apos; largest decentralized trading platform, Hyperion, has announced the official launch of the RION Utility prologue, taking the lead in opening the</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025606058348544</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Labs: Another approximately $30.00 million will be distributed through Sonic GemsOn July 23, according to Sonic Labs, about 49 million $S have been distributed through Sonic Points, but the first season of airdrops has not yet ended. Another 30 million $S will be distributed through Sonic Gems in succession, with no minimum threshold for receiving them, so stay tuned. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948024749963153408</link>
      <description>29 minutes agoPANewsSonic Labs: Another approximately $30.00 million will be distributed through Sonic GemsOn July 23, according to Sonic Labs, about 49 million $S have been distributed through Sonic Points, but the first season of airdrops has not yet ended. Another 30 million $S will be distribute</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948024749963153408</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssiMAG7 index 24hr loss of 3.19%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has fallen by 3.19% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: DOGE -6.06%, XRP -5.77%, ADA -4.98%.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948023641064038400</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoSSI Price BotssiMAG7 index 24hr loss of 3.19%According to SoSoValue, the crypto sector index ssiMAG7 has fallen by 3.19% over the past 24 hours. Key constituent performance: DOGE -6.06%, XRP -5.77%, ADA -4.98%.$XRP$ADA$DOGEShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948023641064038400</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says interest rate cuts could save trillions in interest, but a &quot;Federal Reserve mouthpiece&quot; says it&apos;s impossible.&quot;Fed mouthpiece&quot; Nick Timiraos said that Trump stated that if the Fed lowered short-term interest rates, the U.S.&apos;s interest expenses would decrease by $1 trillion per year. The U.S. spent $1.1 trillion on interest expenses in 2024, so this claim is almost certainly untrue. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025614505676800</link>
      <description>33 minutes agoOdailyTrump says interest rate cuts could save trillions in interest, but a &quot;Federal Reserve mouthpiece&quot; says it&apos;s impossible.&quot;Fed mouthpiece&quot; Nick Timiraos said that Trump stated that if the Fed lowered short-term interest rates, the U.S.&apos;s interest expenses would decrease by $1 trill</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025614505676800</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaulta (formerly EOS) receives a $6.00M investment commitment from WLFI to advance Web3 banking in the USAccording to official sources, WLFI has reached a strategic partnership with Vaulta (formerly EOS). WLFI has committed to investing $6.00M to promote the development of Web3 banking in the United States. Vaulta&apos;s native assets will be incorporated into WLFI&apos;s macro-strategic reserves, and WLFI&apos;s USD1 stablecoin will be directly integrated into Vaulta&apos;s Web3 banking infrastructure. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025622961393664</link>
      <description>34 minutes agoOdailyVaulta (formerly EOS) receives a $6.00M investment commitment from WLFI to advance Web3 banking in the USAccording to official sources, WLFI has reached a strategic partnership with Vaulta (formerly EOS). WLFI has committed to investing $6.00M to promote the development of Web3 b</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948025622961393664</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Wynn Liquidated Again, Hyperliquid Account Falls Below $300,000.00According to Lookonchain monitoring, James Wynn&apos;s BTC and PEPE long positions have once again been liquidated. Despite previously depositing an additional $1.25M into Hyperliquid, his current account balance has fallen below $300,000. [Odaily星球日报]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948023058983358464</link>
      <description>39 minutes agoOdailyJames Wynn Liquidated Again, Hyperliquid Account Falls Below $300,000.00According to Lookonchain monitoring, James Wynn&apos;s BTC and PEPE long positions have once again been liquidated. Despite previously depositing an additional $1.25M into Hyperliquid, his current account balance</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948023058983358464</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antalpha Founder Appointed Chairman of Cango&apos;s Board, Completing Full Transition to Bitcoin Mining BusinessCango has announced the completion of its full transition from an automotive transaction platform to a Bitcoin mining company, and has restructured its board of directors and management team. Antalpha founder and CEO Jin Xin has been appointed Chairman of the Board, further solidifying the connection with Bitmain. Antalpha is a financial services platform backed by Bitmain. The new CEO, Yu Peng, was previously the Chief Strategy Officer of Antalpha and has an asset management background. Several new members with Antalpha backgrounds have also been added to the board of directors. Cango currently holds over 4,000 Bitcoins. [Wu Blockchain]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948022136710434816</link>
      <description>40 minutes ago吴说Antalpha Founder Appointed Chairman of Cango&apos;s Board, Completing Full Transition to Bitcoin Mining BusinessCango has announced the completion of its full transition from an automotive transaction platform to a Bitcoin mining company, and has restructured its board of directors and ma</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948022136710434816</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGHL increases its stake in SUI, bringing total treasury reserves to $9.60 millionOn July 23, Lion Group Holdings Limited (LGHL, NASDAQ: LGHL) announced that it has increased its holdings of SUI tokens, bringing the total purchase amount of its HYPE, SOL and SUI tokens to approximately US$9.6 million. As of July 23, 2025, LGHL&apos;s treasury reserves include 128,929 Hyperliquid (HYPE), 6,629 Solana (SOL) and 1,015,680 Sui (SUI) tokens. The company said it will continue to explore strategic opportunities in the digital asset field and regularly announce the latest progress of its treasury reserves. [PANews]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948020374049984512</link>
      <description>46 minutes agoPANewsLGHL increases its stake in SUI, bringing total treasury reserves to $9.60 millionOn July 23, Lion Group Holdings Limited (LGHL, NASDAQ: LGHL) announced that it has increased its holdings of SUI tokens, bringing the total purchase amount of its HYPE, SOL and SUI tokens to approxi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948020374049984512</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>panews</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow rallies as markets cheer US-Japan trade agreementStocks rallied in early-morning trading on Wednesday, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average adding more than 200 points at the open. Investors appeared to welcome President Donald Trump’s announcement that the U.S. had reached a trade deal with Japan. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rose nearly 240 points, and the S&amp;P 500 inched higher by 0.4% to extend gains at its record highs. Optimism of potentially more trade agreements ahead of Trump’s Aug. 1 tariffs deadline also saw the Nasdaq Composite edge up, adding a modest 0.16% in early trading. With corporate earnings, spotlighted by Tesla (TSLA) and Alphabet (GOOGL, GOOG), set to hit the market after the bell, early cheers had futures across the major U.S. indices flashing rising green. Upbeat sentiment on Wall Street carried through the Asia and European sessions, investors are envisioning the U.S.-Japan deal as a huge one.  In addition to the 15% tariff on Japanese imports, Trump’s administration managed to secure a $550 billion Japanese investment in the U.S.  “There has never been anything like it,” Trump said of the deal in a Truth Social post . “Perhaps most importantly, Japan will open their Country to Trade including Cars and Trucks, Rice and certain other Agricultural Products, and other things. Japan will pay Reciprocal Tariffs to the United States of 15%. This is a very exciting time for the United States of America, and especially for the fact that we will continue to always have a great relationship with the Country of Japan.” The news came as markets weighed the potential impact of fresh trade tensions as the looming Aug. 1 deadline first approaches. However, with U.S. officials noting a likely extension of the Aug. 12 deadline for China, this latest move injects a sense of bullishness for investors. Stocks have shown resilience over the past few months amid tariff uncertainty. Investors also weathered a geopolitical storm in the Middle East. However, none of the headwinds that followed Trump’s so-called “Liberation Day” tariffs have entirely derailed bulls, with U.S. stocks marching to record highs. Corporate earnings have so far provided buyers with upside fuel, even as more clarity on the tariffs’ impact will become clearer with the release of Google-parent Alphabet’s and electric vehicle giant Tesla’s quarterly earnings reports. Mohamed El-Erian, president of Queen’s College at Cambridge University and chief economic advisor at Allianz, has nonetheless cautioned investors to beware of what’s happening in the bond market.  “While media attention is rightly focused on the Japan-U.S. trade deal, don’t overlook what is happening to the long end of the Japanese bond market where, driven mainly by fiscal concerns, yields continue to climb,” El-Erian noted via X . “With what is a correlated, rather than coordinated, fiscal expansion in the three largest advanced economies — the US, Germany, and Japan — global bond markets have a lot of issuance to digest in the period ahead.”</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948019605712211968</link>
      <description>50 minutes agocrypto.newsDow rallies as markets cheer US-Japan trade agreementStocks rallied in early-morning trading on Wednesday, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average adding more than 200 points at the open. Investors appeared to welcome President Donald Trump’s announcement that the U.S. had rea</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948019605712211968</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - Data: The Ethereum validator exit queue is currently around 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024.1. Data: Ethereum validator exit queue size is currently about 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024

With Ethereum&apos;s year-to-date increase of over 160%, the ETH validator exit queue has surged. Data from the validatorqueue website shows that as of July 23, the number of ETH waiting to exit in the queue has reached 519,000, with a total value of approximately $1.92 billion at the current price, and the waiting time for exit exceeds 9 days, a new high since January 2024. Analysts believe that this round of exits is mainly due to some early stakers choosing to take profits after the price increase. At the same time, due to the continuous entry of ETH treasury-like companies including SharpLink Gaming and Bitmine, the market still shows strong staking demand, and currently 357,000 ETH are waiting to enter the network, with a queuing time of more than 6 days.

2. Arthur Hayes: Year-end target is $250,000 for Bitcoin and $10,000 for Ethereum

Arthur Hayes predicted in his latest blog post that the year-end target is $250,000 for Bitcoin and $10,000 for Ethereum. He said that the upcoming Ethereum bull market will completely detonate the market, and Maelstrom (his personal family office) is doing everything related to Ethereum, DeFi, and ERC-20 shitcoins.

3. South Korean Financial Supervisory Service: Restricting the proportion of corporate ETF investments related to crypto assets

The South Korean financial regulator, the Financial Supervisory Service, recently provided oral guidance to local asset management companies, requiring them to control the proportion of investments in crypto asset-related companies such as CoinBase and MicroStrategy in their ETF portfolios, and reiterated that the 2017 &quot;Emergency Measures for Virtual Currencies&quot; is still valid, prohibiting financial institutions from holding, purchasing, or investing in shares of virtual asset-related companies. This move is seen as a response to the recent rapid increase in the weight of &quot;crypto-themed&quot; companies in South Korean ETFs, with the proportion of related constituent stocks in several ETFs currently exceeding 10%.

4. Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon partner to launch tokenized money market fund investment service

Goldman Sachs and BNY Mellon have jointly launched a new service for institutional investors that allows them to invest in tokenized money market funds through Goldman Sachs&apos; blockchain platform. The project has been joined by several asset management institutions, including BlackRock and Fidelity. The two banks stated that the project will lay the foundation for money market funds in a &quot;24/7 real-time trading&quot; digital financial system and is expected to be expanded in the future for use as collateral in financial transactions.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948019417970970624</link>
      <description>50 minutes ago吴说Wu Blockchain Daily Crypto News Highlights - Data: The Ethereum validator exit queue is currently around 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024.1. Data: Ethereum validator exit queue size is currently about 519,000 ETH, a new high since January 2024

With Ethereum&apos;s year-to-date</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948019417970970624</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>吴说</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Institutions: Tariff uncertainty may prompt the ECB to cut interest rates more than onceAccording to a report by Algebris Investments analyst Gabriele Foa, the European Central Bank&apos;s interest rate cuts may exceed current market expectations due to tariff uncertainty. The portfolio manager stated, &quot;Trade tensions and tariff developments may push the end of the easing cycle slightly lower than current market expectations.&quot; LSEG data shows that money markets currently expect the ECB to cut interest rates by another 25 basis points in December. Foa said that the spillover effects of tariffs on Europe may take longer to materialize. (Golden Ten) [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948020588051763200</link>
      <description>54 minutes agoOdailyInstitutions: Tariff uncertainty may prompt the ECB to cut interest rates more than onceAccording to a report by Algebris Investments analyst Gabriele Foa, the European Central Bank&apos;s interest rate cuts may exceed current market expectations due to tariff uncertainty. The portfol</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948020588051763200</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH is now at $3,600According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 1.43% in the past 1H, down 2.47% in the last 24H. Now at $3,600.</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948017605884207104</link>
      <description>57 minutes agoSoSo Price BotETH is now at $3,600According to SoSoValue, ETH(Ethereum) is down 1.43% in the past 1H, down 2.47% in the last 24H. Now at $3,600.$ETHShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948017605884207104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENDRA Life Science to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury and Revenue Generation StrategyAccording to NLNico, US-based ENDRA Life Science Corporation will adopt a cryptocurrency treasury strategy and plans to implement a Bitcoin-based revenue-generating strategy. [Odaily]</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1948018048534908928</link>
      <description>58 minutes agoOdailyENDRA Life Science to Pursue Bitcoin Treasury and Revenue Generation StrategyAccording to NLNico, US-based ENDRA Life Science Corporation will adopt a cryptocurrency treasury strategy and plans to implement a Bitcoin-based revenue-generating strategy. [Odaily]#Bitcoin$BTCShare to</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1948018048534908928</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SosoValue: View</title>
      <link>https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</link>
      <description>Updated  3 days agoSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily | Bitcoin Retests Highs; U.S. Policy Shifts and ETF Uncertainty Shape SentimentSoSo Daily</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <source>SosoValue Research</source>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sosovalue.com/research/1947837858349871104</guid>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>sosovalue research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>
      <category>crypto</category>
      <category>blockchain</category>
      <category>research</category>
      <category>sosovalue</category>

    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>